<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:43:23+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Boxcar/</id><title>Neil_Young - Boxcar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T19:59:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T19:59:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Boxcar/" title="Neil_Young - Boxcar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just a passenger <br>on this old freight train <br>I ride the boxcar <br>through the night <br>I doesn't matter <br>where I might get off <br>I doesn't matter where I lie <br><br>I've been to cities <br>I've been to countries <br>I've left a lover in many towns <br>I don't care if <br>I ever get back to <br>Where I'd already been around <br><br>I'm like an eagle <br>I like to fly high <br>I'm like a snake <br>I like to lay low <br>I'm like a black man <br>I'm like a white man <br>Maybe a red man, I don't know <br><br>I'm just a passenger <br>on this old freight train <br>I ride the boxcar <br>through the night <br>I doesn't matter <br>where I might get off <br>I doesn't matter where I lie]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Boxcar" label="Boxcar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Beautiful_Bluebird/</id><title>Neil_Young - Beautiful Bluebird - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:00:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:00:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Beautiful_Bluebird/" title="Neil_Young - Beautiful Bluebird - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One mornin' when I was ridin' <br>In my old pickup truck <br>A beautiful bluebird <br>came flyin' down <br>My eyes caught the color <br>As it lead me down the road <br>Dippin' and bobbin' in the sun <br>I've never seen that blue before <br>'cept in one place <br>And she's not <br>here with me right now <br>So I followed all the way <br>To the top of the hill <br>That's where she <br>kept on climbin' Lord <br>Someday I will <br><br>Beautiful bluebird <br>See how she flies <br>Looks like she's <br>always goin' home <br>If heaven had a window <br>Where the sun <br>came shinin' through <br>Like a beautiful bluebird <br>I'd come flyin' back to you <br><br>Well it kind of struck me funny <br>Sort of made me smile <br>After all these years <br>on this old road <br>How God could show me somethin' <br>Never say a word <br>There's so much <br>that I don't know <br>I've never seen that blue before <br>Except in one place <br>And she's not <br>here with me right now <br>I followed all the way <br>to the top of the hill <br>That's where she <br>kept on climbin' Lord <br>And someday I will <br><br>Beautiful bluebird <br>See how she flies <br>Looks like she's <br>always goin' home <br>If heaven had a window <br>Where the sun <br>came shinin' through <br>Like a beautiful bluebird <br>I'd come flyin' back to you <br><br>Beautiful bluebird <br>See how she flies <br>Looks like she's <br>always goin' home <br>If heaven had a window <br>Where the sun <br>came shinin' through <br>Like a beautiful bluebird <br>I'd come flyin' back to you]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Beautiful Bluebird" label="Beautiful Bluebird"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/연세디지털콘서바토리_CCM_전공/아_하나님의_은혜로_Morning_Star/</id><title>연세디지털콘서바토리_CCM_전공 - 아 하나님의 은혜로 (Morning Star) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:00:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:00:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B0%EC%84%B8%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%ED%84%B8%EC%BD%98%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%ED%86%A0%EB%A6%AC_CCM_%EC%A0%84%EA%B3%B5/%EC%95%84_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%9D%80%ED%98%9C%EB%A1%9C_Morning_Star/" title="연세디지털콘서바토리_CCM_전공 - 아 하나님의 은혜로 (Morning Star) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아 하나님의 은혜로 <br>이 쓸데없는 자 <br>왜 구속하여 주는지 <br>난 알수 없도다 <br>왜 내게 성령 주셔서 <br>내 맘을 감동해 <br>주 예수 믿게 하는지 <br>난 알 수 없도다 <br>내가 믿고 또 의지함은 <br>내 모든 형편 아시는 주님 <br>늘 보호해 주실 것을 <br>나는 확실히 아네 <br>주 언제 강림하실지 <br>혹 밤에 혹 낮에 <br>또 주님 만날 그곳도 <br>난 알 수 없도다 <br>내가 믿고 또 의지함은 <br>내 모든 형편 아시는 주님 <br>늘 보호해 주실 것을 <br>나는 확실히 아네 <br>내가 믿고 또 의지함은 <br>내 모든 형편 아시는 주님 <br>늘 보호해 주실 것을 <br>나는 확실히 아네 <br>]]></content><category term="연세디지털콘서바토리 CCM 전공" label="연세디지털콘서바토리 CCM 전공"/><category term="아 하나님의 은혜로 (Morning Star)" label="아 하나님의 은혜로 (Morning Star)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/연세디지털콘서바토리_CCM_전공/Saviour_홀리홀리/</id><title>연세디지털콘서바토리_CCM_전공 - Saviour (홀리홀리) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:00:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:00:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B0%EC%84%B8%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%ED%84%B8%EC%BD%98%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%ED%86%A0%EB%A6%AC_CCM_%EC%A0%84%EA%B3%B5/Saviour_%ED%99%80%EB%A6%AC%ED%99%80%EB%A6%AC/" title="연세디지털콘서바토리_CCM_전공 - Saviour (홀리홀리) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[갈보리 그 언덕 길에 <br>하나님 어린양 <br>외롭고 그 험한 길에 <br>십자가 달리신 예수 <br>우릴 온전케 하신 주 <br>다 이루셨네 다 이루셨네 <br>보배로운 피 흘리신 <br>내 영혼 구원하신 주 <br>다 경배하리 다 경배하리 <br>어둠 속에 빛이 되신 주 <br>영원한 생명 주신 주 경배하리라 <br>갈보리 그 언덕 길에 <br>하나님 어린양 <br>외롭고 그 험한 길에 <br>십자가 달리신 예수 <br>우릴 온전케 하신 주 <br>다 이루셨네 다 이루셨네 <br>보배로운 피 흘리신 <br>내 영혼 구원하신 주 <br>다 경배하리 다 경배하리 <br>어둠 속에 빛이 되신 주 <br>영원한 생명 주신 주 <br>다 이루셨네 다 이루셨네 <br>보배로운 피 흘리신 <br>내 영혼 구원하신 주 <br>다 경배하리 다 경배하리 <br>어둠 속에 빛이 되신 주 <br>영원한 생명 주신 주 <br>]]></content><category term="연세디지털콘서바토리 CCM 전공" label="연세디지털콘서바토리 CCM 전공"/><category term="Saviour (홀리홀리)" label="Saviour (홀리홀리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/연세디지털콘서바토리_CCM_전공/능력의_주_InJesus/</id><title>연세디지털콘서바토리_CCM_전공 - 능력의 주 (InJesus) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:00:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:00:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B0%EC%84%B8%EB%94%94%EC%A7%80%ED%84%B8%EC%BD%98%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%ED%86%A0%EB%A6%AC_CCM_%EC%A0%84%EA%B3%B5/%EB%8A%A5%EB%A0%A5%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC_InJesus/" title="연세디지털콘서바토리_CCM_전공 - 능력의 주 (InJesus) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[놀라우신 하나님 <br>이해할 수 없는 신비 <br>죄인을 사랑하사 <br>독생자를 죽인 사랑 <br>말씀으로 창조하신 돌들이 <br>찬양하네 그 위엄 <br>아버지와 화목케 한 <br>다시 사신 예수 그리스도 <br>능력의 주 다스리시니 <br>진리가 날 자유케 해 <br>능력의 주 비추시니 <br>어둠이 사라져 <br>말씀으로 창조하신 돌들이 <br>찬양하네 그 위엄 <br>아버지와 화목케 한 <br>다시 사신 예수 그리스도 <br>능력의 주 다스리시니 <br>진리가 날 자유케 해 <br>능력의 주 비추시니 <br>어둠이 사라져 <br>늘 동일하시고 주님 <br>하늘의 뜻 이루시네 <br>곧 오실 우리 왕 <br>세세토록 영원하리 <br>능력의 주 다스리시니 <br>진리가 날 자유케 해 <br>능력의 주 비추시니 <br>어둠이 사라져 <br>능력의 주 통치하시네 <br>어제와 오늘 또 새로운 내일을 <br>능력의 주 이끄시니 <br>영광 향해 달려가 <br>]]></content><category term="연세디지털콘서바토리 CCM 전공" label="연세디지털콘서바토리 CCM 전공"/><category term="능력의 주 (InJesus)" label="능력의 주 (InJesus)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christophe_Mae/La_Parisienne/</id><title>Christophe_Mae - La Parisienne - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:01:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:01:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Christophe_Mae/La_Parisienne/" title="Christophe_Mae - La Parisienne - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Elle habite Paris depuis moins de 3 Mois <br>Mais elle a deja tout, le mode d'emploi <br>Elle emploie tout plein de mots que je connais pas <br>Roule en Vespa <br><br>Ses amis ont des prenoms etranges, Bene, Alix <br>Fixe, c'est ca c'est pas <br>Leurs prenoms, non qui me derange, ni leurs franges <br>Elle me dit tout le temps qu'il faut qu'on se capte <br>Et qu'on brunch ensemble un de ces quatre <br>Qu'on se mate une expo au 104 Lary Clarck <br>Pourquoi pas <br><br>Mais pas demain <br>Car madame est surbooke toujours bloque sur son Mc Book er <br>Et quand elle me dit qu'on peut se croiser sur Facebook c'est le bouquet <br><br>Elle habite Paris <br>Elle a des converses blanches <br>Je comprends plus ce qu'elle dit <br>Elle habite Paris, pourvu que rien ne change <br><br>Elle habite Paris <br>Elle a des converses blanches <br>Je comprends plus ce qu'elle dit <br>Elle habite Paris, pourvu que rien ne change <br><br>Elle habite Paris, c'est pas que je critique <br>C'est si different passe le peripherique <br>C'est plus les memes musiques, les memes tuniques <br>Sa mere, ses pots et ses votes catholiques <br>Je la vois moins souvent parce que madame oui <br>Pars a la mer pour Pacques <br>Ses amis ont des grandes baraques, Saint Briac <br>Connais pas <br><br>Moi ma ganache tapache et mon accent <br>Je sais ca fait sourire ses amis bien pensant <br>Et pourtant je l'attend souvent dans le vent <br>J'aimerai qu'elle redevienne un peu comme avant <br>Mais elle son Velib c'est ton avion et son iphone <br><br>Son de Boston <br>Moi la pluie me bastonne <br>Pendant que je galere des heures a l'interphone <br>Mais y'a personne <br><br>Elle habite Paris <br>Elle a des converses blanches <br>Je comprends plus ce qu'elle dit <br>Elle habite Paris, pourvu que rien ne change <br><br>Elle habite Paris <br>Elle a des converses blanches <br>Je comprends plus ce qu'elle dit <br>Elle habite Paris, pourvu que rien ne change <br><br>Madame est chic <br>Apero Paris au bord de Seine <br>Madame se complique la vie a etre une boheme <br><br>Madame est chic <br>American apparel HandM <br>C'est une hippie chic <br>Mais elle est ou la dame que j'aime <br><br>Elle habite Paris <br>Elle a des converses blanches <br>Je comprends rien de ce qu'elle dit <br>Elle habite Paris, pourvu que rien ne change <br><br>Elle habite Paris <br>Elle a des converses blanches <br>Je comprends plus ce qu'elle dit <br>Elle habite Paris, pourvu que rien ne change <br><br>Elle habite Paris <br>Je crois qu'elle m'oublie <br>Elle a des nouveaux amis <br>Tu sais de nouveaux avis <br><br>Et moi je traine de Seine <br>Mais elle est ou la dame que j'aime <br><br>Je comprends plus ce qu'elle dit <br>Elle habite Paris, pourvu que rien ne change]]></content><category term="Christophe Mae" label="Christophe Mae"/><category term="La Parisienne" label="La Parisienne"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/대팔/Flight_Feat_바오/</id><title>대팔 - Flight (Feat. 바오) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:02:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:02:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8C%80%ED%8C%94/Flight_Feat_%EB%B0%94%EC%98%A4/" title="대팔 - Flight (Feat. 바오) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let's go <br>어디든 떠나자 <br>답답했던 지루한 <br>일상을 벗어날꺼야 <br>Why not <br>너와의 여행을 <br>걱정말고 손을 뻗어 <br>힘껏 날아오를꺼야 <br>Fly 낮에는 빛나는 무지개 빛 <br>Fly 밤에는 가로수 빛 따라서 <br>Oh we love it yeah <br>시원한 바람과 함께 <br>넌 날아갈거야 <br>까짓것 이러면 어때 <br>너 지쳤었잖아 <br>어디든 가보는거야 <br>다 던져버리고 <br>더이상 힘들어 하지마 <br>Tonight <br>달빛 아래 머물며 <br>어딜갈까 고민하지말고 <br>걸어 가보자 <br>Fly 하늘엔 떠오르는 별하나 <br>Fly 마음엔 차오르는 프리덤 <br>Oh we love it yeah <br>시원한 바람과 함께 <br>넌 날아갈거야 <br>까짓것 이러면 어때 <br>너 지쳤었잖아 <br>어디든 가보는거야 <br>다 던져버리고 <br>더이상 힘들어 하지마 <br>떠오르는 뜨거운 태양처럼 <br>날 뜨겁게 만드는 너란아이 <br>아이처럼 굴고 싶진않아 <br>but when I'm with you <br>아름다운 무지개 타고 <br>흐르는 구름과 <br>하나가 되어 <br>if you are ready go <br>Let'go to the move move <br>미칠 것 같잖아 <br>죽을 것 같잖아 <br>You and I will be together <br>시원한 바람과 함께 <br>넌 날아갈거야 <br>까짓것 이러면 어때 <br>너 지쳤었잖아 <br>어디든 가보는거야 <br>다 던져버리고 <br>더이상 힘들어 하지마 <br>]]></content><category term="대팔" label="대팔"/><category term="Flight (Feat. 바오)" label="Flight (Feat. 바오)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rakta/올라_Remix_3_Feat_Anthony_Dope_Auvers/</id><title>Rakta - 올라 Remix 3 (Feat. Anthony, Dope, Auvers) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:03:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:03:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rakta/%EC%98%AC%EB%9D%BC_Remix_3_Feat_Anthony_Dope_Auvers/" title="Rakta - 올라 Remix 3 (Feat. Anthony, Dope, Auvers) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이건 예의 삼아 <br>이 노래를 들을 때 <br>왜 하필 쟤라고 생각할분들 <br>엿 먹이는 Track <br>Once Upon A Time <br>난 Respect을 바래왔네 <br>허나 내 이름 외치면 <br>비교만 당해왔기에 <br>영하에서도 끓는 피 <br>꿀린다고 해도 <br>시선은 높이 <br>그래서 메모장을 <br>더 빼곡히 나의 <br>가사들로 채워갔지 <br>몇 놈들은 날 물로 봤지 <br>그럼 눈에 불을 <br>붙이고 손에 Hot Six <br>들고 버티며 작업한 <br>시간들이 Guarantee고 <br>나의 Energy <br>니들이 욕한 미운오리새끼는 <br>이제는 쳐다도 못 봐 <br>난 별을 목표로 날테니 <br>바삐 내 뒤꽁무니나 쫓아 <br>지치길 바라던 그놈은 <br>더 이를 악 물고서 <br>날개를 펴 <br>또 다른 무리 속에서도 <br>구름을 자가용삼아 <br>Accel을 밟어 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>사람들은 내게 말해 <br>성공이 아니면 왜 랩해 <br>그럼 나는 말해 <br>성공이 아니어도 난 랩해 <br>올라 몰라 어디까지 <br>갈껀지 몰라도 <br>All Right All Night <br>매일 가사 써대도 <br>쫓기는 맘은 So Tight <br>그래도 I'm So Fine <br>내 선택에 절대 <br>후횐 없어 더 보여줄게 <br>더 밀어 이 자격지심이 <br>등 떠밀어 날 더 <br>높이 올려줘 <br>더 더 높이 올려줘 <br>내 위친 구름위로 <br>물론 그건 내 밑거름이고 <br>이 곡은 내 성공의 <br>첫 걸음이죠 <br>Now I'm Featuring <br>But 일년 후엔 Main이 되겠지 <br>그래서 눈치 안봐 <br>한 길만 걸어 Maintain <br>내 기준은 절대 변하지 않아 <br>Fuckin' 남들 시선 <br>그 딴건 중요하지 않아 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>꿈이 너무 눈이 부셔 <br>넌 두 눈을 감았나 <br>널 둘러쌓던 벽은 <br>실은 허들이었잖아 <br>죽은 척 감은 눈을 떠 <br>눈에 불을 켜 눈을 부릅 떠 <br>나의 나침반 속 <br>바늘 방향은 구름 위 <br>탄 냄새가 배어가고 있는 <br>혓바닥과 누런 이 <br>작은 입과 고사리 손으로 <br>알록달록해 큰 그림 <br>꿇은 적이 없겠어 <br>내 무릎 이미 푸르딩딩 <br>쏟아 부어 <br>내 전부를 겨냥하여 <br>더 크게 울부짖지 <br>줄곧 날 부르는 <br>큰 구름 속을 <br>두루두루 거닐꺼야 <br>하늘위의 연이 되 <br>날 묶은 매듭을 끊을꺼야 <br>이해돼 임마 내 비상에 <br>딸릴 실패 없을꺼야 <br>엉터리로 접은 <br>종이비행기를 날려봐 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>생각에 생각이 자꾸 겹쳐 <br>나를 괴롭혀 <br>떨쳐내야 되는데 <br>지금도 벌벌 떠는 <br>신세가 괴로워 <br>Hold Up <br>미리 미리 준비했던 <br>것들인데 한계를 느껴 <br>Hold Up <br>미련하게 상상했던 미랜지만 <br>여기서 끝낼 수 없어 <br>Hold Up Blue In Ma Back <br>큰 그림 청사진 <br>전부다 어디있는데 <br>Hold Up 새까만 새벽이 <br>Hold Up 내 전부를 삼키면 <br>온통 Hold Up <br>새까만 화면 속 인생 <br>아무것도 몰라도 이젠 <br>느껴볼게 아무것도 <br>구속 말고 치부를 들여다볼게 <br>어릴 적 내가 <br>꿈꾸던 미랠 위해 <br>여전히 원해 <br>히피지지 않아 뒷짐 <br>니가 되고 싶어 했던 <br>행동들은 부질없지 <br>나일 때가 가장 아름답지 <br>딴지를 걸 일도 없지 <br>인생은 원이지 <br>결국 돌다보면 만나지 <br>머리 속 큰 그림 <br>목숨 같았던 펜촉으로 <br>목숨을 끊고 싶던 밤도 <br>무기력하게 방에서 <br>절규하던 과거도 <br>모두 끊어내고 올라가야지 <br>그래 우린 저 높이 올라가야지 <br>계속 올라가야지 <br>어쩌면 이미 올라가는 중이지 <br>어쩌면 이미 정상 위겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="Rakta" label="Rakta"/><category term="올라 Remix 3 (Feat. Anthony, Dope, Auvers)" label="올라 Remix 3 (Feat. Anthony, Dope, Auvers)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rakta/올라_Remix_2_Feat_Ragun_Mackoy_Beaver/</id><title>Rakta - 올라 Remix 2 (Feat. Ragun, Mackoy, Beaver) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:03:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:03:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rakta/%EC%98%AC%EB%9D%BC_Remix_2_Feat_Ragun_Mackoy_Beaver/" title="Rakta - 올라 Remix 2 (Feat. Ragun, Mackoy, Beaver) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여느 때와 다를 때같이 <br>또 일어났어 <br>두고 봐 니들과 다르다 <br>난 생각이 나를 더 조여왔어 <br>압박 또는 갑갑한 <br>이 맘이 꽉 막혀서 또 <br>계속 날 묶어놔 이제 좀 <br>그만 놔 줄 때가 됐어 <br>자 목소릴 풀어봐 <br>우린 목청껏 질러 뒤엎지 <br>저기 먼 산을 올라가 <br>가뿐히 또 넘지 <br>이제 그만 내가 <br>사는 술잔 따라 넘칠 <br>얘들아 네 얘길 풀어봐 <br>어디까지 갈지 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>작은 키와 나의 <br>외모는 그래 <br>자존감을 높여주지는 못했어 <br>사춘기의 나의 <br>Complex Complex <br>감당하기 힘들던 <br>뭇 여자들의 콧대 <br>No Thanks <br>그러던 나도 자신감이 <br>있었던 때가 있어 <br>생각해보면 결국 <br>맘먹기에 따라 달라지는 거 <br>난 바뀌었지만 <br>다시 변할 수 있어 <br>정해진 건 없어 <br>내가 선택한 모습이 <br>나 자신인 걸 <br>완벽하려는 맘이 되려 <br>앞에 벽을 만들었지 <br>남들과 비교하는 <br>눈이 가리는 내 가능성 <br>제대로 가던 <br>느낌을 기억해 다시 <br>남들이 뭐라던 자신에게 <br>당당한 나로 살아 <br>My Life <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>You Know Man <br>나는 Show And Prove <br>거짓된 망상은 <br>절대 No No No <br>언제나 곡을 뽑아 <br>미랠 위해 <br>커리어를 쌓고 <br>몇 명의 사람이 현실에 <br>넘어져도 난 또 <br>밟고 위로 가늠치 못해도 <br>계속해서 Go Go Go <br>어렸을 때와 나는 똑같애 <br>꿈꾸는 철부지 Peter Pen <br>생각 많은 Rodin <br>긍정적 Vibe 좋은 기운만 골라 <br>안좋은 시선은 버리고 <br>난 계속 올라가 <br>Woo Baby I Just Go <br>With The Flow <br>그 저 흐르는 대로 <br>이게 내 Motto <br>쓰면 없어질 것들은 <br>담아 두지 않아 <br>내가 따라가기보단 <br>따라오게 만들지 <br>StrongBerry We High <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>]]></content><category term="Rakta" label="Rakta"/><category term="올라 Remix 2 (Feat. Ragun, Mackoy, Beaver)" label="올라 Remix 2 (Feat. Ragun, Mackoy, Beaver)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rakta/올라_Remix_1_Feat_Taggie_Nyne/</id><title>Rakta - 올라 Remix 1 (Feat. Taggie, Nyne) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:03:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:03:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rakta/%EC%98%AC%EB%9D%BC_Remix_1_Feat_Taggie_Nyne/" title="Rakta - 올라 Remix 1 (Feat. Taggie, Nyne) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[올라가 우리들이 <br>원했던 곳으로 <br>좀더 나은 미랠 위해 <br>존나 멋진 모습으로 <br>Message From 2016 <br>엉터리 TV쇼가 <br>심어버린 힙합에 대한 <br>오해와 불신 Fuck That <br>수만 번 외워왔던 <br>명반들의 가사들을 <br>내 삶으로 옮기는 중이지 <br>So 필요 없는 Ranking <br>Nah Shit 신경 안쓰지 <br>니네 Bull Shit <br>난 안 멈추고 나갈꺼고 <br>니네들은 정지 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>내가 원하던 길을 <br>다 걷고있어 <br>그동안 밀린 페이들도 <br>전부 걷고 있고 <br>돈으로 못살 <br>가치들을 얻고 있어 <br>마침표 대신 <br>난 청사진을 찍는 <br>동시에 올라가겠지 <br>예술 시대의 흐름을 <br>거스른 삶 <br>나 혼자만 지지 <br>내가치를 갈갈이 찢지 <br>유난히 고독한 밤 <br>검정 색깔들만이 <br>진리라고만 생각하지 말어 <br>계속 말해왔듯이 <br>난 검은 청사진을 그려 <br>전부 말하네 올라오지마 <br>우린 영원히 급이 달라 <br>하긴 급이 다르지 한국래퍼들 <br>복사기들과는 급이 달러 <br>노는 물이달러 <br>철학이 달러 <br>자꾸 섞지 말어 <br>내 펜은 검은색인데도 <br>청사진을 그려 <br>Blue In Ma Back <br>그리던 미래 말야 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>올라갈 일만 남았네 <br>밑바닥은 더 없기에 <br>벌써 날아오르고 있네 <br>우리 인생은 High Way <br>그동안 눈앞을 가려왔던 <br>안대를 벗고 바라봤어 <br>나 가려던 곳 그리 멀지 <br>않은 곳에 있다는 걸 보고 <br>깨달았어 내려갈 곳 없어 <br>그럴 일 없어 <br>저기 저 하늘을 향해서 <br>비상 하는 새처럼 <br>날 애처로운 <br>눈빛으로 쳐다보던 <br>부모님 눈에서 눈물 <br>나는 날은 계획에 없어 <br>시원하게 불어오는 <br>순풍 타고 나를 일만 <br>남았어 나이는 <br>상관치마 개의치 않아 <br>뒤돌아볼 생각은 하지도 마 <br>우린 끝까지 저 위로 올라 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>올라 올라 저 하늘 끝까지 <br>몰라 몰라 어디까지 갈껀지 <br>생각에 생각이 겹쳐 <br>계속된 방황 밀쳐내고서 <br>열등감 증발해 생긴 <br>내 구름을 구름을 <br>타고 난 이제 <br>]]></content><category term="Rakta" label="Rakta"/><category term="올라 Remix 1 (Feat. Taggie, Nyne)" label="올라 Remix 1 (Feat. Taggie, Nyne)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신동수/울_엄마/</id><title>신동수 - 울 엄마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:03:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:03:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EB%8F%99%EC%88%98/%EC%9A%B8_%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88/" title="신동수 - 울 엄마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Momy Momy <br>울 엄마 최고 사랑해요 <br>엄마가 최고 울 엄마가 최고 <br>사랑하는 울 엄마 <br>희생과 사랑으로 늘 감싸주시니 <br>너무너무 사랑해요 <br>누구보다 제일 먼저 <br>아침일찍 일어나 <br>못난 아들 밥 해주는 울 엄마 <br>대강대강 만들어도 <br>그맛이 기가 막히는 <br>백종원 저리가라 <br>따귀치실 울 엄마 <br>매일 청소에 빨래에 늙어가시며 <br>몸이 부서져라 궂은일 <br>고생만 하시는 <br>엄마가 최고 울엄마가 최고 <br>사랑하는 울 엄마 <br>엄마가 고생하는 모든 것이 <br>너무너무 미안해요 오 <br>엄마가 최고 울 엄마가 최고 <br>사랑하는 울 엄마 <br>희생과 사랑으로 늘 감싸주시니 <br>너무너무 사랑해요 <br>Momy Momy <br>울 엄마 최고 사랑해요 <br>엄마가 최고 울 엄마가 최고 <br>사랑하는 울 엄마 <br>희생과 사랑으로 늘 감싸주시니 <br>너무너무 사랑해요 <br>백화점에 쇼핑 가면 <br>빈손으로 오시고 <br>이쁜딸 옷 사오는 울 엄마 <br>D 라인에 팔자 주름 <br>지금은 아줌마 지만 <br>송혜교 저리가라 <br>이뻤었던 울 엄마 <br>매일 청소에 빨래에 늙어가시며 <br>몸이 부서져라 굳은 일 <br>고생만 하시는 <br>엄마가 최고 울엄마가 최고 <br>사랑하는 울 엄마 <br>엄마가 고생하는 모든 것이 <br>너무너무 미안해요 오 <br>엄마가 최고 울 엄마가 최고 <br>사랑하는 울 엄마 <br>희생과 사랑으로 늘 감싸주시니 <br>너무너무 사랑해요 <br>희생과 사랑으로 늘 감싸주시니 <br>너무너무 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="신동수" label="신동수"/><category term="울 엄마" label="울 엄마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_아네모스/TORNADO/</id><title>ANEMOS_아네모스 - TORNADO - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:03:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:03:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ANEMOS_%EC%95%84%EB%84%A4%EB%AA%A8%EC%8A%A4/TORNADO/" title="ANEMOS_아네모스 - TORNADO - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람 한 점 불지 않는 <br>사막 같은 강가 <br>차가운 물 속에서 <br>흐려지는 감각 <br>창작을 위해서 <br>불을 지핀 장작은 <br>순간의 빛을 바래 <br>사라지고 말아 <br>현실의 문 앞에서 <br>제 3의 눈을 뜨고 바라보는 <br>선과 악과의 내면의 싸움 <br>밑받침 다 빼고 난 자음 <br>몰아치는 바람에 무너지는 자아 <br>현실을 봐 <br>부서지는 나무라도 잡아야지 다 <br>I'm on fire <br>타올라라 더 높게 타올라 <br>날아가 위로 더 위로 날아가 <br>펜을 쥐고 꽉 이빨을 갈아 <br>세상이란 막장에 한편의 드라마 <br>마지막까지 난 엑셀을 밟아 <br>막다른 길 앞에선 더 쌔게 밟아 <br>한 많은 삶 속에 열정의 화살은 <br>바람을 따라서 하늘을 날아가 <br>박자를 따르되 내 것을 위해서 <br>끝까지 날아가 <br>토네이도처럼 다 집어 삼켜 <br>내 꿈의 원을 더 크게 더 만들어 <br>볼케이노처럼 모두 다 태워 <br>내 미래를 위해서 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>위로 더 높이 <br>커다란 바람을 만들어 <br>토네이도처럼 다 집어 삼켜 <br>내 꿈의 원을 더 크게 더 만들어 <br>볼케이노처럼 모두 다 태워 <br>내 미래를 위해서 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>위로 더 높이 <br>커다란 바람을 만들어 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>제자리에서만 맴돌았어 <br>난 내일이 없다고만 생각했어 <br>막다른 길 앞에서 무너졌어 <br>창이 없는 방안에 날 가둬놨어 <br>나를 스쳐가던 바람이 점점 <br>더 쌔게 불어 나를 만들었어 <br>현실은 나를 더 강하게 만들어 <br>묶어놨던 와이어 <br>불이 붙은 타이어 <br>요동치는 핸들을 잡아 <br>다시 난 현실을 바라봐 <br>차가운 바람이 날 만들어 <br>다시 새로 피어나 <br>타올라라 더 높게 타올라 <br>날아가 위로 더 위로 날아가 <br>맨발로 가시 위에 섰더라도 <br>날카로운 못이 많은 길이라도 <br>한 걸음 더 발을 내디뎌 <br>난 커다란 바람을 만들어 <br>맨발로 가시 위에 섰더라도 <br>날카로운 못이 많은 길이라도 <br>한 걸음 더 발을 내디뎌 <br>난 커다란 바람을 만들어 <br>토네이도처럼 다 집어 삼켜 <br>내 꿈의 원을 더 크게 더 만들어 <br>볼케이노처럼 모두 다 태워 <br>내 미래를 위해서 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>위로 더 높이 <br>커다란 바람을 만들어 <br>토네이도처럼 다 집어 삼켜 <br>내 꿈의 원을 더 크게 더 만들어 <br>볼케이노처럼 모두 다 태워 <br>내 미래를 위해서 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>위로 더 높이 <br>커다란 바람을 만들어 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>나는 계속 더 <br>]]></content><category term="ANEMOS (아네모스)" label="ANEMOS (아네모스)"/><category term="TORNADO" label="TORNADO"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/루또_LUTTO/나그네_려/</id><title>루또_LUTTO - 나그네 려 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:03:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:03:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%98%90_LUTTO/%EB%82%98%EA%B7%B8%EB%84%A4_%EB%A0%A4/" title="루또_LUTTO - 나그네 려 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[발이 닿는대로 가는거야 <br>하고 싶은대로 하는거야 <br>가고 싶은 곳 하고 싶은 것 <br>할 수 있는 것 <br>죄다 하면서 사는거야 <br>역시나 바깥 날씨는 <br>또 화창해 예 <br>이런날은 언제든지 <br>너무 반갑네 예 <br>당연하다는듯 발은 <br>걷지 옥탑 위로 <br>아니 이번엔 인도가방 <br>둘러메고 <br>한강으로 가볼까 <br>내 자유로운 영혼 <br>초록색 푸른색 어울러진 <br>아름다운 자연으로 <br>그속에 숨어있는 <br>어여쁜 처자들 <br>좋아보이네 고맙네 <br>깨워주지 <br>자고있던 영감들 <br>오해하지마 저기 저여자 <br>보겠다고 한시간 <br>동안이나 졸면서 <br>버스타고 온건 아니야 <br>물론 옥탑이 <br>더워서도 아니고 <br>집 밥만 축내기도 그게 <br>너무 눈치 보여서도 <br>그래서 도망 <br>나온것도 아니야 <br>여럿의 무리중 <br>난 혼자 막걸리 무리중 <br>한강라면 사다가 누리는 <br>앞에 경치도 죽이군 <br>이런 여유 어때 <br>놈팽이라 불러도 <br>할말도 없네 어쨌든 좋네 <br>발이 닿는대로 가는거야 <br>하고 싶은대로 하는거야 <br>가고 싶은 곳 하고 싶은 것 <br>할 수 있는 것 <br>죄다 하면서 사는거야 <br>집에 보이는 눈치 <br>불효자가 된 느낌 <br>불효자가 불효자가 <br>효자가 되야지 <br>이제 효자가 되야지 <br>발이 닿는대로 가는거야 <br>뭐 어쨌든 좋지 <br>하고 싶은대로 하는거야 <br>응 역시 날이좋아 당연하게 <br>옥탑이나 가려다가 이번에는 <br>가끔 갔었던 카페나 가볼까 <br>여기는 떨어진 낙엽색 <br>삼삼오오 모여 수다떠네 <br>흘러나오는 힙합노래 <br>내 목소리도 나오겠지 <br>언젠가는 <br>생각 한번쯤 해보고 <br>이어폰을 꽂지 난 <br>그러고는 두리번 거려 <br>뭐있나 내앞엔 커피한잔 <br>오 안양에 어여쁜 처자들 <br>웬일로 여기다 이렇게 모였네 <br>아이고 또 우리 영감님 <br>자다가 벌떡 일어나셨네 <br>오해하지마 저기 저 여자 <br>보겠다고 사천 <br>오백원이나 쿨하게 <br>내면서 온건 아니야 <br>물론 옥탑이 더워서도 <br>거기에 벌레가 많아서도 <br>그게 너무 무서워서도 <br>그래서 도망나온것도 아니야 <br>발이 닿는대로 가는거야 <br>하고 싶은대로 하는거야 <br>가고 싶은 곳 하고 싶은 것 <br>할 수 있는 것 <br>죄다 하면서 사는거야 <br>집에 보이는 눈치 <br>불효자가 된 느낌 <br>불효자가 불효자가 <br>효자가 되야지 <br>이제 효자가 되야지 <br>발이 닿는대로 가는거야 <br>뭐 어쨌든 좋지 <br>하고 싶은대로 하는거야 <br>]]></content><category term="루또 (LUTTO)" label="루또 (LUTTO)"/><category term="나그네 려" label="나그네 려"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초코와_바닐라/아닌_척/</id><title>초코와_바닐라 - 아닌 척 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:04:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:04:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%BD%94%EC%99%80_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%90%EB%9D%BC/%EC%95%84%EB%8B%8C_%EC%B2%99/" title="초코와_바닐라 - 아닌 척 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[몰랐어 <br>그렇게만 믿었었어 <br>why why <br>내 마음만 이러는지 <br>어필은 되지만 <br>슬픔은 약점만 돼 <br>웃자 내게 말해 <br>슬프지 않은 척 <br>기쁘지 않은 척 <br>해야만 하는 것도 <br>이젠 지쳐 <br>아프지 않은 척 <br>적당히 하는 척 <br>있어야 하는 것도 <br>이젠 지쳐 <br>몰랐어 <br>그렇게만 믿었었어 <br>니가 하는 말이 전부 <br>Lie lie <br>눈물을 보여도 <br>마음은 약점만 돼 <br>웃자 내게 말해 <br>슬프지 않은 척 <br>기쁘지 않은 척 <br>해야만 하는 것도 <br>이젠 지쳐 <br>아프지 않은 척 <br>적당히 하는 척 <br>있어야 하는 것도 <br>이젠 지쳐 No no <br>참 바보 같잖아 <br>또 또 그리 눈치를 봐 <br>난 난 그렇게 나대로 안돼 <br>잘 안돼 <br>슬프지 않은 척 <br>기쁘지 않은 척 <br>억울할 수 있는 <br>나의 그 두려움에 <br>내 자신을 묶고 있는 걸 <br>아프지 않은 척 <br>적당히 하는 척 <br>가슴으로 내 맘 안아줄 <br>진심은 어디에 <br>]]></content><category term="초코와 바닐라" label="초코와 바닐라"/><category term="아닌 척" label="아닌 척"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초코와_바닐라/Gentle_Rain/</id><title>초코와_바닐라 - Gentle Rain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:04:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:04:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%BD%94%EC%99%80_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%90%EB%9D%BC/Gentle_Rain/" title="초코와_바닐라 - Gentle Rain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어제는 또 비가 많이 내렸어 <br>책상 위에 가지런히 놓였던 <br>물건들을 정리하려고 보니 <br>이제 조금 실감이 날 것도 같아 <br>자연스레 계절은 지나갔고 <br>익숙해진 것들도 낯설어져 <br>그렇게도 당연했던 것들도 모두 <br>꿈결처럼 느껴질 날도 오겠지 <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>이제 시간이 된 것 같아 <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>돌아가긴 힘들 것 같아 <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>헷갈리지 않도록 해줘 <br>Oh Gentle rain Gentle rain <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>좀 두려웠던 것도 같아 <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>당연하게 잊혀진단 게 <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>이 비가 다 그치고 나면 <br>날 기억할 그 누구도 <br>남아있지 않겠지 <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>Oh Gentle rain <br>이제 내가 떠나고 나면 <br>그 자리에 또 다른 <br>누군가가 오겠지 <br>그럼 그땐 꼭 다정한 <br>인사를 부탁할게 <br>]]></content><category term="초코와 바닐라" label="초코와 바닐라"/><category term="Gentle Rain" label="Gentle Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초코와_바닐라/Somethings_Wrong/</id><title>초코와_바닐라 - Something`s Wrong - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:04:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:04:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%BD%94%EC%99%80_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%90%EB%9D%BC/Somethings_Wrong/" title="초코와_바닐라 - Something`s Wrong - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[믿어야만 했어 그 눈빛을 <br>내게 다가온 듯한 그 느낌도 <br>맘을 열 수 없던 아쉬움도 <br>후회들만 쌓여 날 다그친다 <br>Something's Wrong <br>Something's Wrong <br>그 사람이 너의 그 사람이 <br>나여야만 했어 <br>Everyday Everynight <br>뒤척이며 널 놓친 슬픔에 <br>그리움만 <br>만약 이랬다면 어땠을까 <br>아무 의미도 없는 가정들만 <br>나를 웃게 했던 그 미소도 <br>작은 추억뿐으로 멀어져가 <br>Something's Wrong <br>Something's Wrong <br>그 사람이 너의 그 사람이 <br>나여야만 했어 <br>Everyday Everynight <br>뒤척이며 널 놓친 슬픔에 <br>그리움만 <br>So long So long <br>혼자서 되뇌어봤던 얘기들도 <br>So long So long <br>수없이 떠올린 그 시간들도 <br>Something's Wrong <br>Something's Wrong <br>이제 다신 그 설레임들도 <br>느낄 수 없겠지 <br>Everyday Everytime <br>아름답던 그 기억들은 <br>혼자 간직할게 <br>]]></content><category term="초코와 바닐라" label="초코와 바닐라"/><category term="Something`s Wrong" label="Something`s Wrong"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/초코와_바닐라/1_Page/</id><title>초코와_바닐라 - 1 Page - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:04:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:04:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B4%88%EC%BD%94%EC%99%80_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%90%EB%9D%BC/1_Page/" title="초코와_바닐라 - 1 Page - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 널 잘못 봤나 봐 <br>So long So long <br>멈춰버린 시간들은 또 <br>For long For long <br>Some People Say 넌 너무 착해 <br>조금 더 나빠지라 내게 말해 <br>궁금해 <br>Why Should I change <br>Because of like them <br>Nothing more than <br>Just the one page <br>변하지 않을래 이게 나인걸 <br>Why should I change <br>Just the one page <br>변해야 할 건 내가 아닌걸 <br>더한 상처가 날 비웃고 <br>더한 배신이 다그쳐도 <br>안 들을래 난 이 아픔도 다 <br>Just like one page <br>잠겨진 기억들마저 열어지고 <br>베여버린 상처들은 더 벌어져도 <br>I wanna say 그저 나 감사해 <br>지난 상처마저 가볍게 해 <br>너의 무게가 <br>But I don't need to change <br>you're burning one page <br>Nothing more than <br>Just the one page <br>변하지 않을래 이게 나인걸 <br>Why should I change <br>Just the one page <br>변해야 할 건 내가 아닌걸 <br>더한 상처가 날 비웃고 <br>더한 배신이 다그쳐도 <br>안 들을래 난 이 아픔도 다 <br>Just like one page <br>Now is so bad <br>But Love is not bad <br>Now is so bad <br>But Love is not bad not bad <br>Nothing more than <br>Just the one page <br>또다시 앞을 볼 수 없대도 <br>Why should I change <br>I'll do my best <br>사랑할 시간도 부족한 걸 <br>더한 아픔이 찾아와도 <br>덜 아플 수 있게 해줘서 <br>고마워 넌 재가 돼 버린 <br>Just the one Page <br>]]></content><category term="초코와 바닐라" label="초코와 바닐라"/><category term="1 Page" label="1 Page"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/엔투엔/I_Hate_You/</id><title>엔투엔 - I Hate You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:05:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:05:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%94%ED%88%AC%EC%97%94/I_Hate_You/" title="엔투엔 - I Hate You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밉다 밉다 참 밉다 <br>왜 그렇게 떠났니 <br>니가 그리워져서 <br>잠 못자고 있어 <br>밉다 밉다 참 밉다 <br>왜 날 사랑한거니 <br>내 마음 다 가지고 <br>넌 허무하게 떠났어 <br>사랑한다고 마지막 사랑이라고 <br>왜 말을 했니 나에게 <br>왜 너는 거짓말 했니 <br>정말 밉다 밉다 너무 밉다 <br>내 마음 울려버린 너 <br>너 밖에 없던 내게 <br>그럴 수가 있는지 <br>밉다 밉다 너무 밉다 <br>너를 찾고 싶은데 <br>모든 연락 끊고서 <br>어디로 넌 간거니 <br>밉다 밉다 참 밉다 <br>너를 믿었었는데 <br>냉정하게 떠나고 <br>슬픔만 남았어 <br>밉다 밉다 참 밉다 <br>원래 그런거였니 <br>내가 알지 못하는 <br>비밀이 너무 많구나 <br>난 순진했어 <br>너의 말을 다 믿었어 <br>돌아보면 다 거짓말 <br>내가 참 바보였나봐 <br>정말 밉다 밉다 너무 밉다 <br>내 마음 울려버린 너 <br>너 밖에 없던 내게 <br>그럴 수가 있는지 <br>밉다 밉다 너무 밉다 <br>너를 찾고 싶은데 <br>모든 연락 끊고서 <br>어디로 넌 간거니 <br>어디선가 또 이런 사랑하면 <br>이런 아픔 주지는 마 착하게 살아 <br>밉다 밉다 너무 밉다 <br>내 마음 울려버린 너 <br>너 밖에 없던 내게 <br>그럴 수가 있는지 <br>밉다 밉다 너무 밉다 <br>너를 찾고 싶은데 <br>모든 연락 끊고서 <br>어디로 넌 간거니 <br>밉다 밉다 너무 밉다 <br>내 마음 울려버린 너 <br>너 밖에 없던 내게 <br>그럴 수가 있는지 <br>밉다 밉다 너무 밉다 <br>너를 찾고 싶은데 <br>모든 연락 끊고서 <br>어디로 넌 간거니 <br>]]></content><category term="엔투엔" label="엔투엔"/><category term="I Hate You" label="I Hate You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권PD/울지마_울지마_울지마_Feat_김누리_Of_빅타임/</id><title>권PD - 울지마 울지마 울지마 (Feat. 김누리 Of 빅타임) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:05:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:05:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8CPD/%EC%9A%B8%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88_%EC%9A%B8%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88_%EC%9A%B8%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EB%88%84%EB%A6%AC_Of_%EB%B9%85%ED%83%80%EC%9E%84/" title="권PD - 울지마 울지마 울지마 (Feat. 김누리 Of 빅타임) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[울지마 울지마 울지마 <br>내 마음이 아파 <br>미안해 미안해 미안해 <br>내 잘못이야 <br>가지마 가지마 가지마 <br>내게 한번만 기회를줘 <br>이렇게 애원하는데 <br>어쩜 넌 <br>모두 몰라 <br>우리 둘만의 비밀 <br>너에 대한 내 호기심이 <br>알다가도 모를 <br>사랑이 있어 <br>숨겨야 했었던 그때 우리 <br>서로 더 애뜻할 줄 알았는데 <br>더 사랑할 줄 알았는데 <br>울지마 울지마 울지마 <br>내 마음이 아파 <br>미안해 미안해 미안해 <br>내 잘못이야 <br>가지마 가지마 가지마 <br>내게 한번만 기회를 줘 <br>이렇게 애원하는데 <br>어쩜 넌 <br>속삭여도 크게 들려 <br>들킬까봐 <br>헤어지며 잡은 손 <br>놓아버릴 때 <br>더 아파질 줄 몰랐는데 <br>더 외로울 줄 몰랐는데 <br>울지마 울지마 울지마 <br>내 마음이 아파 <br>미안해 미안해 미안해 <br>내 잘못이야 <br>가지마 가지마 가지마 <br>내게 한번만 기회를 줘 <br>이렇게 애원하는데 <br>어쩜 넌 <br>]]></content><category term="권PD" label="권PD"/><category term="울지마 울지마 울지마 (Feat. 김누리 Of 빅타임)" label="울지마 울지마 울지마 (Feat. 김누리 Of 빅타임)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/L1lPrince/열정페이_Feat_OMG_Black2shit/</id><title>L1lPrince - 열정페이 (Feat. OMG, Black2shit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:07:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:07:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/L1lPrince/%EC%97%B4%EC%A0%95%ED%8E%98%EC%9D%B4_Feat_OMG_Black2shit/" title="L1lPrince - 열정페이 (Feat. OMG, Black2shit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pay me money money money money money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Why’d u hire me <br>when u aint got no money <br>yeah I want it 원해 원 엔 달러 money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>please don’t hire me <br>when u aint got no money <br>yeah I want it 원해 원 엔 달러 money <br>열정은 환전이 안돼요 boss <br>내가 원하는건 오직 원화 <br>열정은 대체 어디 <br>money money money money <br>내가하는 일은 똥으로 보이니 <br>Uh 내 공연 페이 쟤 그림 페이 <br>춤추는 애기들이 <br>poppin 으로 받는 페이 <br>비트메이커가 <br>비트 찍고 받는 페이 <br>니 눈에 우린 그저 <br>분리수거 재활용이지 <br>열정페이 보단 돈이 급해 <br>계좌이체 또는 내놔 지폐 <br>답답해 끊이 짧은 back pack <br>내 스팩은 식스팩 <br>뚜렷하지 않아서 <br>경험이라고 생각하고 <br>하라고 니 인턴 <br>명훈이형이 때려쳤던 에머 인턴 <br>음악가란 title 로 알바뛰는 이유 <br>랩한다는 형이 나랑 <br>교대하는 이유 cuz you <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Why’d u hire me <br>when u aint got no money <br>yeah I want it 원해 원 엔 달러 money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>please don’t hire me <br>when u aint got no money <br>yeah I want it 원해 원 엔 달러 money <br>내 꿈을 이루기 위해 필요한 <br>내 예산은 턱없이 부족해 <br>세상의 기준에 난 열정이 부족해 <br>벌써 몇번째인지 몰라 목말라 난 <br>똑같은 얘기만 계속 반복해 <br>달라지는게 없으니 그런거겠지 <br>난 갖고 있어 값으론 <br>따질 수 없는 가치를 <br>그래서 내게 값을 <br>매겨주질 않나봐 <br>난 앞만 보고 가고 싶은데 <br>놈들은 또 내 지갑을 털어가 <br>왜 열정은 환전이 안돼요 boss <br>내가 원하는건 나의 평화 <br>최소한 필요한 내 <br>money money money money money <br>내 지갑 속에 있던 돈은 어디갔니 <br>다 어디가 빨리 가 금 같은 시간 <br>투자해도 주머니엔 텅 빈 지갑 <br>난 그저 노력의 댓가를 바랄 뿐 <br>뭐라도 해줘봐 가끔 <br>딴 소리 해봤자 결국 <br>할 얘긴 이 말 하나뿐 <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Why’d u hire me <br>when u aint got no money <br>yeah I want it 원해 원 엔 달러 money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>please don’t hire me <br>when u aint got no money <br>yeah I want it 원해 원 엔 달러 money <br>돈 나에 주머니에서 쌔볐니 <br>내 가부칠 좆으로 봤니 <br>U steal ma skillz and ma time bitch <br>And I neva turn ma back <br>On ma money <br>내 돈을 계속 봤니 둘러봐 <br>All these bitches wanna honey <br>그래서 나 꿀을 따러갔다가 <br>우리 사장님 나에게 <br>돈을 계속 뜯어가 <br>전경태 바삐 계속 일했어요 <br>전경태 사장님이 돈 뜯어요 <br>우리 작업실에 <br>월세도 내야되는데 <br>텅빈 주머니에 내가 뭐를 내긴내 man <br>교수님 나도 월급 주세요 <br>교수님 나도 먹고 살게요 <br>말 안돼 이건 보상 아닌 권리 <br>나는 학생 이전 시민 <br>이제 give ma hook and honey <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Why’d u hire me <br>when u aint got no money <br>yeah I want it 원해 원 엔 달러 money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>Pay me money money money money money <br>please don’t hire me <br>when u aint got no money <br>yeah I want it 원해 원 엔 달러 money <br>]]></content><category term="L1lPrince" label="L1lPrince"/><category term="열정페이 (Feat. OMG, Black2shit)" label="열정페이 (Feat. OMG, Black2shit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정직한_멜로디/아픔은_혼자서_느끼는게_아니야/</id><title>정직한_멜로디 - 아픔은 혼자서 느끼는게 아니야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:08:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:08:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%A7%81%ED%95%9C_%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C%EB%94%94/%EC%95%84%ED%94%94%EC%9D%80_%ED%98%BC%EC%9E%90%EC%84%9C_%EB%8A%90%EB%81%BC%EB%8A%94%EA%B2%8C_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%88%EC%95%BC/" title="정직한_멜로디 - 아픔은 혼자서 느끼는게 아니야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 가슴속에 <br>감춰둔 아픔 <br>너는 아니라고 하지만 <br>내겐 감출 수 없는걸 <br>근데 너 그거 아니 <br>너의 아픔은 내게로 와 <br>너만의 것이라고 하지만 <br>세상에 그런 건 없어 <br>아픔은 혼자서 느끼는 게 아냐 <br>혼자만 울지 않기를 <br>그 자리에 서 있기를 <br>니 곁에 같이 서서 울 수 있게 <br>혼자의 아픔이 아니야 <br>세상에 그런 건 없어 <br>내가 널 몰랐으면 몰라도 <br>그런 건 없어 <br>내가 같이 울어줄게 <br>넌 그 자리에 있으면 돼 <br>아픔은 혼자서 느끼는 게 아냐 <br>혼자만 울지 않기를 <br>그 자리에 서 있기를 <br>니 곁에 같이 서서 울 수 있게 <br>혼자의 아픔이 아니야 <br>세상에 그런 건 없어 <br>내가 널 몰랐으면 몰라도 <br>그런 건 없어 <br>더 이상 너 울지 않기를 <br>바보처럼 숨지 않기를 <br>너와 나 같은 것을 볼 수 있게 <br>혼자의 아픔이 아니야 <br>세상에 그런 건 없어 <br>내가 널 몰랐으면 몰라도 <br>그런 건 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="정직한 멜로디" label="정직한 멜로디"/><category term="아픔은 혼자서 느끼는게 아니야" label="아픔은 혼자서 느끼는게 아니야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Kaikuranta/Takki_Auki_Tuulessa/</id><title>Jesse_Kaikuranta - Takki Auki Tuulessa - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:10:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:10:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Kaikuranta/Takki_Auki_Tuulessa/" title="Jesse_Kaikuranta - Takki Auki Tuulessa - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Vahan vaan huimaa <br>kun linnut huutaa <br>sekavaa laulua, en selvaa saa <br><br>siita ne lentaa ylitse mun paan <br>paan joka on vapaana turhista <br>musta tuntuu et sivu oon <br>ma ihan valkee, kohta sydan halkee <br>tuu <br>elama tuu muhun kirjottaa <br>krapula seuraa humalaa aina <br>luonto niin toimii se on fysiikkaa <br>tai jotain karmaa mita se onkaan <br>kavelen takki auki tuulessa <br>musta tuntuu et sivu oon <br>ma ihan valkee, kohta sydan halkee <br>tuu <br>elama tuu muhun kirjottaa <br>musta tuntuu et sivu oon <br>ma ihan valkee, kohta sydan halkee <br>tuu <br>elama tuu muhun kirjottaa]]></content><category term="Jesse Kaikuranta" label="Jesse Kaikuranta"/><category term="Takki Auki Tuulessa" label="Takki Auki Tuulessa"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Kaikuranta/Surusilma/</id><title>Jesse_Kaikuranta - Surusilma - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:10:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:10:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Kaikuranta/Surusilma/" title="Jesse_Kaikuranta - Surusilma - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lahde, jonkun toisen matkaan <br>soita mulle yolla vuoden paasta taas <br>voit olla varma, hetkeekaan en mieti <br>ehdoitta ma saavun sua noutamaan <br><br>Sina oot se paatos jonka pyorran <br>takki jonka kaannan, vaikka pelottaa <br>sina oot se mihin loppuu kohtuus <br>mista alkaa hulluus, jarjeton rakkaus <br><br>Miksi se uskoo <br>miksi se toivoo <br>miksi se karsii mutta kestaa <br>miksi se vain riuhtoo <br>miksei se irtoo <br>miksi se karsii mutta kestaa <br>miksei sita hengilta saa <br><br>Loukkaa tuhat kertaa viela <br>vaita ettet tieda miesta huononpaa <br>voit olla varma anteeksi saat aina <br>ei kai ole sulla sen helpompaa <br><br>Mina oon se paatos jonka pyorrat <br>takki jonka kaannat, kun me suudellaan <br>sina oot se mihin loppuu kohtuus <br>mista alkaa hulluus, jarjeton rakkaus <br><br>Miksi se uskoo <br>miksi se toivoo <br>miksi se karsii mutta kestaa <br>miksi se vain riuhtoo <br>miksei se irtoo <br>miksi se karsii mutta kestaa <br><br>Jarjeton rakkaus pelottavan vahva <br>kuristava voima <br>sano miksi se kaiken uskoo <br>miksi se toivoo <br>miksi se kestaa <br>miksei sita hengilta saa <br><br>Lahden uudelleen <br>sina tiedat kuinka kaipuu kiskaisee <br>suruketjustansa rakkaus riuhtaisee <br>sut takaisin aina, aina <br><br>Miksi se uskoo <br>miksi se toivoo <br>miksi se karsii mutta kestaa <br>miksi se vain riuhtoo <br>miksei se irtoo <br>miksi se karsii mutta kestaa <br><br>Jarjeton rakkaus pelottavan vahva <br>kuristava voima <br>sano miksi se kaiken uskoo <br><br>Miksi se toivoo <br>miksi se kestaa <br>miksei sita hengilta saa]]></content><category term="Jesse Kaikuranta" label="Jesse Kaikuranta"/><category term="Surusilma" label="Surusilma"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Kaikuranta/Viela_Yksi_Laulu/</id><title>Jesse_Kaikuranta - Viela Yksi Laulu - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:10:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:10:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Kaikuranta/Viela_Yksi_Laulu/" title="Jesse_Kaikuranta - Viela Yksi Laulu - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ma en tullut sua ryostamaan keltaan <br>Enka tullut kanssas pelehtimaan <br>Ma tahdoin nahda vain jos hymyilet viela noin <br><br>ja ei sen enempaa <br>ala pelkaa, ma en pyyda mitaan <br><br>Vaikka siina maailmassa <br>missa ma kayn mun unissa <br>ma kylla sain sut lopulta <br>ja joo, me saatiin lapsia <br><br>Tai suudellaanko viela kertaalleen <br>Sa oot aivan mieleton <br>voi jeesus, me oisimme yhteen kuuluneet <br>Nyt on huono aika taas <br>ma meen, ma meen <br>Niinku aina ennen <br>humalassa yhden uuden laulun sulle teen <br><br>Ihan kohta muut jo huolestuu meista <br>heita kohtaan taa ei olisi reiluu <br>Jotkut haaveet ei vaan voi toteutuu <br>siis jaita hattuun <br>Nyt seis, ennen kuin sattuu <br><br>Vaikka siina maailmassa <br>missa ma kayn mun unissa <br>me kylla saatiin rakastaa <br>ei ne olleet pahoillaan <br><br>Mut suudellaanko viela kertaalleen <br>Sa oot aivan mieleton <br>voi jeesus, me oisimme yhteen kuuluneet <br><br>nyt on huono aika taas <br>ma meen, ma meen <br>Niinku aina ennen <br>niinku aina ennenkin <br><br>Mut suudellaanko viela kertaalleen <br>Sa oot aivan mieleton <br>voi jeesus, me oisimme yhteen kuuluneet <br>Nyt on huono aika taas <br>ma meen, ma meen <br>Niinku aina ennen <br>humalassa yhden uuden laulun sulle teen <br><br>Viela yksi laulu <br>sille jota ikina emme saa <br>Viela yksi laulu <br>sille jota ikina emme saa <br>Viela yksi laulu <br>sille jota ikina emme saa <br>Viela yksi laulu]]></content><category term="Jesse Kaikuranta" label="Jesse Kaikuranta"/><category term="Viela Yksi Laulu" label="Viela Yksi Laulu"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/God_Save_The_Queen/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - God Save The Queen - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:11:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:11:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/God_Save_The_Queen/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - God Save The Queen - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[God save our gracious Queen <br>Long live our noble Queen <br>God save the Queen <br>Send her victorious <br>Happy and glorious <br>Long to reign over us <br>God save the Queen <br><br>O Lord, our God, arise <br>Scatter her enemies <br>And make them fall <br>Confound their politics <br>Frustrate their knavish tricks <br>On thee our hopes we fix <br>God save the Queen <br><br>Thy choicest gifts in store <br>On her be pleased to pour <br>Long may she reign <br>May she defend our laws <br>And ever give us cause <br>To sing with heart and voice <br>God save the Queen <br><br>From every latent foe <br>From the assassins blow <br>God save the Queen <br>O'er her thine arm extend <br>For Britain's sake defend <br>Our mother, prince, and friend <br>God save the Queen]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="God Save The Queen" label="God Save The Queen"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Wayfarin_Stranger/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Wayfarin` Stranger - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:11:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:11:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Wayfarin_Stranger/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Wayfarin` Stranger - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm just a poor wayfaring stranger <br>I'm traveling through this world of woe <br>Yet there's no sickness, toil nor danger <br>In that bright land to which I go <br><br>I'm going there to see my mother <br>I'm going there no more to roam <br>I'm only going over Jordan <br>I'm only going over home <br><br>I know dark clouds will gather 'round me <br>I know my way is rough and steep <br>Yet golden fields lie just before me <br>Where God's redeemed shall ever sleep <br><br>I'm going there to see my father <br>He said he'd meet me when I come <br>I'm only going over Jordan <br>I'm only going over home <br><br>I want to wear a crown of glory <br>When I get home to that good land <br>I want to shout salvation's story <br>In concert with the blood washed band <br><br>I'm going there to meet my Saviour <br>To sing his praise forever more <br>I'm just a going over Jordan <br>I'm just a going over home]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Wayfarin` Stranger" label="Wayfarin` Stranger"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/This_Land_Is_Your_Land/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - This Land Is Your Land - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:11:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:11:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/This_Land_Is_Your_Land/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - This Land Is Your Land - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This land is your land, this land is my land <br>From California, to the New York Island <br>From the redwood forest, to the gulf stream waters <br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>As I was walking a ribbon of highway <br>I saw above me an endless skyway <br>I saw below me a golden valley <br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>This land is your land, this land is my land <br>From California, to the New York Island <br>From the redwood forest, to the gulf stream waters <br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>I've roamed and rambled and I've followed my footsteps <br>To the sparkling sands of her diamond deserts <br>And all around me a voice was sounding <br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>This land is your land, this land is my land <br>From California, to the New York Island <br>From the redwood forest, to the gulf stream waters <br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>The sun comes shining as I was strolling <br>The wheat fields waving and the dust clouds rolling <br>The fog was lifting a voice come chanting <br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>This land is your land, this land is my land <br>From California, to the New York Island <br>From the redwood forest, to the gulf stream waters <br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>As I was walkin' I saw a sign there <br>And that sign said no tress passin' <br>But on the other side it didn't say nothin <br>Now that side was made for you and me <br><br>This land is your land, this land is my land <br>From California, to the New York Island <br>From the redwood forest, to the gulf stream waters <br>This land was made for you and me <br><br>In the squares of the city In the shadow of the steeple <br>Near the relief office I see my people <br>And some are grumblin' and some are wonderin' <br>If this land's still made for you and me <br><br>This land is your land, this land is my land <br>From California, to the New York Island <br>From the redwood forest, to the gulf stream waters <br>This land was made for you and me <br>This land is your land, this land is my land <br>From California, to the New York Island <br>From the redwood forest, to the gulf stream waters <br>This land was made for you and me]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="This Land Is Your Land" label="This Land Is Your Land"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Jesus_Chariot/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Jesus` Chariot - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:11:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:11:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Jesus_Chariot/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Jesus` Chariot - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She'll be coming round the mountain when she comes <br>She'll be coming round the mountain when she comes <br>She'll be coming round the mountain, she'll be coming round the mountain <br>She'll be coming round the mountain when she comes <br><br>She'll be driving six white horses when she comes <br>She'll be driving six white horses when she comes <br>She'll be driving six white horses, she'll be driving six white horses <br>She'll be driving six white horses when she comes <br><br>Oh, we'll all go out to meet her when she comes <br>Oh, we'll all go out to meet her when she comes <br><br>Oh, we'll all go out to meet her, we'll all go out to meet her <br>We'll all go out to meet her when she comes <br><br>She'll be wearing red pajamas when she comes <br>She'll be wearing red pajamas when she comes <br><br>She'll be wearing red pajamas, she'll be wearing red pajamas <br>She'll be wearing red pajamas when she comes <br><br>She will have to sleep with Grandma when she comes <br>She will have to sleep with Grandma when she comes <br>She will have to sleep with Grandma, she will have to sleep with Grandma <br>She will have to sleep with Grandma when she comes]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Jesus` Chariot" label="Jesus` Chariot"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/High_Flyin_Bird/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - High Flyin` Bird - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:11:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:11:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/High_Flyin_Bird/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - High Flyin` Bird - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a high flyin' bird, flying way up in the sky <br>And I wonder if she looks down, as she goes on by <br>Well, she's flying so freely in the sky <br><br>Lord, look at me here <br>I'm rooted like a tree here <br>Got those sit down can't cry <br>Oh Lord, gonna die blues <br><br>Now the sun it comes up and lights up the day <br>And when he gets tired, Lord, he goes on down his way <br>To the east and to the west he meets God every day <br><br>Lord, look at me here <br>I'm rooted like a tree here <br>Got those sit down, can't cry <br>Oh Lord, gonna die blues <br><br>Now I had a woman <br>Lord, she lived down by the mine <br>She ain't never seen the sun <br>Oh Lord, never stopped crying <br><br>Then one day my woman up and died <br>Lord, she up and died now <br>Oh Lord, she up and died now <br>She wanted to die and the only way to fly is die, die, die <br><br>Well there's a high flyin' bird, flying way up in the sky <br>And I wonder if she looks down as she goes on by <br>Well, she's flying so freely in the sky, hey <br><br>Lord, look at me here <br>I'm rooted like a tree here <br>Got those sit down, can't cry <br>Oh, Lord, gonna die blues <br><br>Got those sit down, can't cry <br>Oh, Lord, gonna die blues, hey hey]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="High Flyin` Bird" label="High Flyin` Bird"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Travel_On/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Travel On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:11:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:11:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Travel_On/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Travel On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've laid around and played around <br>This old town too long <br>Summer's almost gone <br>Yes, winter's comin' on <br>I've laid around and played around <br>This old town too long <br>And I feel like I gotta travel on <br><br>Poppa writes to Johnny <br>But Johnny can't come home <br>Johnny can't come home <br>No, Johnny can't come home <br>Poppa writes to Johnny <br>But Johnny can't come home <br>Cause he's been on the chain gang too long <br><br>I've laid around and played around <br>This old town too long <br>Summer's almost gone <br>Yes, winter's comin' on <br>I've laid around and played around <br>This old town too long <br>And I feel like I gotta travel on <br><br>High sheriff and police riding after me <br>Riding after me, yes, coming after me <br>High sheriff and police coming after me <br>And I fee like I gotta travel on <br><br>I've laid around and played around <br>This old town too long <br>Summer's almost gone <br>Yes, winter's comin' on <br>I've laid around and played around <br>This old town too long <br>And I feel like I gotta travel on <br><br>Want to see my honey <br>Want to see her bad <br>Want to see her bad <br>Oh, want to see her bad <br>Want to see my honey <br>Want to see her bad <br>She's the best girl <br>This poor boy ever had <br><br>I've laid around and played around <br>This old town too long <br>Summer's almost gone <br>Yes, winter's comin' on <br>I've laid around and played around <br>This old town too long <br>And I feel like I gotta travel on]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Travel On" label="Travel On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Get_A_Job/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Get A Job - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:11:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:11:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Get_A_Job/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Get A Job - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yip yip yip yip yip yip, bmm <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na <br>Ahh, yip yip yip yip yip yip yip yip <br>Mum mum mum mum mum mum, get a job <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na <br><br>Well every morning about this time Sha na na na, sha na na na na <br>She gets me out of bed, a crying get a job Sha na na na, sha na na na na <br>After breakfast everyday she throws the want ads right my way <br>And never fails to say get a job <br><br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na <br>Ahh, yip yip yip yip yip yip yip yip <br>Mum mum mum mum mum mum, get a job <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na <br><br>Lord, and when I get the paper I read it through and through <br>I, my girl never fail to see if there is any work for me <br>I got to go back to the house, hear that woman's mouth <br>Preachin' and a cryin', tell me that I'm lyin' about a job <br>That I never could find <br><br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na <br>Ahh, yip yip yip yip yip yip yip yip <br>Mum mum mum mum mum mum, get a job <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na <br><br>Lord, and when I get the paper I read it through and throu ough <br>I, my girl never fail to see if there is any work for me <br>I better go back to the house, hear that woman's mouth <br>Preachin' and a cryin', tell me that I'm lyin' about a job <br>That I never could find <br><br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do <br>Sha na na na, sha na na na na, ahh do]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Get A Job" label="Get A Job"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Gallows_Pole/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Gallows Pole - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:11:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:11:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Gallows_Pole/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Gallows Pole - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Father, did you bring me the silver <br>Father, did you bring me the gold <br>What did you bring me, dear father <br>Keep me from the gallows pole <br><br>Yeah, what did you <br>Yeah, what did you <br>What did you bring me, keep me from the gallows pole <br><br>Mother, did you bring me the silver <br>Mother, did you bring me the gold <br>What did you bring me, dear mother <br>Keep me from the gallows pole <br><br>Yeah, what did you <br>Yeah, what did you <br>What did you bring me, keep me from the gallows pole <br><br>Son, I brought you some silver <br>Son, I brought you some gold <br>Son, I brought you a little of everything <br>Keep you from the gallows pole <br><br>Yeah, I brought it <br>Yeah, I brought it <br>I brought you, keep you from the gallows pole <br><br>Wife, did you bring me the silver <br>Wife, did you bring me the gold <br>What did you bring me, dear wifey <br>Save me from the gallows pole <br><br>Yeah, what did you <br>Yeah, what did you <br>What did you bring me, keep me from the gallows pole <br><br>Friends, did you bring me the silver <br>Friends, did you bring me the gold <br>What did you bring me, my dear friends <br>Keep me from the gallows pole <br><br>Yeah, what did you <br>Yeah, what did you <br>What did you bring me, keep me from the gallows pole]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Gallows Pole" label="Gallows Pole"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Tom_Dula/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Tom Dula - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:11:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:11:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Tom_Dula/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Tom Dula - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Hang down your head and cry <br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Poor boy, you're bound to die <br>I met her on the mountain <br>There I took her life <br>Met her on the mountain <br>Stabbed her with my knife <br><br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Hang down your head and cry <br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Poor boy, you're bound to die <br><br>This time tomorrow <br>Reckon where I'll be <br>Hadn't a been for Grayson <br>I'd a been in Tennessee <br><br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Hang down your head and cry <br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Poor boy, you're bound to die <br><br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Hang down your head and cry <br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Poor boy, you're bound to die <br><br>This time tomorrow <br>Reckon where I'll be <br>Down in some lonesome valley <br>Hangin' from a white oak tree <br><br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Hang down your head and cry <br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Poor boy, you're bound to die <br><br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Hang down your head and cry <br>Hang down your head, Tom Dooley <br>Poor boy, you're bound to die <br><br>Poor boy, you're bound to die <br>Poor boy you're bound to die <br>Poor boy, you're bound to die]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Tom Dula" label="Tom Dula"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Clementine/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Clementine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:12:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:12:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Clementine/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Clementine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In a cavern, in a canyon <br>Excavating for a mine <br>Dwelt a miner forty niner <br>And his daughter Clementine <br><br>Light she was and like a fairy <br>And her shoes were number nine <br>Herring boxes, without topses <br>Sandals were for Clementine <br><br>Clementine Clementine <br>Oh my darling, Clementine <br><br>Drove she ducklings to the water <br>Ev'ry morning just at nine <br>Hit her foot against a splinter <br>Fell into the foaming brine <br><br>Ruby lips above the water <br>Blowing bubbles, soft and fine <br>But, alas, I was no swimmer <br>So I lost my Clementine <br><br>Clementine Clementine <br>Oh my darling, Clementine <br><br>Then the miner forty niner <br>Soon began to peak and pine <br>Thought he ought'er join his daughter <br>Now he's with his Clementine <br><br>In my dreams she still does haunt me <br>Robed in garments soaked in brine <br>Though in life I used to hug her <br>In death I draw the line <br><br>Clementine Clementine <br>Oh my darling, Clementine <br><br>How I missed her How I missed her <br>How I missed my Clementine <br>So I kissed her little sister <br>I forgot my Clementine <br><br>Clementine Clementine <br>Oh my darling, Clementine]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Clementine" label="Clementine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Oh_Susannah/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Oh Susannah - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:12:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:12:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Oh_Susannah/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Oh Susannah - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Susannah Oh Susannah <br>Oh Susannah Oh Susannah <br><br>I had a dream the other night <br>Everything was still <br>I dreamed I saw Susannah <br>She was comin' down the hill <br><br>Oh, oh, oh, Susannah <br>Don't you cry for me oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br>'cause I come from Alabama with my B A N J O on my knee <br>Oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br><br>Buckwheat cake was in her mouth <br>The tear was in her eye <br>Says I'm comin' from the South <br>Susannah don't you cry <br><br>Oh, oh, oh, Susannah <br>Don't you cry for me oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br>'cause I come from Alabama with a B A N J O on my knee <br>Oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br><br>Rained all night the day I left <br>The weather it was dry <br>Sun so hot I froze to death <br>Susannah don't you cry <br><br>Oh, oh, oh, Susannah <br>Don't you cry for me oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br>'cause I come from Alabama with my B A N J O on my knee <br>Oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br><br>I had a dream the other night <br>Everything was still <br>I dreamed I saw Susannah <br>She was comin' down the hill <br><br>Oh, oh, oh, Susannah <br>Don't you cry for me oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br>'cause I come from Alabama with my B A N J O on my knee <br>Oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br><br>Well I come from Alabama <br>With my banjo on my knee <br>I'm goin' to Louisiana <br>My true love for to see <br><br>Oh, oh, oh, Susannah <br>Don't you cry for me oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br>'cause I come from Alabama with my B A N J O on my knee <br>Oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br>Yeah, I come from Alabama with my B A N J O on my knee <br>Oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br>Yeah, I come from Alabama with my B A N J O on my knee <br><br>I come from Alabama with my B A N J O on my knee <br>Oh Susannah, oh Susannah <br>I come from Alabama with my B A N J O on my knee]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Oh Susannah" label="Oh Susannah"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Sustain/</id><title>Conspire - Sustain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:14:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:14:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Sustain/" title="Conspire - Sustain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The faces that greet us, the places that house us The bars that we drink at, the words that we sing to ourselves You keep down your voice, you keep to yourself Your unwanted things that wanted to help So find a place inside and stay there all the time In a place somewhere where a comforting word from a friend could be heard From a mile away, perhaps it's ringing, perhaps the universe sings to us Perhaps everyone you know is slowly drifting towards the dark, apart But for time to burn I would as well I would burn as well and not keep myself in places where my welcome has worn the hole in which I fell I should have been there when you died I shouldn't have to blame myself I took a ride it was the scenic route Astray Little to gain, so much to lose But I didn't know back at that time, back in the time It wasn't mine, my life has changed so much Just bring it back to before Walk away from home, walk away from Hell Walk away from my loneliness, walk away from myself Walk away from here, walk away from Hell Walk away from my loneliness, walk away from myself 'Cause our time we spent was time spent well And I keep holding onto the memories, the memories everlasting, but I lost track of myself back there And if I could find you I'd give you back these wasted days And it took living in a place where no one wanted me at all, feeling lost everyday before I could finally say, I'm here Doesn't mean that I'm never gonna find you But carry on this way, not a chance]]></content><category term="Conspire" label="Conspire"/><category term="Sustain" label="Sustain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Worth_Waking/</id><title>Conspire - Worth Waking - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:14:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:14:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Worth_Waking/" title="Conspire - Worth Waking - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He was a man my age, his society enforcing an idea He feels like he's under attack all the time He didn't have to fight But we have to navigate through the lies, creating the borders of a nation, and whether you realize it or not, we're all being trained for it You can be enslaved to a thought long enough to forget you can leave You don't have to live with that guilt, you don't owe it anything I'm waking from your dream Alive there are no masters and the clouds keep moving faster I won't say it again I swear to God I won't say it again You're already rich so calm down you're already rich to me Don't you feel like your life's just good enough for now, we're losing everything I am a traitor Inside of every single one of us another one is waiting We must evolve towards peace 'Cause no one ever stood in crosshairs over any good thing humanity has brought here We have a choice to stop feeding this machine May each of us in duty hang our weapons up May all our institutions turn their gazes up towards feeding, and healing, and tracing greed back to the source Turning our backs on what we have could be the greatest thing we've ever done]]></content><category term="Conspire" label="Conspire"/><category term="Worth Waking" label="Worth Waking"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Captive_Son/</id><title>Conspire - Captive Son - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:14:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:14:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Captive_Son/" title="Conspire - Captive Son - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Asleep in a chair, the razor burn a reminder that here sits a new man Left with nothing but a bible that stays shut for peace of mind 'Cause if you open up too much you'll get a twisted spine And anywhere back home is just a place to hold your head up high 'Cause you're the man who took the bait to go on a hunt with fate See it's all about the distance, holding our weapons towards the sky And as the dark clouds continue billowing, we say, as long as it wasn't me Sing praises over these ugly chords that do distort what it means to learn to walk in peace, holding an M16 You shouldn't sleep, but have the thought of waking from this hurtful game and make a stand for your foes Perhaps a vengeful God would be appeased Three years I've trained and now I'm strong enough to say my name's of no use to you I mean you no harm, as I mean any beneath the stars So carry on away renewed I was called to love your worst enemies And my last ditch remains off the battlefield And this crooked back remains here to this day, but the conflict stays contained inside of me]]></content><category term="Conspire" label="Conspire"/><category term="Captive Son" label="Captive Son"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Congruency/</id><title>Conspire - Congruency - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:14:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:14:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Congruency/" title="Conspire - Congruency - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Listen, forgive, hear and act, live Listen, forgive, hear and act, live, survive this sin, reconcile within, and most of all love again Listen, forgive, hear and act, live, survive this sin, reconcile within, and love again A complicated word to fit a complicated world Over complicated hurt and overcompensated terms Into lonely supervision, into hearses and abuse Into sitting with the guilt, and to feeling like no use I can't sleep tonight, there's something keeping me up, I'm ok, I'm secure, I'm protected by blood, but I'm offended by the fact that I thought it was mine I cower and wait, they seek as I hide I was trying to stitch us together to form something greater than me, don't say it was a lie It's so easy to say that you love something then throw it aside, don't throw me aside Sincerity, and openness, and understanding I've had enough to keep me alive Just first give yourself these things, and then join me again I wanna see you reappear, I wanna see my old friend Listen, forgive, hear and act, live, survive this sin, reconcile within and most of all love again A segregated world between the haves and destitution, and people make it worse, forming more division, they're just arbitrary lies behind tired, weary eyes that see not the words they hurl into the darkness that they hide Nothing's gonna make me turn my back on everything I've learned, on everything that's burned me, that's brought me here with you, there's a reason for us both, and what it is I don't know, but you're not alone You are not alone We're not alone]]></content><category term="Conspire" label="Conspire"/><category term="Congruency" label="Congruency"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/By_The_Sword/</id><title>Conspire - By The Sword - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:14:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:14:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/By_The_Sword/" title="Conspire - By The Sword - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I lament the fact that many of today's victimizers were yesterday's victims And I lament the tragedy that results from the clash of opposing violent extremisms Many in the West are too filled with fear and rage that they are unable to see that they themselves are just as radical and extreme as those they call terrorists Each side believes that its own violence is redemptive, but rages against the violence of the other side as senseless and unjust Each side thinks its anger is righteous and is blessed by a divine authority, and each side conceives of its opponents as originating from the realm of absolute evil, and so they see any compromise and reconciliation as immoral The only goal is total elimination of the other side Each side conceives of the conflict in stark extremes, with all goodness on one side and absolute evil on the other To mourn over the deaths of your opponents thus appears nonsensical and morally abhorrent Why would anyone care about the death of someone who represents absolute evil and injustice Both sides deceive themselves by thinking that their war and their violence will usher in an era of peace]]></content><category term="Conspire" label="Conspire"/><category term="By The Sword" label="By The Sword"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Row_Feat_Ricky_Armellino/</id><title>Conspire - Row (Feat. Ricky Armellino) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:14:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:14:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Row_Feat_Ricky_Armellino/" title="Conspire - Row (Feat. Ricky Armellino) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The rights of the oppressed, the warfare overseas, the value of a life is never dwindling You can be so distracted by the lights and the noise, it could feel like your heart is somewhere in the void Know, I wanna feel I'm reevaluating, I'm not gonna lose everyone that I know I wanna feel like myself again, while you're still next to me Walk through the fog, through all of these wrongs Just say that you'll right them with me There's something about the way we behave that contradicts the things that we say, we say we believe, complacency We're going nowhere and there's a storm, It's bearing down to where we are I need you to row Tracing the lives in the places we've bombed I'm not doing it alone Facing the pain from different angles We're interconnected whether you like it or not I'm not doing it alone And if we don't pull one another forward, we stay where we are And if redemptive violence is a deadly sin, I couldn't even imagine what God thinks of preemptive violence And it's wrong to broadly classify others as enemies No rationalization solves this, and clinging to hatred only clouds it further These are commonplace ideas and I thought you were too exceptional for them We're going nowhere, and that's a storm bearing down to where we are I need you to row We're going nowhere, it's a lot of weight to bear, and I'm not doing it on my own I need you to row Looking over people succumbing to sickness I'm not doing it alone Marketing their own poison while consuming everyone else's Taking the time to consider the differences I'm not doing it alone It's a modern crusade for those who remain motionless Your defenses are ruining who you are]]></content><category term="Conspire" label="Conspire"/><category term="Row (Feat. Ricky Armellino)" label="Row (Feat. Ricky Armellino)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Thousand_Oaks/</id><title>Conspire - Thousand Oaks - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:14:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:14:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Thousand_Oaks/" title="Conspire - Thousand Oaks - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[These reasons, they aren't so deep <br>These seasons, they're changing, they're changing me <br>Cause truth be told, the money speaks <br>But this great divide is nothing that love can't breach <br><br>But what's it matter to me <br>Have I lost sight of a college degree <br>An abstract noun doesn't set me free <br>It only binds the bondage of war that apparently only I can see <br><br>Only I, only I, only I, only I can see <br>Only I, only I, only I, only I can see <br><br>The right say I'm wrong, I've got no clue <br>Everything I've been taught, I thought it points to you <br>But I steered myself around and around, and around, and around <br><br>We abuse your name <br>Just like a lover that can only feel their own pain, pain, pain <br>You get used to getting used <br>We abuse your name <br>We abuse your name <br><br>Yeah <br><br>The uniforms need stitches, the plane tickets need printed <br>The missiles, computer systems, the targets investigated <br>Tuition gets more expensive, the churches need more donations <br>The system is all inclusive, you're nothing if you escape it <br><br>Slip through the cracks to God knows where <br>God knows, God knows, God knows where <br>Slip through the cracks to God knows where <br>God knows, God knows, God knows where <br><br>So how's it come to be the church and the army got so intertwined <br>You praise us all for ending up face down in the dirt <br>And scorn us if we ask why <br><br>The right say I'm wrong, I've got no clue <br>Everything I've been taught, I thought it points to you <br>Now I don't even know who you are <br>But at least we have something in common <br>The military needed both of us to change who we are <br>In support of the occupation <br><br>We abuse your name <br>Just like a lover that can only feel their own pain, pain, pain <br>You get used to getting used <br>We abuse your name <br>We abuse your name <br><br>I got out, I got out, I got out <br>I got out while I could <br>I got out, I got out, I got out <br>I got out <br>I got out, I got out, I got out <br>I got out while I could <br>I got out, I got out, I got out <br>I got out]]></content><category term="Conspire" label="Conspire"/><category term="Thousand Oaks" label="Thousand Oaks"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Rescind_Feat_Garrett_Russell/</id><title>Conspire - Rescind (Feat. Garrett Russell) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:14:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:14:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/Rescind_Feat_Garrett_Russell/" title="Conspire - Rescind (Feat. Garrett Russell) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Scream loud the truth, no need to speak <br>When lies float about the air that we breathe, don't inhale <br>They're breaking you down, they're making you weak <br>Making you fear your own kindness like it's a sign that you're an enemy <br>'Cause who are you really fighting <br>If you can't even explain who they are to begin with <br>Or find comfort in that so many others feel like you <br>think like you, and talk like you, and reward you for it <br>I wonder if you've been had, you've been tricked <br>I wonder if I've been too <br>I wonder if we slowly find who we are through the words of <br>aristocratic tacticians who hold all the power <br>We can break the shackles of belief <br>If every day could be a new start <br>We can grow a newer set of wings <br>If every day could be a new start <br>We wouldn't have to feel like we've been chained to these ideals <br>You could be proud of growing out of the ground <br>You can't cling to anything with all that baggage <br>But you can put it down, leave it to rest <br>Reclaim your head <br>Small suicide, every time we change who we are <br>You can try to hide, but the abyss is never afar <br>Your heart keeps racing, but it keeps coming in last <br>'Cause you gave it all too soon, and to whom <br>'Cause to share a popular belief in a culture that <br>has the wealth to end hunger and famine <br>but chooses not to stop it is to share the same sickness and depravity <br>You weren't born to be a henchman for men who'd rather <br>see you dead than to share in their profits <br>'Cause who are you really fighting <br>Just yourself <br>When you can't trust your mind from firing blind <br>at the very first sight of a threat <br>Just yourself <br>Your heart didn't have to grow hard <br>It was better In the first place <br>I don't have to be a part and neither do you and neither do you <br>War is a family system line up your kids for target shooting politicians <br>In this rotten heaven I must implore <br>who made this love letter look like marching orders <br>Sacrifice your children to the new Babylon <br>'Cause we're all orphans and we're throwing <br>our children to the wolves of wealth <br>and our future to the highest bidder]]></content><category term="Conspire" label="Conspire"/><category term="Rescind (Feat. Garrett Russell)" label="Rescind (Feat. Garrett Russell)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/1971/</id><title>Conspire - 1971 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:14:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:14:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Conspire/1971/" title="Conspire - 1971 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[43 years is just enough time <br>To see it differently, to keep an open mind <br>43 years ago was just another time <br>There were other ways to think, it was just a different life <br><br>I came back to see if any minds got loose <br>I checked the rooms, I checked the halls, I checked apartments <br>I checked the tension of the beams in all the roofs <br>I checked the knot to see if it was still a noose <br>I hope the memory's alive and would still wait for me <br>But it hurts too much to hold it to the light <br>'Cause knowledge is a fire, the flames are burning higher <br>And liberty's not that bad if you just close your eyes <br>And liberty's not that bad if you just close your eyes <br><br>What you know doesn't have to burn you away <br>Everything you chose not to feel is gonna find you someday <br>Or could my ghost unlearn everything <br>Or could my ghost unlearn everything <br><br>Frail flames, unlearn everything <br>Frail flames, unlearn everything <br><br>But for my first footstep once again down this very road my friend, oh wouldn't I <br><br>A prophet waiting inside this house <br>Impatiently he keeps his bags all packed <br>Saying, I was never meant to stay here, just come back <br><br>Just paint the walls, repaint the walls, just paint the walls, repaint the walls, paint the walls, paint the walls, paint the walls <br>I was made brand new but that image wasn't you <br><br>Would you really put someone down, if you had the choice Would you really put, really put someone down there <br><br>Frail flames, unlearn everything <br>Frail flames, unlearn everything <br><br>But for my first footstep once again my friend, oh wouldn't I <br>Have never even been here altogether <br>Wouldn't that be such a problem for us both <br>We would've never shared a path <br><br>A prophet waiting inside this house <br>Impatiently he keeps his bags all packed <br>Saying, I was never meant to stay here, just come back <br>A prophet waiting inside this house <br>Impatiently he keeps his bags all packed <br>Saying, I was never meant to stay here, just come back <br><br>I came back to see if any minds got loose <br>I checked the rooms, I checked the halls, I checked apartments <br>I checked the tension of the beams in all the roofs <br>I checked the knot to see if it was still a noose <br>I hope the memory's alive and would still wait for me <br>But it hurts too much to hold it to the light <br>'Cause knowledge is a fire, the flames are burning higher <br>And liberty's not that bad if you just close your eyes <br><br>What you know doesn't have to burn you away <br>Everything you chose not to feel is gonna find you someday <br>Or could my ghost unlearn everything <br>Could my ghost unlearn everything]]></content><category term="Conspire" label="Conspire"/><category term="1971" label="1971"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Puggy/Soul/</id><title>Puggy - Soul - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:15:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:15:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Puggy/Soul/" title="Puggy - Soul - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As the day will come to shore <br>and wash me up at your front door <br>never knew you'd take me back <br><br>Now it seems if all to clear <br>funny how this works my dear <br>only dawn could bring me back <br><br>No, no, no <br>no, no, no <br>now's the time to understand <br>No, no, no <br>no, no, no <br>and now I see <br><br>How we could be so young <br>feeling like we're so strong <br>always believe <br>you always knew your heart's song <br>sang it 'til the break of dawn <br>'til we could see <br>No, no, no <br>no, no, no <br>and now I see <br>how we're headlong rushing <br>you made us something to be <br>you're what I need <br><br>Not a day <br>a month or year <br>without a lie, a trick I hear <br>never thought I'd make it back <br><br>No, no, no <br>no, no, no <br>now's the time to understand <br>No, no, no <br>no, no, no <br>and now I see <br><br>How we could be so young <br>feeling like we're so strong <br>always believe <br>you always knew your heart's song <br>sang it 'til the break of dawn <br>'til we could see <br>No, no, no <br>no, no, no <br>and now I see <br>how we're headlong rushing <br>you made us something to be <br>you're what I need <br>you're what I need <br>you're what I need <br><br>We're headlong rushing <br>to dawn <br>We're headlong rushing <br>to dawn <br>We're headlong rushing <br>to dawn <br>We're headlong rushing <br>to dawn <br><br>How we could be so young <br>feeling like we're so strong <br>always believe <br>you always knew your heart's song <br>sang it 'til the break of dawn <br>'til we could see <br><br>How we could be so young <br>feeling like we're so strong <br>always believe <br>you always knew your heart's song <br>sang it 'til the break of dawn <br>'til we could see <br>you're what I need]]></content><category term="Puggy" label="Puggy"/><category term="Soul" label="Soul"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Puggy/Change_The_Colours/</id><title>Puggy - Change The Colours - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:15:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:15:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Puggy/Change_The_Colours/" title="Puggy - Change The Colours - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Show me through you <br>a thousand ways to Heaven <br>none look the same <br><br>hear me tell you <br>ev'ry breath a whisper <br>with something to say <br><br>it's the shades that make a second last a lifetime <br>and take us away <br>you know <br><br>I'll change the colours <br>I'll change the colours <br>I'll change the colours of your mind <br>I'll change the colours <br>one for another <br>I'll change the colours of your mind <br><br>please <br>close your eyes and realise we're more than we seem <br>and don't you hold on <br>'cause gravity don't mind if we'd only let go <br><br>I'll change the colours <br>I'll change the colours <br>I'll change the colours of your mind <br>I'll change the colours <br>from one to another <br>I'll change the colours of your mind <br><br>oh you know it's never going to be the right time <br>so let each second light up brighter than a lifetime <br><br>one for another <br>I'll change the colours of your mind <br>I'll change, I'll change, I'll change for another <br>I'll change the colours <br>I'll change the colours of your mind]]></content><category term="Puggy" label="Puggy"/><category term="Change The Colours" label="Change The Colours"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cobi/Dont_You_Cry_For_Me_Acoustic/</id><title>Cobi - Don`t You Cry For Me (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:16:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:16:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cobi/Dont_You_Cry_For_Me_Acoustic/" title="Cobi - Don`t You Cry For Me (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hope got my hands tied around my back <br>And time put a rope around my head <br>And hung from the rafters of my fear <br>Dark in the eyes <br>Try and face the world, I can't bear to <br>My knees hit the ground and my hands start shaking <br>Old feelings from new faces <br>A rope on the floor and a poor man hanging <br><br>Please help me chop this tree down <br>Hold me from underneath and they never want <br>Words never once cut me down <br>Oh, don't you cry for me someday I'm where they never want <br><br>I've seen an ocean run away <br>I'm torn from the truth that holds my soul <br>I'm down in the grave where I belong <br>Oh, what a ride <br>Identified my devil <br>Wings to the sky on the run from trouble <br>With my own hands, no shovel <br>I dug through the ground, now I'm hanging above saying <br><br>Please help me chop this tree down <br>Hold me from underneath and they never want <br>Words never once cut me down <br>Oh, don't you cry for me <br><br>Down by the grave that the law man laid <br>When the gravel got paved, finally I'm saved <br>Down by the grave that the law man laid <br>When the gravel got paved, finally I'm saved <br>When the sun went down <br>Down by the grave that the law man laid <br>When the gravel got paved, finally I'm saved <br>It set the sky on fire <br>Down by the grave that the law man laid <br>When the gravel got paved, finally I'm saved <br>I saw an angel fly <br>Down by the grave that the law man laid <br>When the gravel got paved, finally I'm saved <br>I never felt so high <br>Down by the grave that the law man laid <br>When the gravel got paved, finally I'm saved <br><br>Please help me chop this tree down <br>Hold me from underneath and they never want <br>Words never once cut me down <br>Oh, don't you cry for me <br><br>Oh, don't you cry for me <br>Oh, don't you cry for me]]></content><category term="Cobi" label="Cobi"/><category term="Don`t You Cry For Me (Acoustic)" label="Don`t You Cry For Me (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Hey_Hey_My_My_Into_The_Black/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Hey Hey, My My (Into The Black) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:18:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:18:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Hey_Hey_My_My_Into_The_Black/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Hey Hey, My My (Into The Black) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey hey, my my <br>Rock and roll can never die <br>There's more to the picture <br>Than meets the eye <br>Hey hey, my my <br><br>Out of the blue <br>and into the black <br>You pay for this <br>but they give you that <br>And once you're gone <br>you can't come back <br>When you're out of the blue <br>and into the black <br><br>The king is gone <br>but he's not forgotten <br>Is this the story <br>of Johnny Rotten <br>It's better to burn out <br>'cause rust never sleeps <br>The king is gone <br>but he's not forgotten <br><br>Hey hey, my my <br>Rock and roll can never die <br>There's more to the picture <br>Than meets the eye]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Hey Hey, My My (Into The Black)" label="Hey Hey, My My (Into The Black)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Sedan_Delivery/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Sedan Delivery - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:18:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:18:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Sedan_Delivery/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Sedan Delivery - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Last night I was cool <br>at the pool hall <br>Held the table for eleven games <br>Nothing was easier <br>than the first seven <br>I beat a woman with varicose veins <br><br>She stopped to see <br>herself in the mirror <br>Fix her hair and hide heir veins <br>And she lost the game <br><br>Next day I went to the dentist <br>He pulled some teeth <br>and I lost some blood <br>We'd like to thank you <br>for the cards you sent us <br>My wives and I were all choked up <br><br>I recall how Caesar and Cleo <br>Made love in the Milky Way <br>They needed boats <br>and armies to get there <br>I know there's a better way <br><br>I saw the movie and I read the book <br>But when it happened to me <br>I sure was glad I had what it took <br>To get away <br><br>Gotta get away, gotta get away <br>Gotta get away, gotta get away <br><br>I'm making another delivery <br>Of chemicals and sacred roots <br>I'll hold what you have to give me <br>But I'll use what I have to use <br><br>The lasers are in the lab <br>The old man <br>is dressed in white clothes <br>Everybody says he's mad <br>No one knows <br>the things that he knows <br><br>No one knows, no one knows <br>No one knows, no one knows <br><br>I'm sleepin' in every hallway <br>I just can't accept the stares <br>I'm using too many covers <br>I'm warm now so I don't care <br><br>I'm thinkin' of no one in my mind <br>Sedan delivery <br>is a job I know I'll keep <br>It sure was hard to find <br><br>Hard to find hard to find <br>Hard to find hard to find]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Sedan Delivery" label="Sedan Delivery"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Welfare_Mothers/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Welfare Mothers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:18:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:18:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Welfare_Mothers/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Welfare Mothers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[People, pick up <br>on what I'm puttin' down now <br><br>Welfare mothers <br>make better lovers <br><br>Down at every <br>Laundromat in town now <br><br>Welfare mothers <br>make better lovers <br><br>While they're washin' <br>you can hear this sound now <br><br>Welfare mothers <br>make better lovers <br><br>Divorcee <br><br>Hard to believe <br>that love is free now <br><br>Welfare mothers <br>make better lovers <br><br>Out on the street <br>with the whole family now <br><br>Welfare mothers <br>make better lovers <br><br>Hard to believe <br>that love is free now <br><br>Welfare mothers <br>make better lovers <br><br>Divorcee <br><br>People, pick up <br>on what I'm puttin' down now <br><br>Welfare mothers <br>make better lovers <br><br>Down in every <br>Laundromat in town now <br><br>Welfare mothers <br>make better lovers <br><br>While they're washin' <br>you can hear this sound now <br><br>Welfare mothers <br>make better lovers <br><br>Divorcee]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Welfare Mothers" label="Welfare Mothers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Powderfinger/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Powderfinger - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:18:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:18:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Powderfinger/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Powderfinger - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look out, Mama <br>there's a white boat <br>comin' up the river <br>With a big red beacon <br>and a flag <br>and a man on the rail <br>I think you'd better call John <br>'Cause it don't <br>look like they're here <br>to deliver the mail <br>And it's less than a mile away <br>I hope they didn't come to stay <br>It's got numbers on the side <br>and a gun <br>And it's makin' big waves <br><br>Daddy's gone <br>my brother's out hunting <br>in the mountains <br>Big John's been drinking <br>since the river took Emmy Lou <br>So the powers that be <br>left me here <br>to do the thinkin' <br>And I just turned twenty two <br>I was wonderin' what to do <br>And the closer they got <br>The more those feelings grew <br><br>Daddy's rifle in my hand <br>felt reassurin' <br>He told me <br>Red means run, son <br>numbers add up to nothin' <br>But when the first shot <br>hit the docks I saw it comin' <br>Raised my rifle to my eye <br>Never stopped to wonder why <br>Then I saw black <br>And my face splashed in the sky <br><br>Shelter me from the powder <br>and the finger <br>Cover me with the thought <br>that pulled the trigger <br>Think of me <br>as one you'd never figured <br>Would fade away so young <br>With so much left undone <br>Remember me to my love <br>I know I'll miss her]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Powderfinger" label="Powderfinger"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Sail_Away/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Sail Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:18:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:18:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Sail_Away/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Sail Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I could live inside a tepee <br>I could die <br>in Penthouse thirty five <br>You could lose me on the freeway <br>But I would still <br>make it back alive <br><br>As long as we can sail away <br>As long as we can sail away <br>There'll be wind in the canyon <br>Moon on the rise <br>As long as we can sail away <br><br>See the losers in the best bars <br>Meet the winners in the dives <br>Where the people are the real stars <br>All the rest of their lives <br><br>As long as we can sail away <br>As long as we can sail away <br>There'll be wind in the canyon <br>Moon on the rise <br>As long as we can sail away <br><br>There's a road <br>stretched out between us <br>Like a ribbon on the high plain <br>Down from Phoenix through Salinas <br>'Round the bend and back again <br><br>As long as we can sail away <br>As long as we can sail away <br>There'll be wind in the canyon <br>Moon on the rise <br>As long as we can sail away <br>As long as we can sail away]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Sail Away" label="Sail Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Pocahontas/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Pocahontas - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:18:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:18:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Pocahontas/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Pocahontas - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Aurora borealis <br>The icy sky at night <br>Paddles cut the water <br>In a long and hurried flight <br>From the white man <br>to the fields of green <br>And the homeland <br>we've never seen <br><br>They killed us in our tepee <br>And they cut our women down <br>They might have left some babies <br>Cryin' on the ground <br>But the firesticks <br>and the wagons come <br>And the night falls <br>on the setting sun <br><br>They massacred the buffalo <br>Kitty corner from the bank <br>The taxis run across my feet <br>And my eyes have turned to blanks <br>In my little box <br>at the top of the stairs <br>With my Indian rug <br>and a pipe to share <br><br>I wish a was a trapper <br>I would give thousand pelts <br>To sleep with Pocahontas <br>And find out how she felt <br>In the mornin' <br>on the fields of green <br>In the homeland <br>we've never seen <br><br>And maybe Marlon Brando <br>Will be there by the fire <br>We'll sit and talk of Hollywood <br>And the good things there for hire <br>And the Astrodome <br>and the first tepee <br>Marlon Brando, Pocahontas and me <br>Marlon Brando, Pocahontas and me <br>Pocahontas]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Pocahontas" label="Pocahontas"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Ride_My_Llama/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Ride My Llama - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:18:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:18:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Ride_My_Llama/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Ride My Llama - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Remember the Alamo <br>When help was on the way <br>It's better here and now <br>I feel that good today <br><br>I'd like to take a walk <br>But not around the block <br>I really got some news <br>I met a man from Mars <br>He picked up all my guitars <br>And played me traveling songs <br><br>And when we got on ship <br>He brought out <br>something for the trip <br>And said, It's old but it's good <br>Like any other primitive would <br><br>I'm gonna ride my llama <br>From Peru to Texarkana <br>I wanna ride him good <br>In my old neighborhood <br>I'm gonna ride him good <br>In my old neighborhood <br><br>And when we got on ship <br>He brought out <br>something for the trip <br>And said, It's old but it's good <br>Like any other primitive would]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Ride My Llama" label="Ride My Llama"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Thrasher/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Thrasher - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:18:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:18:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/Thrasher/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - Thrasher - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They were hiding behind hay bales <br>They were planting <br>in the full moon <br>They had given all they had <br>for something new <br>But the light of day was on them <br>They could see the thrashers coming <br>And the water <br>shone like diamonds in the dew <br><br>And I was just getting up <br>hit the road before it's light <br>Trying to catch an hour on the sun <br>When I saw <br>those thrashers rolling by <br>Looking more than two lanes wide <br>I was feelin' <br>like my day had just begun <br><br>Where the eagle glides ascending <br>There's an ancient river bending <br>Down the timeless gorge of changes <br>Where sleeplessness awaits <br>I searched out my companions <br>Who were lost in crystal canyons <br>When the aimless blade of science <br>Slashed the pearly gates <br><br>It was then I knew I'd had enough <br>Burned my credit card for fuel <br>Headed out to where the pavement <br>turns to sand <br>With a one way ticket <br>to the land of truth <br>And my suitcase in my hand <br>How I lost my friends <br>I still don't understand <br><br>They had the best selection <br>They were poisoned with protection <br>There was nothing that they needed <br>Nothing left to find <br>They were lost in rock formations <br>Or became park bench mutations <br>On the sidewalks <br>and in the stations <br>They were waiting, waiting <br><br>So I got bored and left them there <br>They were just deadweight to me <br>Better down the road <br>without that load <br>Brings back the time <br>when I was eight or nine <br>I was watchin' my mama's TV <br>It was that great <br>Grand Canyon rescue episode <br><br>Where the vulture glides descending <br>On an asphalt highway bending <br>Thru libraries and museums <br>galaxies and stars <br>Down the windy halls of friendship <br>To the rose clipped by the bullwhip <br>The motel of lost companions <br>Waits with heated pool and bar <br><br>But me I'm not stopping there <br>Got my own row left to hoe <br>Just another line <br>in the field of time <br>When the thrasher comes <br>I'll be stuck in the sun <br>Like the dinosaurs in shrines <br>But I'll know the time has come <br>To give what's mine]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="Thrasher" label="Thrasher"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/My_My_Hey_Hey_Out_Of_The_Blue/</id><title>Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - My My, Hey Hey (Out Of The Blue) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:18:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:18:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse/My_My_Hey_Hey_Out_Of_The_Blue/" title="Neil_Young__Crazy_Horse - My My, Hey Hey (Out Of The Blue) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My my, hey hey <br>Rock and roll is here to stay <br>It's better to burn out <br>Than to fade away <br>My my, hey hey <br><br>Out of the blue <br>and into the black <br>They give you this <br>but you pay for that <br>And once you're gone <br>you can never come back <br>When you're out of the blue <br>and into the black <br><br>The king is gone <br>but he's not forgotten <br>This is the story <br>of a Johnny Rotten <br>It's better to burn out <br>than it is to rust <br>The king is gone <br>but he's not forgotten <br><br>Hey hey, my my <br>Rock and roll can never die <br>There's more to the picture <br>Than meets the eye <br>Hey hey, my my]]></content><category term="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse" label="Neil Young &amp; Crazy Horse"/><category term="My My, Hey Hey (Out Of The Blue)" label="My My, Hey Hey (Out Of The Blue)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/드레인_Drain/시시한_농담/</id><title>드레인_Drain - 시시한 농담 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:19:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:19:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%93%9C%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8_Drain/%EC%8B%9C%EC%8B%9C%ED%95%9C_%EB%86%8D%EB%8B%B4/" title="드레인_Drain - 시시한 농담 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지친 발걸음 <br>발 디딜 틈 없는 전철 <br>내 맘은 어딜 가나 편치 않고 <br>너의 목소리 <br>따뜻한 너의 목소리 <br>듣고 싶어 전화를 걸었어 <br>우울해진 날 좀 웃겨줄래 <br>시시한 농담일수록 좋아 <br>마음 없이 난 지쳐있어 <br>거짓 없는 얼굴을 보여줘 <br>똑같은 풍경 <br>지겨워 <br>너와 나는 점점 변해가도 <br>너의 목소리 <br>익숙한 너의 목소리 <br>듣고 싶어 전화를 걸었어 <br>외로워진 날 좀 웃겨줄래 <br>시시한 농담일수록 좋아 <br>마음 없이 난 지쳐있어 <br>거짓 없는 얼굴을 보여줘 <br>우울해진 날 좀 웃겨줄래 <br>시시한 농담일수록 좋아 <br>우울해진 날 좀 웃겨줄래 <br>시시한 농담일수록 좋아 <br>]]></content><category term="드레인 (Drain)" label="드레인 (Drain)"/><category term="시시한 농담" label="시시한 농담"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/민희/바람같은_인생/</id><title>민희 - 바람같은 인생 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:23:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:23:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%BC%ED%9D%AC/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D/" title="민희 - 바람같은 인생 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[인생을 살다보면 <br>웃는날도 우는날도 있겠지만 <br>이래저래 살아가는 우리네인생 <br>천년만년 살 수 없는 <br>한번뿐인 인생 <br>잠시 왔다 가는 세상 <br>둥글둥글 살아요 <br>바람같은 인생 구름같은 인생 <br>노래하고 웃으면서 살아요 <br>이리가도 짧은인생 <br>저리가도 짧은인생 <br>구름같은 인생 <br>인생을 살다보면 <br>웃는날도 우는날도 있겠지만 <br>이래저래 살아가는 우리네인생 <br>천년만년 살 수 없는 <br>한번뿐인 인생 <br>잠시 왔다 가는 세상 <br>둥글둥글 살아요 <br>바람같은 인생 구름같은 인생 <br>오손도손 즐겁게 살아요 <br>이리가도 짧은인생 <br>저리가도 짧은인생 <br>구름같은 인생 바람같은 인생 <br>]]></content><category term="민희" label="민희"/><category term="바람같은 인생" label="바람같은 인생"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Il_Est_Temps_Quon_Maime_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>Amir - Il Est Temps Qu`on M`aime (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:26:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:26:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Il_Est_Temps_Quon_Maime_Acoustic_Ver/" title="Amir - Il Est Temps Qu`on M`aime (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Chaque jour, le chant du reveil <br>Chaque jour, sa sirene m'appelle <br>Chaque jour, je transperce la ville <br>Aux rayons du soleil <br><br>Comme une fourmi dans la foule <br>J'ai le tournis mais je roule <br>Chaque jour, je traverse ma vie <br>Comme un homme qui se saoule <br><br>Le coeur en dilettante <br>On me dit qu'il est temps de gagner <br>Des trophees, des amantes <br>Il est l'heure d'avancer sans penser <br><br>On me dit qu'il est temps de chercher <br>Ou de me trouver, d'arreter de rever <br>De rentrer dans le rang, d'oublier <br><br>Non Oh oh oh <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br><br>Chaque soir, j'essuie vos regards <br>Chaque soir, je rentre plus tard <br>Et je transperce mes insomnies <br>a la lueur des phares <br><br>Chaque soir, je sens dans ma chair <br>La lame du temps qui opere <br>Chaque soir, je traverse mes nuits <br>En marin solitaire <br><br>L'aventure qui me tente <br>On me dit qu'il est temps de lacher <br>Mes folies, mes attentes <br>Et mes envies latentes sont gachees <br>Moi je sais qu'il est temps, de chercher, de me trouver <br>D'arreter de rester dans le rang et de vivre cache <br><br>Non Oh oh oh <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br><br>La vie defile en histoire ou en idees <br>Il est tant qu'on s'aime <br>Rien n'est facile, mais on a le coeur tranquille <br>Il est tant qu'on s'aime <br>Et meme si les gens disent que c'est inutile <br>Il est tant qu'on s'aime <br>Tant qu'on s'aime <br><br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br><br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="Il Est Temps Qu`on M`aime (Acoustic Ver.)" label="Il Est Temps Qu`on M`aime (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/On_Dirait_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>Amir - On Dirait (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:26:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:26:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/On_Dirait_Acoustic_Ver/" title="Amir - On Dirait (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tu me dis de regarder la vie en couleur <br>Quand il fait noir autour de moi <br>Sur le dos j'ai traine pas mal de douleur <br>Toi, tu m'portais a bout de bras <br><br>Nan, nan, nan, je n'ai pas toujours ete sur de moi <br>J'ai doute tellement de fois <br>Nan, nan, nan, je ne sais pas ce que je ferai sans toi <br>Oh yeah <br><br>On dirait qu'on a tous un ange <br>On dirait, on dirait bien que c'est toi <br>On dirait que dans ce monde etrange <br>On dirait que t'as toujours ete la <br><br>Tu me dis que mon reve est juste a cote <br>Que j'ai juste a tendre la main <br>Toute ma vie j'peux la passer a t'ecouter <br>La douceur est ton seul refrain <br><br>Nan, nan, nan, ce n'est pas toujours facile pour moi <br>J'ai prie tellement de fois <br>Nan, nan, nan, je ne sais pas ce que je ferais sans toi <br>Oh yeah <br><br>On dirait qu'on a tous un ange <br>On dirait, on dirait bien que c'est toi <br>On dirait que dans ce monde etrange <br>On dirait que t'as toujours ete la <br><br>Tout, tout tourne autour de toi <br>Toi, t'es la seul qui voit la beaute bien cache derriere les visages <br>Tout, tout tourne autour de toi <br>Toi, tu sais lire en moi promets moi de n'jamais tourner la page <br><br>On dirait qu'on a tous un ange <br>On dirait, on dirait bien que c'est toi <br>On dirait que dans ce monde etrange <br>On dirait que t'as toujours ete la <br><br>On dirait qu'on a tous un ange <br>On dirait, on dirait bien que c'est toi <br>On dirait que dans ce monde etrange <br>On dirait que t'as toujours ete la <br><br>On dirait]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="On Dirait (Acoustic Ver.)" label="On Dirait (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Jai_Cherche_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>Amir - J`ai Cherche (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Jai_Cherche_Acoustic_Ver/" title="Amir - J`ai Cherche (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You, you <br>J'ai cherche un sens a mon existence <br>J'y ai laisse mon innocence <br>J'ai fini le coeur sans defense <br><br>J'ai cherche l'amour et la reconnaissance <br>J'ai paye le prix du silence <br>Je me blesse et je recommence <br><br>Tu m'as comme donne l'envie d'etre moi <br>Donne un sens a mes pourquoi <br>Tu as tue la peur qui dormait la <br>Qui dormait la dans mes bras <br><br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br><br>J'ai cherche un sens, un point de repere <br>Partage en deux hemispheres <br>Comme une erreur de l'univers <br><br>J'ai jete tellement de bouteille a la mer <br>J'ai bu tant de liqueurs ameres <br>Que j'en ai les levres de pierre <br><br>Tu m'as comme donne l'envie d'etre moi <br>Donne un sens a mes pourquoi <br>Tu as tue la peur qui dormait la <br>Qui dormait la dans mes bras <br><br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br><br>Au gre de nos blessures <br>Et de nos desinvoltures <br>C'est quand on n'y croit plus du tout <br>Qu'on trouve un paradis perdu en nous <br>Oh, you, you, you, you <br><br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br>Like the melody of my song <br><br>Tu m'as comme donne l'envie d'etre moi <br>Donne un sens a mes pourquoi You <br>Tu as tue la peur qui dormait la <br>Qui dormait la dans mes bras <br><br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br><br>You]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="J`ai Cherche (Acoustic Ver.)" label="J`ai Cherche (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Il_Est_Temps_Quon_Maime/</id><title>Amir - Il Est Temps Qu`on M`aime - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Il_Est_Temps_Quon_Maime/" title="Amir - Il Est Temps Qu`on M`aime - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Chaque jour, le chant du reveil <br>Chaque jour, sa sirene m'appelle <br>Chaque jour, je transperce la ville <br>Aux rayons du soleil <br><br>Comme une fourmi dans la foule <br>J'ai le tournis mais je roule <br>Chaque jour, je traverse ma vie <br>Comme un homme qui se saoule <br><br>Le coeur en dilettante <br>On me dit qu'il est temps de gagner <br>Des trophees, des amantes <br>Il est l'heure d'avancer sans penser <br><br>On me dit qu'il est temps de chercher <br>Ou de me trouver, d'arreter de rever <br>De rentrer dans le rang, d'oublier <br><br>Non Oh oh oh <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br><br>Chaque soir, j'essuie vos regards <br>Chaque soir, je rentre plus tard <br>Et je transperce mes insomnies <br>a la lueur des phares <br><br>Chaque soir, je sens dans ma chair <br>La lame du temps qui opere <br>Chaque soir, je traverse mes nuits <br>En marin solitaire <br><br>L'aventure qui me tente <br>On me dit qu'il est temps de lacher <br>Mes folies, mes attentes <br>Et mes envies latentes sont gachees <br>Moi je sais qu'il est temps, de chercher, de me trouver <br>D'arreter de rester dans le rang et de vivre cache <br><br>Non Oh oh oh <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br><br>La vie defile en histoire ou en idees <br>Il est tant qu'on s'aime <br>Rien n'est facile, mais on a le coeur tranquille <br>Il est tant qu'on s'aime <br>Et meme si les gens disent que c'est inutile <br>Il est tant qu'on s'aime <br>Tant qu'on s'aime <br><br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br><br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime <br>Il est temps qu'on m'aime]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="Il Est Temps Qu`on M`aime" label="Il Est Temps Qu`on M`aime"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Broken_Heart_Feat_ABI/</id><title>Amir - Broken Heart (Feat. ABI) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Broken_Heart_Feat_ABI/" title="Amir - Broken Heart (Feat. ABI) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Not before the day you said goodbye <br>Did I even know that I could cry <br>And how I have cried <br>All those reckless games inside my mind <br>Leaving this tortured soul to find <br>Somewhere to hide <br><br>When I told you that I loved you <br>I believed you felt that way too <br><br>Maybe I fell head over heels <br>Maybe I just got it all wrong <br>Ooh, feeling hopeless, not what I dreamed of <br>Maybe if you knew how it feels <br>Maybe you'd be singing this song <br>Where does my broken heart belong <br><br>Days are long and nights are filled with fear <br>I'm falling apart cause you're not here <br>I'm losing control <br>All that's left of who I used to be <br>You've taken it all away from me <br>I gave you my soul <br><br>Maybe I fell head over heels <br>Maybe I just got it all wrong <br>Ooh, feeling hopeless, not what I dream of <br>Maybe if you knew how it feels <br>Maybe you'd be singing this song <br>Where does my broken heart belong <br><br>When I told you that I loved you <br>I believed you felt that way too <br>And I must find a new tomorrow <br>If I am to lose this sorrow <br><br>Maybe I fell head over heels <br>Maybe I just got it all wrong <br>Ooh, feeling hopeless, not what I dreamed of <br>Maybe if you knew how it feels <br>Maybe you'd be singing this song <br>Where does my broken heart belong <br><br>Maybe I fell head over heels <br>Maybe I just got it all wrong <br>Ooh, feeling hopeless, not what I dreamed of <br>Maybe if you knew how it feels <br>Maybe you'd be singing this song <br>Where does my broken heart belong <br><br>Maybe I fell head over heels <br>Maybe I just got it all wrong <br>Ooh, feeling hopeless, not what I dreamed of <br>Maybe if you knew how it feels <br>Maybe you'd be singing this song <br>Where does my broken heart belong]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="Broken Heart (Feat. ABI)" label="Broken Heart (Feat. ABI)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Oasis/</id><title>Amir - Oasis - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Oasis/" title="Amir - Oasis - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Comme un soleil incandescent <br>Ou comme un astre qu'on descend <br>Seule et sublime, je t'imagine <br><br>Danse, tu bouleverses tous mes sens <br>Toi ma divine evidence <br>Le jour decline et deja je te devine <br><br>Lentement, lentement <br>Comme pousse par un vent brulant <br>Jusqu'a toi j'ai navigue <br>Trop longtemps, trop longtemps, j'ai attendu cet instant <br>ca y est, je t'ai trouve <br><br>Comme un oasis <br>Dans le desert de mes desirs <br>Comme un oasis <br>La plus belle source de plaisir <br><br>C'est toi mon horizon, mon phare <br>Toi mon oasis <br><br>Comme deux saisons qui se melangent <br>En moi j'ai le diable et l'ange <br>Je te dessine, quand ma peau est orpheline <br><br>Transe d'un plaisir en abondance <br>Tu es l'amour par essence <br>Mon heroine et je m'incline <br><br>Lentement, lentement <br>Comme pousse par un vent brulant <br>Jusqu'a toi j'ai navigue <br>Trop longtemps, trop longtemps, j'ai attendu cet instant <br>ca y est, je t'ai trouve <br><br>Comme un oasis <br>Dans le desert de mes desirs <br>Comme un oasis <br>La plus belle source de plaisir <br><br>C'est toi mon horizon, mon phare <br>Toi mon oasis <br><br>Dans une mer de sable, toi l'insaisissable <br>Je vois ton visage, mais n'es tu qu'un mirage <br><br>Comme un oasis <br>Comme un oasis <br>Dans le desert de mes desirs <br>Comme un oasis <br>La plus belle source de plaisir <br><br>C'est toi mon horizon, mon phare <br>Toi mon oasis <br>Comme un oasis]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="Oasis" label="Oasis"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Lost/</id><title>Amir - Lost - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Lost/" title="Amir - Lost - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Je suis lost, je suis lost <br>On est dans l'ile des paradoxes <br>Et je me donne de toutes mes forces <br>Je suis lost <br><br>Si tu savais, si tu savais <br>Tout ce que j'aimerai te donner <br>Pour te faire rire, te faire rever <br>Si tu savais, si tu voyais <br>Ces choses que je suis pret a faire <br>Pour eclairer ton univers <br><br>Oui je me trompe si souvent <br>Je me trompe et je ne fais pas ce que tu attends <br>Mais qu'est ce que tu attends <br><br>Lost, je suis lost <br>On est dans l'ile des paradoxes <br>Et je me donne de toutes mes forces <br>Mais je suis lost, je suis lost <br>Je veux t'aimer grand, je veux t'aimer fort <br>On se rend fous, on se renforce <br>Je suis lost <br><br>Je cherche ici, je cherche encore <br>Les endroits ou tu veux aller <br>Les attentions, pour te combler <br><br>Je cherche ici, je cherche encore <br>Quelles sont les poudres et les colliers <br>Les quelques mots improvises <br><br>Mais je tombe tellement a cote <br>Je tombe de ne pas deviner tes etrangetes <br>Si belles etrangetes <br><br>Lost, je suis lost <br>On est dans l'ile des paradoxes <br>Et je me donne de toutes mes forces <br>Mais je suis lost, je suis lost <br>Je veux t'aimer grand, je veux t'aimer fort <br>On se rend fous, on se renforce <br><br>Et puis qu'importe <br>Et puis qu'importe <br>Toutes ces fois ou l'on se desarme <br><br>Et puis qu'importe <br>Et puis qu'importe <br>C'est peut etre ca qui fait le charme <br><br>Je suis lost, je suis lost <br><br>Lost, je suis lost <br>On est dans l'ile des paradoxes <br>Et je me donne de toutes mes forces <br>Mais je suis lost, je suis lost <br>Je veux t'aimer grand, je veux t'aimer fort <br>On se rend fous, on se renforce <br><br>Je suis lost, je suis lost]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="Lost" label="Lost"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Je_Reviendrai/</id><title>Amir - Je Reviendrai - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Je_Reviendrai/" title="Amir - Je Reviendrai - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Si mes reves sont ailleurs, je suis pret a m'en aller <br>Pour aller chercher ce destin qui me ressemble <br>Je n'ai jamais eu peur de changer, de voyager <br>Cents fois j'ai traverse des routes, des ponts qui tremblent <br><br>J'ai beau parcourir le monde <br>Tous mes chemins menent a toi <br>Il y a mille etoiles mais au dessus un seul ciel <br>J'ai beau parcourir le monde <br>Mais mon seul pays c'est toi <br>Meme loin de tes yeux je serai toujours fidele <br><br>Je reviendrai comme on plonge <br>Enfin dans le bain de la vie <br>Je te vois meme dans mes songes <br>Comme le jour cherche la nuit <br>Je trouverai enfin tes bras <br><br>Je suis alle si loin pour trouver la liberte <br>La ou ne vivent que le chagrin et le silence <br>Sans peur du lendemain, j'ai recu comme j'ai donne <br>J'ai perdu souvent, mais j'ai retente ma chance <br><br>J'ai beau parcourir le monde <br>Je ne vois qu'un seul visage <br>Il y a mille etoiles et pourtant je ne vois qu'elle <br><br>J'ai beau parcourir le monde <br>Elle est mon seul paysage <br>Une voix qui s'eleve et vient chanter l'essentiel <br><br>Je reviendrai comme on plonge <br>Enfin dans le bain de la vie <br>Je te vois meme dans mes songes <br>Comme le jour cherche la nuit <br>Je trouverai enfin tes bras <br><br>Je prendrais tous les tournants, tous les tourments <br>Pour te revenir <br>Et sans attendre mon tour, je prendrai tous les detours <br>Puisqu'il y a l'amour a batir <br><br>Je reviendrai comme on plonge <br>Enfin dans le bain de la vie <br>Je te vois meme dans mes songes <br>Comme le jour cherche la nuit <br>Je trouverai enfin tes bras <br><br>Je reviendrai comme on plonge <br>Enfin dans le bain de la vie <br>Je te vois meme dans mes songes <br>Comme le jour cherche la nuit <br><br>Comme le jour cherche la nuit <br>Je trouverai enfin tes bras]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="Je Reviendrai" label="Je Reviendrai"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Tres_Haut/</id><title>Amir - Tres Haut - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Tres_Haut/" title="Amir - Tres Haut - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bien sur, bien sur, on avance a la dur <br>On se trompe parfois <br>On revient sur nos pas <br>On va jusqu'au sommet <br>On se pense arrive <br>On se penche un peu trop <br>Et on tombe, tombe de haut <br><br>Tout le long de la chute on prend des uppercuts <br>Des coups bas et des bleus, on se defend comme on peut <br>Quitte a frapper le sol presque dans le linceul <br>On se releve et on s'en sort seul <br><br>Viser tres haut, tres haut <br>Il y a une place pour nos idees <br>Et nos ideaux deaux <br>Laisser une trace <br>Recommencer <br><br>Je suis pres a perdre le sens <br>Esquiver l'evidence pour enfin trouver ma voie <br>Viser tres haut, tres haut <br>Viser tres haut <br>Viser tres haut <br><br>Bien sur, bien sur, on avance, on rature <br>Entre cris et murmures <br>On ecrit nos blessures <br>Et la chaleur nous manque <br>Et le bonheur se planque <br>Comment trouver les mots <br>Quand on tombe, tombe de haut <br><br>Tout le long de la route, a l'amour on se shoot <br>Pour soigner la nevrose de nos coeurs qui explosent <br>La mort nous ensorcelle <br>L'amour est juste au seuil <br>On se releve et on s'en sort seul <br><br>Viser tres haut, tres haut <br>Il y a une place pour nos idees <br>Et nos ideaux deaux <br>Laisser une trace <br>Recommencer <br><br>Je suis pres a perdre le sens <br>Esquiver l'evidence pour enfin trouver ma voie <br>Viser tres haut, tres haut <br><br>On poursuivra cette course folle <br>Et jusqu'a s'egarer <br>etre seuls et se marrer <br>Bruler nos camisoles <br>Se fabriquer un destin plus grand <br>Pour tenir a deux dedans <br><br>Viser tres haut, tres haut <br>Il y a une place pour nos idees <br>Et nos ideaux deaux <br>Laisser une trace <br>Recommencer <br><br>Je suis pres a perdre le sens <br>Esquiver l'evidence pour enfin trouver ma voie <br>Viser tres haut, tres haut <br>Viser tres haut <br>Viser tres haut]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="Tres Haut" label="Tres Haut"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/I_Know/</id><title>Amir - I Know - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/I_Know/" title="Amir - I Know - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[L'euphorie des jours est passee par nous deja <br>On a fait le tour, on a franchi le delta <br>Y a t il un antidote au poison des details <br>Nos coeurs qui s'erodent <br>C'est le temps qui les entaille, entaille, entaille <br><br>Plus rien ne m'agite <br>Une etincelle, ou je m'eteins sans toi <br>Plus rien ne m'agite <br>Si ta peau hesite <br>Prends moi la flamme et je brule avec toi <br>Si ta peau hesite <br><br>And I know <br>Your fire took away my pride <br>And it's burning down inside <br><br>And I know <br>That only you can turn the tide <br>Lift me up and make me glide <br><br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Viens le temps des anges <br>Qui nous ramene en arriere <br><br>On goute aux mensonges <br>La verite est amere, amere, amere <br><br>Juste a la limite <br>Entre la queue et les envies d'encore <br>Juste a la limite <br><br>Si ta peau me quitte <br>Que reste t il pour faire chanter mon corps <br>Si ta peau me quitte <br><br>And I know <br>Your fire took away my pride <br>And it's burning down inside <br>And I know <br>That only you can turn the tide <br>Lift me up and make me glide <br>x3 <br><br>And I know <br>That only you can turn the tide <br>Lift me up and make me glide <br><br>That only you can turn the tide <br>Lift me up and make me glide]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="I Know" label="I Know"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/A_Ta_Maniere/</id><title>Amir - A Ta Maniere - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/A_Ta_Maniere/" title="Amir - A Ta Maniere - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[S'il faut tout se dire <br>J'ai manque d'un sourire quelques fois <br>Je t'ai vu partir <br>L'enfant que j'etais ne savait pas <br>Il faut du temps pour se comprendre <br>J'ai tellement d'amour a te rendre <br>Que cent vies ne suffiraient pas <br>Je veux t'aimer dans cette vie la <br><br>Sans un mot, tu m'apprends a etre moi <br>Tu reprends mes defauts, mes mauvais choix <br>De moi tu es fier, a ta maniere <br><br>Tu me prends sous ton aile, pas dans tes bras <br>Tu ne me dit pas je t'aime, mais je le vois <br>Je te venere, comme un fils admire son pere <br><br>J'ai peur de l'ecrire <br>Ton silence m'a assourdi parfois <br>Le meilleur, le pire <br>J'ai tout fait pour qu'enfin tu me vois <br><br>J'ai passe des jours et des heures <br>a la fenetre de ton coeur <br>Je sais que tu me regardais <br>Mieux que personne tu me connais <br><br>Sans un mot tu m'apprends a etre moi <br>Tu reprends mes defauts, mes mauvais choix <br>De moi tu es fier, a ta maniere <br><br>Tu me prends sous ton aile, pas dans tes bras <br>Tu ne me dit pas je t'aime mais je le vois <br>Je te venere, comme un fils admire son pere <br>Comme un fils admire son pere <br><br>C'est juste la declaration d'un petit garcon <br>Qui en veut pas lacher ta main <br>Qui a encore tant de chemin avant d'etre aussi fort que toi <br>Papa <br><br>Sans un mot tu m'apprends a etre moi <br>Tu reprends mes defauts mes mauvais choix <br>De moi tu es fier, a ta maniere <br><br>Tu me prends sous ton aile, pas dans tes bras <br>Tu ne me dit pas je t'aime mais je le vois <br>Je te venere, comme un fils admire son pere <br>Comme un fils admire son pere]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="A Ta Maniere" label="A Ta Maniere"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Ma_Vie_Ma_Ville_Mon_Monde/</id><title>Amir - Ma Vie, Ma Ville, Mon Monde - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Ma_Vie_Ma_Ville_Mon_Monde/" title="Amir - Ma Vie, Ma Ville, Mon Monde - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On se rencontrera <br>Ma vie, ma ville, mon monde etait bien trop petit pour moi <br>Parler, crier, partir ou bien se sentir a l'etroit <br>Mes amis ne m'en veuillez pas <br>Mais quand viendra l'ombre du jour <br>Je prendrai le chemin qui mene a l'amour, a l'amour de soi <br><br>Comme elle est comme toi <br>Comme elle est comme toi <br>Je suis ne quelque part <br>Comme elle est comme toi <br>Comme elle est comme toi <br>Je cherche dans le noir <br><br>Et j'espere <br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>Au detour d'un hasard, si on va jusque la <br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>On se rencontrera <br>Je serai sous ta fenetre et je tomberai sur toi <br><br>On se rencontrera <br><br>Ma vie, ma ville, mon monde, tout ca ne me suffisait pas <br>Longtemps le manque se planque <br>Surgit quand le coeur a trop froid <br>Un soleil noir me regardait <br>Ses yeux brulant semblaient me dire <br>Je me leve avec toi si tu veux partir d'ou on ne revient pas <br><br>Comme elle est comme toi <br>Comme elle est comme toi <br>Je suis nee quelque part <br>Comme elle est comme toi <br>Comme elle est comme toi <br>Je cherche sans te voir <br><br>Et j'espere <br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>Au detour d'un hasard si on va jusque la <br><br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>Je serai sous ta fenetre et je tomberai sur toi <br><br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>On se rencontrera <br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>Au detour d'un hasard si on va jusque la <br><br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>Qu'on se rencontrera <br>Je serai sous ta fenetre et je tomberai pour toi <br><br>Ma vie, ma ville, mon monde, etait bien trop petit pour moi <br>Je partirai demain, peut etre <br>En attendant, je reste la]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="Ma Vie, Ma Ville, Mon Monde" label="Ma Vie, Ma Ville, Mon Monde"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Au_Coeur_De_Moi/</id><title>Amir - Au Coeur De Moi - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Au_Coeur_De_Moi/" title="Amir - Au Coeur De Moi - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Un jour, je suis predateur <br>Un jour, je suis la proie <br>Un jour, j'ai chaud au coeur <br>Un jour, j'ai tellement froid <br>Parfois je ne vois plus clair <br>Le miroir me deforme <br>Je me leve sans lumiere <br>Et mes reves s'endorment <br><br>Plonge au coeur de moi <br>Au fond de mes abimes, de mes abimes <br>Dis moi ce que tu vois <br>Plonge au coeur de moi <br>Et quand tout me decime, tout me decime <br>Je veux renaitre en toi <br><br>Viens, ecris sur ma peau les mots que je n'ose pas <br>Meme au bord du KO, si je tombe retiens moi <br><br>Un jour, je suis l'acteur qui fait son cinema <br>Un jour, c'est le destin qui tient la camera <br>Mon esprit solitaire se perd au fond des bois <br>Je vois le monde a l'envers, mes reves sont a l'etroit <br><br>Plonge au coeur de moi <br>Au fond de mes racines, de mes racines <br>Ou personne ne va <br>Plonge au coeur de moi <br>Le temps nous laisse en ruine, nous laisse en ruine <br>Je veux renaitre en toi <br><br>Viens, ecris sur ma peau les mots que je n'ose pas <br>Meme au bord du KO si je tombe retiens moi <br><br>Et j'entends ton echo, ohohohooo <br>C'est la voix d'un jour nouveau <br>Le plus beau des flambeaux <br><br>Viens, ecris sur ma peau les mots que je n'ose pas <br>Meme au bord du KO si je tombe retiens moi <br><br>Viens, ecris sur ma peau les mots que je n'ose pas <br>Meme au bord du KO si je tombe retiens moi]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="Au Coeur De Moi" label="Au Coeur De Moi"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/On_Dirait/</id><title>Amir - On Dirait - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/On_Dirait/" title="Amir - On Dirait - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tu me dis de regarder la vie en couleur <br>Quand il fait noir autour de moi <br>Sur le dos j'ai traine pas mal de douleur <br>Toi, tu m'portais a bout de bras <br><br>Nan, nan, nan, je n'ai pas toujours ete sur de moi <br>J'ai doute tellement de fois <br>Nan, nan, nan, je ne sais pas ce que je ferai sans toi <br>Oh yeah <br><br>On dirait qu'on a tous un ange <br>On dirait, on dirait bien que c'est toi <br>On dirait que dans ce monde etrange <br>On dirait que t'as toujours ete la <br><br>Tu me dis que mon reve est juste a cote <br>Que j'ai juste a tendre la main <br>Toute ma vie j'peux la passer a t'ecouter <br>La douceur est ton seul refrain <br><br>Nan, nan, nan, ce n'est pas toujours facile pour moi <br>J'ai prie tellement de fois <br>Nan, nan, nan, je ne sais pas ce que je ferais sans toi <br>Oh yeah <br><br>On dirait qu'on a tous un ange <br>On dirait, on dirait bien que c'est toi <br>On dirait que dans ce monde etrange <br>On dirait que t'as toujours ete la <br><br>Tout, tout tourne autour de toi <br>Toi, t'es la seul qui voit la beaute bien cache derriere les visages <br>Tout, tout tourne autour de toi <br>Toi, tu sais lire en moi promets moi de n'jamais tourner la page <br><br>On dirait qu'on a tous un ange <br>On dirait, on dirait bien que c'est toi <br>On dirait que dans ce monde etrange <br>On dirait que t'as toujours ete la <br><br>On dirait qu'on a tous un ange <br>On dirait, on dirait bien que c'est toi <br>On dirait que dans ce monde etrange <br>On dirait que t'as toujours ete la <br><br>On dirait]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="On Dirait" label="On Dirait"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Jai_Cherche/</id><title>Amir - J`ai Cherche - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:27:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:27:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Amir/Jai_Cherche/" title="Amir - J`ai Cherche - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You, you <br>J'ai cherche un sens a mon existence <br>J'y ai laisse mon innocence <br>J'ai fini le coeur sans defense <br><br>J'ai cherche l'amour et la reconnaissance <br>J'ai paye le prix du silence <br>Je me blesse et je recommence <br><br>Tu m'as comme donne l'envie d'etre moi <br>Donne un sens a mes pourquoi <br>Tu as tue la peur qui dormait la <br>Qui dormait la dans mes bras <br><br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br><br>J'ai cherche un sens, un point de repere <br>Partage en deux hemispheres <br>Comme une erreur de l'univers <br><br>J'ai jete tellement de bouteille a la mer <br>J'ai bu tant de liqueurs ameres <br>Que j'en ai les levres de pierre <br><br>Tu m'as comme donne l'envie d'etre moi <br>Donne un sens a mes pourquoi <br>Tu as tue la peur qui dormait la <br>Qui dormait la dans mes bras <br><br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br><br>Au gre de nos blessures <br>Et de nos desinvoltures <br>C'est quand on n'y croit plus du tout <br>Qu'on trouve un paradis perdu en nous <br>Oh, you, you, you, you <br><br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br>Like the melody of my song <br><br>Tu m'as comme donne l'envie d'etre moi <br>Donne un sens a mes pourquoi You <br>Tu as tue la peur qui dormait la <br>Qui dormait la dans mes bras <br><br>You <br>You're the one that's making me strong <br>I'll be looking, looking, looking for you <br>Like the melody of my song <br><br>You]]></content><category term="Amir" label="Amir"/><category term="J`ai Cherche" label="J`ai Cherche"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roxette/From_A_Distance_SingSing_Ver/</id><title>Roxette - From A Distance (SingSing Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:28:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:28:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roxette/From_A_Distance_SingSing_Ver/" title="Roxette - From A Distance (SingSing Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Even if you spend time <br>I'm hard to find, in line <br>No tears for me <br>No hint of sadness inside <br>Though I'm angry, lonely <br>Got no life to live <br>And I'm hungry, thirsty <br>For all love can give <br><br>But I, won't show you any sign <br>Everything looks fine <br>From a distance <br><br>I wish I could close <br>And clear my eyes and mind <br>I'm running blind <br>Into the wilderness tonight <br>And it's scary, lonely <br>It's no way to live <br>And I'm hungry, thirsty <br>For all love can give <br><br>But I, won't show you any sign <br>Everything looks fine <br>From a distance <br><br>No I, I won't reveal any sign <br>Everything looks perfectly fine <br>From a distance <br><br>Oh, from a distance <br>Oh, from a distance <br>From a distance <br>From a distance <br>From a distance]]></content><category term="Roxette" label="Roxette"/><category term="From A Distance (SingSing Ver.)" label="From A Distance (SingSing Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roxette/Why_Dont_You_Bring_Me_Flowers_/</id><title>Roxette - Why Don`t You Bring Me Flowers? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:28:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:28:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roxette/Why_Dont_You_Bring_Me_Flowers_/" title="Roxette - Why Don`t You Bring Me Flowers? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me why don't you bring me flowers <br>Tell me why don't you notice me <br>Another stranger on a train, a tip rock in the rain <br>In the rain, in the cold, cold rain <br><br>I will throw the past on the fire <br>I will sing you to sleep when you're tired <br>When the summer's turning small <br>I'll buy you a sweater for the fall <br>Warm and soft like the moonlight <br><br>But the now we part into reveal <br>The truth when we gathered living soul <br>Teach me how to breathe <br><br>Tell me why don't you bring me flowers <br>Tell me why don't you notice me <br>Another stranger on a train, a tip rock in the rain <br>In the rain, in the cold, cold rain <br><br>When the summer's turning small <br>Buy you a sweater for the fall <br>Warm and soft like the moonlight]]></content><category term="Roxette" label="Roxette"/><category term="Why Don`t You Bring Me Flowers?" label="Why Don`t You Bring Me Flowers?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adventure_Club/Fade_Feat_Zak_Waters/</id><title>Adventure_Club - Fade (Feat. Zak Waters) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:28:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:28:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adventure_Club/Fade_Feat_Zak_Waters/" title="Adventure_Club - Fade (Feat. Zak Waters) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I-I won't, I won't <br>I-I won't I won't let you fade away <br>I-I won't, I won't <br>I-I won't let you fade away <br>I-I-I-I won't <br><br>I-I won't I won't let you fade away <br>I-I won't, I won't <br>I-I won't I won't let you fade away <br><br>I won't let you <br>I won't let you fade away <br><br>I won't let, I won't let <br>I won't let you fade away <br><br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br><br>I won't let you <br><br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I won't let you <br><br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>I-I-I-I won't <br>Fade away]]></content><category term="Adventure Club" label="Adventure Club"/><category term="Fade (Feat. Zak Waters)" label="Fade (Feat. Zak Waters)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adventure_Club/Firestorm_Feat_Sara_Diamond/</id><title>Adventure_Club - Firestorm (Feat. Sara Diamond) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:29:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:29:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adventure_Club/Firestorm_Feat_Sara_Diamond/" title="Adventure_Club - Firestorm (Feat. Sara Diamond) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heard all the stories 'bout this life <br>None of 'em for me, not that type <br><br>I wanna run with the wolves in the wild <br>We can go and we'll race right through the night <br>There's no fear in my eyes, just the will to survive <br>No, we'll never stop the fight <br><br>Give me a dream and I'll chase it <br>Lend me your heart and I'll break it <br>Show me the world and I'll take it <br>Baby, I won't quit 'cause I'm a firestorm <br>I'm a firestorm, I'm a firestorm <br>Show me the world and I'll take it <br>Baby, I won't quit 'cause I'm a firestorm <br><br>See all the glory, feel the call <br>Nothing can stop me, I need it all <br><br>I wanna run with the wolves in the wild <br>We can go and we'll race right through the night <br>There's no fear in my eyes, just the will to survive <br>No, we'll never stop the fight <br><br>Give me a dream and I'll chase it <br>Lend me your heart and I'll break it <br>Show me the world and I'll take it <br>Baby, I won't quit 'cause I'm a firestorm <br>I'm a firestorm, I'm a firestorm <br>Show me the world and I'll take it <br>Baby, I won't quit 'cause I'm a firestorm <br><br>I'm a firestorm, I'm a firestorm <br>I'm a firestorm, I'm a firestorm <br>I'm a firestorm, I'm a firestorm <br>I'm a firestorm, I'm a firestorm]]></content><category term="Adventure Club" label="Adventure Club"/><category term="Firestorm (Feat. Sara Diamond)" label="Firestorm (Feat. Sara Diamond)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/일레븐/Take_Me_Out/</id><title>일레븐 - Take Me Out - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:29:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:29:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%BC%EB%A0%88%EB%B8%90/Take_Me_Out/" title="일레븐 - Take Me Out - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[따뜻한 햇살 속에 <br>세상 가득 행복한 <br>따뜻한 햇살 속에 <br>세상 가득 행복한 <br>What I say <br>Take me out take me out <br>What I say <br>Take me out take me out <br>What I say <br>Take me out take me out <br>Suck <br>하루에도 몇번씩이나 너의 모습 <br>지워가지만 <br>하루에도 몇번씩이나 <br>비가 내려와 <br>What I say <br>Take me out take me out <br>What I say <br>Take me out take me out <br>What I say <br>Take me out take me out <br>Suck <br>하루에도 몇번씩이나 너의 모습 <br>지워가지만 <br>하루에도 몇번씩이나 <br>비가 내려와 <br>하루에도 몇번씩이나 너의 모습 <br>지워가지만 <br>하루종일 마음속에서 <br>비가 내려와 <br>하루에도 몇번씩이나 너의 모습 <br>지워가지만 <br>하루에도 몇번씩이나 <br>비가 내려와 <br>하루에도 몇번씩이나 너의 모습 <br>지워가지만 비가 내려와 <br>]]></content><category term="일레븐" label="일레븐"/><category term="Take Me Out" label="Take Me Out"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adventure_Club/Limitless_Feat_Delaney_Jane/</id><title>Adventure_Club - Limitless (Feat. Delaney Jane) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:29:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:29:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Adventure_Club/Limitless_Feat_Delaney_Jane/" title="Adventure_Club - Limitless (Feat. Delaney Jane) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My innocence <br>How it always seem to get lost <br>In violence <br><br>We always seem to get caught <br>It's no coincidence <br>That we're running from the past <br>Forgiveness wasn't something that we have <br><br>Limitless <br>We're living limitless <br>I refuse to just exist <br>I rather shoot and miss <br>So I'mma raise my fist <br>And live it limitless <br>Limitless <br><br>Limitless <br>I refuse to just exist <br>I rather shoot and miss <br>So I'mma raise my fist <br>And live it limitless <br>Limitless <br><br>Limitless <br>Limitless <br>Limitless <br><br>Renegade <br>See the world through open eyes <br>We ricochet <br>Across the dark blue skies <br>While masquerade <br>Is for the ones who want to hide <br>I won't stay in the shadows all my life <br><br>Limitless <br>We're living limitless <br>I refuse to just exist <br>I rather shoot and miss <br>So I'mma raise my fist <br>And live it limitless <br>Limitless <br><br>Limitless <br>I refuse to just exist <br>I rather shoot and miss <br>So I'mma raise my fist <br>And live it limitless <br>Limitless <br>Limitless <br>Limitless <br>Limitless]]></content><category term="Adventure Club" label="Adventure Club"/><category term="Limitless (Feat. Delaney Jane)" label="Limitless (Feat. Delaney Jane)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hat_Boy/공허해/</id><title>Hat_Boy - 공허해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:29:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:29:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hat_Boy/%EA%B3%B5%ED%97%88%ED%95%B4/" title="Hat_Boy - 공허해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[옅은 립스틱 <br>연분홍 빛 볼터치 <br>뽀얀 목덜민 <br>오늘따라 더 빛나 <br>아무것도 모른단 얼굴로 <br>슬쩍슬쩍 스치는 손끝에 <br>내 머린 복잡해져 <br>목 탄다 딱 한잔만 <br>더 시켜볼까 <br>그러다 먼저 <br>취해버림 어쩌나 <br>밤새듣던 연애비법 <br>하나도 생각안난채 <br>차 끊길 시간만 <br>다가오는데 <br>오늘따라 왠지 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>조금만 같이 있어줘 <br>내속맘 어설퍼 <br>뻔하지만 오늘만 속아줘 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>조금만 같이 있어줘 <br>사실 나 많은거 <br>바라지 않아 <br>손만 잡아 주면돼 <br>멀쩡하던 손은 <br>왜 떨리는지 <br>조용하던 심장소린 <br>왜 커졌는지 <br>붉어진 볼 못 <br>마주치는 눈 <br>혹시 눈치챈건 아닐까 <br>내마음 복잡하게 <br>떨린다 딱 한잔만 <br>더 시켜볼까 <br>그러다 먼저 <br>취해버림 어쩌나 <br>바보같은 내모습에 <br>점점 어색해져가고 <br>차 끊길 시간만 <br>다가오는데 <br>오늘따라 왠지 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>조금만 같이 있어줘 <br>내속맘 어설퍼 <br>뻔하지만 오늘만 속아줘 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>조금만 같이 있어줘 <br>사실 나 많은거 <br>바라지 않아 <br>손만 잡아 주면돼 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>오늘밤 널 <br>같이 있고 싶어 <br>안아주고 싶어 <br>밤새 속삭여주고 싶어 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>오늘 공허해 공허해 오늘밤 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>오늘밤 날 맡기고 싶어 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>조금만 같이 있어줘 <br>내속맘 어설퍼 <br>뻔하지만 오늘만 속아줘 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>조금만 같이 있어줘 <br>사실 나 많은거 <br>바라지 않아 <br>손만 잡아 주면돼 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>오늘밤 같이 있고 싶어 <br>안아주고 싶어 <br>밤새 속삭여주고 싶어 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>오늘 공허해 공허해 오늘밤 <br>공허해 공허해 <br>오늘밤 날 맡기고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="Hat Boy" label="Hat Boy"/><category term="공허해" label="공허해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/No_One_Feat_Arie-Elle/</id><title>PEZ - No One (Feat. Arie-Elle) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:31:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:31:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/No_One_Feat_Arie-Elle/" title="PEZ - No One (Feat. Arie-Elle) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cause I am feelin' in a hole now <br>But they don't hear me when I call out <br>Down here <br>There is <br>No one <br><br>It's like you're in a daze, walking 'round, don't know where you are <br>So much pain to talk about, I don't know where to start <br>Life's become a burden, I'm always scared <br>It doesn't matter where I turn because it's always there <br> the worse it gets <br>Over time you'd think I'd learn from this, but I haven't <br>And I wish there was somone there to help me when it happens <br>But instead people tell me I can manage like I'm dealing <br>With the feeling that's inside they don't think I feel <br>Or just because it's in my mind they don't think it's real <br>The fear that's instilled, you don't think it kills <br>If I'm not careful pretty soon, yeah I think it will <br>It's been concealed for so long <br>Sometimes I really don't wanna go on, but I have to <br>I tell myself that other people are to blame <br>But it really doesn't matter what I say anyway <br>'Cause <br><br>'Cause I am feelin' in a hole now <br>But they don't hear me when I call out <br>Down here <br>There is <br>No one <br><br>I don't know why it got so hard for me to say what I feel <br>Or why I seem to fall apart instead of facing my fears <br>I'm just tryna be strong <br>Work through all this hurt and turn it into words that I can write in this song <br>The truth is I ain't written in a while <br>Come to think, it's been a minute since I smiled <br>And I know I should put some music on and write for the day <br>Instead I just put a movie on and try to escape <br>Afraid of a day in the future where I'm looking back <br>Wishin' I could have it all again, now what good is that <br>Mind dwelling over all the things I coulda had <br>All the things I shoulda done or all the things I shouldn't have <br>Man, spent my whole life living in a dream world <br>I'm just tryna find the strength to say this is me world <br>And if my only way to do it is through these words <br>Maybe they don't have to be perfect <br><br>In my head <br>My head, my head <br>My head, my head <br>My head, my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br>Yeah <br><br>'Cause I am figuring it all out <br>Now I'm feeling I call out <br>From here <br>I fear <br>No one <br>'Cause I am figurin' it all out in' it all out, in' it all out <br>Now I'm feeling I can call out I can call out <br>From here from here <br>I fear I fear <br>No one no one <br>No one, nobody, no <br><br>It's all just up in my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br><br>'Cause I am figuring it all out in' it all out, in' it all out <br>Now I'm feeling I can call out I can call out <br>From here from here <br>I fear I fear <br>No one no one <br>No one, nobody, no <br><br>It's all just up in my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br>Yeah <br>It's all just up in my head <br>It's all just up in my head <br>Yeah]]></content><category term="PEZ" label="PEZ"/><category term="No One (Feat. Arie-Elle)" label="No One (Feat. Arie-Elle)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Real_Life_Feat_Arie-Elle/</id><title>PEZ - Real Life (Feat. Arie-Elle) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:31:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:31:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Real_Life_Feat_Arie-Elle/" title="PEZ - Real Life (Feat. Arie-Elle) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Sometimes I wonder what it's all for <br>Do we really seek change or is it all talk Yeah <br>'Cause every time we try we seem to fall short <br>We gotta get it together 'cause we've been forewarned <br>In the belly of the beast, being slowly eaten up <br>We all got our eyes glued to our social media <br>Seeking validation and other people's admiration <br>But what we really need is celebration <br>Of life and elevation in mine <br>If something's making you unhappy why you wastin' your time <br>At times I ponder life and what I think it means <br>Often ends up with me lost within dream, is it me <br>Or does its mystery leave you feelin' incomplete <br>I guess we're all just tryna find some inner peace <br>You gotta love it all even though it's bittersweet <br>The highs, the lows, and everything that's in between <br><br>So it goes by <br>And no one knows why <br>Around we go <br>This merry go round <br><br>It's just real life <br>It's just real life <br>It's just real life <br>It's just real life <br><br>Yeah <br>It can be hard to decide where you stand <br>'Cause there's so many different ways to draw a line in the sand <br>These days, so instead of fighting the man <br>We're fighting each other to try and advance, see that's why they plan <br>To rule, it's always been divide and conquer <br>'Cause they know we can't unite if we fight amongst our Selves, so we're under a spell <br>That's got us all losing our mind, while we all <br>Try our best to be politically correct <br>Which really means living in a prison in our head <br>And fuss and fight over politicians we elect <br>Who never really make a difference in the end, but through it all <br>The sun shines, sometimes I wonder why <br>As I'm looking up at night underneath the southern sky <br>But such is life, and it'll be that way <br>Until we reach the other side, right <br><br>So it goes by <br>And no one knows why <br>Around we go <br>This merry go round <br><br>It's just real life <br>It's just real life So it goes by <br>It's just real life <br>It's just real life Yeah, around and 'round we go <br>It's just real life <br>It's just real life And it doesn't let up <br>It's just real life <br>It's just real life]]></content><category term="PEZ" label="PEZ"/><category term="Real Life (Feat. Arie-Elle)" label="Real Life (Feat. Arie-Elle)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Weekend_Feat_360/</id><title>PEZ - Weekend (Feat. 360) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:31:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:31:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Weekend_Feat_360/" title="PEZ - Weekend (Feat. 360) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We all live for the weekend <br>Just tryna get by <br>But losing track of time <br>And we never need a reason <br>To leave it all behind <br>There's only one thing on my mind <br><br>Man, you know I tried my luck at a few day jobs <br>And every single one I had I used to hate on <br>I swear to God, I'd wake up every morning with a fake cough <br>Hoping maybe I could get the day off <br>I knew the safe option was to stay on <br>Still I couldn't help but muck around till I got laid off <br>Rapping all day long tryna make songs <br>Thinking to myself 'I hope this hard work pays off' <br>So I told my friends I'm an emcee <br>And they were like PEZ, you're a deadbeat yeah <br>How're you gonna make the ends meet <br>Rent's steep, you won't even make it to the next week <br>And it seemed like <br>There was a pretty good chance they would be right <br>But I just kept holding onto my dream like Nah <br>I'm gonna get there in the end, but in the meantime <br><br>We all live for the weekend <br>Just tryna get by <br>But losing track of time <br>And we never need a reason <br>To leave it all behind <br>There's only one thing on my mind <br><br>Before rap I was different in a way <br>Tryna make a living as a chippy in the game <br>My boss figured out a minimum to pay <br>He was giving me a wage, I was literally a slave <br>When's this motherfucka giving me a raise <br>I can barely afford to put some dinner on my plate <br>Spent every day wishing it'd rain <br>'Cause everytime it rains you'd be finished for the day <br>PEZ told me to give the shit away <br>Fuck work, there's something bigger we can chase <br>Taught about belief and the difference it'd make <br>Little did he know I would quit within a day <br>And while at work I was dreaming dreaming <br>Always thinking 'bout the weekend weekend <br>I couldn't wait till the week ends <br>And it will end, but until then <br><br>We all live for the weekend <br>Just tryna get by <br>But losing track of time <br>And we never need a reason <br>To leave it all behind <br>There's only one thing on my mind <br><br>In the deep end <br>On the grind <br>'Nother weekend <br>Is on my mind <br>In the deep end <br>On the grind <br>'Nother weekend <br>Is on my mind <br><br>We all live for the weekend <br>Just tryna get by <br>But losing track of time <br>And we never need a reason <br>To leave it all behind <br>There's only one thing on my mind <br><br>In the deep end <br>On the grind <br>'Nother weekend <br>Is on my mind]]></content><category term="PEZ" label="PEZ"/><category term="Weekend (Feat. 360)" label="Weekend (Feat. 360)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Dont_Look_Down_Feat_Kota_Banks/</id><title>PEZ - Don`t Look Down (Feat. Kota Banks) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:31:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:31:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Dont_Look_Down_Feat_Kota_Banks/" title="PEZ - Don`t Look Down (Feat. Kota Banks) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br><br>Now back when I was younger, man <br>I never thought by this stage I'd become a dad <br>And I don't know if it's something I'm ready to handle <br>But I'll do my best to try and set an example <br>And stay true and stay P <br>'Cause I made you, but at the same time it's feeling like you made me <br>My little lady <br>Life's been a little sweeter lately <br>And I can already sense a bit of cheekiness at hand <br>The way you act up when we're not meeting your demands <br>We might have a little diva on our hands <br>So sorry to your teachers in advance <br>What can you do <br>Right now I've got such an awesome view <br>To watch you grow up, but before you do <br>You got so much to look forward to <br>I can't wait to see what life's got in store for you <br><br>I've been tryna carry on <br>Down this road I'm on <br>Just don't look down, don't look down <br>I'ma look up to you <br>And when the sun is gone <br>I still carry on <br>Just don't look down, I won't look down <br>I'm just looking up to you <br><br>And even in this big bad world <br>There's one or two things I learnt my love <br>When you're a kid you gotta brainstorm <br>Work out what it is you wanna aim for and make sure <br>You're believing it when you're young <br>'Cause when you're older it's easier said than done, trust me <br>Don't be in too much of a rush because <br>Everybody's gotta start it as a novice, but I promise you <br>Dreams come true <br>I know that when you hear that thought it seems untrue <br>See yourself as somebody, it'll become you <br>If I can be one then it means you can be one too <br>I know it's been a minute since we've been on route <br>Not sure where this journey's tryna lead us to <br>But I'm on for the ride, you're welcome to come along if you like <br>It doesn't matter if you got a problem with heights, nah <br><br>I've been tryna carry on <br>Down this road I'm on <br>Just don't look down, don't look down <br>I'ma look up to you <br>Oh, and when the sun is gone <br>I still carry on <br>Just don't look down, I won't look down <br>I'm just looking up to you <br><br>Let's go <br>It's cold outside <br>Feel a shiver through my bones <br>But I will never be alone <br>If I got you <br>Yeah, if I got you <br>So cold tonight <br>Throw sticks and stones <br>But I am on my way back home <br>'Cause I got you <br>Yeah, I got you <br><br>I've been tryna carry on <br>Down this road I'm on <br>Just don't look down, won't look down <br>I'ma look up to you <br>And when the sun is gone <br>I still carry on <br>Just don't look down, I won't look down <br>I'm just looking up to you <br>I've been tryna carry on <br>Down this road I'm on <br>Just don't look down, won't look down I won't look down <br>I'ma look up to you <br>And when the sun is gone <br>I still carry on I'm just looking up <br>Just don't look down, I won't look down <br>I'm just looking up, I'm just looking up <br>I'm just looking up to you]]></content><category term="PEZ" label="PEZ"/><category term="Don`t Look Down (Feat. Kota Banks)" label="Don`t Look Down (Feat. Kota Banks)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Whatever_It_Takes/</id><title>PEZ - Whatever It Takes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:31:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:31:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Whatever_It_Takes/" title="PEZ - Whatever It Takes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Man, last five years has been a weird ride <br>Through some real lows and some real highs <br>When I set sail it was clear skies <br>Then I realised something was missing <br>I started seeing the success that I dreamt of <br>It came in a trade off like ''Guess what <br>Apart from your best song, the rest of is slept on <br>So kept on tryna figure out where I went wrong <br>This ain't the reason I got in it for <br>Is all they're gonna see then I don't even want it anymore <br>Shit, a little voice said Come on Pez, I know that it's hard <br>At some point you're gonna have to let go of the past <br>Start moving on, just move beyond <br>This bullshit, if people doubt you then prove them wrong <br>Instead I seem to fall into this dark place <br>When you pass blame to deal with the hurt <br>And every single day I feel the feeling get worse <br>You can justify through the sets of respons <br>Ibility, this feeling of resentment <br>Relieves and being full of contempt can mislead <br>I had to let go, with that intend to proceed <br>And accept my problem isn't with them, it's with me <br>It took being at my wits end to concede <br>But now I've had some time to reflect and see <br>And after finally feeling that peace of mind <br>Now I think I need some time just to realign <br>Some peace and quiet <br>So I can free these demons eating at me and then try to release this shit I keep inside <br>But instead I have my back up <br>Cause the first one went well and I got pressure now to backup <br>I know when I feel uptight, I can unwind <br>Sometimes I wish I can go back to being unsigned <br>When I'd sit there in my room and I'd just write <br>Didn't give a fuck about the outcome <br>Now I can't think without one and when the doubt comes <br>It's something you can't outrun, I know, I've tried <br>So it's like I'm sitting here tryna find <br>That feeling I used to feel when I would write <br>I don't know what it was, I'm pretty sure it used to be joy <br>Cause it's something that I used to enjoy <br>Now I don't even really know if there's emotion <br>Because most of the time I just feel like I'm just going through the motions <br>I write cause I have to <br>Shit I know that that ain't right but I have to <br>And the thing is there's this image in my mind that I find I'm attached to <br>It's how the guy back in time, I'm like that's you <br>A reminder in the back of my mind <br>Of a high that was at that I'm trying to get back to <br>I never can]]></content><category term="PEZ" label="PEZ"/><category term="Whatever It Takes" label="Whatever It Takes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/I_Wish_I_Could_Stay/</id><title>PEZ - I Wish I Could Stay - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:31:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:31:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/I_Wish_I_Could_Stay/" title="PEZ - I Wish I Could Stay - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wish I could stay <br>I wish I could stay right here <br>You think performing would be fine right <br>Scares the shit out of me <br>I wish I could stay <br>I wish I could stay right here <br><br>'Kay, check it out <br><br>The hands of time tick away <br>As I sit there waiting to go <br>Standing by, anticipatin' <br>'Cause it's the day of a show <br>Yeah, and there's that buzz in the air <br>But amidst the excitement, inside I'm <br>Tryna control my stress <br>And I sit backstage and hold my breath <br>Up in my mind, up in my mind <br>I think I'm already heading home <br>And I've been tryin', and I've been tryin' <br>But I just can't seem to let it go <br>Yeah, I'm so nervous right now <br>Heart racing as they turn the lights down <br>It's like I feel insane <br>Because I can hear my name, and <br><br>I wish I could stay <br>I wish I could stay right here <br>I wish I could that's right <br>I wish I could stay <br>I wish I could stay right here <br><br>Okay, yeah <br><br>But you know that it's just a phase <br>And so that notion begins to fade <br>An' drift away the <br>Moment I hit the stage and hear <br>As a roar erupts from the crowd <br>And I just fall in love with that sound <br>Now I'm gone, up in the clouds <br>And I'm not sure when I'm coming back down <br>Then all my <br>Fears disappear <br>This stage is all mine <br>It's like I'm in a dream <br>And when their energy's up <br>I swear it is such an adrenaline rush yeah <br>This buzz is better than anything <br>That I could get from a drug <br><br>I wish I could stay <br>I wish I could stay right here <br>I wish I could uh huh <br>I wish I could stay <br>I wish I could stay right here yeah <br><br>Can somebody hear me <br>Can somebody hear me <br>Can somebody here me now <br>Oh oh oh oh <br>Can somebody hear me <br>Can somebody hear me <br>Can somebody here me now <br>Oh oh oh oh <br><br>Yeah, uh, uh <br><br>I wish I could stay <br>I wish I could stay right here <br>I wish I could that's right <br>I wish I could stay <br>I wish I could stay right here yeah <br>I wish I could stay <br>I wish I could stay right here uh huh <br>I wish I could whoo <br>I wish I could stay <br>I wish I could stay right here]]></content><category term="PEZ" label="PEZ"/><category term="I Wish I Could Stay" label="I Wish I Could Stay"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/They_Try_To_Tell_Me_Feat_360/</id><title>PEZ - They Try To Tell Me (Feat. 360) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:31:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:31:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/They_Try_To_Tell_Me_Feat_360/" title="PEZ - They Try To Tell Me (Feat. 360) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Forthwrizzy son, let's go <br><br>Ayo, I walk in the room like '60 is here <br>I keep on saying it till somebody gives me a beer <br>Yeah, a comfortable style, wonderful smile <br>You don't like me, you're stuck in denial <br>Yeah, I walk in the room like PEZ is in the room <br>Make the most of it people, I'll be exiting it soon <br>Ridiculous flow, bitch you should know <br>There isn't anybody better that's why everybody says it <br>Forthwrite It's PEZ homie, you know me <br>The dude walking the club in the fluro jeans <br>Yeah, don't even act like you don't know '6 <br>When you go sick that your throats go *retches* <br>Hearing rude folks boo us <br>That's like having 2Pac fans in the Ku Klux Klan <br>Yeah, it doesn't happen because you love rappin' <br>So much that even if you don't you still go nuts <br><br>They try to tell me what to say Wanna critique our songs <br>They try to tell me to write, but what do the people want <br>They try to tell me what to say Yeah <br>But I write <br>I write what I like <br><br>If you say you don't support Aussie Hip Hop <br>Who gives a fuck, at least four ockers pissed off <br>They keep saying to us stay underground <br>Why the fuck would be do that We wanna make money now <br>Yeah, I think I want a figure around eight hundred thou' <br>'Cause I'm getting sick of living in the same fuckin' house <br>I need something bigger than the place I'm in now <br>'Cause I want a lot of space when my mates come around <br>Now you know I'm out to get dough from the get go <br>I wanna slick sick flip phone with a ringtone Ha <br>So everybody thinks I'm rich when I ring home Okay <br>And I can ball out Yeah till I fall down <br>Ayy PEZ, I can lip read Yeah <br>You see that dude talkin' to his mum now, I know exactly what that shit mean <br>You think I'm in need Bitch please <br>I just moved to Switzerland to make heaps of cheddar Swiss Cheese <br><br>They try to tell me what to say Wanna critique my songs <br>They try to tell me to write, what do the people want <br>They try to tell me what to say <br>But I write <br>I write what I like <br><br>'Kay, yo <br>You know I took my first steps way before I could talk yep <br>I didn't need to crawl 'cause I could already walk <br>Right from the first second I was born out the womb <br>I just popped out and dropped down and walked out the room <br>Boom, If we dislike someone then we giving the bird <br>I mean we buy a parrot and we give 'em the bird <br>The first time you hear that you'll probably think it's absurd <br>Until we rock up on your doorstep and give you a bird Ha <br>I love the vibe that a funeral makes <br>Yeah, I love the taste of them urinal cakes God <br>Um that's pretty unusual ayy <br>Nah, put some chutney on the top and they're beautiful mate What <br>See me in a cage with a snake tryna play fight <br>With a canine and great white at the same time <br>Nah, I'm afraid right, the only reason <br>I play and I stage dive's 'cause I literally got stage fright <br>Go Oh ho ho, walk it off mate <br><br>They try to tell me what to say Wanna critique my songs <br>They try to tell me to write, what do the people want <br>They try to tell me what to say , yeah <br>But I write <br>I write down whatever I want '6, that's the point <br>They try to tell me what to say They try to tell me <br>They try to tell me to write They try to tell me <br>They try to tell me what to say <br>But I write <br>I write what I like]]></content><category term="PEZ" label="PEZ"/><category term="They Try To Tell Me (Feat. 360)" label="They Try To Tell Me (Feat. 360)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Calling_Out_Feat_Paul_Dempsey/</id><title>PEZ - Calling Out (Feat. Paul Dempsey) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:31:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:31:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Calling_Out_Feat_Paul_Dempsey/" title="PEZ - Calling Out (Feat. Paul Dempsey) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the technologists, the tradesmen and the apprentices <br>Ray and the young men like him manning 15,000 factories <br><br>Into this life we're thrown <br>Just as if outta nowhere, and from that instant <br>Begin to be program', to decode eve <br>Rything we see in a particular way <br>Now some have the nerve to venture off into the unknown <br>Some don't, they're content to watch from the front row <br>Either way it's still a game that can be cut throat <br>You don't wanna be on the wrong end of all the gun smoke <br>But your destiny waits <br>So there's really no need for precaution, of course <br>We are cautious, it's all we know <br>Just one false move and it's all she wrote, that's what they tell us <br>So we all take aim to stake claim <br>And if you get there just pray you maintain <br>Long enough, not to suffer and <br>No longer have to sing a song for your supper <br>Let's pray <br><br>How we gonna keep on sufferin' <br>And fallin' on our knees for nothin' <br>I'm starting to believe in somethin' <br>It's kinda hard to hear it but it's callin' out <br><br>Okay <br><br>Because I look inside, find this insight <br>Guessin' in this life, people would think I <br>Must know really what mine's for <br>But the truth I'm not quite sure <br>All I'm doin' is tryna follow my heart <br>Even though that my head's sayin', 'what if I can't' <br>What if my path is already planned out <br>I already see how the story will pan out <br>It's not gonna be, well shit still I'm not gonna stop <br>When a job is the only other option I got <br>I'm not sayin' that it's wrong 'cause it's not <br>But if you're workin' and it doesn't make you happy then what <br>Is the point I mean really <br>Either you can take a shot or try to merely make do <br>When you see that that's the only other move <br>Then there really isn't anything to lose, choose <br><br>How we gonna keep on sufferin' <br>And fallin' on our knees for nothin' <br>I'm starting to believe in somethin' <br>It's kinda hard to hear it but it's callin' out <br><br>Hey that's the way everything goes <br>Some get what they want, the rest never get close <br>That's why they say if you ever get chosen <br>You made it 'cause anything goes <br>That's why we find ourself in a time where <br>People deny what's really inside them, frightened <br>Mighta feared that the outcome is doubtful <br>Not knowin' in itself that's the downfall, it's weird right <br>See we think we'll never make an impact <br>Since a young age we've been trained to think that <br>That's the only reason we're beaten <br>They know they can feed us this shit and we'll believe it, either <br>You can struggle through life or take your story <br>And then turn it into something you like it's all up in your mind <br>And in mine man, I'm leavin' on a plane <br>So if you're comin' there too well then I'll see you on the way <br>Let's go <br><br>How we gonna keep on sufferin' <br>And fallin' on our knees for nothin' <br>I'm starting to believe in somethin' <br>It's kinda hard to hear it but it's callin' out <br><br>How we gonna keep on sufferin' <br>And fallin' on our knees for nothin' <br>I'm starting to believe in somethin' <br>It's kinda hard to hear it but it's callin' out <br><br>It's callin' <br>It's callin' <br>It's callin' out <br>It's callin' out <br>It's callin' out <br>It's callin' <br>It's callin' out <br>It's callin' out <br><br>Judy is working in one of the stores until she marries <br>But thousands more spend their working lives serving <br>The needs of a million shoppers]]></content><category term="PEZ" label="PEZ"/><category term="Calling Out (Feat. Paul Dempsey)" label="Calling Out (Feat. Paul Dempsey)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Cant_Wait_Feat_Hailey_Cramer/</id><title>PEZ - Can`t Wait (Feat. Hailey Cramer) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:31:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:31:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Cant_Wait_Feat_Hailey_Cramer/" title="PEZ - Can`t Wait (Feat. Hailey Cramer) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah, it's been a long time coming, huh <br>Ayy <br><br>Let me dust off my feet on the welcome mat <br>'Cause I feel like I just been to hell and back <br>I had to tell you that <br>Because there's been a lot of people asking where's your album at <br>I gotta hand those fans love <br>For sticking with me when I didn't have an answer <br>Now I do I think we need to catch up <br>It's been a minute, hope there isn't any bad blood <br>See I really nearly thought about <br>Getting a job and just walking out, but I'm over that <br>'Cause Aunt Mary got buried that very <br>First minute that I wrote a rap and I'm not going back <br>But at least if I can help her right <br>Cause this is all that I know and it's calling me home <br>I spent too long standing at a fork in a road <br>Thinking what way, but I'm done waiting <br><br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer <br>No mo ohhh I can't wait <br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer, no <br>Can't wait any longer, no <br>No, no, no <br><br>Uh, they got us all on a hunt for wealth <br>If it ain't that then it's something else to fill a void <br>So I thought I'd write for the kids and <br>Let 'em know there's more to life than just this shit <br>'Cause they're in need of some truth <br>Somebody's gotta speak to the youth, tell 'em something real <br>And let 'em know the fucking deal <br>While they're trying to find their way through the maze <br>And I know how you're feeling 'cause I feel for ya <br>Just know as long as you hear me that I'm here for ya <br>And I will always keep speaking from my heart <br>All the way from my very first CD to my last <br>Uh, to help you see it's a mirage <br>It's got us all believing that we can't <br>We're living life and when your aim is attained <br>Life shouldn't have to be mundane <br>So, this is for the people out there tired of being stepped on <br>For the rappers out there tired of being slept on <br>Nah, I wasn't always in the upper echelon <br>Yes, I was once down the bottom but I kept on <br>I hear 'em saying where's Pez gone <br>Man, I'm back, I'm picking up right left off <br>'Cause I ended up inside a maze <br>Took a little while to find my way, but now <br><br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer <br>No mo ohhh I can't wait <br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer, no yeah <br>Can't wait any longer, no <br>No, no, no]]></content><category term="PEZ" label="PEZ"/><category term="Can`t Wait (Feat. Hailey Cramer)" label="Can`t Wait (Feat. Hailey Cramer)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이소라/사랑이_아니라_말하지_말아요/</id><title>이소라 - 사랑이 아니라 말하지 말아요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:34:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:34:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%86%8C%EB%9D%BC/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EC%95%84%EB%8B%88%EB%9D%BC_%EB%A7%90%ED%95%98%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="이소라 - 사랑이 아니라 말하지 말아요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 사랑이 사랑이 아니라고는 <br>말하지 말아요 <br>보이지 않는 길을 걸으려 한다고 <br>괜한 헛수고라 생각하진 말아요 <br>내 마음이 헛된 희망이라고는 <br>말하지 말아요 <br>정상이 없는 산을 오르려 한다고 <br>나의 무모함을 비웃지는 말아요 <br>그대 두 손을 놓쳐서 <br>난 길을 잃었죠 <br>허나 멈출 수가 없어요 <br>이게 내 사랑인걸요 <br>그대 두 손을 놓쳐서 <br>난 길을 잃었죠 <br>허나 멈출 수가 없어요 <br>이게 내 사랑인걸요 <br>내 사랑이 사랑이 아니라고는 <br>말하지 말아요 <br>그대 없이 나 홀로 하려 한다고 <br>나의 이런 사랑이 <br>사랑이 아니라고 <br>나를 설득하려 말아요 <br>]]></content><category term="이소라" label="이소라"/><category term="사랑이 아니라 말하지 말아요" label="사랑이 아니라 말하지 말아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Niro/Mama_Tavais_Raison/</id><title>Niro - Mama T`avais Raison - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:38:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:38:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Niro/Mama_Tavais_Raison/" title="Niro - Mama T`avais Raison - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mama t'avais raison <br>Ouais, mama t'avais raison <br>Mama t'avais raison <br>Ouais, mama t'avais raison <br>Mama t'avais raison <br>Et ouais, hey, hey <br><br>Ma mere m'a dit mon fils, le hasard n'existe pas <br>Avant mes premiers pas, je voulais marcher mais je pouvais pas <br>Je regarde les autres a l'ecole fuirent leurs parents comme la peste <br>Tout ce que je voulais c'etait voir ma mere mon pere dans la meme piece <br>J'ai traine pendant des annees solo dans les rues de ma ville <br>L'impression d'etre condamne, vivre malheureux a vie <br>Me revoila dix ans apres, devenu violent pour de vrai <br>Vos meres nous voient de loin parce que le haram nous suit de pres <br>a l'age de quinze ou seize, une cinquantaine sur le banc <br>On allait dans leur cite pour tabasser leurs grands <br>C'etait pas gratuit, en effet, le poto s'est fait meler <br>J'ai vu plus de violence dans la vraie vie qu'a la tele <br>Ce sera pas pour bricoler si on doit sortir les outils <br>Mineurs, on envoyait des gens dans le coma pour des broutilles <br>On a vole, on a bicrave <br>Pas pour faire de la pub <br>J'ai grandi dans la ZUP donc j'ai grandi dans la stup, ouais <br>Aveugle par la fumee, j'ai vu le temps se consumer <br>Consommer pour me consoler, je reve d'etre riche au fond du tro me <br>Je pensais a tout ce qu'on a rate, le temps perdu sur le rain te <br>a regarder tous ces blindes passer en gros gamos vitres teintees <br>Ils revaient d'avoir leurs diplomes, je revais de braquer la Brinks <br>Acheter une villa a ma mere, mettre la famille a l'abri <br>Mais le reveil est brutal, gros <br>Ouais, le reveil est brutal <br>Mama m'a dit c'est la vie <br>Dehors je suis mieux qu'a la maison <br>Mon soce y perd la raison <br>Il m'a dit je suis malheureux, j'etais mieux quand j'etais en prison <br>Ainsi va la vida <br>Je regarde les voitures bruler <br>Et je les brule a mon tour pour dire au monde de se faire enculer <br>Dans le halal on me regarde chelou, dans le haram congratule <br>On trainait tard entre nous, je voulais pas etre adule <br>Moi j'avais pas de pere, pas de grand frere et pas de flingue <br>Mama j'ai mes raisons, monter en l'air ces baltringues <br>Et j'ai du mal a me raisonner, calcule pas n'importe qui <br>Ils font les 'chants, on les connait <br>On sait qui a peur de qui <br>Poto, je leur ai pardonne <br>Je n'avais que mes couilles et mon schlass gros <br>Ouais, mama t'avais raison <br>Mama t'avais raison <br>Mama t'avais raison <br>Mama t'avais raison <br>Mama t'avais raison <br>Tu perds le sommeil quand ca joue les caids <br>Mama t'avais raison <br>Rendors toi j'ai compris, ouais ca y est j'ai grandi <br>Mama t'avais raison <br>Mes deux fils, mes amis, ma famille, c'est ma iv <br>Mama t'avais raison <br>Je graille, ouais je maillais mais jamais j'ai trahi]]></content><category term="Niro" label="Niro"/><category term="Mama T`avais Raison" label="Mama T`avais Raison"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Locked_Out/</id><title>Crowded_House - Locked Out - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:42:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:42:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Locked_Out/" title="Crowded_House - Locked Out - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been locked out, I've been locked in <br>But I always seem to come back again <br>When you're in that room, oh what do you do <br>I know that I will have you in the end <br><br>And the clouds they are crying on you <br>And the birds are offering up their tunes <br>In a shack as remote as a mansion <br>You escape into a place where nothing moves <br><br>And I've been locked out, and I know we're through <br>But I can't begin to face up to the truth <br>I wait so long for the walls to crack <br>But I know that I will one day have you back <br><br>And the hills are as soft as a pillow <br>And they cast a shadow on my bed <br>And the view when I look through my window <br>Is an altarpiece I'm praying to for the living and the dead <br><br>The twin valleys shines in the morning sun <br>I send a message out to my only one <br><br>Yet I've been locked out, and I know we're through <br>But I can't begin to face up to the truth <br>And I wait so long for the walls to crack <br>But I know that I will one day have you back <br>Yes, I will <br><br>And I work, bees in the honey <br>Every night, I circle like the moon <br>And it's an act of simple devotion <br>But it can take forever when you've got something to prove <br><br>I've been locked out <br>And I've been locked out <br>And I've been locked out]]></content><category term="Crowded House" label="Crowded House"/><category term="Locked Out" label="Locked Out"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Fingers_Of_Love_Alternative_Studio_Take/</id><title>Crowded_House - Fingers Of Love (Alternative Studio Take) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:43:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:43:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Fingers_Of_Love_Alternative_Studio_Take/" title="Crowded_House - Fingers Of Love (Alternative Studio Take) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can you imagine that <br>An itch too sensitive to scratch <br>The light that falls through the cracks <br>An insect too delicate to catch <br>I hear the endless murmur <br>Every blade of grass that shivers in the breeze <br>And the sound that comes to carry me <br>Across the land and over the sea <br><br>And I can't look up <br>Fingers of love move down <br>And I can't look back <br>Fingers of love move down <br><br>Colour is its own reward <br>Colour is its own reward <br>The chiming of a perfect chord <br>Let's go jumping overboard <br>Into waves of joy and clarity <br>Your hands come out to rescue me <br>And I'm playing in the shallow water <br>Laughing while the mad dog sleeps <br><br>And I can't look up <br>Fingers of love move down <br>And I won't be hit <br>Fingers of love move everywhere <br><br>There is time yet <br>Fall by the way <br>From the cradle to the grave <br>From a palace to the gutter <br>Beneath the dying waves of the sun <br>Lie fingers of love <br><br>Through waves of joy and clarity <br>A fallen angel walked on the sea <br>And I'm playing in the shallow water <br>Laughing while the mad dog sleeps <br><br>And I can't look up <br>Fingers of love move down <br>And I won't be hit <br>Fingers of love move everywhere <br><br>There is time yet <br>For you to find me <br>And all I want <br>Fingers of love move down]]></content><category term="Crowded House" label="Crowded House"/><category term="Fingers Of Love (Alternative Studio Take)" label="Fingers Of Love (Alternative Studio Take)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Fingers_Of_Love_Band_Demo/</id><title>Crowded_House - Fingers Of Love (Band Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:43:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:43:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Fingers_Of_Love_Band_Demo/" title="Crowded_House - Fingers Of Love (Band Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can you imagine that <br>An itch too sensitive to scratch <br>The light that falls through the cracks <br>An insect too delicate to catch <br>I hear the endless murmur <br>Every blade of grass that shivers in the breeze <br>And the sound that comes to carry me <br>Across the land and over the sea <br><br>And I can't look up <br>Fingers of love move down <br>And I can't look back <br>Fingers of love move down <br><br>Colour is its own reward <br>Colour is its own reward <br>The chiming of a perfect chord <br>Let's go jumping overboard <br>Into waves of joy and clarity <br>Your hands come out to rescue me <br>And I'm playing in the shallow water <br>Laughing while the mad dog sleeps <br><br>And I can't look up <br>Fingers of love move down <br>And I won't be hit <br>Fingers of love move everywhere <br><br>There is time yet <br>Fall by the way <br>From the cradle to the grave <br>From a palace to the gutter <br>Beneath the dying waves of the sun <br>Lie fingers of love <br><br>Through waves of joy and clarity <br>A fallen angel walked on the sea <br>And I'm playing in the shallow water <br>Laughing while the mad dog sleeps <br><br>And I can't look up <br>Fingers of love move down <br>And I won't be hit <br>Fingers of love move everywhere <br><br>There is time yet <br>For you to find me <br>And all I want <br>Fingers of love move down]]></content><category term="Crowded House" label="Crowded House"/><category term="Fingers Of Love (Band Demo)" label="Fingers Of Love (Band Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/I_Am_In_Love_Band_Demo/</id><title>Crowded_House - I Am In Love (Band Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:43:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:43:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/I_Am_In_Love_Band_Demo/" title="Crowded_House - I Am In Love (Band Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Called out to prove my love <br>You reply by getting defensive <br>Called out to prove my love <br>Now you should be able to sense it <br><br>I'm full of your dreams <br>I let you sleep with the lights on <br>Stay with me might as well <br>Be the kind of girl you want to be <br><br>I am in love <br>I am in love <br>I am a fool <br>Fell from above <br><br>These things that I have done <br>They would be a test of anyone <br>How am I meant to see <br>You dressed up like your mother <br><br>They say you marry your father <br>I hope that don't reflect on me <br>They say you marry your mother <br>I hope that don't put you in her company <br><br>I am in love <br>I am in love <br>And I am a fool <br>There is no other <br>I am in love <br>I am in love <br><br>What I say is don't lie <br>But it's enough to make you wonder <br>I can't be one that you wanna trust <br>And not the one that you wanna trample <br>In the dust <br><br>I am in love <br>I am in love <br>And I am a fool <br>There is no other <br>I am in love <br>I am in love <br><br>Into the fire <br>Tears start coming <br>Good stars surround us <br>It's enough to wanna make you wonder]]></content><category term="Crowded House" label="Crowded House"/><category term="I Am In Love (Band Demo)" label="I Am In Love (Band Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Distant_Sun_Writing_Demo/</id><title>Crowded_House - Distant Sun (Writing Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:43:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:43:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Distant_Sun_Writing_Demo/" title="Crowded_House - Distant Sun (Writing Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me all the things you would change <br>I don't pretend to know what you want <br>When you come around and spin my top <br>Time and again, time and again <br>No fire where I lit my spark <br>I am not afraid of the dark <br>Where your words devour my heart <br>And put me to shame, put me to shame <br><br>When your seven worlds collide <br>Whenever I am by your side <br>And dust from a distant sun <br>Will shower over everyone <br><br>You're still so young to travel so far <br>Old enough to know who you are <br>Wise enough to carry the scars <br>Without any blame, there's no one to blame <br>It's easy to forget what you learned <br>Waiting for the thrill to return <br>Feeling your desire burn <br>You're drawn to the flame <br><br>When your seven worlds collide <br>Whenever I am by your side <br>Dust from a distant sun <br>Will shower over everyone <br>Dust from a distant sun <br>Will shower over everyone <br><br>And I'm lying on the table <br>Washed out in the flood <br>Like a Christian fearing vengeance from above <br>I don't pretend to know what you want <br>But I offer love <br><br>Seven worlds collide <br>Whenever I am by your side <br>Dust from a distant sun <br>Will shower over everyone <br><br>As time slips by, and on and on <br>Let your mind go, anywhere it wants, anywhere it wants <br>Let your mind <br>As time slips by, and on and on <br>Let your mind go, anywhere it wants, anywhere it wants]]></content><category term="Crowded House" label="Crowded House"/><category term="Distant Sun (Writing Demo)" label="Distant Sun (Writing Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Private_Universe_Home_Demo/</id><title>Crowded_House - Private Universe (Home Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:43:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:43:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Private_Universe_Home_Demo/" title="Crowded_House - Private Universe (Home Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No time no place to talk about the weather <br>The promise of love is hard to ignore <br>You said the chance wasn't getting any better <br>Labour of love is ours to endure <br>The highest branch on the apple tree <br>It was my favourite place to be <br>I could hear them breaking free <br>But they could not see me <br><br>I will run for shelter <br>Endless summer lift the curse <br>It feels like nothing matters <br>In our private universe <br><br>I have all I want is that simple enough <br>There's a whole lot more I'm thinking of <br>Every night about six o'clock <br>The birds come back to the palm to talk <br>They talk to me, birds talk to me <br>If I go down on my knees <br><br>I will run for shelter <br>Endless summer lift the curse <br>It feels like nothing matters <br>In our private universe <br><br>And it's a pleasure that I have known <br>And it's a treasure that I have gained <br>And it's a pleasure that I have known <br><br>It's a tight squeeze but I won't let go <br>Love is on the table and the dinner's cold <br><br>I will run for shelter <br>Endless summer lift the curse <br>Feels like nothing matters <br>In our private universe]]></content><category term="Crowded House" label="Crowded House"/><category term="Private Universe (Home Demo)" label="Private Universe (Home Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Fingers_Of_Love_Writing_Demo/</id><title>Crowded_House - Fingers Of Love (Writing Demo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:43:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:43:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Fingers_Of_Love_Writing_Demo/" title="Crowded_House - Fingers Of Love (Writing Demo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Can you imagine that <br>An itch too sensitive to scratch <br>The light that falls through the cracks <br>An insect too delicate to catch <br>I hear the endless murmur <br>Every blade of grass that shivers in the breeze <br>And the sound that comes to carry me <br>Across the land and over the sea <br><br>And I can't look up <br>Fingers of love move down <br>And I can't look back <br>Fingers of love move down <br><br>Colour is its own reward <br>Colour is its own reward <br>The chiming of a perfect chord <br>Let's go jumping overboard <br>Into waves of joy and clarity <br>Your hands come out to rescue me <br>And I'm playing in the shallow water <br>Laughing while the mad dog sleeps <br><br>And I can't look up <br>Fingers of love move down <br>And I won't be hit <br>Fingers of love move everywhere <br><br>There is time yet <br>Fall by the way <br>From the cradle to the grave <br>From a palace to the gutter <br>Beneath the dying waves of the sun <br>Lie fingers of love <br><br>Through waves of joy and clarity <br>A fallen angel walked on the sea <br>And I'm playing in the shallow water <br>Laughing while the mad dog sleeps <br><br>And I can't look up <br>Fingers of love move down <br>And I won't be hit <br>Fingers of love move everywhere <br><br>There is time yet <br>For you to find me <br>And all I want <br>Fingers of love move down]]></content><category term="Crowded House" label="Crowded House"/><category term="Fingers Of Love (Writing Demo)" label="Fingers Of Love (Writing Demo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Together_Alone/</id><title>Crowded_House - Together Alone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:43:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:43:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Together_Alone/" title="Crowded_House - Together Alone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Together alone <br>above and beneath <br>we were as close <br>as anyone can be <br>now you are gone <br>far away from me <br>as is once <br>will always be <br>together alone <br><br>Anei ra maua here we are together <br>e piri tahi nei in a very close embrace <br>e noha tahi nei being together <br>ko maua anake just us alone <br>kei runga a Rangi Rangi the sky father is above <br>ko papa kei raro the earth mother is below <br>e mau tonu nei our love for one another <br>kia mau tonu ra is everlasting <br><br>Together alone <br>shallow and deep <br>holding our breath <br>paying death no heed <br>I'm still your friend <br>when you are in need <br>as is once <br>will always be <br>earth and sky <br>moon and sea <br><br>Anei ra maua here we are together <br>e piri tahi nei in a very close embrace <br>e noha tahi nei being together <br>ko maua anake just us alone <br>kei runga a Rangi Rangi the sky father is above <br>ko papa kei raro the earth mother is below <br>e mau tonu nei our love for one another <br>kia mau tonu ra is everlasting]]></content><category term="Crowded House" label="Crowded House"/><category term="Together Alone" label="Together Alone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Skin_Feeling/</id><title>Crowded_House - Skin Feeling - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-21T20:43:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-21T20:43:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Crowded_House/Skin_Feeling/" title="Crowded_House - Skin Feeling - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see some very nice skin out there <br><br>I like the smell of that shop <br>I like the way it serves me <br>I like the pigment in your skin <br>I like the way it moves me <br>I like kids when they're asleep <br>their little arms around you <br>I like the way we play games <br>don't lose that skin feeling <br><br>I'm looking old, I'm feeling young <br>it's the truth my child <br>My second life has just begun <br>with this hungry girl <br><br>I like black and I like red <br>and I like that orange circle <br>I like the things that you said <br>when you were misbehaving <br>I like the people on TV <br>But no one looks like me <br>I love you and you love me <br>don't lose that skin feeling <br><br>I'm looking old, I'm feeling young <br>it's the truth my child <br>My second life has just begun <br>with this hungry girl <br><br>I love the pigment in your skin <br>I love the way it moves me <br>I like the smell of that shop <br>I like the way it serves me <br>I like the things that you said <br>when you were misbehaving <br>I love you and you love me <br>don't lose that skin feeling <br><br>I'm looking old I'm feeling young <br>It's the truth my child <br>My second life has just begun <br>with this hungry girl <br><br>It's the truth my child <br>let me hold you high <br><br>And I like to get up in the sky <br>I like to look down <br>I like to fly <br>I like to fly, in the sky real high <br>I like to run in the sand like a horse <br><br>That's what I like <br>I like to swim in the ocean like a fish <br>I like to fly high]]></content><category term="Crowded House" label="Crowded House"/><category term="Skin Feeling" label="Skin Feeling"/></entry></feed>