<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:05:57+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/나르빅_Narvik/진심/</id><title>나르빅 (Narvik) - 진심 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:05:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:05:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%B4%EB%B9%85_Narvik/%EC%A7%84%EC%8B%AC/" title="나르빅 (Narvik) - 진심 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 손 놓지 마 날 꼭 붙잡아 <br>니 마음과는 다르게 <br>하는 걸 알아 그러니까 <br>맘에도 없는 그 말 <br>꺼내 놓지 마 다시는 <br>여전히 나를 사랑한다는 걸 알아 <br>하기 싫은 말 안 해도 괜찮아 <br>니가 하고 싶은 말만 해 우리 <br>사랑한다는 말만 하고 살아 우리 <br>맘에도 없는 그 말 <br>꺼내 놓지 마 다시는 <br>여전히 나를 사랑한다는 걸 알아 <br>하기 싫은 말 안 해도 괜찮아 <br>니가 하고 싶은 말만 해 우리 <br>사랑한다는 말만 하고 살아 우리 <br>]]></content><category term="나르빅 (Narvik)" label="나르빅 (Narvik)"/><category term="진심" label="진심"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정주연/딸기빙수/</id><title>정주연 - 딸기빙수 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%A3%BC%EC%97%B0/%EB%94%B8%EA%B8%B0%EB%B9%99%EC%88%98/" title="정주연 - 딸기빙수 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지겹고 따분한 주말 오후 <br>한 낮도 아닌데 너무 더워 <br>난 드라큘라도 아닌데 <br>햇빛을 볼 수가 없어 <br>녹아 버릴지도 몰라 <br>선풍기 바람도 미지근해 <br>오래 묵은 콜라처럼 맹해 <br>이런 날엔 뭘 해도 짜증나 <br>도대체 뭐가 날 <br>위로해 줄 수 있을까 <br>내가 만약 외로울 땐 <br>누가 날 위로해 주지 <br>딸기빙수 <br>시원한 카페에 앉아 <br>새콤달콤 향긋한 딸기빙수 <br>그대와 함께 둘이서 <br>시원하고 상큼한 딸기빙수 <br>시원한 카페에 앉아 <br>새콤달콤 향긋한 딸기빙수 <br>그대와 함께 둘이서 <br>시원하고 상큼한 딸기빙수 <br>그대 그대 <br>그대와 함께 둘이서 <br>여름엔 딸기빙수 <br>날 위로해주네 <br>]]></content><category term="정주연" label="정주연"/><category term="딸기빙수" label="딸기빙수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/나같은_죄인/</id><title>최인혁 - 나같은 죄인 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EB%82%98%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EC%A3%84%EC%9D%B8/" title="최인혁 - 나같은 죄인 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[늘 잊고 사는 하나님의 은혜 <br>가려진 삶 속에서 나 찾기 원하네 <br>늘 다짐하며 힘써 왔지만 <br>연약한 나에겐 주님이 필요해 <br>나 같은 죄인 나 같은 죄인 <br>주님의 사랑의 보혈로 <br>나 구원 얻었네 <br>나 같은 죄인 나 같은 죄인 <br>주님의 사랑의 보혈로 <br>나 자유 얻었네 <br>늘 잊고 사는 하나님의 은혜 <br>가려진 삶 속에서 나 찾기 원하네 <br>늘 다짐하며 힘써 왔지만 <br>연약한 나에겐 주님이 필요해 <br>나 같은 죄인 나 같은 죄인 <br>주님의 사랑의 보혈로 <br>나 구원 얻었네 <br>나 같은 죄인 나 같은 죄인 <br>주님의 사랑의 보혈로 <br>나 자유 얻었네 <br>주님의 보혈 주님의 보혈 <br>나 경배 하리라 <br>주님의 보혈 주님의 보혈 <br>나 경배 하리라 <br>나 경배 하리 나 경배 하리 <br>높으신 보좌의 주님께 <br>나 경배 하리라 <br>나 경배 하리 나 경배 하리 <br>높으신 보좌의 주님께 <br>나 경배 하리라 <br>나 같은 죄인 나 같은 죄인 <br>주님의 사랑의 보혈로 <br>나 구원 얻었네 <br>나 같은 죄인 나 같은 죄인 <br>주님의 사랑의 보혈로 <br>나 자유 얻었네 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="나같은 죄인" label="나같은 죄인"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/성령의_바람_Feat_김지수_주찬미/</id><title>최인혁 - 성령의 바람 (Feat. 김지수, 주찬미) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EC%84%B1%EB%A0%B9%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%EC%88%98_%EC%A3%BC%EC%B0%AC%EB%AF%B8/" title="최인혁 - 성령의 바람 (Feat. 김지수, 주찬미) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[성령의 바람 메마른 영혼 적시는 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>성령의 바람 메마른 영혼 적시는 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>성령의 바람 메마른 영혼 적시는 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>성령의 바람 메마른 영혼 적시는 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>불어 오소서 이곳에 <br>덮어 주소서 이곳을 <br>불어 오소서 이곳에 <br>덮어 주소서 이곳을 <br>성령의 바람 메마른 영혼 적시는 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>성령의 바람 메마른 영혼 적시는 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>불어 오소서 이곳에 <br>덮어 주소서 이곳을 <br>불어 오소서 이곳에 <br>덮어 주소서 이곳을 <br>불어 오소서 이곳에 <br>덮어 주소서 이곳을 <br>불어 오소서 이곳에 <br>덮어 주소서 이곳을 <br>성령의 바람 메마른 영혼 적시는 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>성령의 바람 메마른 영혼 적시는 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>성령의 바람 메마른 영혼 적시는 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>성령의 바람 메마른 영혼 적시는 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>상한 맘 치유 하는 바람 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="성령의 바람 (Feat. 김지수, 주찬미)" label="성령의 바람 (Feat. 김지수, 주찬미)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/쩔어/</id><title>최인혁 - 쩔어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EC%A9%94%EC%96%B4/" title="최인혁 - 쩔어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리의 대장 되신 능력의 주 하나님 <br>우리를 다스리시네 <br>우리를 앞서 가사 주 백성 지키시니 <br>그대로 믿고 따르네 <br>레알 킹왕짱 정말 멋진 주님 <br>다른 이들 주 앞에 안습이네 <br>그 무엇도 비교 할 수 없네 <br>오나전후 왕 GOOD <br>레알 킹왕짱 정말 멋진 주님 <br>우리를 다스리시는 주님은 <br>쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 <br>사단이 다가와도 두려움 없어지니 <br>주께서 굴복시키네 <br>강력한 주의 이름 오직 그 이름만을 <br>세상에 선포하리라 <br>레알 킹왕짱 정말 멋진 주님 <br>다른 이들 주 앞에 안습이네 <br>그 무엇도 비교 할 수 없네 <br>오나전후 왕 GOOD <br>레알 킹왕짱 정말 멋진 주님 <br>우리를 다스리시는 주님은 <br>쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 <br>쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 <br>쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 <br>쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 <br>쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 <br>쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 <br>쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 <br>쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 <br>쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 쩔어 <br>우리의 대장 되신 능력의 주 하나님 <br>우리를 다스리시네 <br>우리를 앞서 가사 주 백성 지키시니 <br>그대로 믿고 따르네 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="쩔어" label="쩔어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/주여_나를_도우소서_Feat_최광원/</id><title>최인혁 - 주여 나를 도우소서 (Feat. 최광원) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EC%A3%BC%EC%97%AC_%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EB%8F%84%EC%9A%B0%EC%86%8C%EC%84%9C_Feat_%EC%B5%9C%EA%B4%91%EC%9B%90/" title="최인혁 - 주여 나를 도우소서 (Feat. 최광원) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주여 난 너무 힘들어요 <br>마음이 너무 힘들어요 <br>주여 난 너무 지쳤나봐요 <br>내게와 나를 도와주세요 <br>비바람 속에도 <br>흔들리지 않는 바위처럼 <br>내게 그런 믿음과 소망을 주셔서 <br>이 슬픔과 눈물 이길수 있도록 <br>주여 나를 도우소서 <br>비바람 속에도 <br>흔들리지 않는 바위처럼 <br>내게 그런 믿음과 소망을 주셔서 <br>이 슬픔과 눈물 이길수 있도록 <br>주여 나를 도우소서 <br>이 슬픔과 눈물 이길수 있도록 <br>주여 나를 도우소서 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="주여 나를 도우소서 (Feat. 최광원)" label="주여 나를 도우소서 (Feat. 최광원)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/오_나는_약한_나그네요_Feat_오은/</id><title>최인혁 - 오 나는 약한 나그네요 (Feat. 오은) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EC%98%A4_%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%95%BD%ED%95%9C_%EB%82%98%EA%B7%B8%EB%84%A4%EC%9A%94_Feat_%EC%98%A4%EC%9D%80/" title="최인혁 - 오 나는 약한 나그네요 (Feat. 오은) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 가네 내 아버지께 <br>더 이상 방황 없는 곳 <br>나는 가네 십자가 앞에 <br>주님 품에 돌아가네 <br>오 나는 약한 나그네요 <br>이 슬픈 세상을 가며 <br>수고도 병도 위험도 없는 <br>내가 가는 저 밝은 곳 <br>나는 가네 내 아버지께 <br>더 이상 방황 없는 곳 <br>나는 가네 십자가 앞에 <br>주님 품에 돌아가네 <br>오 나는 약한 나그네요 <br>이 병든 세상을 가며 <br>수고도 병도 눈물도 없는 <br>내가 가는 저 밝은 곳 <br>나는 가네 내 아버지께 <br>더 이상 방황 없는 곳 <br>나는 가네 십자가 앞에 <br>주님 품에 돌아가네 <br>나는 가네 저 하늘나라 <br>더 이상 눈물 없는 곳 <br>나는 가네 십자가 앞에 <br>주님 품에 돌아가네 <br>나는 가네 내 아버지께 <br>더 이상 방황 없는 곳 <br>나는 가네 십자가 앞에 <br>주님 품에 돌아가네 <br>주님 품에 돌아가네 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="오 나는 약한 나그네요 (Feat. 오은)" label="오 나는 약한 나그네요 (Feat. 오은)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/에바다/</id><title>최인혁 - 에바다 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EC%97%90%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4/" title="최인혁 - 에바다 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[에바다 에바다 에바다 <br>너는 들을 지어다 <br>에바다 에바다 에바다 <br>너는 외칠 지어다 <br>에바다 에바다 에바다 <br>너는 들을 지어다 <br>에바다 에바다 에바다 <br>너는 외칠 지어다 <br>죄로 물든 우리의 영혼을 <br>주께 맡깁니다 <br>에바다 에바다 에바다 <br>너는 열릴 지어다 <br>에바다 에바다 에바다 <br>너는 들을 지어다 <br>에바다 에바다 에바다 <br>너는 외칠 지어다 <br>죄로 물든 우리의 영혼을 <br>주께 맡깁니다 <br>에바다 에바다 에바다 <br>열릴 지어다 <br>죄로 물든 우리의 영혼을 <br>주께 맡깁니다 <br>에바다 에바다 에바다 <br>열릴 지어다 <br>죄로 물든 우리의 영혼을 <br>주께 맡깁니다 <br>에바다 에바다 에바다 <br>열릴 지어다 열릴 지어다 열릴 지어다 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="에바다" label="에바다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/나는_너의_하나님/</id><title>최인혁 - 나는 너의 하나님 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98/" title="최인혁 - 나는 너의 하나님 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 너의 하나님 두려워 말아라 <br>나는 너의 하나님 놀라지 말아라 <br>나는 선한 목자니 널 인도 하리라 <br>나는 아바 아버지 널 품에 안으리 <br>때론 이해 할 수 없는 많은 일들이 <br>네게 닥쳐와도 <br>때론 감당 할 수 없는 어려움들이 <br>너를 둘러 덮어도 <br>두려워 말아라 놀라지 말아라 <br>나는 너의 하나님이라 <br>나는 너의 선한 목자라 <br>때론 이해 할 수 없는 많은 일들이 <br>네게 닥쳐와도 <br>때론 감당 할 수 없는 어려움들이 <br>너를 둘러 덮어도 <br>두려워 말아라 놀라지 말아라 <br>나는 너의 하나님이라 <br>나는 너의 선한 목자라 <br>두려워 말아라 놀라지 말아라 <br>나는 너의 하나님이라 <br>나는 너의 선한 목자라 <br>너 가는 길 두려워 말아라 <br>내가 끝까지 함께 하리니 <br>나는 너의 아버지 여호와 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="나는 너의 하나님" label="나는 너의 하나님"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/너는_내_것이라_Feat_강성식/</id><title>최인혁 - 너는 내 것이라 (Feat. 강성식) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EB%84%88%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%B4_%EA%B2%83%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC_Feat_%EA%B0%95%EC%84%B1%EC%8B%9D/" title="최인혁 - 너는 내 것이라 (Feat. 강성식) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너는 부유해도 가난해도 <br>너를 사랑하여 구원했으니 <br>너는 내 것이라 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 <br>너는 잘 났으나 못 났으나 <br>너의 모든 것을 알고 있으니 <br>너는 내 것이라 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 <br>너는 강하여도 약하여도 <br>너의 힘이 되어 일으키리니 <br>너는 내 것이라 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 <br>너는 의로워도 악하여도 <br>너를 나의 피로 바꾸었으니 <br>너는 내 것이라 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 <br>너는 내 것이라 너는 내 것이라 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="너는 내 것이라 (Feat. 강성식)" label="너는 내 것이라 (Feat. 강성식)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/길/</id><title>최인혁 - 길 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EA%B8%B8/" title="최인혁 - 길 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제쯤 도착 할 수 있을지 <br>그곳을 향한 길 가운데 <br>먼저 간 당신의 흔적 발견 할때면 <br>뭉클해 지는 맘 무언의 깨달음 <br>아직 다 알 수 없는 길고 긴 <br>여정의 끝 향해 하염없이 <br>걸어 가다보니 소중히 쥐고 있던 <br>불편함 버릴 수 있는 용기 생겨나고 <br>사막 한 가운데 홀로 남겨진듯 <br>정체된 외로움 <br>피할수 없는 바람에 휘청이며 <br>결국 쓰러져 가지만 <br>바람 속 희미해져 가는 모래 위 <br>발자국에 묻혀진 감사함 되새기며 <br>진리의 이 길을 따르는 길만이 <br>유일한 위로와 기쁨임을 알게되네 <br>사막 한 가운데 홀로 남겨진듯 <br>정체된 외로움 <br>피할수 없는 바람에 휘청이며 <br>결국 쓰러져 가지만 <br>바람 속 희미해져 가는 모래 위 <br>발자국에 묻혀진 감사함 되새기며 <br>진리의 이 길을 따르는 길만이 <br>유일한 위로와 기쁨임을 알게되네 <br>바람 속 희미해져 가는 모래 위 <br>발자국에 묻혀진 감사함 되새기며 <br>진리의 이 길을 따르는 길만이 <br>유일한 위로와 기쁨임을 알게되네 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="길" label="길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/주님_내_안에_Feat_초롬/</id><title>최인혁 - 주님 내 안에 (Feat. 초롬) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98_%EB%82%B4_%EC%95%88%EC%97%90_Feat_%EC%B4%88%EB%A1%AC/" title="최인혁 - 주님 내 안에 (Feat. 초롬) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언제나 내 모습 너무나 부끄러워 <br>무릎으로 주님께 기도로 가오니 <br>나홀로 서 있는 죽은 내 영 깨우사 <br>주님만 나를 세워 내 영 살게 하소서 <br>주님 내 안에 주님 내 안에 <br>내 안에 계시고 <br>주님 내 안에 주님 내 안에 <br>나를 세워 주소서 <br>언제나 내 모습 너무나 부끄러워 <br>무릎으로 주님께 기도로 가오니 <br>나홀로 서 있는 죽은 내 영 깨우사 <br>주님만 나를 세워 내 영 살게 하소서 <br>주님 내 안에 주님 내 안에 <br>내 안에 계시고 <br>주님 내 안에 주님 내 안에 <br>나를 세워 주소서 <br>주님 내 안에 주님 내 안에 <br>내 안에 계시고 <br>주님 내 안에 주님 내 안에 <br>나를 세워 주소서 <br>나를 세워 주소서 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="주님 내 안에 (Feat. 초롬)" label="주님 내 안에 (Feat. 초롬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최인혁/인생_한번/</id><title>최인혁 - 인생 한번 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D_%ED%95%9C%EB%B2%88/" title="최인혁 - 인생 한번 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[인생 한번 왔다가는 세상 <br>무얼 위해 살까 <br>영원한 내 집을 바라보며 <br>주를 위해 살리 <br>인생 끝이 나고 주께 가면 <br>주님 뭐라실까 <br>그 때 주님 칭찬 하시도록 <br>주를 위해 살리 <br>내 마음 내 능력 모두 주님께 드리리 <br>내 능력 내 소망 모두 드리리라 <br>인생 한번 왔다가는 세상 <br>무얼 위해 살까 <br>영원한 내 집을 바라보며 <br>주를 위해 살리 <br>인생 끝이 나고 주께 가면 <br>주님 뭐라실까 <br>그 때 주님 칭찬 하시도록 <br>주를 위해 살리 <br>내 마음 내 능력 모두 주님께 드리리 <br>내 능력 내 소망 모두 드리리라 <br>가라 세상 향해 못다한 <br>네 꿈 이뤄지리라 <br>세상이 널 감당치 못하리 <br>담대함으로 담대함으로 <br>가라 세상으로 <br>내 마음 내 능력 모두 주님께 드리리 <br>내 능력 내 소망 모두 드리리라 <br>모두 드리리라 모두 드리리라 <br>]]></content><category term="최인혁" label="최인혁"/><category term="인생 한번" label="인생 한번"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성민/몽유병_With_이소리/</id><title>감성민 - 몽유병 (With 이소리) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EB%AF%BC/%EB%AA%BD%EC%9C%A0%EB%B3%91_With_%EC%9D%B4%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC/" title="감성민 - 몽유병 (With 이소리) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 좀 더 깊은 꿈을 꾸어요 <br>꿈속에선 우리 함께 할 거예요 <br>현실의 모든 시간을 멈춰 <br>당신과 함께하는 영원을 꿈꿔요 <br>괜찮아요 <br>외롭지 않아요 <br>행복해요 <br>함께니까 <br>나는 어둡고도 고요한 <br>이곳을 떠나서 <br>깊은 꿈속으로 <br>당신과 난 빠져들어요 <br>수줍게 감은 나의 두 눈 위에 <br>당신의 숨결 <br>이보다 더 좋을 순 없어 <br>나 혼자 있던 악몽 속에는 <br>모든 것이 잠든 채 홀로 깨어 있어 <br>잊고 싶어서 잠이 들었죠 <br>꿈속에서는 우리 함께인 거죠 <br>나는 어둡고도 고요한 <br>이곳을 떠나서 <br>깊은 꿈속으로 <br>당신과 난 빠져들어요 <br>수줍게 감은 나의 두 눈 위에 <br>당신의 숨결 <br>이보다 더 좋을 순 없어 <br>나의 현실에선 항상 함께겠죠 <br>조금 더 사랑할 수 있어요 <br>어둡고도 고요한 <br>이곳을 떠나서 <br>깊은 꿈속으로 <br>당신과 난 빠져들어요 <br>수줍게 감은 나의 두 눈 위에 <br>당신의 숨결 <br>이보다 더 좋을 순 없어 <br>나의 현실에서는 <br>항상 함께하겠죠 <br>나의 현실에서 <br>난 깨지 않기를 바라죠 <br>]]></content><category term="감성민" label="감성민"/><category term="몽유병 (With 이소리)" label="몽유병 (With 이소리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성민/나만_남은_기억_With_이소리/</id><title>감성민 - 나만 남은 기억 (With 이소리) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EB%AF%BC/%EB%82%98%EB%A7%8C_%EB%82%A8%EC%9D%80_%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5_With_%EC%9D%B4%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC/" title="감성민 - 나만 남은 기억 (With 이소리) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그리움에 잠긴 채 잠은 안 오고 <br>머릿속 가득히 선명하던 너 <br>점점 더 흐릿해져 네 미소조차 <br>낯설어지면 난 어떡하나 <br>보고 싶다는 말 사랑한다는 말 <br>전부 표현되지 않아 <br>조금 더 애틋한 일렁이는 불꽃 <br>설명할 수 없어 <br>내 상상 속에서 너와 입 맞추고 <br>그 안에서 나올 수 없어 <br>오늘은 우리의 사랑한 기억에 <br>잠이 오질 않아 <br>보고 싶다는 말 사랑한다는 말 <br>전부 표현되지 않아 <br>조금 더 애틋한 일렁이는 불꽃 <br>설명할 수 없어 <br>너와 나의 기억이 <br>왜 지금에서 이렇게 <br>텅 빈 방 안처럼 <br>지독히도 쓸쓸하게 하네 <br>나만 남은 기억 <br>너만 없는 추억 <br>]]></content><category term="감성민" label="감성민"/><category term="나만 남은 기억 (With 이소리)" label="나만 남은 기억 (With 이소리)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리누/소중함을_몰랐었던/</id><title>리누 - 소중함을 몰랐었던 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:06:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:06:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%88%84/%EC%86%8C%EC%A4%91%ED%95%A8%EC%9D%84_%EB%AA%B0%EB%9E%90%EC%97%88%EB%8D%98/" title="리누 - 소중함을 몰랐었던 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뭐부터 해야 할지 모르겠어 <br>있을 때 잘하라는 말 <br>그 뜻을 이제야 알겠어 <br>평생 내 여자일 것 같았던 너와 <br>이렇게 쉽게 끝 날줄은 몰랐어 <br>사랑한다 널 사랑한다 <br>아무리 외쳐보아도 내겐 닿지 않는 말 <br>잘해준 게 하나도 없어서 <br>못 해줬던 게 기억에만 남아서 <br>곁에 항상 있어서 소중함을 몰랐었던 <br>내 자만을 용서하지는 마 <br>네가 떠난 후에야 난 깨달았어 <br>너 없인 하루도 난 살 순 없단 걸 <br>후회한다 너무 후회한다 <br>더 잘해주지 못한 내가 <br>너무나 원망스럽다 <br>잘해준 게 하나도 없어서 <br>못 해줬던 게 기억에만 남아서 <br>곁에 항상 있어서 소중함을 몰랐었던 <br>내 자만을 용서하지는 마 <br>사랑한다 말하면 네가 떠나갈까 봐 <br>보고 싶다 말하면 네가 멀어질까 봐 <br>못난 자존심만 세운 나를 <br>이런 나를 용서해줘 <br>그의 품에 안겨 있는 널 봤어 <br>예쁘더라 많이 행복해 보여 <br>익숙함에 젖어서 당연하게 느꼈었던 <br>내자만을 제발 용서해줘 <br>예쁘더라 정말 너 예쁘더라 <br>네가 많이 생각날 것 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="리누" label="리누"/><category term="소중함을 몰랐었던" label="소중함을 몰랐었던"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryuk_Kelevra_Joe/Blamed_Feat_Thomas_Prod_Lawrence_Yun/</id><title>Ryuk Kelevra Joe - Blamed (Feat. Thomas) (Prod. Lawrence Yun) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:14:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:14:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryuk_Kelevra_Joe/Blamed_Feat_Thomas_Prod_Lawrence_Yun/" title="Ryuk Kelevra Joe - Blamed (Feat. Thomas) (Prod. Lawrence Yun) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 감이 안잡힐때 <br>모두가 욕을 할때 <br>난 기다렸네 Errday <br>생색이 아냐 이건 절대 <br>무엇이 중요한걸 봤어 <br>다시 Track을 만들고서 <br>같은 Pattern을 깨버리기엔 충분해진 내 나침판도 <br>순수하던 마음일때는 그게 순서 이지 <br>But, 그것들을 넘어설떌 위해서 간다고 보면되 <br>고지는 너무나도 멀던데 <br>다 석연찮다고 욕을해 <br>고맙네 <br>작고도 큰 내방엔 많은 물감 자국들이 한켠에 <br>자리 잡고 있어 또한 봤을땐 그리 나쁜 배색들은 아니기에 <br>사실 내게 욕을 안한 사람은 없잖아 <br>안그래? <br>그게 내 크나큰 오기유발을 했네 <br>Like get the cane <br>솔직히 힘주면 다 되잖아 <br>나한테 욕할때 처럼 <br>하지말아 달라는게 아냐 <br>이겨낼꺼라 선전포고 You know? <br>이제 앨범과 음원이라는 수단으로 철저히 <br>사방에 연락을 돌려 빠르게 신고하듯이 일일이 <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>You ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Please Ill for me <br>Please, Please Ill for me <br>Keep ill for me Yeah I don't give a fuck <br>Please Ill for me <br>Please, Please Ill for me <br>그럴일없지 너희 때문에 관둘일 <br>I know, I know, I know, I know. <br>미워 죽겠지 다들 <br>와당와당 욕을 하고 흉을 보며 안된다 한들 <br>그리 믿어왔던게 싹다 <br>꺠져버려 거짓들로 만들어질 거라는 <br>내 약속들이 모두 진실이 되었음을 (선포) <br>듣기만해도 치와 두손이 벌벌 떨리던 언어들도 <br>내겐 값진 연료가 되네 <br>비록 연비가 최악이라도 <br>내게 애새끼 거론하고 인생사 입위에 오르내린 <br>몇몇 자식들은 잘 모르겠지 <br>갈길이 아직도 멀고 멀지 <br>잘봐둬 내가 얼마나 값비싸게 시간들을 보내는지 <br>몰상식이 필히 필요되는 상식이 되어가는 Timing <br>다시 처음 뮤비처럼 손가락은 내귀를 후며 <br>날 깎아내도 달게 받아들여 <br>Cuz, only for my 후손 <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>You ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Please Ill for me <br>Please, Please Ill for me <br>Keep ill for me Yeah I don't give a fuck <br>Please Ill for me <br>Please, Please Ill for me <br>그럴일없지 너희 때문에 관둘일 <br>더 씹어줘 날 <br>난 그 정도론 모자라 <br>물어 뜯어 날 <br>더 계속 물어 뜯어 날 <br>화풀이야 난 <br>난 니들 화풀이잖아 <br>상관없어 다 <br>난 가면 속에 이들과 겸상안해 <br>면전에 당겨 활시위 <br>많은 고비를 넘긴 뒤 <br>얻은건 악만 남은 입 <br>달콤한 구슬림 <br>보단 내겐 흉이 더 달어 <br>몸에 좋은게 입에는 쓴법 <br>할 시간 이 없어 감정소모 <br>이 가사에 너흴 쓸 정도로 <br>내가 니들 눈에 좋고 안좋고를 떠나서 <br>어리고 꼰대고 여자고 남자고 받아 들여 <br>진짜로 실감이 와닫더라 <br>꺠진 맨탈들의 잔해들과 뒷말들이 <br>To be overfull &amp; all of them <br>근데 그저 불과 <br>몇개월전 몇일전 몇시간전 일수 있지 <br>You know what I'm saying <br>과거라는건 무섭지 <br>모두가 이치라는것을 기억해 <br>So I 피하지 않을꺼야 <br>마치 머리에 삿갓쓴 나그네 <br>비든 눈이든 우박이든 맞고봐 <br>의의를 뒀네 <br>내가 있음에 <br>내게만 부나봐 <br>오늘 날씨는 칼바람 <br>한걸음도 가지못해 <br>지금 여긴 사막의 밤 <br>칼바람에 맞서는 내 몽둥이는 뭉툭해 <br>손에 쥔게 무엇이든 매사에 <br>나는 모두를 위해서 <br>내가 과녁이 되고 많은 사람들이 활을 당기게둬 <br>점차 다가올 미랜 내가 그때 사람들의 등을 두들겨 <br>두들겨대는 그 입으로는 나를 못죽여 <br>이리와 날찔러 <br>부러뜨려 나는 굽어지지 않어 <br>이거야 니네가 원한거? <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>You ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Ill for me? <br>Yeh, I want it <br>Please Ill for me <br>Please, Please Ill for me <br>Keep ill for me Yeah I don't give a fuck <br>Please Ill for me <br>Please, Please Ill for me <br>그럴일없지 너희 때문에 관둘일]]></content><category term="Ryuk Kelevra Joe" label="Ryuk Kelevra Joe"/><category term="Blamed (Feat. Thomas) (Prod. Lawrence Yun)" label="Blamed (Feat. Thomas) (Prod. Lawrence Yun)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이광조/누구라도_그러하듯이_2017/</id><title>이광조 - 누구라도 그러하듯이 (2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:16:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:16:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B4%91%EC%A1%B0/%EB%88%84%EA%B5%AC%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%AC%ED%95%98%EB%93%AF%EC%9D%B4_2017/" title="이광조 - 누구라도 그러하듯이 (2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누구라도 그러하듯이 <br>길을 걸으면 생각이 난다 <br>마주 보며 속삭이던 <br>지난 날의 얼굴들이 <br>꽃잎처럼 펼쳐져 간다 <br>소중했던 많은 날들을 <br>빗물처럼 흘려 보내고 <br>밀려오는 그리움에 <br>나는 이제 돌아다 본다 <br>가득 찬 눈물 너머로 <br>아 아 <br>누구라도 그러하듯이 <br>거울을 보면 생각이 난다 <br>어린 시절 오고 가던 <br>골목길의 추억들이 <br>동그랗게 맴돌아 간다 <br>가슴속의 하얀 꿈들을 <br>어느 하루 잃어 버리고 <br>솟아나는 아쉬움에 <br>나는 이제 돌아다 본다 <br>가득 찬 눈물 너머로 <br>아 아 <br>누구라도 그러하듯이 <br>눈을 감으면 생각이 난다 <br>헤어지던 아픔보다 <br>처음 만난 순간 들이 <br>잔잔하게 물결이 된다 <br>눈이 내린 그 겨울날 <br>첫사랑을 묻어 버리고 <br>젖어드는 외로움에 <br>나는 이제 돌아다 본다 <br>넘치는 눈물 너머로 <br>아 아 <br>누구라도 그러하듯이 <br>창가에 앉아 하늘을 본다 <br>떠다니는 구름처럼 <br>날아가는 새들처럼 <br>내 마음도 부풀어 가네 <br>어디선가 나를 부르는 <br>아름다운 사랑의 노래 <br>지평선을 바라보며 <br>나는 이제 떠나련다 <br>저 푸른 하늘 넘어 <br>아 아 <br>]]></content><category term="이광조" label="이광조"/><category term="누구라도 그러하듯이 (2017)" label="누구라도 그러하듯이 (2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이광조/괜찮다_2017/</id><title>이광조 - 괜찮다 (2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:16:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:16:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B4%91%EC%A1%B0/%EA%B4%9C%EC%B0%AE%EB%8B%A4_2017/" title="이광조 - 괜찮다 (2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[또 하루가 시작됐는지 <br>햇살이 눈이 부시네 <br>어제도 못 다한 말을 남기고 <br>당신은 떠나갔네 <br>미련들이 남은 것인지 <br>가슴이 답답해지네 <br>훌훌 털어내고 방을 나설 때 <br>코끝이 찡해오네 <br>지난 일은 지나간 거지 <br>곱씹어 되뇌어보네 <br>또 하루가 저물면 <br>생각이 멈춰질까 <br>거울 속 또 다른 날 보며 <br>딱히 할 말도 없지만 <br>괜찮다 괜찮아 하네 <br>지난 일은 지나간 거지 <br>곱씹어 되뇌어보네 <br>또 하루가 저물면 <br>생각이 멈춰질까 <br>거울 속 또 다른 날 보며 <br>딱히 할 말도 없지만 <br>괜찮다 괜찮다 하네 <br>괜찮다 괜찮아 괜찮다 <br>]]></content><category term="이광조" label="이광조"/><category term="괜찮다 (2017)" label="괜찮다 (2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이광조/엄마_2017_Duet_전준한/</id><title>이광조 - 엄마 (2017) (Duet 전준한) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:16:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:16:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B4%91%EC%A1%B0/%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88_2017_Duet_%EC%A0%84%EC%A4%80%ED%95%9C/" title="이광조 - 엄마 (2017) (Duet 전준한) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[상고머리 긁적대던 내 어린 시절 <br>뭐가 그리 궁금했을까 동네 한 바퀴 <br>이웃집의 누렁이 짖어대면 <br>깜짝 놀라 멈칫 숨었다가 <br>어흥하고 도망쳤었지 <br>동구 밖에 당산나무 그네를 타고 <br>풀을 뜯는 염소 쫒다 발이 <br>엉켜 넘어졌었지 <br>서산에 해가 뉘엿 질 때면 <br>저 멀리 뚝방 위로 어렴 풋 <br>엄마의 손짓 <br>왜 나왔니 집에 가자 하셨지 <br>동구 밖에 당산나무 그네를 타고 <br>풀을 뜯는 염소 쫒다 발이 <br>엉켜 넘어졌었지 <br>서산에 해가 뉘엿 질 때면 <br>저 멀리 뚝방 위로 어렴 풋 <br>엄마의 손짓 <br>왜 나왔니 집에 가자 하셨지 <br>그 목소리 그 손길이 그립다 <br>]]></content><category term="이광조" label="이광조"/><category term="엄마 (2017) (Duet 전준한)" label="엄마 (2017) (Duet 전준한)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이광조/내가_그대_얼마나_사랑했는지_2017/</id><title>이광조 - 내가 그대 얼마나 사랑했는지 (2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:16:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:16:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B4%91%EC%A1%B0/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_%EC%96%BC%EB%A7%88%EB%82%98_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%96%88%EB%8A%94%EC%A7%80_2017/" title="이광조 - 내가 그대 얼마나 사랑했는지 (2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대가 떠난 지 몇 년이 지났지만 <br>난 아직 그대를 지우지 못 했네요 <br>아 그댄 나를 잊고 살지 몰라도 <br>내가 그대 얼마나 사랑 했는지 <br>그대는 아나요 <br>이젠 모두 지나간 일이지만 <br>이별을 이기고 살아간다는 일이 <br>나에겐 너무나 모진 아픔이네요 <br>아 내가 그댈 잊고 살 수 있을까 <br>얼마나 더 많은 시간이 지나야 <br>그대를 지울까 <br>얼마나 더 울어야 잊혀 질까 <br>아 그댄 나를 잊고 살지 몰라도 <br>내가 그대 얼마나 사랑 했는지 <br>그대는 아나요 <br>이젠 모두 지나간 일이지만 <br>끝내 우린 이루지 못할 <br>사랑을 꿈꾸었던 가요 <br>내가 그대 얼마나 사랑 했는지 <br>]]></content><category term="이광조" label="이광조"/><category term="내가 그대 얼마나 사랑했는지 (2017)" label="내가 그대 얼마나 사랑했는지 (2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/베비_Beby/Stars/</id><title>베비 (Beby) - Stars - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:17:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:17:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%A0%EB%B9%84_Beby/Stars/" title="베비 (Beby) - Stars - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 생각하지 않을 수가 없는 <br>밤 하늘의 별 쏟아지는 날에 <br>몇 광년 전 흘러나온 빛이 <br>꼭 우리 같아 <br>어둠 속 빛나는 별이 <br>사진으로도 담겨지지 않네 <br>오늘따라 아련하게 보여서 <br>한참을 나 멍하니 바라보다 <br>그리워 뜨거운 눈물이 흐른다 <br>꿈같던 사랑 <br>이젠 다 보낼게 저 별에 <br>꿈에서라도 다시 만나기를 바래 <br>네 생각에 오늘도 눈물 짓지만 <br>부디 너는 행복하기를 <br>Star is bright without you tonight <br>우리가 했던 사랑만큼 빛나 <br>아름다웠던 너와 나의 사랑 <br>너도 나와 같은 별을 보고 있진 않을까 <br>이제는 함께 볼 순 없겠지만 <br>꿈같던 사랑 <br>이젠 다 보낼게 저 별에 <br>꿈에서라도 다시 만나기를 바래 <br>꿈같던 추억 다 보낼게 <br>너도 나와 같은 별을 보고 있기를 바래 <br>네 생각에 오늘도 눈물 짓지만 <br>부디 너는 행복하기를 <br>Star is bright without you tonight <br>]]></content><category term="베비 (Beby)" label="베비 (Beby)"/><category term="Stars" label="Stars"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임수연/Color_Of_My_Life/</id><title>임수연 - Color Of My Life - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:17:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:17:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%88%98%EC%97%B0/Color_Of_My_Life/" title="임수연 - Color Of My Life - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The very first time <br>I met you in town <br>You were wearing the lobster hat <br>I still make fun of <br>Yeah I was shy <br>and you were a goof ball <br>You made me look straight <br>at the wall <br>You had the perfect smile <br>I wanted to make you mine <br>No one could ever take me <br>to another world <br>Your voice is my love song <br>You are the cherry <br>on the top of the cake <br>You are the reason <br>for every move I make <br>So here is my confession <br>Will you be my lover forever <br>You We'll be floating <br>in this world together <br>You I will try for your love <br>'Cause you are the color my life <br>Yea we're swaying like palm trees <br>in the blue sky with a warm breeze <br>Hey you have a perfect smile <br>I can't believe that you're mine <br>No one could ever take me <br>to another world <br>Your voice is my love song <br>You are cherry <br>on the top of the cake <br>You are the reason <br>for every move I make <br>So here is my confession <br>Will you be my lover forever <br>You We'll be floating <br>in this world together <br>You I will try for your love <br>'Cause you are the color <br>of my <br>The way you move <br>The way you smile <br>The way you look into my eyes <br>The way you touch <br>The way you blush <br>The way you make me feel your love <br>You We'll be floating <br>in this world together <br>You I will try for your love <br>'Cause you are the color <br>of my life <br>]]></content><category term="임수연" label="임수연"/><category term="Color Of My Life" label="Color Of My Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임수연/담배/</id><title>임수연 - 담배 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:17:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:17:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%88%98%EC%97%B0/%EB%8B%B4%EB%B0%B0/" title="임수연 - 담배 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[답답하게 짜증나게 굴지 마 <br>깔끔하게 네 생각 안 나게 떠나가 줘 <br>한두 가지보다 많은 헤어질 이유들 <br>너도 알고 있는데 모르는 척 아닌 척 <br>사랑이고 정이고 이제 와서 <br>네 몸짓들도 지겹다는 게 느껴져 <br>찢겨지고 무너졌단 말 <br>내게 늘어놓지 마 <br>네 감정 내 책임 아냐 <br>먼저 일어설게 나 <br>보기 싫어 <br>쓸쓸한 네 표정도 지긋지긋해 <br>만지지 말고 얘기하자 <br>손 닿는 것도 이상하니까 <br>사랑이란 건 <br>짧고 또 허무하단 거 <br>지겹도록 네가 피워대던 담배 <br>그 연기같이 사라져 줘 <br>듣기 싫어 <br>익숙한 네 목소리도 싫증만 나 <br>만날 일 없게 정리하자 <br>시간이 아까우니까 <br>사랑이란 건 <br>짧고 또 허무하단 거 <br>지겹도록 네가 피워대던 담배 <br>그 연기같이 사라져 줘 <br>사라져 줘 <br>사라져 줘 <br>]]></content><category term="임수연" label="임수연"/><category term="담배" label="담배"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임수연/모래성/</id><title>임수연 - 모래성 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:17:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:17:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%88%98%EC%97%B0/%EB%AA%A8%EB%9E%98%EC%84%B1/" title="임수연 - 모래성 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[끝없이 걸었어 <br>널 잊을 수 있을까 봐 <br>시간이 갈수록 어려워져도 <br>무너진 약속을 <br>너도 아쉬워할까 봐 <br>밤이 다 지나도록 <br>이런저런 미련에 <br>쌓았다가 부쉈다 <br>굳혔다 흩트렸다 <br>미웠다가 슬펐다 <br>다시 그리웠다 <br>네가 모래성이면 <br>다 부숴 없앨 텐데 <br>쌓지도 않을 텐데 <br>커져만 가는 후회에 <br>아주 오래 전이면 <br>보내지 않을 텐데 <br>내가 좀 더 잘할 텐데 <br>터질 것 같은 맘에 <br>잠 못 들어 난 <br>그때 널 떠난 건 <br>내가 빛을 잃을까 봐 <br>너의 별이던 <br>내가 짐이 될까 봐 <br>이뤄질 수 없단 <br>이유만 늘어가잖아 <br>같은 그 이유로 <br>이어졌던 너와 내가 <br>쌓았다가 부쉈다 <br>굳혔다 흩트렸다 <br>미웠다가 슬펐다 <br>다시 그리웠다 <br>네가 모래성이면 <br>다 부숴 없앨 텐데 <br>쌓지도 않을 텐데 <br>커져만 가는 후회에 <br>아주 오래 전이면 <br>보내지 않을 텐데 <br>내가 좀 더 잘할 텐데 <br>터질 것 같은 맘에 <br>잠 못 들어 난 <br>네가 없어지지 않아서 <br>모두 선명하게 남아서 <br>너에게 다시 닿을 수 있다면 <br>아님 네 기억들이 닳아서 <br>흩어져 다 흐려졌으면 <br>널 다시 보게 된다면 <br>너에게 물을 텐데 <br>이젠 날 지웠냐고 <br>나 없이 안 된다던 <br>너의 웃음이 보이면 <br>보낼 수 있을 텐데 <br>부수고 없앨 텐데 <br>쌓여만 가던 모래성 같은 너를 <br>]]></content><category term="임수연" label="임수연"/><category term="모래성" label="모래성"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/케미라이트_Chemilight/또_만나요/</id><title>케미라이트 (Chemilight) - 또 만나요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:17:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:17:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BC%80%EB%AF%B8%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%ED%8A%B8_Chemilight/%EB%98%90_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94/" title="케미라이트 (Chemilight) - 또 만나요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 언제 또 만날까 <br>다시 만날 날이 기대돼요 <br>비록 오늘 처음 봤어도 <br>다시 또 보고파요 <br>다음 만날 때는 우리 <br>오늘보다 반가울 거예요 <br>그때까지 더 좋은 일만 <br>생기길 바랄게요 <br>우리 또 만나요 굿바이 <br>우리 또 만나요 사요나라 <br>우리 또 만나요 짜이찌엔 <br>우리 또 만나요 잘가 <br>다음 만날 때는 우리 <br>오늘보다 반가울 거예요 <br>그때까지 더 좋은 일만 <br>생기길 바랄게요 <br>우리 또 만나요 굿바이 <br>우리 또 만나요 사요나라 <br>우리 또 만나요 짜이찌엔 <br>우리 또 만나요 잘가 <br>우리 또 만나요 굿바이 <br>우리 또 만나요 사요나라 <br>우리 또 만나요 짜이찌엔 <br>우리 또 만나요 잘가 <br>우리 또 만나요 잘가 <br>]]></content><category term="케미라이트 (Chemilight)" label="케미라이트 (Chemilight)"/><category term="또 만나요" label="또 만나요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/디자인트루/You__I/</id><title>디자인트루 - You &amp; I - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:17:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:17:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%94%94%EC%9E%90%EC%9D%B8%ED%8A%B8%EB%A3%A8/You__I/" title="디자인트루 - You &amp; I - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 나의 하루 또 했던 얘기들 <br>몇 번이고 들어줄 사람 <br>뭐가 그리 좋은지 <br>웃는 일만 많았던 <br>그때 난 행복한 사람 <br>늘 사랑이란 내 입모양을 <br>변치 않고 지켜줄 사람 <br>서로 많이 달라도 <br>걱정뿐인 사람 <br>영원이라 믿었어 <br>Remember You &amp; I <br>우리 사랑하던 날들과 <br>너로 인해 빛나던 하루 <br>난 매일 그날에 살아 <br>Remember You &amp; I <br>그럴 수만 있다면 <br>다시 돌아갈 수만 있다면 <br>오랜 그때 우리 <br>너 먼저 용기 내줄래 <br>여기서 뭐라도 해봐 <br>여전히 나에겐 <br>여전히 나에겐 너여야만 해 <br>늘 우리 사이 두려운 것들 <br>다른 사람들의 시선이 <br>부럽기만한 사람 <br>좋아 보일 사람 <br>그때 난 그런 척 <br>난 안녕이란 니 이별에도 <br>끝내 물어보지 않았던 <br>지켜내지도 못할 <br>약속뿐인 사람 <br>Remember You &amp; I <br>Remember You &amp; I <br>우리 사랑하던 날들과 <br>너로 인해 빛나던 하루 <br>난 매일 그날에 살아 <br>Remember You &amp; I <br>그럴 수만 있다면 <br>다시 돌아갈 수만 있다면 <br>오랜 그때 우리 <br>너 먼저 용기 내줄래 <br>여기서 뭐라도 해봐 <br>여전히 나에겐 <br>여전히 나에겐 너여야만 해 <br>]]></content><category term="디자인트루" label="디자인트루"/><category term="You &amp; I" label="You &amp; I"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요_천사/색칠놀이/</id><title>동요 천사 - 색칠놀이 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:17:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:17:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94_%EC%B2%9C%EC%82%AC/%EC%83%89%EC%B9%A0%EB%86%80%EC%9D%B4/" title="동요 천사 - 색칠놀이 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[색칠놀이를 해봅시다 <br>여러 색깔 크레용을 준비해보자 <br><br>도화지 위에 선 그리고 <br>빈 칸을 색깔로 채워봐요 <br><br>정말 재밌는 색칠놀이 <br>시간도 잘 간다 색칠놀이 <br><br>색칠놀이를 해봅시다 <br>여러 색깔 크레용을 준비해보자 <br><br>도화지 위에 선 그리고 <br>빈 칸을 색깔로 채워봐요 <br><br>정말 재밌는 색칠놀이 <br>시간도 잘 간다 색칠놀이]]></content><category term="동요 천사" label="동요 천사"/><category term="색칠놀이" label="색칠놀이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다미/잭과_콩나무/</id><title>다미 - 잭과 콩나무 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:18:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:18:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%AF%B8/%EC%9E%AD%EA%B3%BC_%EC%BD%A9%EB%82%98%EB%AC%B4/" title="다미 - 잭과 콩나무 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[젖소와 바꾼 신기한 콩 <br>커다란 나무가 됐죠 <br>콩 나무 타고 성으로 <br>거인의 보물 가져왔죠 <br>부자가 된 잭은 놀다가 <br>보물을 모두 잃었죠 <br><br>잭은 또 콩나무 타고 <br>신기한 하프 가져왔죠 <br>잠깬 거인은 쫓아오고 <br>콩나무는 쓰러졌죠 <br>거인의 성은 사라지고 <br>잭은 열심히 일했죠]]></content><category term="다미" label="다미"/><category term="잭과 콩나무" label="잭과 콩나무"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다미/아기돼지_삼형제/</id><title>다미 - 아기돼지 삼형제 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:18:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:18:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%AF%B8/%EC%95%84%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%BC%EC%A7%80_%EC%82%BC%ED%98%95%EC%A0%9C/" title="다미 - 아기돼지 삼형제 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꿀꿀꿀 꿀꿀 돼지 삼형제 <br>꿀꿀꿀 꿀꿀 집을 지어요 <br>난난 짚으로 집 지을래 <br>첫째 돼지 꿀꿀꿀꿀 <br>난난 나무집 지을래 <br>둘째 돼지 꿀꿀꿀꿀 <br>난 벽돌로 집 지을래 <br>셋째 돼지 꿀꿀꿀꿀 <br><br>살금살금 배고픈 늑대가 <br>후후 불어 집을 날렸죠 (후) <br>첫째 둘째 놀라 도망 나왔죠 <br>튼튼한 벽돌집에 숨자 <br>늑대는 굴뚝으로 들어갔죠 <br>뜨거운 솥에 빠졌죠 <br>아기돼지 삼형제 새집을 지었죠 <br>꿀꿀꿀꿀꿀꿀꿀]]></content><category term="다미" label="다미"/><category term="아기돼지 삼형제" label="아기돼지 삼형제"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DNFL/Said/</id><title>DNFL - Said - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:18:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:18:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DNFL/Said/" title="DNFL - Said - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[aye ya 어젯밤엔 너무 좋았어 <br>aye ya 밤새 너랑 같이 있어서 <br>aye ya 오늘도 나랑 있어줘 <br>aye ya 잠깐 갔다 올게 돈 벌러 <br>편하게 있어도 돼 너의 집이잖아 <br>어제 우리가 그렸던 <br>그림이 떠오르잖아 <br>난 일에 집중을 못 해 <br>내 손이 널 찾아 <br>내 손이 널 찾아 <br>내 몸이 널 찾아 <br>시간은 너랑 만 만나면 빨라져 <br>난 그게 싫어서 <br>시간을 사기로 생각을 했어 <br>난 그래서 더 벌어 돈을 더 <br>나중에 우리가 육체를 초월해 <br>서로가 정신을 나누면 <br>그때는 모든 걸 버리고 떠나자 <br>너랑 나 둘만의 장소로 <br>aye ya 그때 까지 좀 <br>참고 기다려 줘 <br>aye ya 기다려 줘 aye ya 음 <br>우리가 그리던 그림은 지금껏 <br>한번도 못 봤던 거야 ya <br>못 봤던 거야 ya <br>음 니 대답이 궁금해 난 <br>음 니 대답이 궁금해 난 <br>음 니 대답이 궁금해 난 <br>음 니 대답이 궁금해 난 <br>aye ya 흘러가는 시간이 <br>멈춰줬으면 해 <br>눈 깜빡이면 어제로 돌아가졌으면 해 <br>oh yeah <br>나는 내 눈앞에 니가 서 있었음 해 <br>나를 바라보고 있는 니가 <br>웃고 있었으면 해 oh yeah <br>우리에 몸이 잠시 멀리 떨어져 있어도 <br>흐르는 시간을 이대로 멈출 순 없어도 <br>그 자리에서 조금만 더 <br>참고 기다려줘 aye ya <br>부정 못해 고독 안은 날 aye <br>절망이란 늪에 빠진 날 aye <br>헤어나올 용기가 없어 난 aye <br>아무 말 말고 안아줄래 날 aye <br>고개를 돌려 너를 안 봐도 aye <br>항상 그랬듯 날 안아줘 aye <br>의지하는 모든 것 들이 날 떠밀어내도 <br>넌 나에게 손을 내밀어줘 aye ya <br>우리가 다시 만날 그때가 오면 ya <br>내가 널 찾아 갈 테니 <br>조금만 더 참고 날 믿어줘 <br>]]></content><category term="DNFL" label="DNFL"/><category term="Said" label="Said"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/익토미_IKTOMI/INTRO_Narr_김장훈/</id><title>익토미 (IKTOMI) - INTRO (Narr. 김장훈) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:19:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:19:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B5%ED%86%A0%EB%AF%B8_IKTOMI/INTRO_Narr_%EA%B9%80%EC%9E%A5%ED%9B%88/" title="익토미 (IKTOMI) - INTRO (Narr. 김장훈) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[제아무리 많은 시간이 흘러도 <br>떠나보내지 못해 <br>갇혀 사는 시간이 있다 <br>누구를 떠나보내던 날과 <br>하지 말았으면 좋았을 일들 <br>누군가 떠나가던 날과 <br>하지못해 아쉬웠던 일들 <br>그 때 그 시간을 향한 한 걸음에는 <br>먹먹한 눈물도 후회도 흐린 먹구름도 <br>웃음도 행복도 설렘도 맑은 하늘도 <br>낡아버린 시간이란 <br>이다지도 심란하고 숭고한 것 <br>때론 너를 향해 내딛던 <br>최초의 한 발자국 같은 것 <br>많은 달이 스쳐갔다 <br>나는 늘 가던 카페에 들러 <br>늘 앉던 자리에 앉아 <br>언제 떠날지 모를 기억을 <br>노심초사 붙들어맨다 <br>]]></content><category term="익토미 (IKTOMI)" label="익토미 (IKTOMI)"/><category term="INTRO (Narr. 김장훈)" label="INTRO (Narr. 김장훈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로큰마인드/Backyard/</id><title>브로큰마인드 - Backyard - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:19:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:19:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%ED%81%B0%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C/Backyard/" title="브로큰마인드 - Backyard - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>서쪽에 해가 떨어지면 <br>WE HANGING OUT IN THE BACKYARD <br>IN THE BACKYARD <br>누구든 여기 오면 우리랑 밤새 춤쳐 <br>AND WE NEVER <br>EVER LEAVE THE BACKYARD <br>WE HAVE NEVER BEEN IN HOLLYWOOD <br>어두운 CONCRETE 안에 <br>숨어서 우린 춤춰 <br>WE DON'T GO TO CLUBS <br>DON'T NEED MONEYSHOTS <br>그냥 우리 힙합은 내 무기 <br>AND WE WILL NEVER LEAVE THIS PLACE <br>여긴 리듬이 가득 찬 <br>색깔이 다양한 PLACE <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>차갑고 눈빛엔 격노가 가득 거리는 <br>회색 분위기 싸늘해 <br>YOU HAVE SEEN IT BEFORE AIGHT <br>밤 되면 COLORFUL ALL NIGHT <br>MOTHERFUCKERS WANNA GO <br>BANG BITCHES <br>OR MAKE A DAMN BUSINESS <br>우린 반대로 딴대로 맘대로 <br>NOT IN IT <br>NEVER DOING LAST MINUTE <br>NOT IN IT <br>NEVER DOING LAST MINUTE <br>AND WHEN THE LIGHT <br>꺼질 때면 <br>BABY WHEN THE NIGHT <br>깊어질 때면 <br>WE TAKE A RIDE TO THE NEXT CORNER <br>ONE HIT FOR MA BRAIN AND <br>내 영혼은 떠나 <br>WE HAVE NEVER BEEN IN HOLLYWOOD <br>어두운 CONCRETE 안에 <br>숨어서 우린 춤춰 <br>WE DON'T GO TO CLUBS <br>DON'T NEED MONEYSHOTS <br>그냥 우리 힙합은 내 무기 <br>AND WE WILL NEVER LEAVE THIS PLACE <br>여긴 리듬이 가득 찬 <br>색깔이 다양한 PLACE <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>MAKE MONEY MONEY <br>MAKE MONEY MONEY MONEY <br>MAKE MONEY MONEY <br>MAKE MONEY MONEY MONEY <br>MAKE MONEY MONEY <br>MAKE MONEY MONEY MONEY <br>MAKE MONEY MONEY <br>MAKE MONEY MONEY MONEY <br>AND WE WILL NEVER LEAVE THIS PLACE <br>여긴 리듬이 가득 찬 <br>색깔이 다양한 PLACE <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>여긴 우리가 왕 밖엔 NOBODY <br>]]></content><category term="브로큰마인드" label="브로큰마인드"/><category term="Backyard" label="Backyard"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로큰마인드/아홉시/</id><title>브로큰마인드 - 아홉시 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:19:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:19:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%ED%81%B0%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C/%EC%95%84%ED%99%89%EC%8B%9C/" title="브로큰마인드 - 아홉시 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여긴 밤길이 밝아 대낮은 짧아 <br>Imma motherfuckin killah <br>비트 위 미쳐 <br>우리 동네 매일 밤 파란 불 비춰 <br>칼날이 목에 들어와도 쉿 <br>나는 못 본척해 <br>COZ I DONT GIVA SHIT HELLO <br>YELLOW GHETTO FELLOW <br>불상한 놈 <br>WHY U WALK IN THE SHADOW <br>어둠속을 직진 친구들은 <br>몽땅 고3때 일진 <br>떠들지 마 네가 뭘 알아 <br>우리 동네 여자들은 <br>다 몸 팔아 돈벌이에 미쳐 <br>나는 모든 게 꼴 보기 싫어 <br>여긴 밤길이 밝아 대낮은 짧아 <br>Nobody is welcome here <br>아침 9시 여긴 텅 비어 <br>우리 동네 9시 거리에 아무도 9시 <br>아침 햇살 9시 모두가 깊은 잠 9시 <br>우리 동네 9시 아무도 거리에 9시 <br>아침 햇살 9시 모두가 깊은 잠 9시 <br>거지 같은 삶 누가 살고 싶댔어 <br>모두가 우리 탓 너네 권력 위해서 <br>U TAKE WHAT WE GOT 우린 바닥 <br>FUCKING 반항아 <br>너는 감당 할수 있겠어 Tres Records <br>어둠을 뚫고서 <br>거리를 쑤셔 눈 깔어 <br>MOTHERFUCKER 뭐 하러 훑어 <br>여긴 우리도 꿈꿔 <br>밤에 불 질러 놓고선 <br>춤줘 빤짝이는 거릴 보면 <br>휘발류로 덮고 싶어 <br>fuck all highclass people <br>다들 바닥으로 끌어당겨 <br>Nobody is welcome here <br>아침 9시 여긴 텅 비어 <br>우리 동네 9시 거리에 아무도 9시 <br>아침 햇살 9시 모두가 깊은 잠 9시 <br>우리 동네 9시 아무도 거리에 9시 <br>아침 햇살 9시 모두가 깊은 잠 9시 <br>어두운 거리들이 익숙한 우리 <br>익숙한 우리 <br>달빛이 비쳐주는 밤길을 같이 걸어 <br>우린 춤춰 밤새도록 다음날 <br>아침까지 이건 우리 동네 9시 9시 <br>우리 동네 9시 거리에 아무도 9시 <br>아침 햇살 9시 모두가 깊은 잠 9시 <br>우리 동네 9시 아무도 거리에 9시 <br>아침 햇살 9시 모두가 깊은 잠 9시 <br>]]></content><category term="브로큰마인드" label="브로큰마인드"/><category term="아홉시" label="아홉시"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로큰마인드/INTRO_Incanation/</id><title>브로큰마인드 - INTRO:Incanation - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:19:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:19:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%ED%81%B0%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B8%EB%93%9C/INTRO_Incanation/" title="브로큰마인드 - INTRO:Incanation - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어두운 골목을 뚫어 <br>바람을 타는 천사 <br>피땀과 눈물들을 <br>가슴에 담은 희망으로 덮자 <br>깃발을 뽑아 넓게 휘두르며 <br>힙합을 살리러 <br>한 손엔 MIC 가운데 손가락 <br>TRES RECORDS 등을 지켜 <br>BROKNMIND 다시 태어나도 <br>관객을 위하여 <br>앵콜에 화음 맞춰 <br>MOTHERFUCKER 이겨내 <br>사복 입은 정신병자 달려라 <br>BROKNMIND Hater들은 옆에 재끼고 <br>밝은 미래로 나가자 <br>사복 입은 정신병자 달려라 <br>BROKNMIND 비바람 쳐도 <br>지진이 나도 태풍처럼 해치워 <br>]]></content><category term="브로큰마인드" label="브로큰마인드"/><category term="INTRO:Incanation" label="INTRO:Incanation"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dall_달/고백/</id><title>Dall (달) - 고백 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:19:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:19:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dall_%EB%8B%AC/%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1/" title="Dall (달) - 고백 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니 옆자리가 아니어도 돼 <br>난 충분해 이렇게 마주 보는 걸로 <br>매일매일 만나지 않아도 <br>꿀처럼 달달하지 않아도 돼 <br>소소한 얘기 나눈 걸로 만족해 <br>손잡고 걷지 않아도 <br>같이 걷기만 해도 좋아 <br>손끝이 살며시 스치기만 해도 <br>온몸이 떨려와 짜릿짜릿해 <br>이런 내 맘 꽁꽁 숨긴 채 <br>고백하지 않을 거에요 <br>욕심내지 않아요 <br>가깝지도 않은 <br>그렇다고 멀지도 않은 <br>우리 사이 지금처럼만 <br>그래 딱 거기까지만 <br>내 표정 눈빛 말투 애틋해 <br>내 눈에 하트가 막 가득해 <br>진짜 내 속마음이 그래 <br>티 내지 않을래 <br>한걸음 물러서 잘 숨겨둘게 <br>잠들기 전에 전화해도 돼 <br>까만 밤 이불 속에서 듣고 싶어 <br>내 귓가에 속삭여줄래 <br>나를 녹여줄 수 있는 건 <br>달콤한 니 목소리뿐 <br>그거면 돼 다른 건 안 바래 <br>고백하지 않을 거에요 <br>욕심내지 않아요 <br>가깝지도 않은 <br>그렇다고 멀지도 않은 <br>우리 사이 지금처럼만 <br>그래 딱 거기까지만 <br>쳐다볼래 몰래 <br>니 주윌 맴돌래 <br>혹시 내 맘 알아챘다면 <br>그냥 모른 척해줘 <br>고백하지 않을 거에요 <br>욕심내지 않아요 <br>가깝지도 않은 <br>그렇다고 멀지도 않은 <br>우리 사이 지금처럼만 <br>그래 딱 거기까지만 <br>]]></content><category term="Dall (달)" label="Dall (달)"/><category term="고백" label="고백"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/크나큰/해_달_별/</id><title>크나큰 - 해, 달, 별 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:22:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:22:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%AC%EB%82%98%ED%81%B0/%ED%95%B4_%EB%8B%AC_%EB%B3%84/" title="크나큰 - 해, 달, 별 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[애써 괜찮은 척 했어 <br>아니 괜찮을 줄 알았어 <br>시간이 지나면 <br>희미하게 곧 사라질 것 같았어 <br>밤이 오면 달처럼 넌 떠오르고 <br>우리 추억이 별처럼 빛나서 <br>눈 감으려 해도 피해보려 해도 <br>계속해 날 비추고 있어 <br>내 전부를 다해 사랑했던 네가 <br>떠나간 그 순간부터 난 아무것도 <br>할 수가 없는데 <br>어떻게 해야 해 난 <br>아무리 벗어나려 해봐도 <br>멀어지려 해봐도 <br>끝없이 너의 주위를 맴돌아 <br>시간이 더 지나도 널 잊으려 해봐도 <br>너를 지울 수 없어 <br>You're my Sun woo woo <br>You're like the Moon woo woo <br>밤 하늘 가득히 <br>아름답게 빛나는 넌 해 달 별 <br>하루 이틀 시간이 지나갈수록 <br>네가 더 보고 싶어 <br>너도 나와 같은 달을 보고 있을까 <br>하늘에 널 그려 본다 <br>내 전부를 다해 사랑했던 네가 <br>떠나간 그 순간부터 난 아무것도 <br>할 수가 없는데 <br>어떻게 해야 해 난 <br>아무리 벗어나려 해봐도 <br>멀어지려 해봐도 <br>끝없이 너의 주위를 맴돌아 <br>시간이 더 지나도 널 잊으려 해봐도 <br>너를 지울 수 없어 <br>You're my Sun woo woo <br>You're like the Moon woo woo <br>밤 하늘 가득히 <br>아름답게 빛나는 넌 해 달 별 <br>언젠가는 나도 널 잊을 수 있을까 <br>언제쯤이면 널 지울 수 있을까 <br>해가 지고 달이 뜨면 <br>희미하던 추억이 별처럼 내려와 <br>아무리 벗어나려 해봐도 <br>멀어지려 해봐도 <br>끝없이 너의 주위를 맴돌아 <br>시간이 더 지나도 널 잊으려 해봐도 <br>너를 지울 수 없어 <br>You're my Sun woo woo <br>You're like the Moon woo woo <br>밤 하늘 가득히 <br>아름답게 빛나는 넌 해 달 별 <br>]]></content><category term="크나큰" label="크나큰"/><category term="해, 달, 별" label="해, 달, 별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/크나큰/너무_예뻐/</id><title>크나큰 - 너무 예뻐 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:22:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:22:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%AC%EB%82%98%ED%81%B0/%EB%84%88%EB%AC%B4_%EC%98%88%EB%BB%90/" title="크나큰 - 너무 예뻐 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Woo I've been thinkin' <br>about you girl yeah Hey <br>눈이 부셔 내 숨이 멎을 듯 <br>지금 내 두 눈엔 너 밖에 안 보여 <br>이런 기분 처음이야 <br>말로 설명할 수 없지만 <br>나도 모르게 어느새 훅 <br>네게 빠져든 거야 <br>하루 종일 머릿속이 너로 가득 차 <br>아무 일도 손에 안 잡혀 <br>이러다가 큰일 나겠어 Oh No <br>그 동안 관심 없던 TV 맛 집도 <br>네가 좋아할만한 예쁜 Cafe도 <br>다 찾아놨으니까 시간 비워 <br>어디든 말만해 Let's ride <br>넌 너무 예뻐 잠시도 눈을 뗄 수 없어 <br>네 남자 이길 원해 Oh <br>너도 나와 같길 바래 yeah <br>넌 너무 예뻐 너를 내 품에 <br>안고서 얘기 할래 <br>I love you love you love you <br>love you love you <br>요즘 내가 이상해졌어 <br>눈을 감아도 네가 보이는 듯 해 <br>나 조차 이런 내가 조금은 낯설지만 <br>나도 모르게 어느새 훅 <br>네게 빠져든 거야 <br>하루 종일 머릿속에 네가 떠올라 <br>바보처럼 또 웃고 있어 <br>이러다가 나 병 나겠어 Oh No <br>그 동안 관심 없던 TV 맛 집도 <br>니가 좋아할만한 예쁜 Cafe도 <br>다 찾아놨으니까 시간 비워 <br>어디든 말만해 Let's ride <br>넌 너무 예뻐 잠시도 눈을 뗄 수 없어 <br>네 남자 이길 원해 Oh <br>너도 나와 같길 바래 yeah <br>넌 너무 예뻐 너를 내 품에 <br>안고서 얘기 할래 <br>I love you love you love you <br>love you love you <br>이젠 너의 맘 속에 나를 가득 채울래 <br>Oh 나 아닌 그 누구도 담을 수가 없게 <br>항상 너의 곁에 있어줄게 <br>내게 너를 맡겨도 돼 <br>너도 나와 같기를 바래 yeah <br>넌 너무 예뻐 잠시도 눈을 뗄 수 없어 <br>네 남자 이길 원해 Oh <br>너도 나와 같길 바래 yeah <br>넌 너무 예뻐 너를 내 품에 <br>안고서 얘기 할래 <br>I love you love you love you <br>love you love you <br>]]></content><category term="크나큰" label="크나큰"/><category term="너무 예뻐" label="너무 예뻐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/크나큰/Think_About_You/</id><title>크나큰 - Think About You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:22:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:22:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%AC%EB%82%98%ED%81%B0/Think_About_You/" title="크나큰 - Think About You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Think About You girl <br>자꾸 네가 보고 싶어 <br>I wanna hold you tight <br>이젠 더 가까워지고 싶어 yeah <br>조금씩 너와 나의 거리를 <br>좁혀 가고 싶어 <br>눈을 뗄 수 없을 만큼 <br>넌 너무 예뻐 예뻐 <br>You You <br>나 이런 적은 처음이야 <br>You You <br>믿을지 모르겠지만 <br>하루 종일 너의 생각으로 <br>일도 제대로 하지를 못해 못해 <br>You You <br>온통 내게는 너뿐이야 <br>You You <br>Everyday Everytime <br>네가 좋아 너도 나와 같길 바래 <br>Think About You <br>Think About You <br>Think About You <br>너의 남자이길 원해 yeah <br>Think About You <br>Think About You <br>Think About You <br>너도 나와 같길 바래 <br>]]></content><category term="크나큰" label="크나큰"/><category term="Think About You" label="Think About You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/크나큰/Feel_So_Good/</id><title>크나큰 - Feel So Good - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:22:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:22:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%AC%EB%82%98%ED%81%B0/Feel_So_Good/" title="크나큰 - Feel So Good - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뜨거운 한 여름 밤의 <br>꿈이라면 깨지 않게 <br>조심스럽게 <br>네게 다가가서 속삭여줄게 <br>내가 널 좋아해 그것도 아주 많이 <br>진심이야 Oh <br>그냥 웃어넘기지 말아줘 <br>나는 바래 이젠 내 품에 <br>너를 꼭 안고 싶어 <br>네 손을 꼭 잡고 싶어 <br>너를 원해 언제나 곁에 <br>있어줄 남자이고 싶어 <br>I Feel so good good <br>난 너와 함께라면 <br>Feel so good good <br>너도 나와 같다면 <br>I Feel so good good <br>아무것도 필요 없어 <br>그냥 너와 나 나는 너 하나면 돼 <br>I feel good <br>어디든 너와 함께이고 싶어 baby <br>지금 이 순간이 멈추길 바래 내겐 <br>너와 함께인 모든 곳이 Neverland <br>되어줄게 오직 너만의 Peter pan <br>나 거짓말은 못해 좀 더 솔직히 말해 <br>내가 너무 좋아해 <br>진심이야 Oh <br>그냥 웃어넘기지 말아줘 <br>나는 바래 이젠 내 품에 <br>너를 꼭 안고 싶어 <br>네 손을 꼭 잡고 싶어 <br>너를 원해 언제나 곁에 <br>있어줄 남자이고 싶어 <br>I Feel so good good <br>난 너와 함께라면 <br>Feel so good good <br>너도 나와 같다면 <br>I Feel so good good <br>아무것도 필요 없어 <br>그냥 너와 나 나는 너 하나면 돼 <br>I feel good <br>시간이 지나도 변하지 않을 수 있게 <br>처음 이 맘을 기억해 둘 거야 <br>I feel so good 너와 함께면 <br>너도 내 마음과 같다면 <br>Oh 난 아무것도 필요 없어 <br>I Feel so good good <br>난 너와 함께라면 <br>Feel so good good <br>너도 나와 같다면 <br>I Feel so good good <br>아무것도 필요 없어 <br>그냥 너와 나 나는 너 하나면 돼 <br>I Feel so good good <br>난 너와 함께라면 <br>Feel so good good <br>너도 나와 같다면 <br>I Feel so good good <br>아무것도 필요 없어 <br>그냥 너와 나 나는 너 하나면 돼 <br>I feel good <br>]]></content><category term="크나큰" label="크나큰"/><category term="Feel So Good" label="Feel So Good"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/크나큰/Good_Night/</id><title>크나큰 - Good Night - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:22:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:22:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%AC%EB%82%98%ED%81%B0/Good_Night/" title="크나큰 - Good Night - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[별처럼 하얗게 반짝이며 <br>내게 날아오던 너 <br>숨처럼 가볍게 짧은 인사하고 <br>날 떠나가던 널 <br>천천히 잊어 보려해 <br>이 밤과 보내려고 해 <br>내게서 <br>매일 함께였던 밤 <br>행복하게 얘기하던 우리도 <br>바람처럼 흘러 사라질 이 밤 <br>내 모든 곳에 너의 흔적들과 <br>추억은 남지만 <br>Good Night 이 밤이 지나가면 <br>웃는 널 볼 수 없겠지 <br>우린 닿을 수 없겠지 <br>Good Night 이 밤이 지나면 <br>꿈처럼 흐려지는 저기 저 별처럼 <br>사실은 덤덤할 줄 알았는데 <br>이별 앞에 태연할거라 생각했는데 <br>나도 크게 다르지는 않나봐 <br>우린 특별할거라고 생각했지만 <br>우린 같은 하늘 다른 곳 같은 마음 <br>다른 사랑을 하게 되겠지 <br>이 밤이 지나가면 이 밤이 지나가면 <br>매일 함께였던 밤 <br>행복하게 얘기하던 우리도 <br>바람처럼 흘러 사라질 이 밤 <br>내 모든 곳에 너의 흔적들과 <br>추억은 남지만 <br>Good Night 이 밤이 지나가면 <br>웃는 널 볼 수 없겠지 <br>우린 닿을 수 없겠지 <br>Good Night 이 밤이 지나면 <br>꿈처럼 흐려지는 저기 저 별처럼 <br>Like a shooting star in the sky <br>Like a shooting star in the sky <br>이 밤이 지나면 <br>]]></content><category term="크나큰" label="크나큰"/><category term="Good Night" label="Good Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/크나큰/비/</id><title>크나큰 - 비 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:22:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:22:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%81%AC%EB%82%98%ED%81%B0/%EB%B9%84/" title="크나큰 - 비 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[안개가 짙게 내린 어두운 밤 <br>창밖에 빗소리만이 고요히 울리고 <br>또다시 찾아온 비가 내리는 밤이면 <br>니 생각에 또 난 무너진 마음에 <br>I can't sleep tonight <br>추억 속에 남은 미련일 뿐인데 <br>I can't sleep tonight <br>이젠 끝이라는 걸 알고 있는데 <br>아직 난 아니란 말야 <br>널 지울 수가 없단 말야 <br>내리는 빗속에 소리쳐도 <br>네게 닿을 수 없는데 <br>이렇게 비 내리는 밤엔 <br>니 생각이 밀려온다 <br>가슴깊이 스며든다 <br>또다시 비가 내리는 밤엔 <br>너를 그리다 잠 못 이루고 <br>진한 너의 그리움만 더 커져가 <br>Du ru ru Du ru ru <br>빗소리에 멍하니 난 창밖을 바라봐 <br>Du ru ru Du ru ru <br>너도 나와 같은 하늘을 보고 있을까 <br>빛이 번진 가로등 불빛 <br>흩날리던 꽃잎이 떨어지던 그 길 <br>이젠 나 혼자만의 추억이 됐지 <br>I can't sleep tonight <br>지난 시간 속에 미련일 뿐인데 <br>I can't sleep tonight <br>되돌릴 수 없단 걸 알고 있는데 <br>아직 난 아니란 말야 <br>널 지울 수가 없단 말야 <br>내리는 빗속에 소리쳐도 <br>네게 닿을 수 없는데 <br>이렇게 비 내리는 밤엔 <br>니 생각이 밀려온다 <br>가슴깊이 스며든다 <br>또다시 비가 내리는 밤엔 <br>너를 그리다 잠 못 이루고 <br>진한 너의 그리움만 더 커져가 <br>언젠가 이 비가 그치겠지만 <br>얼마나 더 지나야 <br>난 널 잊을 수 있을까 <br>구름사이로 가려진 달빛 <br>어둠이 사라지면 널 데려갈 런지 <br>흐린 기억마저도 떠오르지 못하게 <br>이렇게 비 내리는 밤엔 <br>니 생각이 밀려온다 <br>가슴깊이 스며든다 <br>또다시 비가 내리는 밤엔 <br>너를 그리다 잠 못 이루고 <br>진한 너의 그리움만 더 커져가 <br>]]></content><category term="크나큰" label="크나큰"/><category term="비" label="비"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/매드클라운/세탁중_PROD_starRo_WASH_WASH/</id><title>매드클라운 - 세탁중 (PROD. starRo) (WASH! WASH!) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:23:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:23:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A7%A4%EB%93%9C%ED%81%B4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%84%B8%ED%83%81%EC%A4%91_PROD_starRo_WASH_WASH/" title="매드클라운 - 세탁중 (PROD. starRo) (WASH! WASH!) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[세탁 중 wash wash <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>어제는 벌고서 오늘은 써 <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Look everybody does look <br>everybody does <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Keepin' it clean keepin' it clean <br>somewhere now <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Keepin' it clean keepin' it clean <br>somewhere now <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>U don’t need to show me the money <br>I show up when my nose <br>smell the monies <br>근데 흥민 안 생겨 보여지는 돈엔 <br>I'm fallin’ in love with <br>LAN선을 타고 입금되는 돈에 <br>Tryna get this money to disappear <br>0번째는 예술 첫번째는 safety <br>Zino처럼 clean하고 <br>flexible like KZN <br>음악을 들어본 적도 없는 <br>프로듀서들과 내가 왜 해 작업 <br>본 모습은 걷어내고 <br>너네가 좋아할 혹은 <br>욕할 모습만 내보내려는 피디에게 왜 <br>바꿔달라 해 인생을 <br>돈 때문이지 돈 <br>그럼 너는 대체 왜 해 이 랩을 <br>Fuck off I’mma show u <br>what’s the real level <br>starRo in the building mo' fucker <br>과장할 필요도 없지 <br>이건 Grammy level <br>너넨 그저 갑을 나는 free 마치 <br>앞에 B 달린 듯이 dash <br>Shout out to my real brothers <br>out there <br>대부분의 삶에서 <br>trust gets you killed <br>So I'm blessed <br>Bring the fuckin bars Mad C <br>I'm cleaning out your closet <br>like Em did it to his mommy <br>I just want to believe that <br>Everybody's trying 근데 모르겠어 <br>look even presidents <br>어제는 벌고서 오늘은 써 <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Look everybody does look <br>everybody does <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Keepin' it clean keepin' it clean <br>somewhere now <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Keepin' it clean keepin' it clean <br>somewhere now <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Cause I made a lot of mistakes <br>But I'll be alright <br>Cause I do believe we all try <br>Even snakes they want to be a man <br>Cause I made a lot of mistakes <br>But I'll be alright <br>Cause I do believe we all try <br>Even snakes they want to be a man <br>내가 사랑에 대해 말할 때 <br>난 혀로 재떨이를 핥는 기분이야 man <br>너무 예쁘장해서 똥 내나는 장미냄샐 <br>맡는 기분이야 man <br>똑똑 세상 밖에 나갔다 온 <br>내가 더럽혀져 오면 <br>엄마의 세탁기 소린 항상 외로웠고 <br>난 그걸 들으면서 맘이 괴로워져 <br>새까매진 속 표백젤 <br>통째로 삼키고 싶은 충동 <br>더러워진 피 필요한 코인이 <br>모자라면 다시 충전해 <br>fuck around too much <br>암만 씻어도 때가 안 빠져 <br>난 또 돈 벌러 가면 쓰고 <br>애새끼들 머리 위에 <br>올라 췄어 탱고 사람 <br>좋다고 생각할 때 <br>그 새끼는 완전히 좇됀거 play on <br>판짜고 그림 그려 <br>연필 잡는 대신 녹색 크레용 <br>Fuck I’m beast mode <br>걍 가버리지 개썅마이웨이 <br>내 안에 신까지 새까매 <br>암만 불러도 대답 안 해 <br>Clean <br>어제는 벌고서 오늘은 써 <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Look everybody does look <br>everybody does <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Keepin' it clean keepin' it clean <br>somewhere now <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Keepin' it clean keepin' it clean <br>somewhere now <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>Cause I made a lot of mistakes <br>But I'll be alright <br>Cause I do believe we all try <br>Even snakes they want to be a man <br>Cause I made a lot of mistakes <br>But I'll be alright <br>Cause I do believe we all try <br>Even snakes they want to be a man <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>세탁 중 wash wash <br>]]></content><category term="매드클라운" label="매드클라운"/><category term="세탁중 (PROD. starRo) (WASH! WASH!)" label="세탁중 (PROD. starRo) (WASH! WASH!)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/If_You_Gotta_Go_Go_Now_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - If You Gotta Go, Go Now (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/If_You_Gotta_Go_Go_Now_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - If You Gotta Go, Go Now (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Listen to me, baby <br>There's something that you must see <br>I want to be with you, boy <br>If you want to be with me <br><br>But if you gotta go, it's all right <br>But if you gotta go, go now <br>Or else you gotta stay all night <br><br>It's not that I'm questioning you <br>To take part in some kind of quiz <br>It's just that I have got no watch <br>And you keep askin' me what time it is <br><br>But if you gotta go, it's all right <br>But if you gotta go, go now <br>Or else you gotta stay all night <br><br>I am just a poor girl, baby <br>Trying to connect <br>I certainly don't want you thinkin' <br>That I haven't got any respect <br><br>If you gotta go, it's all right <br>But if you gotta go, go now <br>Or else you gotta stay all night <br><br>It ain't that I am wanting <br>Anything you never gave before <br>It's just that I'll be sleeping soon <br>It'll be too dark for you to find the door <br><br>If you gotta go, it's all right <br>But if you gotta go, go now <br>Or else you gotta stay all night]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="If You Gotta Go, Go Now (Live)" label="If You Gotta Go, Go Now (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Escape_Is_So_Simple_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Escape Is So Simple (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Escape_Is_So_Simple_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Escape Is So Simple (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The way you kissed me this morning <br>it told me that you soon would be going <br>You didn't even look in my eyes <br>when you said goodbye <br><br>And last night in your sleep you broke all the promises <br>that I knew you would never keep <br>Now I'm reading the letter which you placed on the dresser <br>and you're five hundred miles down the road <br><br>Escape is so simple <br>in a world where sunsets can be raced <br>But distance only looses the knife <br>the pattern of its scar <br>can always be traced <br><br>Yeah, I remember when we said 'forever' <br>was the craziest word that we knew <br>but I think that I like it much better than I do 'goodbye' <br><br>And I could sit here all evening and think of the reasons <br>why you are not by my side <br>Instead I'll go to the kitchen, find a strong chair to sit in <br>and drink myself far, far away <br><br>Escape is so simple <br>in a world where sunsets can be raced <br>But distance only looses the knife <br>the pattern of its scar <br>can always be traced]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Escape Is So Simple (Live)" label="Escape Is So Simple (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Dead_Flowers_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Dead Flowers (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Dead_Flowers_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Dead Flowers (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, when you're sitting there in your silk upholstered chair <br>Talking to some rich folk that you know <br>Well, I hope you won't see me in my ragged company <br>'cause you know I could never be alone <br><br>Take me down little Susie, take me down <br>I know you think you're the queen of the underground <br>And you can send me dead flowers every morning <br>Send me dead flowers by the mail <br>Send me dead flowers to my wedding <br>And I won't forget to put roses on your grave <br><br>Well, when you're sitting back in your rose pink Cadillac <br>Making bets on Kentucky Derby Day <br>I'll be in my basement room with a needle and a spoon <br>And another girl to take my pain away <br><br>Take me down little Susie, take me down <br>I know you think you're the queen of the underground <br>And you can send me dead flowers every morning <br>Send me dead flowers by the mail <br>Send me dead flowers to my wedding <br>And I won't forget to put roses on your grave <br><br>Take me down little Susie, take me down <br>I know you think you're the queen of the underground <br>And you can send me dead flowers every morning <br>Send me dead flowers by the US mail <br>Say it with dead flowers in my wedding <br>And I won't forget to put roses on your grave <br>No, I won't forget to put roses on your grave]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Dead Flowers (Live)" label="Dead Flowers (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Powderfinger_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Powderfinger (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Powderfinger_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Powderfinger (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look out, Mama, there's a white boat coming up the river <br>with a big red beacon and a flag and a man on the rail <br>I think you'd better call John <br>'cause it don't look like they're here to deliver the mail <br>And it's less than a mile away <br>I hope they didn't come to stay <br>It's got numbers on the side and a gun <br>and it's making big waves <br><br>Daddy's gone, my brother's out hunting in the mountains <br>Big John's been drinking since the river took Emmy Lou <br>So the powers that be left me here to do all the thinking <br>And I just turned twenty two <br>I was wondering what to do <br>And the closer they got <br>The more those feelings grew <br><br>Daddy's rifle in my hand felt reassuring <br>He told me, 'Red means run, Son, numbers add up to nothing' <br>But when that first shot hit the dock, I saw it coming <br>Raised the rifle to my eye <br>Never stopped to wonder why <br>Then I saw black and my face flash in the sky <br><br>Shelter me from the powder and the finger <br>Cover me with the thought that pulled the trigger <br>Just think of me as one you never figured <br>to fade away so young <br>with so much left undone <br>Remember me to my love <br>I know I'll miss her]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Powderfinger (Live)" label="Powderfinger (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Walking_After_Midnight_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Walking After Midnight (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Walking_After_Midnight_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Walking After Midnight (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was walking after midnight <br>Yeah, out in the moonlight <br>The way we used to do <br>I'm always walking after midnight <br>Searching for you <br>I'm always walking after midnight <br>Searching for you <br><br>I stop to see a weeping willow <br>Crying on his pillow <br>Maybe he's a crying for me <br>and as the skys turn gloomy <br>The night winds whisper to me <br>I'm lonesome as I can be <br>I'm always walking after midnight <br>Searching for you <br><br>I walk for miles along the highway <br>Well that's just my way <br>of saying I love you <br>I'm always walking after midnight <br>Searching for you <br>I walk for miles along the highway <br>Searching for you <br><br>I'm always walking after midnight <br>Yeah, out in the moonlight <br>Hoping you may be <br>Somewhere a walking after midnight <br>Searching for me <br>I'm always walking after midnight <br>Searching for you]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Walking After Midnight (Live)" label="Walking After Midnight (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/To_Love_Is_To_Bury_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - To Love Is To Bury (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/To_Love_Is_To_Bury_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - To Love Is To Bury (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I buried him down by the river <br>'cause that's where he liked to be <br>and every night when the moon is high <br>I go there and weep openly <br><br>He and I were married <br>By this river 'neath this willow tree <br>and with God and friends witnessing it <br>He pledged his life to me <br><br>To me he was Earth <br>and I rooted in his soil <br>I to he was Sky vast and free <br>of the burdens from which he toiled <br><br>Then one night a terrible fight <br>Words spoken better left unsaid <br>With his wedding vows ringing in my ears <br>He gave his life to me <br><br>They say to love is to bury <br>Those demons from which we all hide <br>But tonight by this river 'neath this willow tree <br>Becoming one of Earth and Sky]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="To Love Is To Bury (Live)" label="To Love Is To Bury (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Captain_Kidd_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Captain Kidd (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Captain_Kidd_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Captain Kidd (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My name was Captain Kidd, when I sailed, when I sailed <br>My name was Captain Kidd, when I sailed, when I sailed <br>And so wickedly I did <br>God's laws I did forbid <br><br>I roamed from sound to sound, and many ships I've found <br>I roamed from sound to sound, and many ships I've found <br>And that night I saw <br><br>I murdered William Moore and I laid him in his gore <br>I murdered William Moore and I laid him in his gore <br>And this I did to him <br>A many leagues from shore <br><br>Farewell to young and old, the jolly sea <br>Farewell to young and old, the jolly sea <br>And welcome to my <br>And the open door <br><br>Farewell to London town and the pretty girls around <br>Farewell to London town and the pretty girls around <br>My friends <br>In the garden can be found <br><br>Farewell, for I must die, I must die, I must die <br>Farewell, for I must die, I must die, I must die <br>And in my own misery I must lie, I must lie <br>I must lie, must lie, must lie, must lie]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Captain Kidd (Live)" label="Captain Kidd (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/You_Will_Be_Loved_Again_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - You Will Be Loved Again (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/You_Will_Be_Loved_Again_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - You Will Be Loved Again (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How could he take you in his arms <br>and help you to be free <br>then leave you forgotten <br>and is it enough to cry <br>When you're so broken <br><br>Her cold eyes tell you you're not welcome <br>she tells lies but you'll take her back again <br>and is it enough to die <br>When you're so taken <br><br>You will be loved again <br>You will be loved again <br><br>But will she sing and will she dance <br>and will she forever <br>and will he sing and will he dance <br>and will he forever <br><br>Someday you will feel a love so deep <br>and you'll find someone not lost in sleep <br><br>And you will be loved again <br>you will be loved again <br>you will be loved again]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="You Will Be Loved Again (Live)" label="You Will Be Loved Again (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Thirty_Summers_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Thirty Summers (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Thirty_Summers_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Thirty Summers (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Caught in the vice of heaven and earth <br>he turned his life into a cell <br>imprisoned by the doubts which hound us all <br>and those desires which we all know so well <br>His days he lost to promises, his nights he purged of dreams <br>and he would wake in the hours before sunrise <br>and dread the coming of the day <br><br>Never thought a man could become so desperate <br>never thought a life could lose so much hope <br>to be tearing at the roots around you <br>as if in manacles, or irons, or ropes <br>They say he told his children that all he taught was lost <br>that love and pride and honesty <br>were to be gained at too high a cost <br><br>It's been thirty summers that I've spent with him <br>and I expect thirty more to pass <br>he has blessed my life in so many ways <br>that I could never turn my back <br>But I need just one more reminder <br>of the man that he used to be <br>if he would just look deep into my eyes <br>and say it's in you my love that I will find the key]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Thirty Summers (Live)" label="Thirty Summers (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Sun_Comes_Up_Its_Tuesday_Morning_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Sun Comes Up, It`s Tuesday Morning (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Sun_Comes_Up_Its_Tuesday_Morning_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Sun Comes Up, It`s Tuesday Morning (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sun comes up, it's Tuesday morning <br>hits me straight in the eye <br>guess you forgot to close the blind last night <br>Oh, that's right, I forgot, it was me <br><br>I sure do miss the smell of black coffee in the morning <br>the sound of water splashing all over the bathroom <br>the kiss that you would give me even though I was sleeping <br>but I kind of like the feel of this extra few feet in my bed <br>Telephone's ringing, but I don't answer it <br>'cause everybody knows that good news always sleeps till noon <br><br>Guess it's tea and toast for breakfast again <br>maybe I'll add a little TV too <br>No milk God, how I hate that <br>Guess I'll go to the corner, get breakfast from Jenny <br>She's got a black eye this morning, 'Jen how'd ya get it' <br>she says, 'Last night, Bobby got a little bit out of hand' <br><br>Lunchtime I start to dial your number <br>then I remember so I reach for something to smoke <br>and anyways I'd rather listen to Coltrane <br>than go through all that shit again <br><br>There's something about an afternoon spent doing nothing <br>Just listening to records and watching the sun falling <br>Thinking of things that don't have to add up to something <br>and this spell won't be broken <br>by the sound of keys scraping in the lock <br><br>Maybe tonight it's a movie <br>with plenty of room for elbows and knees <br>a bag of popcorn all to myself <br>black and white with a strong female lead <br>and if I don't like it, no debate, I'll leave <br><br>Here comes that feeling that I'd forgotten <br>how strange these streets feel <br>when you're alone on them <br>Each pair of eyes just filled with suggestion <br>So I lower my head, make a beeline for home <br>Seething inside <br><br>Funny, I'd never noticed <br>the sound the streetcars make as they pass my window <br>Which reminds me that I forgot to close the blind again <br>Yeah, sure I'll admit there are times when I miss you <br>Especially like now when I need someone to hold me <br>but there are some things that can never be forgiven <br>and I just gotta tell you <br>that I kinda like this extra few feet in my bed]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Sun Comes Up, It`s Tuesday Morning (Live)" label="Sun Comes Up, It`s Tuesday Morning (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Sweet_Jane_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Sweet Jane (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:27:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:27:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Sweet_Jane_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Sweet Jane (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Anyone who's ever had a heart <br>Wouldn't turn around and break it <br>And anyone who's ever played a part <br>Wouldn't turn around and hate it <br>Sweet Jane, sweet Jane <br>Sweet, sweet Jane <br><br>You're waiting for Jimmy down in the alley <br>Waiting there for him to come back home <br>Waiting down on the corner <br>And thinking of ways to get back home <br>Sweet Jane, sweet Jane <br>Sweet, sweet Jane <br><br>Anyone who's ever had a dream <br>Anyone who's ever played a part <br>Anyone who's ever been lonely <br>And anyone who's ever split apart <br>Sweet Jane, sweet Jane <br>Sweet, sweet Jane <br><br>Heavenly wine and roses <br>Seem to whisper to me when you smile <br>Heavenly wine and roses <br>Seem to whisper to me when you smile <br><br>La la la la, la la la, etc <br><br>Sweet Jane <br>Sweet, sweet Jane]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Sweet Jane (Live)" label="Sweet Jane (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Misguided_Angel_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Misguided Angel (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:28:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:28:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Misguided_Angel_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Misguided Angel (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I said Mama, he's crazy and he scares me <br>But I want him by my side <br>though he's wild and he's bad <br>and sometimes just plain mad <br>I need him to keep me satisfied <br><br>I said Papa, don't cry cause it's alright <br>And I see you in some of his ways <br>Though he might not give me the life that you wanted <br>I'll love him the rest of my days <br><br>Misguided angel hangin' over me <br>Heart like a Gabriel, pure and white as ivory <br>Soul like a Lucifer, black and cold like a piece of lead <br>Misguided angel, love you 'til I'm dead <br><br>I said Brother, you speak to me of passion <br>You said never to settle for nothing less <br>Well, it's in the way he walks <br>it's in the way he talks <br>His smile, his anger and his kisses <br><br>I said Sister, don't you understand <br>He's all I ever wanted in a man <br>I'm tired of sittin' around the TV every night <br>Hoping I'm finding a Mr Right <br><br>Misguided angel hangin' over me <br>Heart like a Gabriel, pure and white as ivory <br>Soul like a Lucifer <br>Black and cold like a piece of lead <br>Misguided angel, love you 'til I'm dead <br><br>He says Baby, don't listen to what they say <br>There comes a time when you have to break away <br>He says Baby there are things we all cling to all our life <br>It's time to let them go and become my wife <br><br>Misguided angel hangin' over me <br>Heart like a Gabriel, pure and white as ivory <br>Soul like a Lucifer <br>Black and cold like a piece of lead <br>Misguided angel, love you 'til I'm dead]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Misguided Angel (Live)" label="Misguided Angel (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Mariners_Song_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Mariner`s Song (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:28:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:28:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Mariners_Song_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Mariner`s Song (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The last of man's great unchained beasts lies lapping at my door <br>The last of man's great unchained beasts lies lapping at my door <br>I would give it what it wants, but I do know <br>it would just ask for more <br><br>I search for you with every crest I ride <br>in every trough I travel through <br>I search for you in every trough I travel through <br><br>I didn't mean to leave you <br>I unfurled my sail and the wind did blow <br>I didn't mean to leave you, darling <br>I unfurled my sail and the wind did blow <br>Why why why why why, oh why I did not drop my anchor <br>Oh Lord, I will never know <br><br>I search for you with every crest I ride <br>in every trough I travel through <br>I search for you in every trough I travel through <br><br>On the lee of the island I hear your voice deep inside the calm <br>On the lee of the island I hear your voice deep inside the calm <br>Whispering baby, I'll be your delight, if you promise <br>to be my red sky tonight <br><br>I search for you with every crest I ride <br>in every trough I travel through <br>I search for you in every trough I travel through <br><br>In the storm you are my destination, in the port you are my storm <br>In the storm you are my destination, in the port you are my storm <br>But I would weather you my love, if you would be my guide <br>if you would be my stars in the sky tonight <br><br>I search for you with every crest I ride <br>in every trough I travel through <br>I search for you in every trough I travel through]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Mariner`s Song (Live)" label="Mariner`s Song (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Shining_Moon_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Shining Moon (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:28:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:28:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Shining_Moon_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Shining Moon (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't the moon look pretty <br>Shining down through the trees <br>Don't that shining moon look pretty, baby <br>Shining down through the trees <br>You know I can see my baby <br>When he can't see me <br><br>Yeah, I tiptoe to his window <br>Just to see my baby snore <br>I tiptoe to his window <br>Just to see how sweetie snores <br>You know it makes me feel like jumping, lord, lord <br>Through the keyhole in his door <br><br>Come crawl up to your window <br>Let me whisper in your ear <br>Come on and crawl up to your window, darling <br>Let me whisper in your ear <br>You know, I got somthing to tell you, baby <br>I don't want that girl around here <br>keep her away]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Shining Moon (Live)" label="Shining Moon (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/200_More_Miles_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - 200 More Miles (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:28:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:28:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/200_More_Miles_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - 200 More Miles (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Atlanta's a distant memory <br>Montgomery a recent birth <br>and Tulsa burns on the desert floor <br>like a signal fire <br><br>I got Willie on the radio <br>a dozen things on my mind <br>and number one is fleshing out <br>these dreams of mine <br><br>I've got 200 more miles of rain asphalt in line <br>before I sleep <br>But there'll be no warm sheets or welcoming arms <br>to fall into tonight <br><br>In Nashville there is a lighter <br>in a case for all to see <br>it speaks of dreams and heartaches <br>left unsung <br><br>And in the corner stands a guitar and <br>lonesome words scrawled in a drunken hand <br>I don't travel past, travel hard before <br>and I'm beginning to understand <br><br>That I've got 200 more miles of rain asphalt in line <br>before I sleep <br>But there'll be no warm sheets or welcoming arms <br>to fall into tonight <br><br>They say that I am crazy <br>my life wasting on this road <br>that time will find my dreams <br>scared or dead and cold <br><br>But I heard there is a light <br>drawing me to reach an end <br>and when I reach there, I'll turn back <br>and you and I can begin again <br><br>I've got 200 more miles of rain asphalt in line <br>before I sleep <br>But there'll be no warm sheets or welcoming arms <br>to fall into tonight <br><br>I've got 200 more miles of rain asphalt in line <br>before I sleep <br>But I wouldn't trade all your golden tomorrows <br>for one hour of this night <br><br>Atlanta's a distant memory <br>Montgomery a recent birth <br>and Tulsa burns on the desert floor <br>like a signal fire]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="200 More Miles (Live)" label="200 More Miles (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Me__The_Devil_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Me &amp; The Devil (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:28:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:28:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Me__The_Devil_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Me &amp; The Devil (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Early this morning, he knocked on my door <br>Early this morning he knocked on my door <br>I said Hello, Satan, I believe it's time to go <br><br>Me and The Devil are walkin' side by side <br>Me and The Devil are walkin' side by side <br>Well, I'm goin' to beat my man until I get satisfied <br><br>He says I don't do him right <br>That I dog him around <br>Well, babe, you know you ain't treating me right <br>He says I don't do him right <br>that I dog him around <br>Well, it must be this old evil spirit <br>So deep down within the ground <br><br>You may bury my body down by the highway side <br>oh, babe I don't care what you do with my body <br>You may bury my body down by the highway side <br>So my old evil spirit can catch a Greyhound bus and ride <br><br>Early this morning, he knocked on my door <br>Now me and The Devil are walking side by side <br>Side by side]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Me &amp; The Devil (Live)" label="Me &amp; The Devil (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Cause_Cheap_Is_How_I_Feel_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - `Cause Cheap Is How I Feel (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:28:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:28:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Cause_Cheap_Is_How_I_Feel_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - `Cause Cheap Is How I Feel (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's the kind of night that's so cold, when you spit <br>it freezes before it hits the ground <br>And when a bum asks you for a quarter, you give a dollar <br>if he's out tonight he must be truly down <br>And I'm searching all the windows for a last minute present <br>to prove to you that what I said was real <br>for something small and frail and plastic, baby <br>'cause cheap is how I feel <br><br>Half moon in the sky tonight, bright enough <br>to come up with an answer <br>to the question why is it that every time I see you <br>my love grows a little stronger <br>But your memory leaves my stomach churning <br>feeling like a lie about to be revealed <br>but I'll horde all this to myself <br>'cause cheap is how I feel <br><br>It's not the smell in here that gets to me it's the lights <br>I hate the shadows that they cast <br>and the sound of clinking bottles is the one sure thing <br>I'll always drag with me from my past <br>I think I'll find a pair of eyes tonight, to fall into <br>and maybe strike a deal <br>Your body for my soul, fair swap <br>'cause cheap is how I feel]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="`Cause Cheap Is How I Feel (Live)" label="`Cause Cheap Is How I Feel (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Blue_Moon_Revisited_Song_For_Elvis_Live/</id><title>Cowboy Junkies - Blue Moon Revisited (Song For Elvis) (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:28:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:28:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cowboy_Junkies/Blue_Moon_Revisited_Song_For_Elvis_Live/" title="Cowboy Junkies - Blue Moon Revisited (Song For Elvis) (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I only want to say <br>That if there is a way <br>I want my baby back with me <br>'cause he's my true love <br>my only one don't you see <br><br>And on that fateful day <br>Perhaps in the new sun of May <br>My baby walks back into my arms <br>I'll keep him beside me <br>forever from harm <br><br>You see I was afraid <br>to let my baby stray <br>I kept him too tightly by my side <br>and then one sad day <br>he went away and he died <br><br>Blue Moon, you saw me standing alone <br>without a dream in my heart <br>without a love of my own <br>Blue Moon, you knew just what I was there for <br>You heard me saying a prayer for <br>someone I really could care for <br><br>I only want to say <br>That if there is a way <br>I want my baby back with me <br>'cause he's my true love <br>my only one don't you see]]></content><category term="Cowboy Junkies" label="Cowboy Junkies"/><category term="Blue Moon Revisited (Song For Elvis) (Live)" label="Blue Moon Revisited (Song For Elvis) (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ovenz/相杵歌_상저가/</id><title>O.venz - 相杵歌 (상저가) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:29:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:29:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ovenz/%E7%9B%B8%E6%9D%B5%E6%AD%8C_%EC%83%81%EC%A0%80%EA%B0%80/" title="O.venz - 相杵歌 (상저가) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일렁이는 빛을 따라서 <br>시선을 추켜 올려 <br>홀로 한 시간 고독이 <br>제일 친한 친구가 됐어 <br>환각처럼 보여 <br>사랑하는 어머니 아버지 <br>이젠 환자복을 입고 계시네 <br>나의 어머니 <br>아버지 60 하고 1 일을 하고 계셔 <br>가족을 위해서 <br>그들을 위해서 할 수 있는 게 <br>아무것도 없는 차가운 현실이 띠꺼워 <br>죄책감이 들 때면 전화를 걸어 <br>아픈 덴 없죠 <br>건강 챙겨요 부모님 <br>아들은 잘 지내요 <br>이만 끊을게요 괜찮아요 <br>걱정 말아요 또 연락할게요 <br>골목을 지나 보이는 즐비한 네온사인 <br>그래 대도시의 밤은 <br>결코 잠들지 않아 <br>불이 꺼져있는 안식처 붉은색 옥탑방 <br>딱딱한 소파에 기대 단잠을 청한다 <br>꿈에서 만난 아이 손에 가득한 사탕 <br>봄처럼 따뜻한 시선으로 바라본다 <br>손을 내밀자 저 멀리 도망가네 <br>그 아이와 손을 잡은 다정한 연인이 <br>멀리 서있네 나의 어머니 아버지 <br>눈물을 흘려 미소를 띄우네 <br>다정한 연인 <br>꿈에서 깨어도 보여 그 눈빛이 <br>무기력의 덫에서 다시 벗어나게 하지 <br>신은 평등함을 주지 않아 <br>십자가를 놓았지 <br>그 손 위 부모님 주름진 손 꽉 잡고 <br>이를 악물고 지옥을 버텨야지 <br>그들의 인생을 태워서 <br>내 삶에 등불이 됐으니 <br>두 사람에게 남은 건 <br>오직 자식들뿐이니 <br>가족만을 위해 살아오신 아버지 <br>평생 가족만을 위해 살아오신 어머니 <br>사랑한다는 말도 못했네요 papa <br>사랑한다는 말도 못했어요 <br>love you mama <br>가족만을 위해 살아오신 아버지 <br>평생 가족만을 위해 살아오신 어머니 <br>사랑한다는 말도 못했네요 papa <br>사랑한다는 말도 못했어요 <br>love you mama <br>mama don`t cry 이젠 울지 마요 <br>mama I never cry <br>나도 울지 않을게요 <br>아직 혼자 힘들어도 <br>언제나 난 think of you <br>all the time and the time <br>i will remember you <br>i will love of you <br>all the time <br>]]></content><category term="O.venz" label="O.venz"/><category term="相杵歌 (상저가)" label="相杵歌 (상저가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정연호/Always/</id><title>정연호 - Always - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:29:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:29:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%97%B0%ED%98%B8/Always/" title="정연호 - Always - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주의 손이 날 인도해 <br>강한 방패가 되어 <br>고난과 시련이 와도 <br>결코 난 두렵지 않네 <br>고통이 나를 누르고 <br>어둠이 나를 덮어도 <br>강하신 주님의 팔로 날 지키리 <br>언제 어디서든지 내가 무얼 하든지 <br>나를 나보다 더 잘 아시는 분 <br>항상 함께 하시고 늘 지켜 주시네 <br>내가 길 잃고 방황 할 때도 <br>언제 어디서든지 내가 무얼 하든지 <br>나를 나보다 더 잘 아시는 분 <br>항상 함께 하시고 늘 지켜 주시네 <br>내가 길 잃고 방황 할 때도 <br>어떠한 말도 할 수 없을 때 <br>이미 모든 걸 알고 계셔 <br>어두움이 날 숨기려 해도 <br>언제 어디서나 찾아 내시는 <br>주의 손이 날 인도해 <br>강한 방패가 되어 <br>고난과 시련이 와도 <br>결코 난 두렵지 않네 <br>고통이 나를 누르고 <br>어둠이 나를 덮어도 <br>강하신 주님의 팔로 날 지키리 <br>어떠한 말도 할 수 없을 때 <br>이미 모든 걸 알고 계셔 <br>어두움이 날 숨기려 해도 <br>언제 어디서나 찾아 내시는 <br>주의 손이 날 인도해 <br>강한 방패가 되어 <br>고난과 시련이 와도 <br>결코 난 두렵지 않네 <br>고통이 나를 누르고 <br>어둠이 나를 덮어도 <br>강하신 주님의 팔로 날 지키리 <br>주의 손이 날 인도해 <br>강한 방패가 되어 <br>고난과 시련이 와도 <br>결코 난 두렵지 않네 <br>고통이 나를 누르고 <br>어둠이 나를 덮어도 <br>강하신 주님의 팔로 날 지키리 <br>]]></content><category term="정연호" label="정연호"/><category term="Always" label="Always"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안은선/사탕/</id><title>안은선 - 사탕 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:29:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:29:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EC%9D%80%EC%84%A0/%EC%82%AC%ED%83%95/" title="안은선 - 사탕 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금이 봄인지 여름인지 <br>계절도 모르고 살던 나에게 <br>봄 봄이 찾아왔어 <br>그 앨 보고 알게 되었어 <br>나 사랑에 빠졌나 봐 <br>그 앨 보면 얼굴이 빨개져 <br>사실 잘 보지도 못해 <br>생각만 해도 온몸이 떨리거든 <br>그런 너에게 내 마음 전하고 싶어 <br>한참을 두근두근 고민하다가 <br>네가 좋아하는 사탕 한가득 담아 <br>아무도 몰래 네 서랍에 넣었어 <br>너는 아마 모를 거야 <br>네가 좋아하는 그 사탕 <br>그 사탕 누가 준 건지 <br>모를 거야 <br>너는 아마 모를 거야 <br>너를 좋아하는 내 맘도 <br>사탕도 내 마음도 다 몰라도 <br>그래도 네가 좋아 <br>그런 너에게 내 마음 전하고 싶어 <br>한참을 두근두근 고민하다가 <br>네가 좋아하는 사탕 한가득 담아 <br>아무도 몰래 네 서랍에 넣었어 <br>너는 아마 모를 거야 <br>네가 좋아하는 그 사탕 <br>그 사탕 누가 준 건지 <br>모를 거야 <br>너는 아마 모를 거야 <br>너를 좋아하는 내 맘도 <br>사탕도 내 마음도 다 몰라도 <br>그래도 네가 좋아 <br>]]></content><category term="안은선" label="안은선"/><category term="사탕" label="사탕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정훈/엄마_삼계탕/</id><title>조정훈 - 엄마 삼계탕 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:29:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:29:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9B%88/%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88_%EC%82%BC%EA%B3%84%ED%83%95/" title="조정훈 - 엄마 삼계탕 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[덥다 더워도 너무 더워 <br>삼계탕 먹으러 왔네 <br>오돌톨하니 먹음직스런 <br>한그릇 보는데 갑자기 <br>엄마 생각이 나 <br>그때 난 왜 삼계탕 싫다고 했나 <br>좁고 더운 부엌 고생하신 사랑을 <br>징그럽다 외면한 나 맛을 몰랐네 <br>진짜 사랑을 진한 이 맛을 몰랐네 <br>아무래도 엄마가 보고 싶어 <br>삼계탕 먹다 엄마 생각이 났다 <br>전화했더니 <br>아이고 그랬나 엄마 생각 나더나 <br>그때 난 왜 삼계탕 싫다고 했나 <br>허약하게 낳아 미안하다 하시던 <br>따뜻한 엄마의 마음을 왜 몰라 줬나 <br>진짜 사랑을 진한 이 맛을 몰랐네 <br>그때 난 왜 삼계탕 싫다고 했나 <br>그때 난 왜 <br>엄마 삼계탕 먹고 싶다 <br>엄마 삼계탕 먹고 싶다 <br>덥다 더워도 너무 더워 <br>삼계탕 먹으러 왔네 <br>엄마 보고싶다 <br>]]></content><category term="조정훈" label="조정훈"/><category term="엄마 삼계탕" label="엄마 삼계탕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/명성_Castle/</id><title>Tommy Strate - 명성 (Castle) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:32:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:32:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/%EB%AA%85%EC%84%B1_Castle/" title="Tommy Strate - 명성 (Castle) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh look look look <br>넌 진짜 정말 대단해 <br>U make me go up up up up <br>날 세워 주는 게 <br>물론 이상한 생각으로 <br>내뱉은 말은 아니야 <br>너의 존재가 내 명성을 <br>높여준다는 말이야 <br>Ohhh 내 성은 너를 위한 곳이야 <br>마음대로 해 <br>Baby 내가 더 노력할게 <br>너를 위해서야 babe <br>내 명성을 더 높게 세워 <br>내 여왕이 되 줄래 <br>I'll be a king 또는 너를 위한 <br>하인이 되 줄게 <br>Hunnid bands super cars vroom <br>U can have everything everything <br>Just tell me wutchu want babe <br>tell me wutchu need <br>여기는 내 궁전이니까 <br>원하는 건 다 말해 <br>네 생일 wutchu wishin' wishin' <br>Make it pop out 난 <br>magician magician <br>then we cause a little <br>friction friction <br>Yea we cause a lot of <br>friction friction <br>U gon tell me I'm the best <br>날 대신 소문 내 소문 내 <br>넌 날 위해 business 해 <br>넌 내 존재를 널리 마켓팅 해 <br>Baby u the best <br>I don't need nobody <br>Only ur body <br>Turn me on the best <br>날 움직이게 할 수 있는 건 just you <br>넌 나를 시동 걸어주는 열쇠 <br>내 병사들은 길을 터 <br>너의 등장은 기적 같아 모세 <br>No time I don't play <br>내 왕국의 평수 네 마음처럼 넓게 <br>짓기 위해 난 오늘 다시 <br>내 성의 도안을 작업해 <br>I said I need u right here baby <br>With u l'll go <br>신비롭게 빛나는 곳 odd places <br>I can tell I can tell I can tell <br>I know u gon love it as much as I do <br>Leaning on me on the couch with u <br>I'm trying all I can <br>널 위해 희생해 <br>And I'm gonna be ur man always <br>Always be there for u <br>Hunnid bands super cars vroom <br>U can have everything everything <br>Just tell me wutchu want babe <br>tell me wutchu need <br>여기는 내 궁전이니까 <br>원하는 건 다 말해 <br>네 생일 wutchu wishin' wishin' <br>Make it pop out 난 <br>magician magician <br>then we cause a little <br>friction friction <br>Yea we cause a lot of <br>friction friction <br>네 생일 wutchu wishin' wishin' <br>Make it pop out 난 <br>magician magician <br>then we cause a little <br>friction friction <br>Yea we cause a lot of <br>friction friction <br>]]></content><category term="Tommy Strate" label="Tommy Strate"/><category term="명성 (Castle)" label="명성 (Castle)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/열시_조금_넘어서_Little_past_ten/</id><title>Tommy Strate - 열시 조금 넘어서 (Little past ten) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:32:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:32:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/%EC%97%B4%EC%8B%9C_%EC%A1%B0%EA%B8%88_%EB%84%98%EC%96%B4%EC%84%9C_Little_past_ten/" title="Tommy Strate - 열시 조금 넘어서 (Little past ten) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do you mind <br>if I just take a little time <br>You know that I'm always <br>busy up all night <br>Just a little past ten <br>just a little past ten <br>I'm gon hit u up tonight <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>열 시 조금 넘어서 <br>네 생각에 나는 쉴 수가 없어 <br>Sending u a message 오늘 뭐했어 <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>열 시 조금 넘어서 <br>네 생각에 나는 쉴 수가 없어 <br>Sending u a message 오늘 뭐했어 <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>요즘엔 너무 바쁘지 <br>어제와는 다르지 <br>날이 밝아오면 어제 없던 신상들이 <br>금새 자리를 채우지 <br>Got u instead of gold <br>u my baby my dime <br>새로운 건 원치 않아 u original fine <br>U just packed full of gold in ur heart <br>좀만 기달려 네 구찌 백은 곧 아령급 <br>heavy Yay <br>I'm sippin <br>I'm tippin not trippin just leanin <br>On top of ur body <br>시간은 빠르게 달려와서 <br>우리를 잡으려 하지 <br>난 급하지 않게 이 순간에 <br>모든걸 즐기며 baby <br>오늘도 내일같이 내일도 오늘같이 <br>fuckin' u baby <br>I need u on my wave <br>I be doin this for u to be in my game <br>U my controller and I'll be in my lane <br>Giving u my trust <br>u could put me in the fame <br>I don't need nobody cuz i need none <br>Always been alone never had one <br>Ive been full of that stress <br>til u came on <br>Now proudly I could tell u <br>u the best one <br>Do you mind <br>if I just take a little time <br>You know that I'm always <br>busy up all night <br>Just a little past ten <br>just a little past ten <br>I'm gon hit u up tonight <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>열 시 조금 넘어서 <br>네 생각에 나는 쉴 수가 없어 <br>Sending u a message 오늘 뭐했어 <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>열 시 조금 넘어서 <br>네 생각에 나는 쉴 수가 없어 <br>Sending u a message 오늘 뭐했어 <br>I don't wanna be alone tonight <br>]]></content><category term="Tommy Strate" label="Tommy Strate"/><category term="열시 조금 넘어서 (Little past ten)" label="열시 조금 넘어서 (Little past ten)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/Ya_Prod_Dakshood/</id><title>Tommy Strate - Ya (Prod. Dakshood) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:32:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:32:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/Ya_Prod_Dakshood/" title="Tommy Strate - Ya (Prod. Dakshood) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ya 핸드폰은 집에 있으니까 <br>지금 연락하지마 <br>Ya 나 지금 작업 중이니까 <br>보고 싶음 로데오로 와 <br>Ya 고요하지 우리 동네 <br>저기 예수님이 걸어와 <br>Ya 천사들이 나를 반겨주지 <br>여긴 작업실이야 <br>Ay I'm goin up <br>헬륨 가득 채운 복식호흡 <br>풍선 터져 like <br>Ay blowing up <br>공중 위에 배영하지 <br>나는 본명부터가 <br>별이니 위험해 <br>그 중에서 제일 큰 태양이야 man <br>이름처럼 크게 될 놈이니까 man <br>내게 접근할 땐 진짜로 조심해 <br>Wanna fuck wit me than come through <br>The fucking house <br>나를 느낀다면 너는 진짜야 <br>절반은 가식으로 전염됐잖아 <br>내 음악이 치료해줄 거니 걱정 마 <br>Gonna pull up in the south <br>know I'm talking about <br>미국 찍고 일본으로 가 멀리 가 <br>Rolling rolling rolling rolling <br>Rolling go packing and up <br>here we go <br>Getting litty every shows like <br>Ya 핸드폰은 집에 있으니까 <br>지금 연락하지마 <br>Ya 나 지금 작업 중이니까 <br>보고 싶음 로데오로 와 <br>Ya 고요하지 우리 동네 <br>저기 예수님이 걸어와 <br>Ya 천사들이 나를 반겨주지 <br>여긴 작업실이야 <br>Getting litty litty <br>전국 투어 돌겠지 <br>나는 미리 미리 미리 <br>준비해놨어 <br>wit my team we get it get it <br>멋있는 놈들끼리 모였지 끼리끼리 <br>붙어 다니는 법이지 <br>no 비리 비리 <br>우린 좋아하지 <br>pussy 말고 kitty kitty <br>나를 이해 못한다면 <br>영어 배워 미리 <br>합법적으로 난 죽여놨지 <br>곡을 killy killy <br>Bakka 멍청이들은 몰라 <br>10을 알면 100은 몰라 <br>뭘 해도 딱딱 아래 말고 네 박자 <br>전부 어색하지 you ain't got no 절차 <br>머리가 내 bank <br>돈을 버는 flows <br>Gotta lot of it <br>You know Ima get stax <br>Rolling with the best <br>나는 주위에 <br>천재들 밖에 <br>없으니까 내가 이렇지 flex <br>Million dollar things <br>Ima get it on my bed <br>If I like a bitch <br>ima tell her gimme head <br>Putting up sound <br>문제없어 in a day <br>매일 작업하지 <br>곡은 나와 like a bank <br>Like ooohh <br>환전하지 매일 <br>Exchanging in the booth <br>가사지가 현찰 yea <br>Flippin through the phone <br>난 액수를 확인해 <br>공이 맞다 싶음 나는 바로 녹음해 <br>Ya 핸드폰은 집에 있으니까 <br>지금 연락하지마 <br>Ya 나 지금 작업 중이니까 <br>보고 싶음 로데오로 와 <br>Ya 고요하지 우리 동네 <br>저기 예수님이 걸어와 <br>Ya 천사들이 나를 반겨주지 <br>여긴 작업실이야 <br>]]></content><category term="Tommy Strate" label="Tommy Strate"/><category term="Ya (Prod. Dakshood)" label="Ya (Prod. Dakshood)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/GOAT_Feat_Ja_Mezz/</id><title>Tommy Strate - GOAT (Feat. Ja Mezz) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:32:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:32:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/GOAT_Feat_Ja_Mezz/" title="Tommy Strate - GOAT (Feat. Ja Mezz) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 변해 goin goat ya <br>시간은 오늘도 ya <br>늦지 않아 hit me up ya <br>내 젊음 경험에 환전 ya <br>Switch it up <br>cuz I'm goin all night ohh <br>사람들이 잠에 들 때 나는 꿈을 꿔 <br>Walkin with my angels <br>in the clouds beautiful <br>나를 찾는다면 소리구름 통해서 <br>I gotta go with the pack <br>Building a house with the stacks <br>여기까지 나는 전부 다 <br>혼자 했어 너랑 비교 마 <br>I'm from the place call it 6 <br>Maple syrup on my dish <br>Serve it with music I mix <br>Master that shit with the kiss <br>On my way on my way <br>나 지금 가는 중이야 산으로 <br>내 소리 말고 나라고 <br>I'm just on the way be the goat <br>Got hades with me goin gold <br>Oh yeahh <br>U don't fuck with the goat <br>I'm just tryna be myself <br>Tryna get hella dough <br>Oh yeahh <br>U don't fuck with the goat <br>I'm just tryna be myself <br>Tryna get hella dough <br>I ain't paying <br>I ain't joking <br>I ain't playing <br>I ain't paying <br>I ain't joking <br>I ain't playing <br>I ain't paying <br>I ain't joking <br>I ain't playing <br>I ain't paying <br>I ain't joking <br>I ain't playing <br>i ain't playing <br>i ain't playing i ain't playing <br>switching lanes <br>i'm done switching lanes <br>나는 변해 going goat <br>with my boy tommy strate <br>on my way up <br>i'm gon GET IT GET IT GET IT <br>우리 끼리 끼리 끼리 <br>다 가져가 cake cake cake <br>너넨 꿈 깨길 깨길 깨길 <br>아가씨들 be my baby <br>아가씨들 have my baby <br>김민희 민희 민희 태리 태리 태리 <br>let's have three way way way <br>fuck you thought i be the goat <br>mama told me i be the goat <br>GOD told me i be the goat <br>그냥 철석같이 믿었어 yeah <br>물어봐 성공에 대해 사람들은 <br>말하지 망망대해 <br>가야 돼 제일 깊은 곳까지 <br>lil yachty get me a boat <br>i ain't playing i ain't playing <br>애들 장난 같애 <br>너넨 lame lame lamb <br>너넨 어린 양 <br>나는 염소 i'm the goat <br>내 소꿉놀인 유부녀랑 해 <br>you never know <br>Oh yeahh <br>U don't fuck with the goat <br>I'm just tryna be myself <br>Tryna get hella dough <br>Oh yeahh <br>U don't fuck with the goat <br>I'm just tryna be myself <br>Tryna get hella dough <br>I ain't paying <br>I ain't joking <br>I ain't playing <br>I ain't paying <br>I ain't joking <br>I ain't playing <br>I ain't paying <br>I ain't joking <br>I ain't playing <br>I ain't paying <br>I ain't joking <br>I ain't playing <br>]]></content><category term="Tommy Strate" label="Tommy Strate"/><category term="GOAT (Feat. Ja Mezz)" label="GOAT (Feat. Ja Mezz)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/Soundwave/</id><title>Tommy Strate - Soundwave - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:32:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:32:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/Soundwave/" title="Tommy Strate - Soundwave - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ay ay Man I'm turning 25 <br>and I'm feelin boujee <br>I just never had no problems all <br>I wanted was this <br>내가 바보같데 <br>나는 상관안해 <br>나는 다른 언어로 말할게 <br>call it soundwave <br>야이야이야 <br>I be swervin in a lot <br>I'll be schemin til I die <br>Drinkin' henney wit my pot ooooh <br>나를 비교하지마 <br>나는 위로가자나 <br>하나님이 부르자나 <br>나는 아직 젊으니까 ooh <br>밀어붙힐거야 with the crew <br>시간끌지않아 make a move and then <br>We make it happen poof <br>멀지않아 내가 가야할 내 길은 <br>생각보다 좁아 한길로 걸어 <br>난 느낀대로 흘러나는 강물처럼 wavy <br>새끼들은 느낌 알아도 <br>멋을 몰라 이건 잘해도 <br>Can't follow me in my coupe <br>My soundwave goin in a loop <br>음악으로 doin private shows 나는 <br>그걸 즐기면서 dab u know <br>이건 간지나는 느낌이래두 <br>넌 모를거야 til my interview <br>I just wanna roll it up <br>Tryna get u high as fuck <br>배게 위에 머릴 얹혀봐 baby <br>하늘 위에 떠있어 <br>Sippin' on 구름 별에 앉아 ay <br>천국에서 보자 ay <br>예수님이 내려 오기전에 <br>우리가 먼저 가자 <br>잠깐 <br>Turn it up loud <br>신의 음역대는 높아 <br>올라 가는길에 깔아줄래 나의 음악 <br>이건 나의 간지 브금 등장부터 달라 <br>Soundwave 이게 바로 나의 언어니까 <br>I don't do the talkin' unless <br>U talkin bout my music really my <br>Drums talk <br>Bangin bangin bangin to ur brains <br>Can u get the message <br>in the beat ya <br>I'm not into phone calls <br>Hit u up with a song <br>U need to be speaking my language <br>And U better know it soundwave <br>]]></content><category term="Tommy Strate" label="Tommy Strate"/><category term="Soundwave" label="Soundwave"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/Tommy/</id><title>Tommy Strate - Tommy - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:32:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:32:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tommy_Strate/Tommy/" title="Tommy Strate - Tommy - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They just always want <br>more no pay ya <br>걔네들은 몰라 이런 느낌 ya <br>내 음악은 음질부터가 wav ya <br>상어때로 가득차있어 내 wave ya <br>Bitches dancing <br>on my body no hands ya <br>I could flip em all night <br>like cards ya <br>She's an ace and I give her a 10 <br>I hold that <br>She yelling timber timber timber <br>I feel like jack <br>Yea that way I'm just havin' fun <br>Ay Roll up a blunt <br>I don't even smoke no more <br>but I get it on <br>I'm pop it like a virgin <br>in a pair of thongs <br>She a thot i don't give a fuck <br>I smoke it tho <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>thats what she be calling me <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>my iphone just never sleep <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>thats what they be calling me <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>makin' hits yea that be me <br>Ya ya I go hard <br>like a mofuckin' gang <br>밀어붙여 나는 백 없어도 돼 ya <br>계집애들 전부 매던데 왜 ya <br>네가 맨 명품의 값을 못해 <br>내 음악은 fuckin lit lit <br>Flowing on my fuckin wave wave <br>타고싶음 돈내 hey <br>Roller coastin coastin coastin <br>너네들은 전부다 lame lame <br>Bitch what u do in my lane <br>왜 이제 와서 척해 hey <br>내가 필요하면 돈내 wooh <br>내 모든게 boujee ooh <br>내가 만지는 이 소리 ay <br>나는 실력이 잘생김 ooh <br>물론 내 fashion도 boomin' ya <br>Okay 신은 내게 말을 건네 <br>Don't give a fuck about them <br>그의 음역대는 so high <br>내 귀에 닿을때 I feel fly high <br>Fuck u know <br>Bout a thing or more <br>아는척 하지마 그건 졸라 멋없어 <br>나를 봐 oh <br>doing that hoe <br>Doing dabs throwing backflips <br>Soon on ur tv shows <br>Yea that way I'm just havin' fun <br>Ay Roll up a blunt <br>I don't even smoke no more <br>but I get it on <br>I'm pop it like a virgin <br>in a pair of thongs <br>She a thot i don't give a fuck <br>I smoke it tho <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>thats what she be calling me <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>my iphone just never sleep <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>thats what they be calling me <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>makin' hits yea that be me <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>thats what she be calling me <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>my iphone just never sleep <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>thats what they be calling me <br>Tommy TOMMY TOMMY <br>makin' hits yea that be me <br>]]></content><category term="Tommy Strate" label="Tommy Strate"/><category term="Tommy" label="Tommy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤종신/Welcome_Summer/</id><title>윤종신 - Welcome Summer - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:32:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:32:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EC%A2%85%EC%8B%A0/Welcome_Summer/" title="윤종신 - Welcome Summer - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그까짓 자질구레한 거 <br>내 인생의 작은 모래 알갱이도 안돼 <br>Open the window <br>let me feel that <br>사랑한다 말해 <br>다 내려놓고 올라타 <br>걱정 따윈 태양이 녹여줘 <br>바싹 그을려 돌아올 생각해 <br>Open your heart <br>please let me feel that <br>모두 잊겠다고 말해줘 <br>우리 지쳤던 지난 계절도 <br>땀이 흐르겠지 <br>올여름도 똑같겠지 <br>뭐 그 여느 해처럼 어제까진 <br>너의 선글라스 속 설레지 <br>우리 둘만의 Summer night <br>거긴 별이 가득해서 잠 못 이룬대 <br>돌아올 땐 나로 가득 <br>채워 줄게 My love <br>Welcome summer <br>숨 막히게 파란 바다 위 <br>우린 하늘에게 두 눈 감고 말 걸겠지 <br>Open the sky <br>please let me feel that <br>행복하다 말해 <br>짜릿 탄산 한 모금에 <br>버블버블 나를 붕 뜨게 해 <br>The kiss &amp; Swimming <br>뭘 더 바라겠어 <br>Open your heart <br>please let me feel that <br>기억하겠다고 말해줘 <br>우리 다가올 다음 계절도 <br>땀이 흐르겠지 <br>올여름밤 꿈같겠지 <br>추억 어느 해 보다 빛나겠지 <br>달빛 와인글라스 속 비추지 <br>우리 둘만의 Summer night <br>가는 하루하루 아쉬워 잠 못 이룬대 <br>돌아올 땐 나로 가득 <br>채워 줄게 My love <br>Welcome summer <br>Welcome summer <br>]]></content><category term="윤종신" label="윤종신"/><category term="Welcome Summer" label="Welcome Summer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박양원/예수로_죽고/</id><title>박양원 - 예수로 죽고 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:32:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:32:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%96%91%EC%9B%90/%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EB%A1%9C_%EC%A3%BD%EA%B3%A0/" title="박양원 - 예수로 죽고 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 위하여 죽으신 주님 <br>그 십자가 그 사랑의 흔적 <br>나를 위하여 흘리신 보혈 <br>그 보혈로 다시 내가 사네 <br>나를 위하여 죽으신 주님 <br>그 십자가 그 사랑의 흔적 <br>나를 위하여 흘리신 보혈 <br>그 보혈로 다시 내가 사네 <br>예수로 죽고 예수로 사는 <br>하나님의 나라 내 삶에 임하네 <br>그 말씀 따라서 믿음으로 서리라 <br>그 영원한 나라 이뤄지리 <br>나를 위하여 죽으신 주님 <br>그 십자가 그 사랑의 흔적 <br>나를 위하여 흘리신 보혈 <br>그 보혈로 다시 내가 사네 <br>예수로 죽고 예수로 사는 <br>하나님의 나라 내 삶에 임하네 <br>그 말씀 따라서 믿음으로 서리라 <br>그 영원한 나라 이뤄지리 <br>날 구원하신 주의 십자가 <br>그 능력 의지하여 날아가리라 <br>내가 예수로 죽고 그가 내 안에 사는 <br>완전한 그 사랑으로 <br>예수로 죽고 예수로 사는 <br>하나님의 나라 내 삶에 임하네 <br>그 말씀 따라서 믿음으로 서리라 <br>그 영원한 나라 주님의 나라 <br>이뤄지리 <br>주님의 나라 <br>이뤄지리 <br>]]></content><category term="박양원" label="박양원"/><category term="예수로 죽고" label="예수로 죽고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미스티/그거면_돼/</id><title>미스티 - 그거면 돼 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:32:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:32:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B0/%EA%B7%B8%EA%B1%B0%EB%A9%B4_%EB%8F%BC/" title="미스티 - 그거면 돼 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 바라보던 너의 그 두 눈이 <br>이젠 기억조차 나질 않아 <br>너를 떠올리려 눈을 감아봐도 <br>더는 네가 없는 나뿐인 걸 <br>우리 함께했던 추억들 모두다 <br>이젠 나 혼자서 간직할게 <br>같은 마음 이길 바랬었던 나를 <br>전부 잊고 행복하길 바래 <br>난 그거면 돼 <br>하나 둘 스쳐 지나는 <br>우리 둘만의 감정들 <br>이제는 느낄 수 없는 <br>숨을 쉬지 않는 기억들 <br>나 없는 넌 어딘가에서 <br>누군가와 있니 <br>너 없는 여기에서 <br>난 무엇도 할 수가 없는데 <br>나를 바라보던 너의 그 두 눈이 <br>이젠 기억조차 나질 않아 <br>너를 떠올리려 눈을 감아봐도 <br>더는 네가 없는 나뿐인 걸 <br>우리 함께했던 추억들 모두다 <br>이젠 나 혼자서 간직할게 <br>같은 마음 이길 바랬었던 나를 <br>전부 잊고 행복하길 바래 <br>난 그거면 돼 <br>너를 다시 볼 수 없을까 <br>우리 다시 할 순 없을까 <br>이대로만 가야 할까 <br>나를 바라보던 너의 그 두 눈이 <br>이젠 기억조차 나질 않아 <br>너를 떠올리려 눈을 감아봐도 <br>더는 네가 없는 나뿐인 걸 <br>우리 함께했던 추억들 모두다 <br>이젠 나 혼자서 간직할게 <br>같은 마음 이길 바랬었던 나를 <br>전부 잊고 행복하길 바래 <br>난 그거면 돼 <br>]]></content><category term="미스티" label="미스티"/><category term="그거면 돼" label="그거면 돼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/폴킴/있잖아/</id><title>폴킴 - 있잖아 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:32:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:32:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8F%B4%ED%82%B4/%EC%9E%88%EC%9E%96%EC%95%84/" title="폴킴 - 있잖아 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[있잖아 좀 늦은 거 아는데 <br>해야 하는 말이 꼭 생겼어 <br>아직 거기 서있다면 <br>잠깐만 내 얘길 들어줄래 <br>두드리고 계속 두드렸던 <br>너를 왜 몰랐을까 <br>닫힌 내 마음 앞에 앉아 <br>날 기다린 것도 말야 <br>지금 나 하나도 괜찮지가 않아 <br>지금 널 이대로 그냥 잃어버릴까봐 <br>널 보던 내 눈도 <br>널 떠올리면 웃고 있던 내 입술도 <br>사랑이더라 <br>알잖아 보기엔 참 쉬운데 <br>내가 하면 얘기가 다른 거 <br>겨우 내 맘을 알았고 <br>내겐 아직 많이 어려운데 <br>근데 말야 나는 하고 싶어 <br>너랑 그 연애란 거 <br>사실 난 엄청 신경 쓰여 <br>너에 대한 모든 게 다 <br>지금 나 하나도 괜찮지가 않아 <br>지금 널 이대로 그냥 잃어버릴까봐 <br>널 보던 내 눈도 <br>널 떠올리면 웃고 있던 내 입술도 <br>사랑이더라 <br>딴 생각은 안 할 거야 <br>이 감정에만 이젠 솔직할게 <br>날 헷갈리게 만들던 <br>그 이유를 좀 알 것 같아 <br>궁금해 넌 어때 어서 대답해봐 <br>어떻게 생각해 지금 고백하는 거야 <br>널 사랑한다고 <br>가슴 벅차게 사랑하고 있다고 <br>나 요즘에 너 땜에 괜찮지가 않아 <br>지금 널 이대로 그냥 잃어버릴까봐 <br>널 보던 내 눈도 <br>널 떠올리며 웃고 있던 내 입술도 <br>사랑이더라 <br>]]></content><category term="폴킴" label="폴킴"/><category term="있잖아" label="있잖아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Peg_O_My_Heart/</id><title>Gene Vincent - Peg O` My Heart - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Peg_O_My_Heart/" title="Gene Vincent - Peg O` My Heart - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Peg o'my heart <br>I love you, don't let us part <br>I love you, I always knew it would be you <br>Since I heard your lilting laughter <br>It's your Irish heart I'm after <br>Peg o'my heart <br>Your glances make my heart say How's chances <br>Come, be my own, come make your home in my heart]]></content><category term="Gene Vincent" label="Gene Vincent"/><category term="Peg O` My Heart" label="Peg O` My Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Bop_Street/</id><title>Gene Vincent - Bop Street - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Bop_Street/" title="Gene Vincent - Bop Street - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey cat, where are ya goin' man <br>Man, I'm going down to bop street <br>Tell me cat, where's that di rection <br>Man, ain't you heard they got one of 'em in every town <br>Real cool <br><br>Ba a op street, ba a op street <br>Oh, it's the cat and kittens of ol' bop street <br><br>Jumpin' jacks, they ain't no square <br>A green paint pants and great pair <br>On bop street they're the main attraction <br>'Cause they're the cats who crave the action <br>A jumpin' here, a jumpin' there <br>A jump jump jumpin' everyhere <br>The jumpin' Jacksons are hard to beat <br>'Cause they're the cats 'n' kittens of ol' bop street rock <br><br>Well, a dreamy day when it starts at nine <br>A rockin' and a rollin' all the time <br>A green blue jeans and crazy shoes <br>A jumpin' on bop street, losing the blues <br>A jumpin' here, a jumpin' there <br>A jump jump jumpin' everyhere <br>The jumpin' Jacksons are hard to beat <br>'Cause they're the cats 'n' kittens of ol' bop street jump, jack, jump <br><br>Well it's the street where the cool cats go <br>To spend their time and their hard earned dough <br>A boppin' on bop street, goin' 'round <br>The juke box music with the rockin' sound <br>Well a jumpin' here, jumpin' there <br>A jump jump jumpin' everyhere <br>The jumpin' jacksons are hard to beat <br>'Cause they're the cats 'n' kittens of ol' bop street <br><br>Ba a op street, ba a op street <br>Come on man, let's get going <br>Yeah, let's go on down to bop street <br>Ba a op street]]></content><category term="Gene Vincent" label="Gene Vincent"/><category term="Bop Street" label="Bop Street"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Jumps_Giggles_And_Shouts/</id><title>Gene Vincent - Jumps, Giggles And Shouts - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Jumps_Giggles_And_Shouts/" title="Gene Vincent - Jumps, Giggles And Shouts - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, I got a gal and her name is Jane <br>All the kids call her couldn't tame <br>Always boppin' 'round the town <br>Every bit all of her pound <br><br>She jumps giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts <br>Jump, Cliff, jump jump <br><br>Oh, I got a girl and her name is Lizzy <br>Ah man that woman sure is dizzy <br>Boppin' to the juke machine <br>Craziest cat you ever seen <br><br>She jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts <br>Jump, Jack, jump jump <br><br>She jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts <br>Jump, Dickie, jump jump <br><br>Oh, I got a girl and her name is Lizzy <br>Ah man that woman sure is dizzy <br>Boppin' to the juke machine <br>Craziest cat you ever seen <br><br>She jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts <br>Jump, Cliff, jump jump <br><br>She jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts, go <br>Jumps, giggles and shouts <br>Go, go, go, go o o o]]></content><category term="Gene Vincent" label="Gene Vincent"/><category term="Jumps, Giggles And Shouts" label="Jumps, Giggles And Shouts"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Wedding_Bells_Are_Breaking_Up_That_Old_Gang_Of_Mine/</id><title>Gene Vincent - Wedding Bells (Are Breaking Up That Old Gang Of Mine) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Wedding_Bells_Are_Breaking_Up_That_Old_Gang_Of_Mine/" title="Gene Vincent - Wedding Bells (Are Breaking Up That Old Gang Of Mine) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Not a soul down on the corner <br>That's a pretty certain sign <br>Those wedding bells are breaking up <br>That old gang of mine <br>All the boys are singing love songs <br>They forgot sweet Adeline <br>Those wedding bells are breaking up <br>That old gang of mine <br>Well, there goes Jack, there goes Jim <br>Strollin' down lover's lane <br>Now and then, we meet again <br>But they don't seem the same <br>Life gets that lonesome feeling <br>Then I hear the churchbells ring <br>Those wedding bells are breaking up <br>That old gang of mine <br><br>Well, there goes Jack, there goes Jim <br>Strollin' down lover's lane <br>Now and then, we meet again <br>But they don't seem the same <br>Life gets that lonesome feeling <br>Then I hear the churchbells ring <br>Those wedding bells are breaking up <br>That old gang of mine]]></content><category term="Gene Vincent" label="Gene Vincent"/><category term="Wedding Bells (Are Breaking Up That Old Gang Of Mine)" label="Wedding Bells (Are Breaking Up That Old Gang Of Mine)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/I_Flipped/</id><title>Gene Vincent - I Flipped - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/I_Flipped/" title="Gene Vincent - I Flipped - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I flipped flipped, flipped a flipped <br>I flipped flipped, flipped a flipped <br>I flipped flipped, flipped a flipped <br>I flipped flipped, flipped a flipped <br><br>I flipped my lane, I be in my town <br>When I get a rollin' on a real cool bop <br>I flipped flipped, flipped a flipped <br>I flipped flipped, flipped a flipped <br><br>Well my baby wandered in about a quarter to nine <br>A put it to me right on the line <br>She said you're square, join the ol' rat race <br>And come on hit the beat at a rapid pace <br>My oh my and slow girl slow <br>A come and get with it and go girl go <br>Go <br><br>Well, I slipped slipped, slipped a slipped <br>I slipped slipped, slipped a slipped <br>I slipped slipped, slipped a slipped <br>I slipped slipped, slipped a slipped <br><br>I slipped her calm, I swivel my back <br>Makin' like a jumping Jack <br>I slipped slipped, slipped a slipped <br>I slipped slipped, slipped a slipped <br>Rock it Blue Caps]]></content><category term="Gene Vincent" label="Gene Vincent"/><category term="I Flipped" label="I Flipped"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Aint_She_Sweet/</id><title>Gene Vincent - Ain`t She Sweet - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Aint_She_Sweet/" title="Gene Vincent - Ain`t She Sweet - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh ain't she sweet <br>Well see her walking down that street <br>Yes I ask you very confidentially <br>Ain't she sweet <br><br>Oh ain't she nice <br>Well look her over once or twice <br>Yes I ask you very confidentially <br>Ain't she nice <br><br>Just cast an eye <br>In her direction <br>Oh me oh my <br>Ain't that perfection <br><br>Oh I repeat <br>Well don't you think that's kind of neat <br>Yes I ask you very confidentially <br>Ain't she sweet <br><br>Oh ain't she sweet <br>Well see her walking down that street <br>Well I ask you very confidentially <br>Ain't she sweet <br><br>Oh ain't that nice <br>Well look it over once or twice <br>Yes I ask you very confidentially <br>Ain't she nice <br><br>Just cast an eye <br>In her direction <br>Oh me oh my <br>Ain't that perfection <br><br>Oh I repeat <br>Well don't you think that's kind of neat <br>Yes I ask you very confidentially <br>Ain't she sweet <br><br>Oh ain't she sweet <br>Well see her walking down that street <br>Well I ask you very confidentially <br>Ain't she sweet <br>Well I ask you very confidentially <br>Ain't she sweet]]></content><category term="Gene Vincent" label="Gene Vincent"/><category term="Ain`t She Sweet" label="Ain`t She Sweet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Who_Slapped_John_/</id><title>Gene Vincent - Who Slapped John? - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Who_Slapped_John_/" title="Gene Vincent - Who Slapped John? - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well I heard John say, Man, she's my gal <br>I heard another say, Man, she my pal <br>Well John jumped up, then he screamed <br>Well she's may gal, man, and that I mean <br>Well, who who, who slapped John <br>Who who, who slapped John <br>Baby, who slapped John when the lights went low oh <br>Who who, who slapped John <br>Jump, go cats go, all you cats cool it <br>Well, the lights went on, then went off <br>John got slapped tryin' to hold his own <br>Well, who who, who slapped John <br>Who who, who slapped John <br>Baby, who slapped John when the lights went low oh <br>Who who, who slapped John Jump <br>Well I heard John say, Man, she's my gal <br>I heard another say, Man, she my pal <br>Well John jumped up, then he screamed <br>She's may gal, man, and that I mean <br>Well, who who, who slapped John <br>Who who, who slapped John <br>Baby, who slapped John when the lights were low oh <br>Who who, who slapped John <br>Jump, go go go John go <br>Well, the lights went on, then went off <br>John got slapped tryin' to hold his own <br>Well, who who, who slapped John <br>Who who, who slapped John <br>Baby, who slapped John when the lights went low oh <br>Who who, who slapped John]]></content><category term="Gene Vincent" label="Gene Vincent"/><category term="Who Slapped John?" label="Who Slapped John?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Jezebel/</id><title>Gene Vincent - Jezebel - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Jezebel/" title="Gene Vincent - Jezebel - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jezebel It was you <br><br>If ever the devil was born <br>Without a pair of horns <br>It was you <br>Jezebel, it was you <br><br>If ever an angel fell <br>Jezebel <br>It was you <br>Jezebel, it was you <br><br>If ever a pair of eyes <br>Promised paradise <br>Deceiving me, grieving me <br>Leavin' me blue <br>Jezebel, it was you <br><br>If ever the devil's plan <br>Was made to torment man <br>It was you <br>Jezebel, it was you <br><br>If ever a pair of eyes <br>Promised paradise <br>Deceiving me, grieving me <br>Leavin' me blue <br>Jezebel, it was you <br><br>If ever the devil's plan <br>Was made to torment man <br>It was you <br>Night an' day, Jezebel <br>Oh, Jezebel, Jezebel, Jezebel]]></content><category term="Gene Vincent" label="Gene Vincent"/><category term="Jezebel" label="Jezebel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Bluejean_Bop/</id><title>Gene Vincent - Bluejean Bop - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Vincent/Bluejean_Bop/" title="Gene Vincent - Bluejean Bop - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bluejean baby, with your big blue eyes <br>Don't want you looking at other guys <br>Got to make you give me, one more chance <br>I can't keep still, so baby let's dance <br><br>Well the bluejean bop is the bop for me <br>It's the bop that's done in a dungaree <br>You flip your hip, free your knee <br>Squeel on your heel baby, one to three <br>Well the bluejean bop, bluejean bop <br>Oh baby, bluejean bop, bluejean bop <br>Oh baby, bluejean bop, baby won't you bop with Gene Bop Blue Caps, Bop <br><br>Well bluejean baby when I bop with you <br>Well my heart starts hoppin' like a kangaroo <br>My feet do things they never done before <br>Well bluejean baby, give me more more more <br>Well the bluejean bop, bluejean bop <br>Oh baby, bluejean bop, bluejean bop <br>Oh baby, bluejean bop, baby won't you bop with Gene Rock again Blue Caps, Go <br><br>Well the bluejean bop, bluejean bop <br>Oh baby, bluejean bop, bluejean bop <br>Oh baby, bluejean bop, baby won't you bop with Gene <br>Blue Caps, bop with Gene, Let's go <br><br>Well the bluejean bop, bluejean bop <br>Oh baby, bluejean bop, bluejean bop <br>Oh baby, bluejean bop, baby won't you bop with Gene]]></content><category term="Gene Vincent" label="Gene Vincent"/><category term="Bluejean Bop" label="Bluejean Bop"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Willie_The_Pimp_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - Willie The Pimp (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Willie_The_Pimp_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - Willie The Pimp (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm a little pimp with my hair gassed back <br>Pair a khaki pants with my shoe shined black <br><br>Got a little lady . . . walk the street <br>Tellin' all the boys that she cain't be beat <br><br>Twenny dollah bill (I can set you straight) <br>Meet me onna corner boy 'n don't be late <br><br>Man in a suit with a bow-tie neck <br>Wanna buy a grunt with a third party check <br><br>Standin' onna porch of the Lido Hotel <br>Floozies in the lobby love the way I sell: <br>HOT MEAT <br>HOT RATS <br>HOT CATS <br>HOT RITZ <br>HOT ROOTS <br>HOT SOOTS <br><br>HOT MEAT <br>HOT RATS <br>HOT CATS <br>HOT ZITZ <br>HOT ROOTS <br>HOT SOOTS]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="Willie The Pimp (Live)" label="Willie The Pimp (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Advance_Romance_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - Advance Romance (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Advance_Romance_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - Advance Romance (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No more credit <br>From the liquor store <br>Suit is all dirty, boy <br>Shoes is all wore <br>Tired and lonely, my <br>Heart is all sore <br>Advance romance <br>I can't stand it no more <br><br>Told me she loved me <br>I believed what she said <br>Took me for a sucker, boy <br>All corn-fed <br>Next thing I knew <br>She had a bolt on the door <br>Advance romance <br>I can't use it no more <br><br>She took George's watch <br>Like they always do <br>(It was a Timex, too!) <br>No more money, boy <br>I shoulda knew <br>The way she do me, boy <br>She might do you, too <br>Advance romance <br>People I am through! <br><br>Potato-head Bobby <br>was a friend of mine <br>Open three of his eyes <br>In the food stamp line <br>Open four of his eyes <br>In the food stamp line <br>Open five of his eyes <br>In the food stamp line <br>Open six of his yes <br>In the food stamp line <br>Said she might be a devil <br>But she sure was fine <br>Advance romance <br>He wanna try it one time <br><br>Later that night <br>He drop on by <br>Told her all he wanna do <br>Was step up and say "Hi" <br>Half an hour later <br>She had frenched his fry <br>Advance romance <br>Bobby, say good-bye]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="Advance Romance (Live)" label="Advance Romance (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Poofters_Froth_Wyoming_Plans_Ahead_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - Poofter`s Froth Wyoming Plans Ahead (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:33:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:33:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Poofters_Froth_Wyoming_Plans_Ahead_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - Poofter`s Froth Wyoming Plans Ahead (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Poofter's Froth, Wyoming <br>March Eleven Sixty-Seven <br>Take a letter <br>Miss Abetter <br>As our pigeons <br>Will be homing <br><br>To our jobbers in Dakota <br>And to Merwyn, Minnesota <br>This is merely just a note about <br>Performance to our quota <br><br>Well, we all come out <br>To show dem <br>An' the Elks have helped us <br>Load 'em <br>Little packets full of jackets <br>Little rackets, little rackets <br><br>Little Poofter - Cloth Appointments <br>Little Poofter's Froth Anointments <br>Little hoods, little goods <br>Little doo-dads from the woods <br>The entire stock is shipping <br>Oh our shod is hardly slipping <br>To the markets of the world <br>Our wrinkled pennants are unfurled! <br><br>T-shirt racks, rubber snacks <br>Poster rolls with matching tacks <br>Yes, a special beer for sports <br>(and paper cups that hold two quarts) <br><br>Everything a nation needs <br>For making hoopla while if feeds <br>The trash compactors, small reactors <br>Mowers, blowers, throwers &amp; the glowers: <br><br>This is Buy-Cent-Any-All Salute (HYULK!) <br>Two hundred years have gone ka-poot! <br>Ah but we have been astute! <br>Signed: Anon. - Wyo. Galoot!]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="Poofter`s Froth Wyoming Plans Ahead (Live)" label="Poofter`s Froth Wyoming Plans Ahead (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Penguin_In_Bondage_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - Penguin In Bondage (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Penguin_In_Bondage_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - Penguin In Bondage (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Thank you. (Brian, I could use a little bit more monitor). Hello hello (can't you turn it up any more than that?) Hello hello . . . Hey! Alright! Pardon me, folks. The name of this song is "Penguin in Bondage," an' it's a song that, uh, deals with the possible variations on a basic theme which is . . . well, you understand what the basic theme is. And then the variations include, uh, manoeuvres that might be executed with the aid of, uh, extra-terrestrial gratification and devices which might or might not be supplied in a local department store or perhaps a drugstore but at very least in one of those fancy new shops that they advertise in the back-pages of the free press. This song suggests to the suggestible listener that the ordinary procedure, uh, that I'm circumlocuting at this present time in order to get this text on television, is that, uh, if you wanna do something other than what you thought you were gonna do when you first took your clothes off and you just happened to have some DEVICES around . . . then it's, it's not only okay to get into the PARAPHERNALIA of it all but . . . hey! What did he say? Ready? <br><br>She's just like a Penguin in Bondage, boy <br>Oh yeah, Oh yeah, Oh . . . <br>Rennenhenninnahenninnenninahennn <br>Way over on the wet side <br>Of the bed (Knirps for moisture) <br><br>Just like the mighty Penguin <br>Flappin' her eight ounce wings <br>(The Penguin Flap) <br><br>Lord, you know it's all over <br>If she come atcha on the strut &amp; wrap 'em all around yer head <br>Flappin' her eight ounce wings, flappinumm <br><br>She's just like a Penguin in Bondage, boy <br><br>Shake up the pale-dry <br>Ginger ale <br><br>Tremblin' like a Penguin <br>When the battery fail <br><br>Lord, you must be havin' her jumpin' through a hoopa real fire <br>With some Kleenex wrapped around a coat-hang wire <br><br>She's just like a Penguin in Bondage, boy <br>Oh yeah, Oh yeah, Oh . . . <br>Rennenhenninnahenninneninahenn <br>Howlin' over to some <br>Antarcticulated moon <br><br>In the frostbite nite <br>With her flaps gone white <br>Shriekin' as she spot the hoop across the room <br>(Everytime she sees the hoop) <br><br>You know it must be a Penguin bound down <br>If you hear that terrible screamin' and there ain't no other <br>Birds around <br><br>She's just like a Penguin in Bondage, boy <br>Oh yeah, Oh yeah, Oh . . . <br>She's just like a Penguin in Bondage, boy <br>Oh yeah, Oh yeah, Oh . . . <br>Rennenhenninnahenninneninahennnn <br>Aw, you must be careful <br>Not to leave her straps <br>TOO LOOSE <br><br>'Cause she just might box yer dog <br>She just might box yer doggie <br>An' leave you a dried-up dog biscuit . . .]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="Penguin In Bondage (Live)" label="Penguin In Bondage (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Sam_With_The_Showing_Scalp_Flat_Top_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - Sam With The Showing Scalp Flat Top (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Sam_With_The_Showing_Scalp_Flat_Top_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - Sam With The Showing Scalp Flat Top (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sam with the showing scalp flat top <br>Particular about the point it made. <br>(I got it . . . ) <br>Why, when I was knee-high to a grasshopper <br>This black juice came out on a hard shelled chin. <br>And they called that 'tobacco juice'. <br>I used to fiddle with my back feet music for a black onyx. <br>My entire room absorbed every echo. <br>The music was . . . thud like. <br>The music was . . . thud like. <br>I usually played such things as rough-neck and thug. <br>Opaque melodies that would bug most people. <br>Music from the other side of the fence. <br>A black swan figurine lay on all color lily pads. <br>On a little conglomeration table of pressed black felt. <br>With same color shadows, in seamed knobbed knees, and what-nots. <br>The long hallway rolled out into oddball odd. <br>Beside the fly-pecked black doorway <br>That looked closed on the tar-lattice street. <br>Up a wrought iron fire escape. <br>Rolled out a tiny wooden platform with dark, hard, dark rubber wheels. <br>Roll, skreek! Roll, skreek! Roll, skreek! <br>Sam with the showing scalp flat top <br>Particular about the point it made. <br><br>Sam was a BASKET CASE! <br>A hardened dark ivory clip held . . . saleable everyday pencils. <br>I wish I had a pair 'o bongos! <br>Bongo Fury! <br>Bongo Fury! <br>Oowwwww! Bongo Fury! <br>(Boogie!) <br>Bongo Fury! <br>Bongo Fury . . . <br>Bongo Fury]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="Sam With The Showing Scalp Flat Top (Live)" label="Sam With The Showing Scalp Flat Top (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Montana_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - Montana (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Montana_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - Montana (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I might be movin' to Montana soon <br>Just to raise me up a crop of <br>Dental Floss <br><br>Raisin' it up <br>Waxen it down <br>In a little white box <br>That I can sell uptown <br><br>By myself I wouldn't <br>Have no boss <br>But I'd be raisin' my lonely <br>Dental Floss <br><br>Raisin' my lonely <br>Dental Floss <br><br>Well I just might grow me some bees <br>But I'd leave the sweet stuff <br>To somebody else . . . but then, on the other hand I would <br><br>Keep the wax <br>'N melt it down <br>Pluck some Floss <br>'N swish it aroun' <br><br>I'd have me a crop <br>An' it'd be on top (that's why I'm movin' to Montana) <br><br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>Gonna be a Dental Floss tycoon (yes I am) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>Gonna be a mennil-toss flykune <br><br>I'm pluckin' the ol' <br>Dennil Floss <br>That's growin' on the prairie <br>Pluckin' the floss! <br>I plucked all day an' all nite an' all <br>Afternoon . . . <br><br>I'm ridin' a small tiny hoss <br>(His name is MIGHTY LITTLE) <br>He's a good hoss <br>Even though <br>He's a bit dinky to strap a big saddle or <br>Blanket on anyway <br>He's a bit dinky to strap a big saddle or <br>Blanket on anyway <br>Any way <br><br>I'm pluckin' the ol' <br>Dennil Floss <br>Even if you think it is a little silly, folks <br>I don't care if you think it's silly, folks <br>I don't care if you think it's silly, folks <br><br>I'm gonna find me a horse <br>Just about this big <br>An' ride him all along the border line <br><br>With a <br>Pair of heavy-duty <br>Zircon-encrusted tweezers in my hand <br>Every other wrangler would say <br>I was mighty grand <br><br>By myself I wouldn't <br>Have no boss <br>But I'd be raisin' my lonely <br>Dental Floss <br><br>Raisin' my lonely <br>Dental Floss <br>Raisin' my lonely <br>Dental Floss <br><br>Well I might <br>Ride along the border <br>With my tweezers gleamin' <br>In the moon-lighty night <br><br>And then I'd <br>Get a cuppa cawfee <br>'N give my foot a push . . . <br>Just me 'n the pygmy pony <br>Over by the Dennil Floss Bush <br><br>'N then I might just <br>Jump back on <br>An' ride <br>Like a cowboy <br>Into the dawn to Montana <br><br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay) <br>Movin' to Montana soon <br>(Yippy-Ty-O-Ty-Ay)]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="Montana (Live)" label="Montana (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/The_Torture_Never_Stops_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - The Torture Never Stops (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/The_Torture_Never_Stops_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - The Torture Never Stops (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Flies all green 'n buzzin' in his dungeon of despair <br>Prisoners grumble and piss their clothes and scratch their matted hair <br>A tiny light from a window hole a hundred yards away <br>Is all they ever get to know about the regular life in the day; <br>An' it stinks so bad the stones been chokin' <br>'N weepin' greenish drops <br>In the room where the giant fire puffer works <br>'N the torture never stops <br>The torture never stops <br><br>Slime 'n rot, rats 'n snot 'n vomit on the floor <br>Fifty ugly soldiers, man, holdin' spears by the iron door <br>Knives 'n spikes 'n guns 'n the likes of every tool of pain <br>An' a sinister midget with a bucket an' a mop where the blood goes down the drain; <br><br>An' it stinks so bad the stones been chokin' <br>'N weepin' greenish drops <br>In the room where the giant fire puffer works <br>'N the torture never stops <br>The torture never stops <br>The torture <br>The torture <br>The torture never stops. <br><br>Flies all green 'n buzzin' in his dungeon of despair <br>An evil prince eats a steamin' pig in a chamber right near there <br>He eats the snouts 'n the trotters first <br>The loin's 'n the groin's is soon dispersed <br>His carvin' style is well rehearsed <br>He stands and shouts <br>All men be cursed <br>All men be cursed <br>All men be cursed <br>All men be cursed <br>And disagree, well no-one durst <br>He's the best of course of all the worst <br>Some wrong been done, he done it first <br><br>(Well, well) An' he stinks so bad, his bones been chokin' <br>(Yeah) 'N weepin' greenish drops <br>(Well) In the night of the iron sausage <br>(Well) Where the torture never stops <br>The torture never stops <br>The torture <br>The torture <br>The torture never stops. <br><br>Flies all green 'n buzzin' in his dungeon of despair <br>Who are all those people that he's locked away up there <br>Are they crazy? <br>Are they sainted? <br>Are they zeros someone painted? <br>It has never been explained since at first it was created <br>But a dungeon like a sin <br>Requires naught but lockin' in <br>Of everything that's ever been <br>Look at hers <br>Look at him <br>That's what's the deal we're dealing in <br>That's what's the deal we're dealing in <br>That's what's the deal we're dealing in <br>That's what's the deal we're dealing in]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="The Torture Never Stops (Live)" label="The Torture Never Stops (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/A_Pound_For_A_Brown_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - A Pound For A Brown (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/A_Pound_For_A_Brown_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - A Pound For A Brown (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uncle Meat <br>Ahead Of Their Time <br>Zappa In New York <br>You Can't Do That On Stage Anymore Vol. 4 <br>You Can't Do That On Stage Anymore Vol. 5 <br>The Yellow Shark <br><br>Fade!]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="A Pound For A Brown (Live)" label="A Pound For A Brown (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Carolina_Hard-Core_Ecstasy_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - Carolina Hard-Core Ecstasy (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Carolina_Hard-Core_Ecstasy_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - Carolina Hard-Core Ecstasy (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I coulda swore her hair was made of rayon <br>She wore a Milton Bradley Crayon <br>But she was something I could lay on <br>Can't remember what became of me . . . <br>Carolina Hardcore Ecstasy <br><br>She put a Doobie Brothers tape on <br>I had a Roger Daitrey cape on <br>There was a bed I dumped her shape on <br>Can't remember what became of me . . . <br>Carolina Hardcore Ecstasy <br><br>Somewhat later on <br>I woke up and she was gone <br>There was dew out on the lawn <br>In the sunrise <br>Later she came back <br>With a rumpled paper sack <br>Which she told me would contain <br>A surprise <br><br>She stuck her hand right in it to the bottom <br>Said she knew I'd be surprised she got'em <br>Take a Charleston pimp to spot 'em <br>Then she gave a pair of shoes to me ... <br>Plastic leather, 14 Triple D <br><br>I said: I wonder what's the shoes for <br>She told me: Don't you worry no more <br>And got right down there on the tile floor: <br>Now Darling STOMP ALL OVER ME! ... <br>Carolina Hardcore Ecstasy <br><br>Is this something new <br>Having people stomp on you? <br>Is it what I need to do <br>For your pleasure? <br>What is this, a quiz? <br>Don't you worry what it is <br>It is merely just a moment <br>I can treasure <br><br>By ten o'clock her arms and legs were rendered <br>She couldn't talk 'cause her mouth had been extendered <br>Looked to me as though she had been blendered <br>But was this abject misery? <br>No! No! <br>Carolina Hardcore Ecstasy! <br><br>It might seem strange to Herb and Dee - <br>Carolina Hardcore Ecstasy!]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="Carolina Hard-Core Ecstasy (Live)" label="Carolina Hard-Core Ecstasy (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Im_Not_Satisfied_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - I`m Not Satisfied (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Im_Not_Satisfied_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - I`m Not Satisfied (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah! <br><br>Got no place to go <br>(I'm tired of walking <br>Up and down the street all by myself) <br>No love left for me to give <br>(I tried and tried <br>But no one wants me the way I am) <br>Why should I pretend I like <br>To roam from door to door <br>Maybe I'll just kill myself <br>I just don't care no more <br><br>Because <br>I'm not satisfied <br>Everything I've tried <br>I don't like the way <br>Life has been abusing me <br><br>Yeah! <br>Yeah! <br><br>Who would care <br>If I was gone <br>(I never met no one <br>Who'd care if I was dead and gone) <br>Who needs me <br>To care for them <br>(Nobody needs me <br>Why should I just hang around?) <br>Why should I just sit and watch <br>While the others smile <br>I just wish that someone cared <br>If I was happy for a while <br>Because <br>I'm not satisfied <br>Everything I've tried <br>I don't like the way <br>Life has been abusing me <br><br>Yeah!]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="I`m Not Satisfied (Live)" label="I`m Not Satisfied (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Stinkfoot_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - Stinkfoot (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Stinkfoot_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - Stinkfoot (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the dark <br>Where all the fevers grow <br>Under the water <br>Where the shark bubbles blow <br>In the mornin' <br>By yer radio <br>Do the walls close in t' suffocate ya <br>You ain't got no friends . . . <br>An' all the others: they hate ya <br>Does the life you been livin' gotta go, hmmm? <br>Well, lemme straighten you out <br>About a place I know . . . <br>(Get yer shoes 'n socks on people <br>It's right aroun' the corner!) <br>Out through the night <br>An' the whispering breezes <br>To the place where they keep <br>The Imaginary Diseases <br>Out through the night <br>An' the whispering breezes <br>To the place where they keep <br>The Imaginary Diseases, mmm . . . <br><br>This has to be the disease for you <br>Now scientists call this disease <br>Bromidrosis <br>But us regular folks <br>Who might wear tennis shoes <br>Or an occasional python boot <br>Know this exquisite little inconvenience <br>By the name of: <br>STINK FOOT <br>Y'know, my python boot is too tight <br>I couldn't get it off last night <br>A week went by, an' now it's July <br>I finally got it off <br>An' my girl-friend cry <br>"You got STINK FOOT! <br>STINK FOOT, darlin' <br>Your STINK FOOT puts a hurt on my nose! <br>STINK FOOT! STINK FOOT! I ain't lyin' <br>Can you rinse it off, d'you suppose?" <br>Here Fido . . . Fido . . . <br>C'mere little puppy . . . bring the slippers <br>"Arf, arf, arf!" (crash-crumble-bump-bump-bump) <br>Heh heh heh . . . sick . . . <br><br>Well then Fido got up off the floor an' he rolled over <br>An' he looked me straight in the eye <br>An' you know what he said? <br>Once upon a time <br>Somebody say to me <br>(This is a dog talkin' now) <br>What is your Conceptual Continuity? <br>Well, I told him right then <br>(Fido said) <br>It should be easy to see <br>The crux of the biscuit <br>Is the Apostrophe(') <br>Well, you know <br>The man who was talkin' to the dog <br>Looked at the dog an' he said: (sort of staring in disbelief) <br>"You can't say that!" <br>He said: <br>"IT DOESN'T, 'n YOU CAN'T! <br>I WON'T, 'n IT DON'T! <br>IT HASN'T, IT ISN'T, IT EVEN AIN'T <br>'N IT SHOULDN'T . . . <br>IT COULDN'T!" <br>He told me NO NO NO! <br>I told him YES YES YES! <br>I said: "I do it all the time . . . <br>Ain't this boogie a mess!" <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES <br>THE POODLE CHEWS IT <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES <br>THE POODLE CHEWS IT <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES <br>THE POODLE CHEWS IT <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES <br>THE POODLE CHEWS IT <br>(POO-DLE . . . ) <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES <br>( . . . BITES) <br>THE POODLE CHEWS IT <br>(POO-DLE . . . ) <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES <br>( . . . BITES) <br>THE POODLE CHEWS IT <br>(POO-DLE . . . ) <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES <br>( . . . BITES) <br>THE POODLE CHEWS IT <br>(POO-DLE . . . ) <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES <br>( . . . BITES) <br>THE POODLE CHEWS IT <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES <br>THE POODLE CHEWS IT <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES <br>THE POODLE CHEWS IT <br>THE POODLE BY-EE-ITES]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="Stinkfoot (Live)" label="Stinkfoot (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Muffin_Man_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - Muffin Man (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Muffin_Man_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - Muffin Man (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The Muffin Man is seated at the table <br>In the laboratory of the Utility Muffin <br>Research Kitchen . . . <br>Reaching for an oversized chrome spoon <br>He gathers an intimate quantity of dried muffin remnants <br>And brushing his scapular aside <br>Proceeds to dump these inside of his shirt. . . <br>He turns to us and speaks: <br>"Some people like cupcakes better. I for one <br>Care less for them!" <br>Arrogantly twisting the sterile canvas snoot <br>of a fully charged icing anointment utensil <br>He pools forth a quarter-ounce green rosette (oh ah yuk yuk. <br>let's try that again . . .!) <br>He pools forth a quarter-ounce green rosette <br>Near the summit of a dense but radiant muffin <br>of his own design. <br>Later he says: "Some people . . . some people like cupcakes exclusively <br>While I myself say there is naughl nor ought there be <br>Nothing so exalted on the faceof God's grey earth <br>As that prince of foods . . . The Muffin!" <br><br>Girl you thoughl he was a man <br>Bul he was a muffin <br>He hung around lill you found <br>That he didn't know nuthin' <br>Girl you thought he was a man <br>But he only was a-puffin' <br>No cries is heard in the night <br>As a result of him stuffin']]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="Muffin Man (Live)" label="Muffin Man (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Camarillo_Brillo_Live/</id><title>Frank Zappa - Camarillo Brillo (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Zappa/Camarillo_Brillo_Live/" title="Frank Zappa - Camarillo Brillo (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She had that <br>Camarillo brillo <br>Flamin' out along her head <br>I mean her Mendocino bean-o <br>By where some bugs had made it red <br><br>She ruled the Toads of the Short Forest <br>And every newt in Idaho <br>And every cricket who had chorused <br>By the bush in Buffalo <br><br>She said she was <br>A Magic Mama <br>And she could throw a mean Tarot <br>And carried on without a comma <br>That she was someone I should know <br><br>She had a snake for a pet <br>And an amulet <br>And she was breeding a dwarf <br>But she wasn't done yet <br>She had gray-green skin <br>A doll with a pin <br>I told her she was awright <br>But I couldn't come in <br>(I couldn't come in right then . . . ) <br><br>And so she wandered <br>Through the door-way <br>Just like a shadow from the tomb <br>She said her stereo was four-way <br>An' I'd just love it in her room <br><br>Well, I was born <br>To have adventure <br>So I just followed up the steps <br>Right past her fuming incense stencher <br>To where she hung her castanets <br><br>She stripped away <br>Her rancid poncho <br>An' laid out naked by the door <br>We did it till we were un-concho <br>An' it was useless any more <br><br>She had a snake for a pet <br>And an amulet <br>And she was breeding a dwarf <br>But she wasn't done yet <br>She had gray-green skin <br>A doll with a pin <br>I told her she was awright <br>But I couldn't come in <br>(actually, I was very busy then) <br><br>And so she wandered <br>Through the door-way <br>Just like a shadow from the tomb <br>She said her stereo was four-way <br>An' I'd just love it in her room <br><br>Well, I was born <br>To have adventure <br>So I just followed up the steps <br>Right past her fuming incense stencher <br>To where she hung her castanets <br><br>She said she was <br>A Magic Mama <br>And she could throw a mean Tarot <br>And carried on without a comma <br>That she was someone I should know <br><br>(Is that a real poncho . . . I mean <br>Is that a Mexican poncho or is that a Sears poncho? <br>Hmmm . . . no foolin' . . . )]]></content><category term="Frank Zappa" label="Frank Zappa"/><category term="Camarillo Brillo (Live)" label="Camarillo Brillo (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Clark/Ill_Feel_A_Whole_Lot_Better_Live/</id><title>Gene Clark - I`ll Feel A Whole Lot Better (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Clark/Ill_Feel_A_Whole_Lot_Better_Live/" title="Gene Clark - I`ll Feel A Whole Lot Better (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The reason why oh, I can't say <br>I gotta let you go, babe and run away <br>After what you did I can't stay on <br>And I'll probably feel a whole lot better when you're gone <br>Baby, for a long time (Baby, for a long time) you had me believe (Had me believe) <br>You said your love was all mine (That your love was all mine) that's the way it would be (Ah, ah, ah) <br>But I didn't know (I didn't know) that you were putting me on (Ah, ah, ah) <br>And I'll probably feel a whole lot better when you're gone <br>Oh, when you're gone <br><br>Now I got to say (I got to say) that it's not like before (That it's not like before) <br>And I'm not gonna play (And I'm not gonna play) your game anymore (Oh, oh, oh) <br>After what you did (After what you did) I can't stay on (Ah, ah, ah) <br>And I'll probably feel a whole lot better when you're gone <br>Oh, when you're gone <br>Oh, when you're gone <br>Oh, when you're gone]]></content><category term="Gene Clark" label="Gene Clark"/><category term="I`ll Feel A Whole Lot Better (Live)" label="I`ll Feel A Whole Lot Better (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Clark/Mr_Tambourine_Man_Live/</id><title>Gene Clark - Mr Tambourine Man (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:34:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:34:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Clark/Mr_Tambourine_Man_Live/" title="Gene Clark - Mr Tambourine Man (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, Mr. Tambourine Man, play a song for me <br>I'm not sleepy and there is no place I'm going to <br>Hey, Mr. Tambourine Man, play a song for me <br>In the jingle jangle morning, I'll come followin' you <br><br>Though I know that evenin's empire has returned into sand <br>Vanished from my hand <br>Left me blindly here to stand but still not sleeping <br>My weariness amazes me, I'm branded on my feet <br>I have no one to meet <br>And the ancient empty street's too dead for dreaming <br><br>Hey, Mr. Tambourine Man, play a song for me <br>I'm not sleepy and there is no place I'm going to <br>Hey, Mr. Tambourine Man, play a song for me <br>In the jingle jangle morning, I'll come followin' you <br><br>Take me on a trip upon your magic swirlin' ship <br>My senses have been stripped, my hands can't feel to grip <br>My toes too numb to step <br>Wait only for my boot heels to be wanderin' <br>I'm ready to go anywhere, I'm ready for to fade <br>Into my own parade, cast your dancing spell my way <br>I promise to go under it <br><br>Hey, Mr. Tambourine Man, play a song for me <br>I'm not sleepy and there is no place I'm going to <br>Hey, Mr. Tambourine Man, play a song for me <br>In the jingle jangle morning, I'll come followin' you <br><br>Though you might hear laughin', spinnin', swingin' madly across the sun <br>It's not aimed at anyone, it's just escapin' on the run <br>And but for the sky there are no fences facin' <br>And if you hear vague traces of skippin' reels of rhyme <br>To your tambourine in time, it's just a ragged clown behind <br>I wouldn't pay it any mind, it's just a shadow you're seein' that he's chasing <br><br>Hey, Mr. Tambourine Man, play a song for me <br>I'm not sleepy and there is no place I'm going to <br>Hey, Mr. Tambourine Man, play a song for me <br>In the jingle jangle morning, I'll come followin' you <br><br>Then take me disappearin' through the smoke rings of my mind <br>Down the foggy ruins of time, far past the frozen leaves <br>The haunted, frightened trees, out to the windy beach <br>Far from the twisted reach of crazy sorrow <br>Yes, to dance beneath the diamond sky with one hand waving free <br>Silhouetted by the sea, circled by the circus sands <br>With all memory and fate driven deep beneath the waves <br>Let me forget about today until tomorrow <br><br>Hey, Mr. Tambourine Man, play a song for me <br>I'm not sleepy and there is no place I'm going to <br>Hey, Mr. Tambourine Man, play a song for me <br>In the jingle jangle morning, I'll come followin' you]]></content><category term="Gene Clark" label="Gene Clark"/><category term="Mr Tambourine Man (Live)" label="Mr Tambourine Man (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Clark/Rain_Song_Live/</id><title>Gene Clark - Rain Song (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-04T00:35:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-04T00:35:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gene_Clark/Rain_Song_Live/" title="Gene Clark - Rain Song (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Today the rain came down again <br>And washed away the light <br>So night could then descend <br>I saw your face again <br>The rain came down today <br>The things we had to say <br>Were also washed away <br>Again that was yesterday <br>And though I feel the same <br>I can't go back again <br><br>Ooh, the rain <br>Ooh, the rain <br><br>Oh, I had that dream again <br>In the hour before the dawn <br>And I don't know what it means <br>But I saw your face again <br>The rain came down today <br>The things we had to say <br>Were also washed away <br>Again that was yesterday <br>And though I feel the same <br>I can't go back again <br>Because the rain is gonna come another day <br><br>Ooh, the rain <br><br>Ooh, the rain <br>Ooh, the rain]]></content><category term="Gene Clark" label="Gene Clark"/><category term="Rain Song (Live)" label="Rain Song (Live)"/></entry></feed>