<feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:07:10+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송도엘/선덕여왕_Feat_숨니/</id><title>송도엘 - 선덕여왕 (Feat. 숨니) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:07:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:07:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%8F%84%EC%97%98/%EC%84%A0%EB%8D%95%EC%97%AC%EC%99%95_Feat_%EC%88%A8%EB%8B%88/" title="송도엘 - 선덕여왕 (Feat. 숨니) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄이 왔죠 어김없이 당신도 <br>나에게로 왔나요 봄바람 <br>닮은 당신은 참 설레이네요 <br>날 감싸줄껀가요 봄처럼 <br>사람들 속 수많은 무리 중에 <br>저기 그대 보여요 내 맘은 <br>그대보다 먼저 봄이 온거죠 <br>그댈 보다 봄이 온걸 느끼죠 <br>그대는 살랑살랑해 <br>내 맘은 또 두근 두근대 <br>그대를 보고 있으면 <br>마주하고 있으면 <br>그대가 아른아른해 <br>내 맘은 또 선덕 선덕해 <br>이런 내 마음을 흩날리는 <br>벚꽃 잎 속에 숨겨보아요 <br>오지 않을 것 같던 봄이 왔고 <br>널 닮은 봄바람마저 난 느껴 <br>근데 내심 불안한건 계절이 <br>떠나가듯 너도 날 떠날까봐 <br>봄이 왔죠 어김없이 당신도 <br>나에게로 왔나요 봄바람 <br>닮은 당신은 참 설레이네요 <br>날 안아줄껀가요 봄처럼 <br>사람들 속 수많은 무리 중에 <br>저기 그대 보여요 내 맘은 <br>그대보다 먼저 봄이 온거죠 <br>그댈 보다 봄이 온 걸 느끼죠 <br>그대는 살랑살랑해 <br>내 맘은 또 두근 두근대 <br>그대를 보고 있으면 <br>마주하고 있으면 <br>그대가 아른아른해 <br>내 맘은 또 선덕 선덕해 <br>이런 내 마음을 흩날리는 <br>벚꽃 잎 속에 숨겨 <br>그대는 살랑 살랑해 <br>내 맘은 또 두근 두근대 <br>그대를 보고 있으면 <br>마주하고 있으면 <br>그대가 아른 아른해 <br>내 맘은 또 선덕 선덕해 <br>이런 내 마음을 흩날리는 <br>벚꽃 잎 속에 숨겨보아요 <br>그대는 선덕 선덕해 <br>]]></content><category term="송도엘" label="송도엘"/><category term="선덕여왕 (Feat. 숨니)" label="선덕여왕 (Feat. 숨니)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Natasha_Bedingfield/Let_Go/</id><title>Natasha Bedingfield - Let Go - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:07:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:07:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Natasha_Bedingfield/Let_Go/" title="Natasha Bedingfield - Let Go - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah Yeah Yeah <br>Hey <br><br>Foggy mornings, weekday grind <br>Take a minute to free your mind <br>Monday madness, Sunday's best <br>Let's go take a walk and catch our breath <br><br>Can't let the little things, get you down <br>The sun is shining, let's enjoy right now <br>No matter where we go, when we close our eyes <br>Know it'll be alright alright <br>Well dive through the ocean <br>And soar through the skies <br>Let go and enjoy the ride <br>Hey <br><br>La La La La La La La La La <br>La La La La La La La La La <br>La La La La La La La La La <br>Let go and enjoy the ride <br><br>Waves are crashing <br>Sandy feet <br>Let our troubles wash out to sea <br>Climb a mountain, name a star <br>We are free to be who we are <br>You know it doesnt get better than this <br><br>No matter where we go, when we close our eyes <br>Know it'll be alright alright <br>We'll dive through the ocean <br>And soar through the skies <br>Let go and enjoy the ride enjoy the ride <br>Yeah <br><br>La La La La La La La La La enjoy the ride <br>La La La La La La La La La <br>La La La La La La La La La <br>Let go and enjoy the ride <br><br>Just let it go <br>Just let it go <br>Just let it go just let it go <br>Just let it go, oh, oh <br>Oh <br><br>No matter where we go, when we got our eyes closed <br>We know we'll be alright, hey hey <br>No matter where we go, when we got our eyes closed <br>We know we'll be alright, hey hey we know we'll be alright <br>No matter where we go, when we got our eyes closed <br>We know we'll be alright <br><br>La La La La La La La La La enjoy the ride <br>La La La La La La La La La <br>La La La La La La La La La <br>Let go and enjoy the ride]]></content><category term="Natasha Bedingfield" label="Natasha Bedingfield"/><category term="Let Go" label="Let Go"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mansionz/Gorgeous/</id><title>Mansionz - Gorgeous - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:13:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:13:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mansionz/Gorgeous/" title="Mansionz - Gorgeous - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Chorus: blackbear] <br>Did you know you're on fire? <br>Did you know that you're beautiful? <br>Did you know you got me fucked up? <br>Did you know that you're gorgeous? <br><br>[Verse 1: Mike Posner] <br>Alright, I can still remember how the weed smelled <br>When you were riding shotgun, no seat belt <br>Or the SS just taking hits <br>Sold that car and fucked up that relationship <br>I've built up my walls perhaps too tall <br>Got issues with trusting but that's not all <br>Knots tied by fame and not easily undone <br>I fucked 200 women, said, "I love you" to one <br>She used to speak like she was reading a scene <br>And make love like she was a martyr <br>The only thing about flames that bright <br>Is they tend to make mine seem darker <br><br>[Chorus: blackbear] <br>Did you know you're on fire? <br>Did you know that you're beautiful? <br>Did you know you got me fucked up? <br>Did you know that you're gorgeous? <br>Did you know that you're <br>Did you know that you're gorgeous? <br>Did you know that you're <br>Did you know that you're gorgeous? <br><br><br>[Verse 2: blackbear] <br>Yeah, yeah, in and out of love <br>On and off of drugs <br>I ask you where you've been <br>And you give me shoulder shrugs <br>Pink polka dot top from Saint Laurent <br>I bought you but you never wore it <br>And I don't even send the text <br>I know you just ignore it <br>And I'm so high <br>Could be the drugs, could be the moment <br>But either way I can't keep my eyes off you <br><br>[Chorus: blackbear] <br>Did you know you're on fire? <br>Did you know that you're beautiful? <br>Did you know you got me fucked up? <br>Did you know that you're gorgeous? <br>Did you know that you're <br>Did you know that you're gorgeous? <br>Did you know that you're <br>Did you know that you're gorgeous?]]></content><category term="Mansionz" label="Mansionz"/><category term="Gorgeous" label="Gorgeous"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DJ_Snake/Here_Comes_The_Night_Acoustic_Ver_Feat_Mr_Hudson/</id><title>DJ Snake - Here Comes The Night (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. Mr Hudson) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:16:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:16:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DJ_Snake/Here_Comes_The_Night_Acoustic_Ver_Feat_Mr_Hudson/" title="DJ Snake - Here Comes The Night (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. Mr Hudson) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's no light, no light in the sky <br>And it gets so cold when she leaves my side <br>Maybe she's the light, the light in my eyes <br>'Cause everything looks old and tired when she leaves my side <br><br>I know, I know, I know, I know you got to leave <br>So I'll bite my tongue until that fuck completes <br>Yeah, I know, I know, I know, I can be alright <br>But see, you set my sun, so here comes the night <br>Here comes the night, here comes the night <br>Yeah, I know, I know, I know, I can be alright <br>Here comes the night, here comes the <br>Here comes the night <br><br>Here comes the night <br>Here comes the night <br><br>There's no light, no light in the sky <br>And it gets so cold when she leaves my side <br>Maybe she's the light, the light in my eyes <br>'Cause everything looks old and tired when she leaves my side <br><br>I know, I know, I know, I know you got to leave <br>So I'll bite my tongue until that fuck completes <br>Yeah, I know, I know, I know, I can be alright <br>But see, you set my sun, so here comes the night <br>Here comes the night, here comes the night here comes the night <br>Yeah, I know, I know, I know, I can be alright <br>Here comes the night, here comes the <br>Here comes the night <br><br>Here comes the night <br>Here comes the night <br><br>I know, I know, I know, I know you got to leave]]></content><category term="DJ Snake" label="DJ Snake"/><category term="Here Comes The Night (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. Mr Hudson)" label="Here Comes The Night (Acoustic Ver.) (Feat. Mr Hudson)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hjalmer/Marie/</id><title>Hjalmer - Marie - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:22:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:22:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hjalmer/Marie/" title="Hjalmer - Marie - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Marie var som skabt for mig <br>Men sa snart hun viste sig <br>Ku' jeg maerke modet svinde <br><br>Og med ord, der kun blev faerre <br>Sku' jeg prove at erklaere <br>Hva' jeg folte for hende <br><br>Men alt jeg ville sige <br>Det sagde Marie <br>For jeg ku' ytre mig <br>Hand i hand gik vi hjemad <br>Fra det ojeblik af <br>Var vi aldrig hver for sig <br><br>En dag smilte hun og sagde <br>At om to og fyrre dage <br>Tog hun et ars tid til Mexico <br><br>Der var et liv for hende der <br>Men selv om jeg sku' blive her <br>Ku' det stadig vaere os to <br><br>Og hvad kunne jeg sige <br>Da jeg sa Marie <br>Fuld af mod pa eventyr <br>Jeg matte da kunne laere <br>At kunne baere <br>Vi sku' vaere hver for sig <br><br>Ja, hvem sagde, du sku' vaere nemt <br>At bo pa hvert sit kontinent <br>Jeg taenker kun pa hendes faerden <br><br>Vi ligger, som vi selv har redt <br>Men mit indre, det er spredt <br>For hver en vind i hele verden <br><br>Er der mon mere at sige <br>Nar mig og Marie <br>Endelig ses igen <br>Eller ender det hele <br>Og skal vi sa dele <br>Gyldne minder hver for sig <br><br>Traekke vejret hver for sig <br>Marie, kom nu hjem til mig]]></content><category term="Hjalmer" label="Hjalmer"/><category term="Marie" label="Marie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Riot_Kidz/Birthday/</id><title>Riot Kidz - Birthday - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:22:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:22:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Riot_Kidz/Birthday/" title="Riot Kidz - Birthday - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everything that I made <br>Was it good <br>Was it nice for your birthday <br>I don't have anything <br>but little peace <br>And I know you won't like it <br>Cuz it's cheap <br>Everything that I made <br>Was it good <br>Was it nice for your birthday <br>I don't have anything <br>but little peace <br>And I know you won't like it <br>Cuz it's cheap <br>Oh you got up <br>It's a fine day right <br>You want something <br>to eat for breakfast <br>How do you feel <br>Are you excited <br>Are you gonna hang out <br>with your friends tonight <br>I know you don't really care <br>about the price if the gift <br>but I wanna give you <br>something special <br>I wanted to give you <br>what you want so I tried <br>but I couldn't give you <br>cuz of your boys <br>I'm sorry Ah Ah <br>Everything that I made <br>Was it good <br>Was it nice for your birthday <br>I don't have anything <br>but little peace <br>And I know you won't like it <br>Cuz it's cheap <br>Oh you got a date for sunday <br>I think he's very handsome <br>cuz his yours <br>Okay then um <br>Have a nice day <br>I'm just gonna keep the gift <br>that I got for you <br>I know you don't really care <br>about the price if the gift <br>but I wanna give you <br>something special <br>I wanted to give you <br>what you want so I tried <br>but I couldn't give you <br>cuz of your boys <br>I'm sorry Ah Ah <br>Everything that I made <br>Was it good <br>Was it nice for your birthday <br>I don't have anything <br>but little peace <br>And I know you won't like it <br>Cuz Everything that I made <br>Was it good <br>Was it nice for your birthday <br>I don't have anything <br>but little peace <br>And I know you won't like it <br>Cuz it's cheap <br>]]></content><category term="Riot Kidz" label="Riot Kidz"/><category term="Birthday" label="Birthday"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이해리_다비치/소주_한_잔_장화신고_노래할고양/</id><title>이해리 (다비치) - 소주 한 잔 (장화신고 노래할고양) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:23:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:23:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%B4%EB%A6%AC_%EB%8B%A4%EB%B9%84%EC%B9%98/%EC%86%8C%EC%A3%BC_%ED%95%9C_%EC%9E%94_%EC%9E%A5%ED%99%94%EC%8B%A0%EA%B3%A0_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%95%A0%EA%B3%A0%EC%96%91/" title="이해리 (다비치) - 소주 한 잔 (장화신고 노래할고양) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[술이 한 잔 생각나는 밤 <br>같이 있는 것 같아요 <br>그 좋았던 시절들 <br>이젠 모두 한숨만 되네요 <br>사람이 변하는 걸요 <br>다시 전보다 그댈 원해요 <br>이렇게 취할 때면 <br>꺼져버린 전화를 붙잡고 <br>여보세요 나야 거기 잘 지내니 <br>여보세요 왜 말 안하니 <br>울고 있니 내가 오랜만이라서 <br>사랑하는 사람이라서 <br>그대 소중한 마음 밀쳐낸 <br>이기적인 그 때의 나에게 <br>그대를 다시 불러오라고 <br>미친 듯이 외쳤어 <br>떠나는 그대 얼굴이 <br>마치 처음과 같아서 <br>나 눈물이 났어요 <br>그 때부터 그리워요 <br>사람이 변하는 걸요 <br>다시 전보다 그댈 원해요 <br>이렇게 취할 때면 <br>바뀌어버린 전화번호 누르고 <br>여보세요 나야 <br>여보세요 나야 거기 잘 지내니 <br>오랜만이야 내 사랑아 <br>그대를 다시 불러오라고 <br>미친 듯이 울었어 <br>여보세요 나야 <br>정말 미안해 <br>이기적인 그 때의 나에게 <br>그대를 다시 불러오라고 <br>미친 듯이 울었어 <br>]]></content><category term="이해리 (다비치)" label="이해리 (다비치)"/><category term="소주 한 잔 (장화신고 노래할고양)" label="소주 한 잔 (장화신고 노래할고양)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소향/사랑아_노래_9단_흥부자댁/</id><title>소향 - 사랑아 (노래 9단 흥부자댁) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:23:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:23:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%ED%96%A5/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%95%84_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_9%EB%8B%A8_%ED%9D%A5%EB%B6%80%EC%9E%90%EB%8C%81/" title="소향 - 사랑아 (노래 9단 흥부자댁) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혼자서 불러보는 <br>가슴 아픈 그 이름 <br>눈물이 새어 나올까봐 <br>입술을 깨물고 <br>또 다시 다짐한 듯 <br>가슴을 펴 보지만 <br>홀로 남겨진 내 모습이 <br>더욱 초라해져 <br>사랑아 그리운 내 사랑아 <br>이렇게 아픈 내 사랑아 <br>얼마나 아프고 아파해야 <br>아물 수 있겠니 <br>혼자서 불러보는 <br>가슴 아픈 그 이름 <br>워 <br>사랑아 그리운 내 사랑아 <br>이렇게 아픈 내 사랑아 <br>얼마나 아프고 아파해야 <br>아물 수 있겠니 <br>사랑아 미련한 내 사랑아 <br>버릴 수 없는 내 욕심에 <br>못다한 사랑이 서러워서 <br>또 이렇게 운다 <br>사랑아 내 사랑아 <br>사랑아 그리운 내 사랑아 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>널 사랑해 아픈 내 사랑아 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>못다한 사랑이 서러워서 <br>또 이렇게 또 이렇게 또 이렇게 <br>운다 <br>]]></content><category term="소향" label="소향"/><category term="사랑아 (노래 9단 흥부자댁)" label="사랑아 (노래 9단 흥부자댁)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/배인혁/담배_가게_아가씨_양천구_목동_양치기소년/</id><title>배인혁 - 담배 가게 아가씨 (양천구 목동 양치기소년) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:23:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:23:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B0%EC%9D%B8%ED%98%81/%EB%8B%B4%EB%B0%B0_%EA%B0%80%EA%B2%8C_%EC%95%84%EA%B0%80%EC%94%A8_%EC%96%91%EC%B2%9C%EA%B5%AC_%EB%AA%A9%EB%8F%99_%EC%96%91%EC%B9%98%EA%B8%B0%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84/" title="배인혁 - 담배 가게 아가씨 (양천구 목동 양치기소년) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리 동네 담배가게에는 <br>아가씨가 예쁘다네 <br>짧은 머리 곱게 빗은 것이 <br>정말로 예쁘다네 <br>온 동네 청년들이 <br>너도 나도 기웃기웃기웃 <br>그러나 그 아가씨는 새침떼기 <br>앞 집의 꼴뚜기 녀석은 <br>딱지를 맞았다네 <br>만화가게 용팔이 녀석도 <br>딱지를 맞았다네 <br>그렇다면 동네에선 <br>오직 하나 나만 남았는데 <br>자 기대하시라 개봉박두 <br>다음날 아침 일찍부터 <br>담배 하나 사러가서 <br>가지고 간 장미 한 송이를 <br>살짝 건네어 주고 <br>그 아가씨 놀랄 적에 <br>눈싸움 한 판을 벌인다 <br>아자자 자자자자 <br>자자 자자 자자 자자아 <br>그 아가씨 웃었어 <br>하루 종일 가슴 설레이며 <br>퇴근시간 기다렸지 <br>오랜만에 말끔히 차려 입고 <br>그 아가씨 기다렸지 <br>점잖게 다가서서 <br>미소 띄며 인사를 했지 <br>그러나 그 아가씨는 하 콧방귀 <br>그렇다고 이대로 물러나면 <br>대장부가 아니지 <br>그 아가씨 발걸음 소리 맞춰 <br>뒤따라 걸어간다 <br>틀려서는 안되지 번호 붙여 <br>One Two Three <br>아 위대할 손 나의 끈기 <br>바로 그 때 이 것 참 야단났네 <br>골목길 어귀에서 <br>아랫동네 불량배들에게 <br>그 아가씨 포위됐네 <br>옳다구나 이때다 <br>백마의 기사가 나가신다 <br>아자자 자자자자 <br>자자 자자 자자 자자아 <br>와자 짯자 와자 짯자 <br>와자 짯자 와자 짯자 <br>와 하늘빛이 노랗다 <br>우리 동네 담배가게에는 <br>아가씨가 예쁘다네 <br>지금은 그 때보다 <br>백배는 예쁘다네 <br>나를 보면 웃어주는 아가씨 <br>나는 정말 I Love You <br>아자자 자자자자 <br>자자 자자 자자 자자 <br>이리 오너라 업고 놀자 <br>아 나는 지금 담배 사러 간다 <br>]]></content><category term="배인혁" label="배인혁"/><category term="담배 가게 아가씨 (양천구 목동 양치기소년)" label="담배 가게 아가씨 (양천구 목동 양치기소년)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/소향/아틀란티스_소녀_노래_9단_흥부자댁/</id><title>소향 - 아틀란티스 소녀 (노래 9단 흥부자댁) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:23:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:23:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%8C%ED%96%A5/%EC%95%84%ED%8B%80%EB%9E%80%ED%8B%B0%EC%8A%A4_%EC%86%8C%EB%85%80_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_9%EB%8B%A8_%ED%9D%A5%EB%B6%80%EC%9E%90%EB%8C%81/" title="소향 - 아틀란티스 소녀 (노래 9단 흥부자댁) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저 먼 바다 끝엔 뭐가 있을까 <br>다른 무언가 세상과는 먼 얘기 <br>구름 위로 올라가면 보일까 <br>천사와 나팔부는 아이들 <br>숲 속 어디엔가 귀를 대보면 <br>오직 내게만 <br>작게 들려오는 목소리 <br>꿈을 꾸는 듯이 날아가볼까 <br>저기 높은 곳 아무도 없는 세계 <br>그렇게도 많던 질문과 <br>풀리지 못한 <br>나의 수많은 얘기가 <br>돌아보고 서면 언제부턴가 <br>나도 몰래 잊고 있던 나만의 비밀 <br>이제 정말 왜 이래 <br>나 이제 커버린 걸까 <br>이제 정말 뭔가 잃어버린 기억 <br>지금 내 맘 <br>이젠 나의 그 작은 소망과 <br>꿈을 잃지 않기를 <br>저 하늘 속에 속삭일래 <br>다른 무언가 <br>까만 밤하늘에 밝게 빛나던 <br>별들 가운데 <br>나 태어난 곳 있을까 <br>나는 지구인과 다른 곳에서 <br>내려 온 거라 <br>믿고 싶기도 했어 <br>그렇게도 많던 질문과 풀리지 못한 <br>나의 수많은 얘기가 <br>돌아보고 서면 언제 부턴가 <br>나도 몰래 잊고 있던 나만의 비밀 <br>이제 정말 왜 이래 <br>나 이제 커버린 걸까 <br>이제 정말 뭔가 잃어버린 기억 <br>지금 내 맘 <br>이젠 나의 그 작은 소망과 <br>꿈을 잃지 않기를 저 하늘 속에 <br>왜 이래 나 이제 커버린 걸까 <br>이제 정말 뭔가 잃어버린 기억 <br>지금 내 맘 <br>이젠 나의 그 작은 소망과 <br>꿈을 잃지 않기를 <br>저 하늘 속에 속삭일래 <br>너무나도 좋은 향기와 <br>바람이 나에게로 다가와 <br>어느샌가 나도 모르게 <br>가만히 들려오는 작은 속삭임 <br>귀를 기울이고 불러보세요 <br>다시 찾게 될 거예요 잊혀진 기억 <br>생각해봐 나 이제 <br>더 이상 놓치진 않아 <br>소중했던 나의 잃어버린 기억 <br>지금 내 맘 이젠 <br>나의 그 작은 소망과 <br>꿈을 잃지 않기를 저 하늘 속에 <br>왜 이래 나 이제 커버린 걸까 <br>왜이래 <br>이제 정말 나 이제 커버린 걸까 <br>이젠 나의 그 작은 소망과 <br>꿈을 잃지 않기를 저 하늘 속에 <br>기도할래 <br>]]></content><category term="소향" label="소향"/><category term="아틀란티스 소녀 (노래 9단 흥부자댁)" label="아틀란티스 소녀 (노래 9단 흥부자댁)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이홍기_FT_아일랜드/서쪽하늘_여심도둑_괴도루팡/</id><title>이홍기 (FT 아일랜드) - 서쪽하늘 (여심도둑 괴도루팡) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:23:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:23:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%99%8D%EA%B8%B0_FT_%EC%95%84%EC%9D%BC%EB%9E%9C%EB%93%9C/%EC%84%9C%EC%AA%BD%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98_%EC%97%AC%EC%8B%AC%EB%8F%84%EB%91%91_%EA%B4%B4%EB%8F%84%EB%A3%A8%ED%8C%A1/" title="이홍기 (FT 아일랜드) - 서쪽하늘 (여심도둑 괴도루팡) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[서쪽 하늘로 노을은 지고 <br>이젠 슬픔이 돼 버린 그대를 <br>다시 부를 수 없을 것 같아 <br>또 한 번 불러보네 <br>소리쳐 불러도 늘 허공에 <br>부서져 돌아오는 너의 이름 <br>이젠 더 견딜힘조차 없게 <br>날 버려두고 가지 <br>사랑하는 날 떠나가는 날 <br>하늘도 슬퍼서 울어준 날 <br>빗속에 떠날 나였음을 <br>넌 알고 있는 듯이 <br>비가 오는 날엔 <br>난 항상 널 그리워해 <br>언젠간 널 다시 만나는 <br>그 날을 기다리며 <br>비 내린 하늘은 <br>왜 그리 날 슬프게 해 <br>흩어진 내 눈물로 널 잊고 싶은데 <br>사랑하는 날 떠나가는 날 <br>하늘도 슬퍼서 울어준 날 <br>빗속에 떠날 나였음을 <br>넌 알고 있는 듯이 <br>비가 오는 날엔 <br>난 항상 널 그리워해 <br>언젠간 널 다시 만나는 <br>그 날을 기다리며 <br>비 내린 하늘은 <br>왜 그리 날 슬프게 해 <br>흩어진 내 눈물로 널 잊고 싶은데 <br>가고 싶어 널 보고 싶어 <br>꼭 찾고 싶었어 <br>하지만 너의 모습은 <br>아직도 그 자리에 <br>비가 오는 날엔 <br>비가 오는 날엔 <br>난 항상 널 그리워해 <br>언젠간 널 다시 만나는 <br>그 날을 기다리며 <br>비 내린 하늘은 <br>왜 그리 날 슬프게 해 <br>흩어진 내 눈물로 널 잊고 싶은데 <br>하지만 난 널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="이홍기 (FT 아일랜드)" label="이홍기 (FT 아일랜드)"/><category term="서쪽하늘 (여심도둑 괴도루팡)" label="서쪽하늘 (여심도둑 괴도루팡)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핫펠트_예은/크로스컨트리_Cross_Country_Inst/</id><title>핫펠트 (예은) - 크로스컨트리 (Cross Country) (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:24:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:24:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%AB%ED%8E%A0%ED%8A%B8_%EC%98%88%EC%9D%80/%ED%81%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%8A%A4%EC%BB%A8%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC_Cross_Country_Inst/" title="핫펠트 (예은) - 크로스컨트리 (Cross Country) (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저 먼 곳에 있는 듯해 <br>닿을 수 있을까 some day <br>꿈을 꾸네 when sky is grey <br>Rains falling in California <br>막다른 길 한계선 끝에 다다라도 <br>We gotta go though it seems <br>like a dead end dead end <br>숨막히는 짙은 어둠 속의 반복 <br>Still gotta go <br>새 길을 열어 <br>walk thru the dead end <br>We‘re not afraid <br>길을 잃어도 갈래 빛을 향해 <br>Must ride again <br>답을 찾을때까진 끝난게 아냐 <br>멈추지마 Cuz hope never die <br>이 가리워진 길 속에 <br>희미하게 비추는 별빛 <br>보이지 않아도 느껴져 <br>Stars crying in California <br>메마른 땅엔 두 뺨을 <br>스치는 모래바람 <br>그속에서 견뎌내 <br>like Joshua tree yeah tree yeah <br>결국에는 비도 바람도 그치는 법 <br>Then sun will rise 새롭게 시작해 <br>from the dead end <br>We‘re not afraid <br>길을 잃어도 갈래 빛을 향해 <br>Must ride again <br>답을 찾을때까진 끝난게 아냐 <br>멈추지마 Cuz hope never die <br>저 먼 곳에 있는 듯해 <br>내 카오스가 낳은 춤추는 별 <br>꿈을 꾸네 when sky is grey <br>가장 밝게 빛날 my star <br>We‘re not afraid <br>길을 잃어도 갈래 빛을 향해 <br>Must ride again <br>답을 찾을때까진 끝난게 아냐 <br>멈추지마 Cuz hope never die <br>We‘re not afraid <br>길을 잃어도 갈래 빛을 향해 <br>Must ride again <br>답을 찾을때까진 끝난게 아냐 <br>멈추지마 Cuz hope never die <br>]]></content><category term="핫펠트 (예은)" label="핫펠트 (예은)"/><category term="크로스컨트리 (Cross Country) (Inst.)" label="크로스컨트리 (Cross Country) (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핫펠트_예은/크로스컨트리_Cross_Country/</id><title>핫펠트 (예은) - 크로스컨트리 (Cross Country) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:24:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:24:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%AB%ED%8E%A0%ED%8A%B8_%EC%98%88%EC%9D%80/%ED%81%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%8A%A4%EC%BB%A8%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC_Cross_Country/" title="핫펠트 (예은) - 크로스컨트리 (Cross Country) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[크로스컨트리 (Cross Country) <br><br>저 먼 곳에 있는 듯해 <br>닿을 수 있을까 some day <br>꿈을 꾸네 when sky is grey <br>Rains falling in California <br>막다른 길 한계선 끝에 다다라도 <br>We gotta go though it seems <br>like a dead end dead end <br>숨막히는 짙은 어둠 속의 반복 <br>Still gotta go <br>새 길을 열어 <br>walk thru the dead end <br>We‘re not afraid <br>길을 잃어도 갈래 빛을 향해 <br>Must ride again <br>답을 찾을때까진 끝난게 아냐 <br>멈추지마 Cuz hope never die <br>이 가리워진 길 속에 <br>희미하게 비추는 별빛 <br>보이지 않아도 느껴져 <br>Stars crying in California <br>메마른 땅엔 두 뺨을 <br>스치는 모래바람 <br>그속에서 견뎌내 <br>like Joshua tree yeah tree yeah <br>결국에는 비도 바람도 그치는 법 <br>Then sun will rise 새롭게 시작해 <br>from the dead end <br>We‘re not afraid <br>길을 잃어도 갈래 빛을 향해 <br>Must ride again <br>답을 찾을때까진 끝난게 아냐 <br>멈추지마 Cuz hope never die <br>저 먼 곳에 있는 듯해 <br>내 카오스가 낳은 춤추는 별 <br>꿈을 꾸네 when sky is grey <br>가장 밝게 빛날 my star <br>We‘re not afraid <br>길을 잃어도 갈래 빛을 향해 <br>Must ride again <br>답을 찾을때까진 끝난게 아냐 <br>멈추지마 Cuz hope never die <br>We‘re not afraid <br>길을 잃어도 갈래 빛을 향해 <br>Must ride again <br>답을 찾을때까진 끝난게 아냐 <br>멈추지마 Cuz hope never die <br>]]></content><category term="핫펠트 (예은)" label="핫펠트 (예은)"/><category term="크로스컨트리 (Cross Country)" label="크로스컨트리 (Cross Country)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/위아영_WeAreYoung/사실은_Inst/</id><title>위아영 (WeAreYoung) - 사실은 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:24:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:24:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%84%EC%95%84%EC%98%81_WeAreYoung/%EC%82%AC%EC%8B%A4%EC%9D%80_Inst/" title="위아영 (WeAreYoung) - 사실은 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사실은 내가 너를 좋아한다 <br>그 한마디가 내겐 왜 힘들까요 <br>누군가 떠나간 빈 공간에도 <br>내 자린 없는 걸까요 <br>그럴 수는 없나요 <br>얼마나 많은 날들을 <br>홀로 외로워했는지 <br>얼마나 오랜 시간을 <br>홀로 괴로워했는지 <br>그럴 땐 항상 곁에서 <br>서있는 나를 돌아봐주기를 <br>얼마나 많은 날들을 <br>너로 채워왔는지 <br>얼마나 오랜 시간을 <br>너로 그려왔는지 <br>곁에서 있는 나를 <br>한번쯤 돌아봐주길 바랄게 <br>사실은 내가 너를 좋아한다 <br>그 한마디 오늘도 난 참을게요 <br>너의 빈 공간에 나란 존재가 <br>부담이 아닐 때까지 <br>]]></content><category term="위아영 (WeAreYoung)" label="위아영 (WeAreYoung)"/><category term="사실은 (Inst.)" label="사실은 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/위아영_WeAreYoung/사실은/</id><title>위아영 (WeAreYoung) - 사실은 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:25:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:25:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%84%EC%95%84%EC%98%81_WeAreYoung/%EC%82%AC%EC%8B%A4%EC%9D%80/" title="위아영 (WeAreYoung) - 사실은 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사실은 내가 너를 좋아한다 <br>그 한마디가 내겐 왜 힘들까요 <br>누군가 떠나간 빈 공간에도 <br>내 자린 없는 걸까요 <br>그럴 수는 없나요 <br>얼마나 많은 날들을 <br>홀로 외로워했는지 <br>얼마나 오랜 시간을 <br>홀로 괴로워했는지 <br>그럴 땐 항상 곁에서 <br>서있는 나를 돌아봐주기를 <br>얼마나 많은 날들을 <br>너로 채워왔는지 <br>얼마나 오랜 시간을 <br>너로 그려왔는지 <br>곁에서 있는 나를 <br>한번쯤 돌아봐주길 바랄게 <br>사실은 내가 너를 좋아한다 <br>그 한마디 오늘도 난 참을게요 <br>너의 빈 공간에 나란 존재가 <br>부담이 아닐 때까지 <br>]]></content><category term="위아영 (WeAreYoung)" label="위아영 (WeAreYoung)"/><category term="사실은" label="사실은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lee_Kernaghan/High_Country/</id><title>Lee Kernaghan - High Country - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:25:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:25:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lee_Kernaghan/High_Country/" title="Lee Kernaghan - High Country - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Honey pack your bags, grab your old blue jeans <br>We're gonna go fishin' in a mountain stream <br>Well I know a little shack way up in the hills <br>Twenty five miles from Harrietville <br>In the high country <br><br>Honey you should see all the stars up there <br>They shine so bright through the cold night air <br>I'm gonna build you a fire that'll burn real hot <br>And I'll stay with you at the old camp hut <br>In the high country <br><br>I've got my four wheel drive and I'm ready to roll <br>I wanna go flying'UP an old dirt road <br>Up in the hills where the brumbies roam <br>This land must be surely be gods own <br>In the high country, in the high country <br><br>In the drought of 1882 <br>The Maddisons brought the cattle through <br>From Mountain Creek to the Staircase Spur <br>We'll follow the tracks where they pushed the herd <br>In the high country <br><br>High country that's where I wanna be <br>Walkin' with you by a mountain stream <br>High country that's where I wanna go <br>Got my bags packed, I'm ready to roll <br><br>I've got my four wheel drive and I'm ready to roll <br>I wanna go flying'UP an old dirt road <br>Up in the hills where the brumbies roam <br>This land must be surely be gods own <br>In the high country, in the high country <br>I'm headin' for the hi gh country <br>Headin' for the hi gh country <br>Headin' for the high country <br>That's where I wanna go, High country]]></content><category term="Lee Kernaghan" label="Lee Kernaghan"/><category term="High Country" label="High Country"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이루/바보같아요_Inst/</id><title>이루 - 바보같아요 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:29:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:29:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A3%A8/%EB%B0%94%EB%B3%B4%EA%B0%99%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94_Inst/" title="이루 - 바보같아요 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하지 못한 말이 있어요 <br>그대에겐 할 수 없는 <br>내 마음 하나 전할 수 없는 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>하고 싶은 말이 있어요 <br>그대에겐 할 수 없는 <br>나 혼자서만 말할 수 있는 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>가슴속 깊은 곳 숨겨둔 <br>그대를 향한 내 마음을 <br>아직도 꺼내지 못하고 있죠 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>가슴속 깊은 곳 숨겨둔 <br>그대를 향한 내 마음을 <br>아직도 꺼내지 못하고 있죠 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>하지 못한 말이 있어요 <br>그대에겐 할 수 없는 <br>내 마음 하나 전할 수 없는 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>하고 싶은 말이 있어요 <br>그대에겐 할 수 없는 <br>나 혼자서만 말할 수 있는 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>]]></content><category term="이루" label="이루"/><category term="바보같아요 (Inst.)" label="바보같아요 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이루/바보같아요/</id><title>이루 - 바보같아요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:29:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:29:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A3%A8/%EB%B0%94%EB%B3%B4%EA%B0%99%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="이루 - 바보같아요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하지 못한 말이 있어요 <br>그대에겐 할 수 없는 <br>내 마음 하나 전할 수 없는 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>하고 싶은 말이 있어요 <br>그대에겐 할 수 없는 <br>나 혼자서만 말할 수 있는 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>가슴속 깊은 곳 숨겨둔 <br>그대를 향한 내 마음을 <br>아직도 꺼내지 못하고 있죠 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>가슴속 깊은 곳 숨겨둔 <br>그대를 향한 내 마음을 <br>아직도 꺼내지 못하고 있죠 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>하지 못한 말이 있어요 <br>그대에겐 할 수 없는 <br>내 마음 하나 전할 수 없는 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>하고 싶은 말이 있어요 <br>그대에겐 할 수 없는 <br>나 혼자서만 말할 수 있는 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>이런 내가 바보 같아요 <br>]]></content><category term="이루" label="이루"/><category term="바보같아요" label="바보같아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/영크림_Young_Cream/Better_know_Feat_J-Boog/</id><title>영크림 (Young Cream) - Better know (Feat. J-Boog) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:29:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:29:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%81%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%BC_Young_Cream/Better_know_Feat_J-Boog/" title="영크림 (Young Cream) - Better know (Feat. J-Boog) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You better understand <br>Yeah I’ve been working all day <br>Cuz I really wanna get it <br>Money who can hate it <br>So let's turn on the light <br>Better know yeah <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>난 쉬고 싶지 않고 원해 <br>더 많은 것을 비싼 차 돈 명예 <br>여자와 도시 속 고급빌딩 그 높은 <br>옥상 위에서 매주 벌어지는 Party <br>So I wake up in the morning <br>날 부르고 있어 돈이 <br>누구처럼 멍청하게 살기엔 <br>부족하잖아 시간이 <br>땜에 늘어지지 않지 <br>아침부터 새벽까지 <br>Keep makin’ my song <br>When I’m in the zone <br>Don’t look at my phone <br>집중해 놀지 않고 <br>가사대로 지켜야지 내 가족도 <br>You better know 더 바쁘게 일하지 <br>죽어 관에 들어가기 전 <br>관둘 리는 없으니까 늘 성실히 <br>How u feelin' How u feelin’ <br>I’m at the 서초 반포대로 28길 <br>작업이 끝난 뒤엔 Chillin’ <br>Young Cream &amp; DBC를 찾는다면 <br>Hit me up <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>I gotta go better know <br>that you should go away <br>Being together won't get us <br>no where <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>I gotta go yeah <br>Better know we ain’t sleeping <br>Get it all for the weekend <br>Get it all for my people <br>Put it all on the visa <br>And all I need <br>all I need is a shot <br>We got the keys &amp; this dream <br>shit on lock <br>Yeah I swear this shit too easy <br>And I know they hating on us <br>I won’t sweat the shit <br>believe me <br>Yeah now they all know <br>Hop in let’s all roll <br>&amp; Bitch I don’t do off-days <br>no re-runs <br>No ahh waits just keep up <br>I’m always so deep huh <br>It’s all ours say aww lawwd <br>Let’s all ball &amp; ball hard <br>Yeah I’m getting all I see <br>yeah all I see <br>I’m Feelin’ <br>like I’m real life greedy <br>I gotta kill these niggas <br>feel like they real life need me <br>I know they do They know <br>it’s true <br>I gotta go said it’s time <br>to get some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>I gotta go better know <br>that you should go away <br>Being together won't get us <br>no where <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>You better know bitch <br>I want some mo’ <br>I gotta go yeah <br>]]></content><category term="영크림 (Young Cream)" label="영크림 (Young Cream)"/><category term="Better know (Feat. J-Boog)" label="Better know (Feat. J-Boog)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/퓨어킴/딸_또래/</id><title>퓨어킴 - 딸 또래 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:29:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:29:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%93%A8%EC%96%B4%ED%82%B4/%EB%94%B8_%EB%98%90%EB%9E%98/" title="퓨어킴 - 딸 또래 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여기선 지금 이렇게 말하고 <br>저기선 나중에 저렇게 하라지 <br>모든 사람의 모든 이야길 <br>모두 믿고 앉아서 <br>일어나 섰다가 <br>걷고 뛰었다가 날았다 <br>니가 사는 핑계가 <br>일 년에 한 만개쯤은 될 거야 <br>때 되면 차갑듯 불안해하면서 <br>이 분은 바로 이러라고 하고 <br>저 분은 이따가 저래라 하시지 <br>하던 대로 하면 <br>서서히 비치다 <br>퍼져 나가게 될 거야 <br>이대로가 좋아 <br>좋은 거라서 좋다고 하는 거야 <br>기억해 니가 잘하면 남기고 <br>못 하면 넘길게 <br>남기다 넘기다가 <br>사랑 안에 담겨서 <br>곧게 솟을 때에 그 다음에도 <br>이곳은 이제 가야 한다 하고 <br>저곳은 지나서 갈 수 있다 하지 <br>모든 사람의 모든 이야길 <br>모두 믿고 앉아서 <br>일어나 섰다가 <br>걷고 뛰었다가 날았다 <br>니가 파는 관심들 <br>일 년에 한 만개쯤은 될 거야 <br>때 되면 뜨겁듯 답답해하면서 <br>]]></content><category term="퓨어킴" label="퓨어킴"/><category term="딸 또래" label="딸 또래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Codigo_FN/¿Por_Que_He_De_Ser_Yo__Album_Ver/</id><title>Codigo FN - ¿Por Que He De Ser Yo? (Album Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:35:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:35:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Codigo_FN/%C2%BFPor_Que_He_De_Ser_Yo__Album_Ver/" title="Codigo FN - ¿Por Que He De Ser Yo? (Album Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo no imagine <br>Que haberte encontrado y despues perderte <br>Me doliera tanto <br><br>Y luego pense <br>Si deje las huellas en tu corazon <br>Porque no me has buscado <br><br>Y la conclusion <br>A este problema <br>Jamas te he importado <br><br>Por Que He De Ser Yo <br>Quien acepta el error si siempre has sido tu <br>Quien ya se canso de compartir conmigo <br>Toda una ilusion <br><br>Por Que He De Ser Yo <br>Si en vez de compania <br>Nunca estas conmigo <br><br>Por Que He De Ser Yo <br>Si aqui en el error <br><br>Siempre has sido tu <br><br> Y simplemente Codigo FN <br><br>Por Que He De Ser Yo <br>Quien acepta el error si siempre has sido tu <br>Quien ya se canso de compartir conmigo <br>Toda una ilusion <br><br>Por Que He De Ser Yo <br>Si en vez de compania <br>Nunca estas conmigo <br><br>Por Que He De Ser Yo <br>Si aqui en el error <br><br>Siempre has sido tu <br><br>Por Que He De Ser Yo <br>Quien acepta el error si siempre has sido tu <br>Quien ya se canso de compartir conmigo <br>Toda una ilusion <br><br>Por Que He De Ser Yo <br>Si en vez de compania <br>Nunca estas conmigo <br><br>Por Que He De Ser Yo <br>Si aqui en el error <br><br>Siempre has sido tu]]></content><category term="Codigo FN" label="Codigo FN"/><category term="¿Por Que He De Ser Yo? (Album Ver.)" label="¿Por Que He De Ser Yo? (Album Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Lonesome_George/</id><title>Hollerado - Lonesome George - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:37:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:37:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Lonesome_George/" title="Hollerado - Lonesome George - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Talk slow my love <br>This weary heart don't hear so good <br>We sleep all day <br>So we can love through one more night <br>Don't wait <br>When its time for you <br>To walk, brave, into the dark <br>And I'm low in this world for a while <br>Walk over me <br>Walk over me <br>You got no way <br>You got no way to break my heart <br>You got no way <br>You got no way to break my heart <br>You got no way <br>You got no way to break my heart <br>Cause its mine <br>And it knows <br>Your are everywhere <br>Walk over me <br>Walk over me]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Lonesome George" label="Lonesome George"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Too_Much_To_Handle/</id><title>Hollerado - Too Much To Handle - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:37:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:37:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Too_Much_To_Handle/" title="Hollerado - Too Much To Handle - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Another week where I wanna try stealing <br>Air with some of the kindness, I'm suicide <br>You had to smile at the break boards baby <br>And you, you used to build me a place to hide <br><br>Although through the meetings <br>I will meet you were I go <br>And maybe I will realize that pressure comes, pressure is low <br><br>Too much to handle <br>That's just what I need <br>We've been out all night to prove <br>We are free <br><br>And we will make it to the weekend <br>And we will learn how to breathe <br>When it's too much handle <br>Being free <br><br>I'm up again in the middle of the night <br>That time when it's too easy to judge myself on everything <br>I read about the secret life of plants <br>Still I'd be of small enough to get back to sleep <br><br>All is getting cornered and it could get where I'm looking at you <br>Sunday's on our hearts and so many things what I didn't go through <br><br>Too much to handle <br>That's just what I need <br>When it's too much handle <br>We are free <br><br>And we will make it to the weekend <br>And we will learn how to breathe <br>When it's too much handle <br>Being free <br><br>Too much to handle <br>That's just what I need <br>We've been out all night to prove <br>We are free <br><br>And we will make it to the weekend <br>And we will learn how to breathe <br>When it's too much handle <br>Being free <br><br>And we will make it to the weekend <br>And we will learn how to breathe <br>When it's too much handle <br>Too much handle <br>Too much handle <br>Being free]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Too Much To Handle" label="Too Much To Handle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Desire_126/</id><title>Hollerado - Desire 126 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:37:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:37:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Desire_126/" title="Hollerado - Desire 126 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh how she loved the smell of dandelions, she had <br>That golden springtime hair <br>Her daddy voted for the stubborn side, the lying guys <br>But I did not care <br><br>You see <br>Sometimes there's people you meet <br>That stay a while and then they go <br>You either miss them or move on <br>She said <br>She wanna go be a big big star <br>I said <br>I'm better off on my own <br><br>Love is something like <br>It ain't imagination <br>Love is something like <br>It's calm and it is patience <br>It's waiting at the station <br><br>Desire, it's just a chemical <br>It comes and it goes and it comes and it goes <br>Desire, sometimes it's good enough <br>It comes and it goes and it comes and it goes <br><br>That time we walked down from Mount Royal Metral Square <br>You assholes French kissed to score <br>You talk the whole way there 'bout <br>How you're such a great listener, and <br>How you drink your wine through <br>Colored straws and mason jars <br><br>Sometimes I relate my stream <br>my mind just views what I could be <br>If I could get out of here <br>And maybe I'm confused <br>And maybe lust is true <br>But I want a love that I can lean on <br>Like the tide leans on the moon <br><br>Love is something like <br>It ain't imagination <br>Love is something like <br>It's calm and it is patience <br>It's waiting at the station <br><br>Desire, it's just a chemical <br>It comes and it goes and it comes and it goes <br>Desire, sometimes it's good enough <br>It comes and it goes and it comes and it goes <br><br>Would you stand by <br>Would you, would you stand by x2 <br><br>Would you stand by me, oh <br><br>Desire, it's just a chemical <br>It comes and it goes and it comes and it goes <br>Desire, sometimes it's good enough <br>It comes and it goes and it comes and it goes <br><br>Desire, it's just a chemical <br>It comes and it goes and it comes and it goes <br>Desire, sometimes it's good enough <br>It comes and it goes and it comes and it goes]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Desire 126" label="Desire 126"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Thanks_For_The_Venom/</id><title>Hollerado - Thanks For The Venom - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:37:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:37:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Thanks_For_The_Venom/" title="Hollerado - Thanks For The Venom - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Met you in a dog town, I was leaving out of a store <br>In the desert of my mind it was not and I was alone <br>You took me to the cold black top, you let me fly on my back <br>And you still don't know that shit until the story goes and my muscle's relaxed <br><br>Oh, we could be friends <br>But you are a rattle snake <br>Thanks for the venom <br>Oh, we could be friends <br>But you are a rattle snake <br>You are a rattle snake <br>Yea, yea, a rattle snake <br><br>You told me that your name was legs and hair, the irony <br>Surround the world into your place and we're talking about things and thoughts <br>Til we came home on a Saturday night, I'll cancel your snack <br>And I watched just how you drop on grind, swear I'll never go back to you <br><br>Oh, we could be friends <br>But you are a rattle snake <br>Thanks for the venom <br>Oh, we could be friends <br>But you are a rattle snake <br>You are a rattle snake <br>Yea, yea, yea a rattle snake <br><br>Went and did it all again love <br>I was right into your eye of fear <br>I am letting go <br>When I get out of here <br><br>By the end of that summer I crawled back to your kitchen floor <br>Covered in the felons of bronze or by the meals before <br>And you get about the dead addictions I left in your sink <br>And your bags come and flash before I had one second to think about it <br><br>Oh, you were my friend, we had a simple love <br>As simple as it, it gets up <br>We could be friends, we had a simple love <br>But you are a rattle snake <br>x2 <br>Oh, you were my friend <br>But you are a rattle snake <br>You are a rattle snake <br>Thanks for the venom <br>Oh, you were my friend <br>But you are a rattle snake <br>You are a rattle snake <br>Yea, yea, you a rattle snake]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Thanks For The Venom" label="Thanks For The Venom"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Dont_Think/</id><title>Hollerado - Don`t Think - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:37:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:37:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Dont_Think/" title="Hollerado - Don`t Think - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I remember the time late at spring we went to the museum's floor <br>I said dinosaurs look sad, you said just stop thinking <br><br>I wanna feel the claws of planets not exploding love <br>An elusive element on earth, a periodic just stop thinking <br><br>I just wanna know <br><br>At the end of time and space <br>Who will remember the human race <br>All those books yet all that pain <br>Who'll remember the fun we had <br><br>Do you think Einstein had a parakeet or just reality as company <br>It's singing how and now, just stop thinking <br><br>Remember the time we flew by rubber bands off California <br>With sweaty hands and wished that we could just, just stop thinking <br><br>I just wanna know <br><br>At the end of time and space <br>Who will remember the human race <br>All those books yet all that pain <br>Who'll remember the fun we had <br><br>At the end of space and time <br>Who'll remember human kind <br>All that good and all that bad <br>Well become with the fun we had <br><br>With asteroids and outer space <br>The moon town block is my favorite place <br>Release the place to get more settled <br>Well I don't think about you're at home <br>Melting ice inspire the price <br>We have both form out all night <br>Fortified, glory time <br>Slipped it through <br>Gallery got in reverse <br>Lord <br>We were in cars, we'll have a race until <br>Just stop thinking <br>We were in cars, we'll have a race until <br>Just stop thinking <br>We were in cars, we'll have a race until <br>Just stop thinking <br>We were in cars, we'll have a race until <br>Just stop thinking <br>Driving yea, it's our territory <br>Just stop thinking <br>Driving yea, it's our territory <br>Just stop thinking <br>Driving yea, it's our territory <br>Just stop thinking <br>Driving yea, it's our territory, territory]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Don`t Think" label="Don`t Think"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Wonder_Velocity_Charlie_And_Me/</id><title>Hollerado - Wonder, Velocity, Charlie And Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:37:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:37:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hollerado/Wonder_Velocity_Charlie_And_Me/" title="Hollerado - Wonder, Velocity, Charlie And Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I had a dream we were standing in a grand ovation <br>And computers played along in a play about creation <br>I was born in a house but I lived in this world <br>And for now it's the best place we got <br>And for now it's the best home we got <br><br>And Elation 'bout space can replace gravitation <br>Levitation is made out of jet fuel and patience <br>And words conserved can create frustration <br>Observed by the herds and the hopes of a nations <br>Procreation, Is a patient <br>And creation, A station <br>A Haitian, a fashion <br>Evasion, magician <br>Hibernation evation <br>Litration Libation <br>Linguation mutation <br>Deration Belation awaken <br>Distration Abrasion Punctuation]]></content><category term="Hollerado" label="Hollerado"/><category term="Wonder, Velocity, Charlie And Me" label="Wonder, Velocity, Charlie And Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김대승/어느_봄날/</id><title>김대승 - 어느 봄날 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:51:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:51:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8C%80%EC%8A%B9/%EC%96%B4%EB%8A%90_%EB%B4%84%EB%82%A0/" title="김대승 - 어느 봄날 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느 봄날 문득 서서 <br>녹음 짙은 햇살 보며 <br>다시 못 올 그 시절에 <br>가슴 시리도록 슬펐다면 <br>그건 아마도 이미 <br>내가 많은 세월 <br>지나왔기 때문이겠지 <br>어느 새벽 문득 깨어 <br>옆을 보고 안도하며 <br>언제까지 함께일까 <br>가슴 저리도록 아팠다면 <br>그건 아마도 이미 <br>내가 오랜 세월 <br>걸어왔기 때문이겠지 <br>그래 이제 더는 <br>슬픔 따윈 없는 거야 <br>한 줌마저 불태우며 사는 거야 <br>그래 이제 더는 <br>아픔 따윈 없는 거야 <br>불꽃처럼 사랑하며 사는 거야 <br>어느 봄날 문득 서서 <br>녹음 짙은 햇살 보며 <br>다시 못 올 그 시절에 <br>가슴 시리도록 슬펐다면 <br>그건 아마도 이미 <br>내가 많은 세월 <br>지나왔기 때문이겠지 <br>그건 아마도 이미 <br>내가 오랜 세월 <br>걸어왔기 때문이겠지 <br>그래 이제 더는 <br>슬픔 따윈 없는 거야 <br>한 줌마저 불태우며 사는 거야 <br>그래 이제 더는 <br>아픔 따윈 없는 거야 <br>불꽃처럼 사랑하며 사는 거야 <br>불꽃처럼 사랑하며 사는 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="김대승" label="김대승"/><category term="어느 봄날" label="어느 봄날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김대승/사랑해요_노래해요/</id><title>김대승 - 사랑해요 노래해요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:51:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:51:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8C%80%EC%8A%B9/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4%EC%9A%94_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%95%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="김대승 - 사랑해요 노래해요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑해요 그대만을 <br>영원토록 사랑해요 <br>안아줘요 그대 품에 <br>나의 영혼 쉴 수 있게 <br>이 세상 그 무엇이 <br>우리 사이 갈라놓아도 <br>난 오직 난 오직 <br>그대만을 그대만을 <br>사랑해요 그대만을 <br>보랏빛의 무지개를 <br>노래해요 우리 사랑 <br>영원토록 노래해요 <br>들려줘요 그대 사랑 <br>지친 영혼 쉴 수 있게 <br>이 세상 그 무엇이 <br>우리 사이 갈라놓아도 <br>난 오직 난 오직 <br>우리 사랑 우리 사랑 <br>노래해요 우리 사랑 <br>보랏빛의 무지개를 <br>사랑해요 노래해요 <br>보랏빛의 무지개를 <br>사랑 사랑해요 노래해요 <br>보랏빛의 무지개를 <br>사랑 사랑해요 노래해요 <br>]]></content><category term="김대승" label="김대승"/><category term="사랑해요 노래해요" label="사랑해요 노래해요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김대승/Crazy_Woman/</id><title>김대승 - Crazy Woman - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:51:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:51:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8C%80%EC%8A%B9/Crazy_Woman/" title="김대승 - Crazy Woman - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know a woman <br>She never stops cooling <br>and heating her office <br>It’s freezing inside <br>in the summer melting <br>in the winter <br>Because she pays nothing <br>but the boss does <br>I know a woman <br>She never stops pumping gas <br>till it’s overflowing <br>The car always suffers <br>from vomiting at the gas station <br>Because she pays nothing <br>but the boss does <br>Hey poor lady now <br>we call you a crazy woman <br>Hey poor lady now <br>we call you a crazy woman <br>I know a woman <br>She never stops cooling <br>and heating her office <br>It’s freezing inside <br>in the summer melting <br>in the winter <br>Because she pays nothing <br>but the boss does <br>Hey poor lady now <br>we call you a crazy woman <br>Hey poor lady now <br>we call you a crazy woman <br>you a crazy woman <br>you a crazy woman <br>you a crazy woman <br>you a crazy woman <br>you a crazy woman <br>you a crazy woman <br>you a crazy woman <br>you a crazy <br>Hey poor lady now <br>we call you a crazy woman <br>]]></content><category term="김대승" label="김대승"/><category term="Crazy Woman" label="Crazy Woman"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김대승/No_Money_For_The_Blues/</id><title>김대승 - No Money For The Blues - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:51:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:51:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8C%80%EC%8A%B9/No_Money_For_The_Blues/" title="김대승 - No Money For The Blues - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Got a cigar box guitar <br>That’s not enough to be blue babe <br>Got the pignose amp too <br>Still not enough to be blue babe <br>You ain’t got no money <br>Then you got the blues <br>Got a blues harp <br>That’s not enough to be blue babe <br>Got the green <br>bullet microphone too <br>Still not enough to be blue babe <br>You ain’t got no money <br>Then you got the blues <br>Got a cigar box guitar <br>That’s not enough to be blue babe <br>Got the pignose amp too <br>Still not enough to be blue babe <br>You ain’t got no money <br>Then you got the blues <br>]]></content><category term="김대승" label="김대승"/><category term="No Money For The Blues" label="No Money For The Blues"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이네/나의_바다/</id><title>이네 - 나의 바다 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:54:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:54:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%84%A4/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4/" title="이네 - 나의 바다 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바다가 우네 고요했던 바다 <br>바람이 부네 내 몸을 스쳐 가네 <br>고요해지네 일렁이던 파도 <br>잠잠해지네 아무 일도 없었던 듯이 <br>내게 왜 다가온 건지 왜 손 내민 건지 <br>왜 그런 말 했는지 <br>고요해지네 일렁이던 파도 <br>잠잠해지네 아무 일도 없었던 듯이 <br>너를 왜 마주한 건지 왜 손 잡은 건지 <br>왜 놓지 못한 건지 <br>자꾸 나의 바다를 왜 <br>요동치게 했는지 눈물짓게 했는지 <br>이제 다시 잠잠해진 바다 <br>]]></content><category term="이네" label="이네"/><category term="나의 바다" label="나의 바다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Steve_Forbert/Listen_To_The_Mockingbird/</id><title>Steve Forbert - Listen To The Mockingbird - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Steve_Forbert/Listen_To_The_Mockingbird/" title="Steve Forbert - Listen To The Mockingbird - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Woke up one bright morning <br>Woke up in the rain <br>Woke up to the sunshine and the pain <br><br>Stood out in the rosebuds <br>Stood out in the dew <br>Stood out in the clear and got a clue <br><br>Listen to the mockingbird <br>Sing his sweet song <br>Listen to the mockingbird <br>And know that life goes on <br><br>Been inside a coal mine <br>Been inside a whale <br>Been inside a grief just like a jail <br><br>Listen to the mockingbird <br>Sing his sweet song <br>Listen to the mockingbird <br>And know that life goes on <br><br>On that morning, dressed in black <br>I began my journey back <br>Through old cobwebs colors blew <br>From my footsteps shadows flew <br><br>Through these eyes of light now <br>I begin to know <br>All good things in time will come and go <br><br>Listen to the mockingbird <br>Sing his sweet song <br>Listen to the mockingbird <br>And know that life goes on]]></content><category term="Steve Forbert" label="Steve Forbert"/><category term="Listen To The Mockingbird" label="Listen To The Mockingbird"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김지민/길_One_Way/</id><title>김지민 - 길 (One Way) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%BC/%EA%B8%B8_One_Way/" title="김지민 - 길 (One Way) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 마음 매일 갈대같이 흔들리지만 <br>나를 붙들고 계신 분 있죠 <br>내 마음 나보다 잘 아셔서 <br>위로해 주시죠 <br>내 마음 매일 연약하여 넘어지지만 <br>나를 지키고 계신 분 있죠 <br>목숨 다해 내게 생명 주셔서 <br>끝까지 날 사랑하시죠 <br>좁은 길이라 해도 <br>험한 길이라 해도 <br>주님 먼저 가신 그 언덕을 넘어 <br>세상은 몰라 줘도 <br>모두 비웃는 대도 <br>내 영혼 가장 안전한 그길 <br>예수 그리스도 <br>내 영혼 매일 연약하여 넘어지지만 <br>나를 지키고 계신 분 있죠 <br>목숨 다해 내게 생명 주셔서 <br>끝까지 날 사랑하시죠 <br>좁은 길이라 해도 <br>험한 길이라 해도 <br>주님 먼저 가신 그 언덕을 넘어 <br>세상은 몰라 줘도 <br>모두 비웃는 대도 <br>내 영혼 가장 안전한 그길 <br>예수 그리스도 <br>오 주님 같은 분은 없어요 <br>주님만이 나의 전부 생명 되시죠 <br>좁은 길이라 해도 <br>험한 길이라 해도 <br>주님 먼저 가신 그 언덕을 넘어 <br>세상은 몰라 줘도 <br>모두 비웃는 대도 <br>내 영혼 가장 안전한 그길 <br>예수 그리스도 <br>내 영혼 가장 안전한 그길 <br>예수 그리스도 <br>]]></content><category term="김지민" label="김지민"/><category term="길 (One Way)" label="길 (One Way)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Nothing_Not_Nearly/</id><title>Laura Marling - Nothing, Not Nearly - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Nothing_Not_Nearly/" title="Laura Marling - Nothing, Not Nearly - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I won't forget the late September <br>Where we danced among the midnight embers <br>But it's going like a half remembered dream <br>Left and north of where we met <br>Thinking better of going west <br>Yeah we lost each other in a river stream <br>I thought I'd come and find you there <br>Wait until you lost your hair <br>And got your place out in the woods <br>You're not afraid of trees or bears <br>Or anything with tendencies <br>To wanna hurt you good <br><br>The only thing I learnt in a year <br>Where I didn't smile once, not really <br>Nothing matters more than love, no <br>Nothing, no, not nothing no, not nearly <br><br>We've not got long, you know <br>To bask in the afterglow <br>Once it's gone it's gone <br><br>I won't forget the late September <br>Where we danced among the midnight embers <br>But it's going like a half remembered dream <br>Left and north of where we met <br>Thinking better of going west <br>Yeah we lost each other in a river stream <br><br>The only thing I learnt in a year <br>Where I didn't smile once, not really <br>Nothing matters more than love, no <br>Nothing, no, not, nothing no, not nearly <br><br>We've not got long, you know <br>To bask in the afterglow <br>Once it's gone it's gone <br>Love waits for no one <br><br>We've not got long, you know <br>To bask in the afterglow <br>Once it's gone it's gone <br>Love waits for no one]]></content><category term="Laura Marling" label="Laura Marling"/><category term="Nothing, Not Nearly" label="Nothing, Not Nearly"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Nouel/</id><title>Laura Marling - Nouel - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Nouel/" title="Laura Marling - Nouel - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She sings along to sailor's song <br>In a dress that she made <br>When she's gone I sing along <br>But it doesn't sound the same <br><br>Oh Nouel, you seem so well <br>Sing only for me <br>Fickle, unchangeable <br>Though I may always be <br><br>I pulled a thorn from her tiny paw <br>Her feet were unclean <br>Fetch water, blessed twice <br>And hand that sponge to me <br><br>I do well to serve Nouel <br>Whatever service I may be <br>Fickle, unchangeable <br>Weighing down on me <br><br>She speaks a word which gently turns <br>To perfect metaphor <br>She likes to say I only play <br>When I know what I'm playing for <br><br>Oh Nouel, you must know me well <br>And I didn't even show you the scar <br>Fickle, unchangeable <br>Semper femina <br><br>She'd like to be the kind of free <br>Women can't be alone <br>I wish I could hit the switch <br>That keeps you from getting gone <br><br>Oh Nouel, it must hurt like hell <br>When you're so afraid to die <br>Semper femina <br>So am I <br><br>She lays herself across the bed <br>The origine du monde <br>Slight of shoulder, long and legged <br>Her hair a faded blonde <br><br>Oh Nouel, you sit so well <br>A thousand artists' muse <br>You'll be anything you choose <br>Fickle, unchangeable are you <br>And long may that continue <br><br>I do well to serve Nouel <br>My only guiding star <br>Fickle, unchangeable <br>Semper femina]]></content><category term="Laura Marling" label="Laura Marling"/><category term="Nouel" label="Nouel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Next_Time/</id><title>Laura Marling - Next Time - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Next_Time/" title="Laura Marling - Next Time - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It feels like a long time since I was free <br>It feels like the right time to take that seriously <br>It feels like the trees are a peculiar green <br>It feels like the air is hung heavily <br><br>I don't want to be the kind <br>Struck by fear to run and hide <br>I'll do better next time <br><br>It feels like warning signs were there for us to see <br>It feels like they taught us ignore diligently <br>I feel her, I hear her weakly scream <br><br>Am I really so unkind <br>To turn around and close my eyes <br>I'll do better next time <br>I'll do better next time <br><br>It feels like the last breath we will ever share <br>It feels like the last time I'll run my fingers through you hair <br><br>I can no longer close my eyes <br>While the world around me dies <br>At the hands of folks like me <br>It seems they fail to see <br>There may never <br>Next time be]]></content><category term="Laura Marling" label="Laura Marling"/><category term="Next Time" label="Next Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Wild_Once/</id><title>Laura Marling - Wild Once - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Wild_Once/" title="Laura Marling - Wild Once - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They put my hands in water <br>Told me I'm a god <br>I might be someone's daughter <br>Might be somewhat odd <br><br>But I was wild once <br>I know I can't forget it <br>I was wild, chasing stones <br><br>The martyr who feels the fire <br>And the child who knows his name <br>They remember that there's something wild <br>And it's something you can't explain <br>Oh it's something you can't explain <br><br>They are wild <br>And they can't forget it <br>They are wild, chasing stones <br><br>It's hard if you can't change it <br>It's worse if you don't try <br>You will sit down to explain it <br>And you're constantly asking why <br>You are constantly asking why <br><br>Well, you are wild <br>And you must remember <br>You are wild, chasing stones <br><br>Does no one understand you <br>Is that tired and familial long <br>You must change what hands you <br>Give me something to go on <br>Give me something to go on <br><br>You are wild <br>And I won't forget it <br>You are wild, chasing stones <br><br>There is something just beneath <br>There is something just beneath <br>Something shy and hard to see <br>It's a ring that is clean <br>It's a ring]]></content><category term="Laura Marling" label="Laura Marling"/><category term="Wild Once" label="Wild Once"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Always_This_Way/</id><title>Laura Marling - Always This Way - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Always_This_Way/" title="Laura Marling - Always This Way - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'd like to say that I could've stayed <br>But she didn't want me to <br>I'd like to know if she had to go <br>Or if she made a point to <br><br>It's so hard to say <br>Is it always this way <br>Must every heart break <br>Like a wave on the bay <br><br>Like to think that we're all a link <br>In what makes the world go round <br>Lately I wonder if all my pondering's <br>Taken up too much ground <br><br>I make my own way <br>So at the end of the day <br>At least I can say <br>That my debts have been paid <br><br>25 years, nothing to show for it <br>Nothing of any weight <br>25 more, will I never learn from it <br>Never learn from my mistakes <br><br>It's too soon to say <br>Was I always this way <br>Well at the end of the day <br>My debts have been paid <br><br>Now she's gone and I'm all alone <br>And she will not be replaced <br>Stare at the phone, try to carry on <br>But I have made my mistake <br><br>At the end of the day <br>At least I can say <br>I made my own way <br>And my debts have been paid]]></content><category term="Laura Marling" label="Laura Marling"/><category term="Always This Way" label="Always This Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Dont_Pass_Me_By/</id><title>Laura Marling - Don`t Pass Me By - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Dont_Pass_Me_By/" title="Laura Marling - Don`t Pass Me By - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You see my oldest friend <br>Tell her that I'm gone again <br>You take my old guitar <br>One that I once said was ours <br>Don't be blue <br><br>You haul that old tune <br>One I used to sing for you <br>When we were alone <br>You ask her if she knew <br>Was this something I would do <br>From the start <br><br>Please don't pass me by <br>If I'm walking but I don't know why <br>It something that I have to try <br>Can you love me if I put up a fight <br><br>Take my old guitar <br>And sell it off for parts <br>As you should <br>Take my old tune <br>Turn it into something new <br>Something good <br><br>Please don't pass me by <br>If I'm walking but I don't know why <br>I can't keep you off of my mind <br>Can you love me if I put up a fight <br><br>Is it something you've made a habit of <br>It's not what I need from love, right now <br>Right now, right now, right now]]></content><category term="Laura Marling" label="Laura Marling"/><category term="Don`t Pass Me By" label="Don`t Pass Me By"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Wild_Fire/</id><title>Laura Marling - Wild Fire - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Wild_Fire/" title="Laura Marling - Wild Fire - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You wanna get high <br>Yeah overcome those desires before you come to me <br>I think your mama's kinda sad <br>And your papa's kinda mean <br>I can take it all away <br>You can stop playing that shit out on me <br><br>She keeps a pen behind her ear <br>Because she's got something she really really needs to say <br>She puts it in a notepad <br>She's gonna write a book someday <br><br>Of course the only part that I want to read <br>Is about her time spent with me <br>Wouldn't you die to know how you seem <br>Are you getting away with who you're trying to be <br><br>Of course there's things upon the Earth that we must really try to defend <br>You lonely beast <br>You kind heart <br>Something we can all trend <br>I do it all for her, for free <br>I need nothing back for me <br>There's no sweeter deed maybe <br>Than to love something enough to want to have to get free <br><br>Is there something on your mind <br>Something you need to get by <br>D you cry sometimes <br>Do you cry sometimes <br><br>You always say you love me most <br>But I don't know I'm being seen <br>Maybe someday when God takes me away <br>I'll understand what the fuck that means <br>I just know your mama's kinda sad <br>And your papa's kinda mean <br>I can take it all away <br>You could stop playing that shit out on me <br><br>Is there something on your mind <br>Something you need to get by <br>D you cry sometimes <br>Do you cry sometimes <br><br>I know your mama's kinda sad <br>I know your papa's kinda mean <br>I can take it all away <br>And you can stop playing that shit out on me]]></content><category term="Laura Marling" label="Laura Marling"/><category term="Wild Fire" label="Wild Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/The_Valley/</id><title>Laura Marling - The Valley - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/The_Valley/" title="Laura Marling - The Valley - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know she stayed in town last night <br>Didn't get in touch <br>I know she has my number right <br>She can't face seeing us <br><br>She sings in the valley in the morning <br>Many a morning I have woke <br>Longing to ask her what she's mourning <br>Course I know it can't be spoke <br><br>Perhaps she's had too much of love <br>Can be a sickly thing <br>That's why she mourns the morning dew <br>And the newness that it brings <br><br>She sings in the valley in the morning <br>Many a morning I have woke <br>Longing to ask her what she's mourning <br>Of course I know it can't be spoke <br><br>I love you in the morning <br>I love you in the day <br>I'd love you in the evening <br>If only she would stay <br><br>We love beauty 'cause it needs us to <br>It needs our brittle glaze <br>And innocence reminds us to <br>Cover our drooling gaze <br><br>She's down there in the valley <br>I know she wanders there <br>She's down there in the valley <br>I can see her golden hair <br><br>I love you in the morning <br>My angel of the west <br>I love you in the evening <br>And I will do my very best <br>I'll do my very best]]></content><category term="Laura Marling" label="Laura Marling"/><category term="The Valley" label="The Valley"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Soothing/</id><title>Laura Marling - Soothing - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Laura_Marling/Soothing/" title="Laura Marling - Soothing - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, my hopeless wanderer <br>You can't come in <br>You don't live here anymore <br>Oh, some creepy conjurer <br>Who touched the rim <br>Whose hands are in the door <br><br>I need soothing <br>My lips aren't moving <br>My God is brooding <br><br>Drawn in chalk across the floor <br>You made it yours <br>Your private door to my room <br>May those who find you find remorse <br>A change of course, a strange discord resolved <br><br>I need soothing <br>My lips aren't moving <br>My God is brooding <br><br>I banish you with love <br>I banish you with love <br><br>You can't come in <br>You don't live here anymore]]></content><category term="Laura Marling" label="Laura Marling"/><category term="Soothing" label="Soothing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Skiy/I_Wanna_Dance_With_Somebody_Who_Loves_Me_Extended/</id><title>Skiy - I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me) (Extended) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Skiy/I_Wanna_Dance_With_Somebody_Who_Loves_Me_Extended/" title="Skiy - I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me) (Extended) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Clock strikes upon the hour <br>And the sun begins to fade <br>Still enough time to figure out <br><br>How to chase my blues away <br>I've done alright up to now <br>It's the light of day that shows me how <br>And when the night falls, loneliness calls <br><br>Oh wanna dance with somebody <br>I wanna feel the heat with somebody <br>Yeah wanna dance with somebody <br>With somebody who loves me <br><br>I've been in love and lost my senses <br>Spinning through the town <br>Sooner or later the fever ends <br>And I wind up feeling down <br>I need a man who'll take a chance <br>On a love that burns hot enough to last <br>So when the night falls <br>My lonely heart calls <br><br>Oh wanna dance with somebody <br>I wanna feel the heat with somebody <br>Yeah wanna dance with somebody <br>With somebody who loves me]]></content><category term="Skiy" label="Skiy"/><category term="I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me) (Extended)" label="I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me) (Extended)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Skiy/I_Wanna_Dance_With_Somebody_Who_Loves_Me/</id><title>Skiy - I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Skiy/I_Wanna_Dance_With_Somebody_Who_Loves_Me/" title="Skiy - I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Clock strikes upon the hour <br>And the sun begins to fade <br>Still enough time to figure out <br><br>How to chase my blues away <br>I've done alright up to now <br>It's the light of day that shows me how <br>And when the night falls, loneliness calls <br><br>Oh wanna dance with somebody <br>I wanna feel the heat with somebody <br>Yeah wanna dance with somebody <br>With somebody who loves me <br><br>I've been in love and lost my senses <br>Spinning through the town <br>Sooner or later the fever ends <br>And I wind up feeling down <br>I need a man who'll take a chance <br>On a love that burns hot enough to last <br>So when the night falls <br>My lonely heart calls <br><br>Oh wanna dance with somebody <br>I wanna feel the heat with somebody <br>Yeah wanna dance with somebody <br>With somebody who loves me]]></content><category term="Skiy" label="Skiy"/><category term="I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me)" label="I Wanna Dance With Somebody (Who Loves Me)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/자스민/같은_사랑이길/</id><title>자스민 - 같은 사랑이길 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:55:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:55:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%90%EC%8A%A4%EB%AF%BC/%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EA%B8%B8/" title="자스민 - 같은 사랑이길 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 어깨에 <br>기대어 잠든 너 <br>내 팔 위로 <br>흘러내린 머릿결 <br>나의 가슴은 <br>뛰고 있지만 <br>나는 알아 <br>사랑일 수 없다고 <br>그대도 똑같은 <br>마음일순 없는지 <br>나의 마음속에 <br>사랑이기를 기도해 <br>너의 꿈에 지금 <br>편지를 보내 <br>같은 맘 이길 <br>같은 사랑 이길 <br>너의 맘에 이제 <br>나를 받아줘 <br>우리 사랑할 <br>시간만 남게 <br>그대도 똑같은 <br>마음일순 없는지 <br>나의 마음속에 <br>사랑이기를 기도해 <br>너의 꿈에 지금 <br>편지를 보내 <br>같은 맘 이길 <br>같은 사랑 이길 <br>너의 맘에 이제 <br>나를 받아줘 <br>우리 사랑할 <br>시간만 남게 <br>]]></content><category term="자스민" label="자스민"/><category term="같은 사랑이길" label="같은 사랑이길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/은가은/4월_10일/</id><title>은가은 - 4월 10일 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:56:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:56:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%80/4%EC%9B%94_10%EC%9D%BC/" title="은가은 - 4월 10일 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 본다 나를 본다 <br>다가온다 다가온다 <br>미소 지으며 내게 말건다 <br>감싸 안아준다 안아준다 <br>추운 겨울이 녹는다 <br>좋아한다 좋아한다 <br>나를 보며 속삭이고 <br>난 그대 품에 안긴다 <br>심장소리 듣다 고갤 들면 <br>그대가 웃는다 <br>넌 나의 다다다다 다다 <br>우린 다다다다 <br>널 사랑하고 또 사랑하는 나야 <br>난 너의 다다다다 다다 <br>우린 다다다다 <br>날 사랑하고 <br>또 사랑하는 너는 다다 <br>달콤하다 달콤하다 <br>하나하나 부드럽다 <br>그대 손이 나를 잡는다 <br>감싸 안아준다 안아준다 <br>추운 겨울이 녹는다 <br>사랑한다 사랑한다 <br>나를 보며 속삭이고 <br>그대 내 품에 안긴다 <br>심장소리 들린다며 <br>환한 미소를 짓는다 <br>넌 나의 다다다다 다다 <br>우린 다다다다 <br>널 사랑하고 또 사랑하는 나야 <br>난 너의 다다다다 다다 <br>우린 다다다다 <br>날 사랑하고 <br>또 사랑하는 너는 다다 <br>다다다 다다 <br>]]></content><category term="은가은" label="은가은"/><category term="4월 10일" label="4월 10일"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Hard_Headed_Woman_Single_Ver/</id><title>Bobby Darin - Hard Headed Woman (Single Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:56:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:56:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Hard_Headed_Woman_Single_Ver/" title="Bobby Darin - Hard Headed Woman (Single Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm lookin' for a hard headed woman <br>One who will take me for myself <br>And, if I find my hard headed woman <br>You know I won't need nobody else <br><br>I'm lookin' for a hard headed woman <br>One who will make me do my best <br>When I find my hard headed woman <br>I know the rest of my life will be blessed <br><br>I met a lot of fancy dancers <br>People who can slide you on the floor <br>They move so smooth but have no answer <br>When you ask, What'd you come here for <br><br>I'm lookin' for a hard headed woman <br>One who will make me feel so good <br>And, if I find my hard headed woman <br>I know my life will be as it should <br><br>I know many fine, fair friends <br>But the friendliness depends o oh on how you do <br>Ain't no many sure fired ways to find that one who pays <br>And they always do <br><br>I'm lookin' for a hard headed woman <br>One who will make me do my best <br>When I find my hard headed woman <br>You know I'll take care of the rest <br><br>You know <br>I'll know how to take care of the rest <br>Let me get hold of a hard headed woman <br>I'll know what to do with the rest]]></content><category term="Bobby Darin" label="Bobby Darin"/><category term="Hard Headed Woman (Single Ver.)" label="Hard Headed Woman (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Ill_Be_Your_Baby_Tonight_Single_Ver/</id><title>Bobby Darin - I`ll Be Your Baby Tonight (Single Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:56:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:56:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Ill_Be_Your_Baby_Tonight_Single_Ver/" title="Bobby Darin - I`ll Be Your Baby Tonight (Single Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Close your eyes, close the door <br>You don't have to worry any more <br>'Cause I'll be your baby tonight <br><br>Shut the light, shut the shade <br>You don't have to be afraid <br>'Cause I'll be your baby tonight <br><br>Give me a little time <br><br>Mockingbird is gonna sail away <br>We're gonna forget it <br>Big old moon is gonna shine like a spoon <br>We're gonna let it, you won't regret it <br><br>Little girl kick your shoes off, have no fear <br>Bring that bottle over here <br>And I'll be your baby tonight <br><br>Give me a little room <br><br>Mockingbird is gonna sail away <br>We're gonna forget it <br>Big old moon is gonna shine like a spoon <br>We're gonna let it, you won't regret it <br><br>Little girl kick both them your shoes off, have no fear <br>Bring your own self over here <br>And I'll be your baby tonight <br><br>Give me a little time <br><br>And I'll be your baby tonight <br>Don't you take away all my covers <br>And I'll be your baby tonight]]></content><category term="Bobby Darin" label="Bobby Darin"/><category term="I`ll Be Your Baby Tonight (Single Ver.)" label="I`ll Be Your Baby Tonight (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Someday_Well_Be_Together_Single_Ver/</id><title>Bobby Darin - Someday We`ll Be Together (Single Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:56:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:56:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Someday_Well_Be_Together_Single_Ver/" title="Bobby Darin - Someday We`ll Be Together (Single Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're far away from me my love, and just as sure my <br>My baby as there are stars above <br>I wanna say, I wanna say, I wanna say some day we'll be <br>Together <br>Yes we will, yes we will say some day we'll be <br>Together <br>I know, I know, I know, I know <br>Long time ago my, my sweet thing, I made a big mistake <br>Honey <br>I say, I said goodbye <br>Oh, Oh baby ever ever, ever since that day now <br>Now all I, all I wanna do awh is cry, cry <br>Oh hey, hey, hey <br><br>You know my love is yours, baby <br>Oh, right from the start <br>You, you, you possess my soul now honey <br>And I know, I know you won my heart <br>And I wanna say someday we'll be together <br>Yes we will, yes we will <br>I long for you, every night <br>Just to kiss your sweet, sweet lips <br>Hold you ever so tight and I wanna say <br>Someday we'll be together <br>Oh, yes we will, yes we will <br><br>You're far away from me my love, and just as sure my <br>My baby as there are stars above <br>I wanna say, I wanna say, I wanna say some day we'll be <br>Together <br>Yes we will, yes we will some day we'll be together <br>Yes we will, yes we will some day we'll be together <br>Yes we will, yes we will some day we'll be together]]></content><category term="Bobby Darin" label="Bobby Darin"/><category term="Someday We`ll Be Together (Single Ver.)" label="Someday We`ll Be Together (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Hard_Headed_Woman/</id><title>Bobby Darin - Hard Headed Woman - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:56:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:56:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Hard_Headed_Woman/" title="Bobby Darin - Hard Headed Woman - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm lookin' for a hard headed woman <br>One who will take me for myself <br>And, if I find my hard headed woman <br>You know I won't need nobody else <br><br>I'm lookin' for a hard headed woman <br>One who will make me do my best <br>When I find my hard headed woman <br>I know the rest of my life will be blessed <br><br>I met a lot of fancy dancers <br>People who can slide you on the floor <br>They move so smooth but have no answer <br>When you ask, What'd you come here for <br><br>I'm lookin' for a hard headed woman <br>One who will make me feel so good <br>And, if I find my hard headed woman <br>I know my life will be as it should <br><br>I know many fine, fair friends <br>But the friendliness depends o oh on how you do <br>Ain't no many sure fired ways to find that one who pays <br>And they always do <br><br>I'm lookin' for a hard headed woman <br>One who will make me do my best <br>When I find my hard headed woman <br>You know I'll take care of the rest <br><br>You know <br>I'll know how to take care of the rest <br>Let me get hold of a hard headed woman <br>I'll know what to do with the rest]]></content><category term="Bobby Darin" label="Bobby Darin"/><category term="Hard Headed Woman" label="Hard Headed Woman"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Something_In_Her_Love/</id><title>Bobby Darin - Something In Her Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:56:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:56:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Something_In_Her_Love/" title="Bobby Darin - Something In Her Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As long as she's around <br>There'll be a mornin' sun <br>Even when the sky is gray above <br>All she has to do is say, Good mornin' hun <br>'cause there's somethin' in her love I love <br><br>She keeps me warm at night <br>And whispers tenderly <br>She will follow anywhere I lead <br>Let her go and I would see the end of me <br>'cause there's somethin' in her love I need <br><br>Take a yellow rose and add it to a waterfall <br>Then stir a rainbow in a glass of wine <br>Take a melody and blend it with the leaves of fall <br>It still would not describe this love of mine <br><br>And anytime I think of leavin' her <br>Somethin' always makes me change my mind <br>Friends will ask me what is it I see in her <br>I say somethin' in her love so fine <br><br>Take a yellow rose and add it to a waterfall <br>Then stir a rainbow in a glass of wine <br>Take a melody and blend it with the leaves of fall <br>It still would not describe this love of mine <br><br>And anytime I think of leavin' her <br>Somethin' always makes me change my mind <br>Friends will ask me what it is I see in her <br>I say somethin' in her love so fine]]></content><category term="Bobby Darin" label="Bobby Darin"/><category term="Something In Her Love" label="Something In Her Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dopebwoy/Iets_Verdiend/</id><title>Dopebwoy - Iets Verdiend - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:57:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:57:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dopebwoy/Iets_Verdiend/" title="Dopebwoy - Iets Verdiend - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ey <br>Heb een moneytje geslagen, kan weer lopen in de stad <br>Haal een nieuwe patta, of ik blow het aan m'n mams <br>Of het word gevierd, dan connect ik heel de squad <br>Kan het spenden in de club, of ik zet het aan de kant <br>Kan investeren en ik zorg dat ik meer pak <br>Ik kan spenden op de dagen dat ik skeer was <br>Dan bestel ik honderd flessen en ik drink wat <br>Klick een picca en dan zie het op m'n insta <br><br>Ooooh, we breken ze <br>Er is hella champagne, ja we leven het <br>Houd jezelf voor de gek, jullie spelen het <br>Ik kan spenden wat ik wil, je berekent het <br><br>Ik heb iets verdiend, ik heb iets verdiend <br>Ik heb iets verdiend, ik heb iets verdiend <br>Ik heb iets verdiend <br>Meer goud, bye bitch, strooi met money <br>Ik heb iets verdiend <br>Ze ziet het draaien, now she wants me <br><br>Wilde met d'r hangen maar toen vond ze me niks <br>Nu toont ze interesse want m'n Insta is lit <br>Ze zegt wanneer kom je bij me schat, ik had me vergist <br>Sorry ik ga niet in zee, je hebt deze boot al gemist <br>En ik heb niet gehapt, maar nu ben ik op m'n guap <br>Sta je financieel sterk worden alle chicks thots <br>Situatie is veranderd dus de mind is nu geswitcht <br>Vroeger kwamen we niet binnen, nu bestellen we de VIP <br><br>Ooooh, we breken ze <br>Er is hella champagne, ja we leven het <br>Houd jezelf voor de gek, jullie spelen het <br>Ik kan spenden wat ik wil, je berekent het <br>Ooooh, we breken ze <br>Er is hella champagne, ja we leven het <br>Houd jezelf voor de gek, jullie spelen het <br>Ik kan spenden wat ik wil, je berekent het <br><br>Ik heb iets verdiend, ik heb iets verdiend <br>Ik heb iets verdiend, ik heb iets verdiend <br>Ik heb iets verdiend <br>Meer goud, bye bitch, strooi met money <br>Ik heb iets verdiend <br>Ze ziet het draaien, now she wants me <br><br>Ik heb iets verdiend, ik heb iets verdiend <br>Ik heb iets verdiend, ik heb iets verdiend <br>Ik heb iets verdiend <br>Meer goud, bye bitch, strooi met money <br>Ik heb iets verdiend <br>Ze ziet het draaien, now she wants me]]></content><category term="Dopebwoy" label="Dopebwoy"/><category term="Iets Verdiend" label="Iets Verdiend"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dopebwoy/Minimaal_Feat_Jayh__Zefanio/</id><title>Dopebwoy - Minimaal (Feat. Jayh &amp; Zefanio) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:57:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:57:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dopebwoy/Minimaal_Feat_Jayh__Zefanio/" title="Dopebwoy - Minimaal (Feat. Jayh &amp; Zefanio) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Weet je zeker dat je dit wilt met me <br>Ze zeggen lobi kan je niet plannen, woi <br>Dit had ik niet verwacht, nee nooit <br>Dit is niet normaal meer, no <br>Dit is niet normaal meer <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal, yeah <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal <br>Dit is niet normaal nee, no <br>Dit is niet normaal meer <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal, yeah <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal <br>Minimaal, eh, minimaal <br><br>Iedereen wil weten wat je naam is <br>Mi no play around, ben op mad tings <br>Nu hebben we stacks, ik betaal dit <br>Want ik heb je back, weet dat het minimaal is <br>Jij, nu ben je van mij <br>Zeg wat wil je doen, schatje voel je vrij <br>Ik voel die love, dit is wederzijds <br>Dus ik stunt op je ex, hij is verleden tijd <br><br>Jij hebt 't, I know you want ik geef je I know you like <br>Dat's mini minimaal <br>Wat wij delen, I know you want is eeuwig I know you like <br>Want nu ben je m'n darling <br><br>Dit is niet normaal meer, no <br>Dit is niet normaal meer <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal, yeah <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal <br>Dit is niet normaal nee, no <br>Dit is niet normaal meer <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal, yeah <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal <br>Minimaal, eh, minimaal <br><br>Spend geen time meer op die wijven <br>Want, binnenkort ben je de mijne <br>En ik, weet niet hoe lang dit gaat blijven <br>Maar ik, wil je hebben tot het einde <br>Ik wil mini maal die maal, die maal, die maal <br>Die <br>Geen relatie, vraag niet eens hoe <br>Ooh oh oh oh oh oh oh <br><br>Jij hebt 't, I know you want ik geef je I know you like <br>Dat's mini minimaal <br>Wat wij delen, I know you want is eeuwig I know you like <br>Want nu ben je m'n darling <br><br>Dit is niet normaal meer, no <br>Dit is niet normaal meer <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal, yeah <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal <br>Dit is niet normaal nee, no <br>Dit is niet normaal meer <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal, yeah <br>Je love, wil ik minimaal <br>Minimaal, eh, minimaal <br><br>Minimaal <br>Minimaal]]></content><category term="Dopebwoy" label="Dopebwoy"/><category term="Minimaal (Feat. Jayh &amp; Zefanio)" label="Minimaal (Feat. Jayh &amp; Zefanio)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dopebwoy/Tranquilo___Doe_Relax/</id><title>Dopebwoy - Tranquilo / Doe Relax - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:57:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:57:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dopebwoy/Tranquilo___Doe_Relax/" title="Dopebwoy - Tranquilo / Doe Relax - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ehh, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax, blijf rustig <br>Ehh, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax, blijf rustig <br>Ehh, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax, blijf rustig <br>Ehh, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax, blijf rustig <br>Ehh <br>Chino <br>Ehh <br>Rustaagh <br>Ehh, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax, blijf rustig <br>Hmm, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax blijf rustig <br>Yeah, doe relax <br>Doe relax lax lax <br>Doe relax, ohh <br>Doe relax lax lax <br>Flex op balkon, man ik zit goed <br>Schatje kom niet verder als je stiff doet <br>On fleek want ik draag Parcon, wat gebeurd in die pangpang ohoho <br>Kalm aan, ik zie je kijken naar m'n dresscode <br>Fly boy, je gaat niet halen met je Kenzo <br>Doe relax ga zitten voor ik je expose <br>Vroeger was ze lit, maar nu zet ik d'r in friendzone <br>Wat ik spend maak ik later weer terug <br>Want vandaag ben ik de baas van de club <br>Al m'n guys zijn fly net <br>Kalm aan tranquilo ohoho <br><br>Ehh, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax, blijf rustig <br>Hmm, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax blijf rustig <br>Yeah, doe relax <br>Doe relax lax lax <br>Doe relax, ohh <br>Doe relax lax lax <br><br>Kalm aan doe niet druk <br>Maak kennis met de baas van de club <br>Grey Goose puur man, ik mix niet <br>Everybody in de club get tipsy ohoho <br>Bil hoog, hoofd laag, outfit PC Hooftstraat <br>Club is van mij, dus ik proost daar <br>Stack contant, je moet spenden als je groot praat <br>Je zegt je bent baller baller <br>Jij draagt maar ik leef het eehee <br>Praat mannen om salaris <br> als het geleend is eehee, ohoho <br><br>Ehh, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax, blijf rustig <br>Hmm, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax blijf rustig <br>Yeah, doe relax <br>Doe relax lax lax <br>Doe relax, ohh <br>Doe relax lax lax <br>Ehh, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax, blijf rustig <br>Hmm, blijf rustig <br>Doe relax blijf rustig <br>Yeah, doe relax <br>Doe relax lax lax <br>Doe relax, ohh <br>Doe relax lax lax ohoho]]></content><category term="Dopebwoy" label="Dopebwoy"/><category term="Tranquilo / Doe Relax" label="Tranquilo / Doe Relax"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Achee_Flips/Sluta_Aldrig_Dromma/</id><title>Achee Flips - Sluta Aldrig Dromma - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Achee_Flips/Sluta_Aldrig_Dromma/" title="Achee Flips - Sluta Aldrig Dromma - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eeeeh <br>Dom far aldrig nansin glomma mig <br>Eeeeeh <br>Lat dom aldrig nansin glomma dig <br>Eeeeeh <br>Alla har ju sina drommar <br>Eyeeeh <br>Sa jag slutar aldrig dromma, neeej <br><br>De galenskaper som vi lever i, hassla, jaga sedlar i <br>Tid ar pengar, broder ge mig mera tid <br>Ja later ingen satta hinder, lat ingen peka fingret <br>Sta inte still, du tar dig dit du vill <br><br>Sager tro pa din broder for du kan bli storst <br>Sager tro pa din syster, hoj din fucking rost <br>Lat dom aldrig trycka ner dig <br>Du maste kriga, aldrig ge dig <br>Pusha dig fram yea sa alla ser dig <br><br>Sager skit for att varlden ar var <br>Dom langar och vi star har vi star <br>Jag sager skin for att varlden ar var <br>Dom langar a vi gar dar vi gar <br>Men de ar lugnt <br><br>Dom vill satta oss i kedjor, dom vill snurra oss i loop <br>Se va dom har gjort me vara youths <br>De finns vagar ur allting, sa lange du ba tror <br>Sa lange du har lagan inombords yeeey <br><br>Eeeeh <br>Dom far aldrig nansin glomma mig <br>Eeeeeh <br>Lat dom aldrig nansin glomma dig <br>Eeeeeh <br>Alla har ju sina drommar <br>Eyeeeh <br>Sa jag slutar aldrig dromma, neeej <br><br>Jag slutar aldrig dromma, nej nej <br>Jag slutar aldrig dromma, nej nej nej nej neejj <br>Sa jag slutar aldrig dromma, neej <br><br>Gick livets harda skola, inga drommar ar for stora <br>Hade hal i vara skor, men ingen har som tappa tron <br>Vi kriga a vi kampa, hoppas a vi langta <br>Nagon dan en tjalla, hoppas vindarna ska vanda <br><br>Du maste vaga vara den du ar <br>Och inte den dom vill att du ska va <br>Du maste vaga vara den du ar <br>Va stark och aldrig visa dig svag <br><br>Dom vill slosa bort ditt liv, dom vill slosa bort din tid <br>Dom vill aldrig se dig dromma, dom vill aldrig se dig fri <br>Vi tittar upp mot stjarnorna, vi tittar upp i skyn <br>Mannen kasta allt de dar, sprid ut vingarna och flyg <br><br>Dom vill satta oss i kedjor, dom vill snurra oss i loop <br>Se vad dom har gjort med vara youths <br>De finns vagar ur allting, sa lange du ba tror <br>Sa lange du var lagan inombords, yeeey <br><br>Eeeeh <br>Dom far aldrig nansin glomma mig <br>Eeeeeh <br>Lat dom aldrig nansin glomma dig <br>Eeeeeh <br>Alla har ju sina drommar <br>Eyeeeh <br>Sa jag slutar aldrig dromma, neeej <br><br>Eeeeh <br>Dom far aldrig nansin glomma mig <br>Eeeeeh <br>Lat dom aldrig nansin glomma dig <br>Eeeeeh <br>Alla har ju sina drommar <br>Eyeeeh <br>Sa jag slutar aldrig dromma, neeej]]></content><category term="Achee Flips" label="Achee Flips"/><category term="Sluta Aldrig Dromma" label="Sluta Aldrig Dromma"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Locos_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Locos (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Locos_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Locos (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Estoy contento de tenerte cerca <br>Muy cerca de mi <br>Que me digas loco <br>Que me des de besos <br>Y que te rias de mi <br><br>Sabes que quiero decir <br>Ya no me mires asi <br>Y si me ves <br>Yo puedo decirte <br>Que eres lo mas bonito <br>Que he visto en toda mi vida <br><br>Y se que nunca te lo he dicho <br>Y me da miedo confesarte <br>Pero antes quiero besarte <br><br>Y llevo un rato tratando de decirte <br>Que ya no puedo vivir sin ti <br>Llevo anos tratando de decirte <br>Que te amo <br><br>Estoy contento de tenerte cerca <br>Muy cerca de mi <br>Que me digas loco <br>Que me des de besos <br>Y que te rias de mi <br><br>Sabes que quiero decir <br>Ya no me mires asi <br>Y si me ves <br>Yo puedo decirte <br>Que eres lo mas bonito <br>Que he visto en toda mi vida <br><br>Y se que nunca te lo he dicho <br>Y me da miedo confesarte <br>Pero antes quiero besarte <br><br>Y llevo un rato tratando de decirte <br>Que ya no puedo vivir sin ti <br>Llevo anos tratando de decirte <br>Que te amo <br>Esta noche estas loca como yo <br>Esta noche <br>Esta noche estas loca como yo <br>Estas loca]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Locos (Live)" label="Locos (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Brillas_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Brillas (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Brillas_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Brillas (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nos dimos todo lo que se nos dio <br>Nos dimos todo eso y mucho mas <br>Para despues reconocernos otra vez <br><br>Nos damos todo lo que se nos da <br>Nos damos todo eso y mucha mas <br>Amanecer colgado de tus labios <br><br>Oh <br><br>Brillas y brillas tan lindo <br>Y brillamos juntos entre pestanas <br>Divina, divina sonrisa <br>Abrazo de luna, de luna llena <br><br>Ah <br><br>Nos dimos todo lo que se nos dio <br>Nos dimos todo eso y mucho mas <br>Para despues reconocernos otra vez <br><br>Oh <br><br>Brillas y brillas tan lindo <br>Y brillamos juntos entre pestanas <br>Divina, divina sonrisa <br>Abrazo de luna, de luna llena <br>Y asi, juntitos los dos <br>Y asi, lo que se nos dio <br>Y asi, juntitos los dos <br>Y asi, lo que se nos da <br><br>Ah]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Brillas (Live)" label="Brillas (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Mar_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Mar (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Mar_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Mar (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bendito mar <br>Que limpias toda la maldad <br>Retiras toda la ansiedad <br>Y alivias los sentidos <br>Me haces convertirme en paz <br>Me desinfectas la ciudad <br>Y se me calma el alma <br><br>Descansar <br>Al ritmo de esta perfeccion <br>El tiempo suele perdonar <br>En esos ratos de armonia <br>Mira como pinta el sol <br>Las nubes de felicidad <br>De purpura frecuencia <br><br>Cargar energia para sentirse bien <br>Agarrar sincronia con la naturaleza <br>No quiero perderme, no <br>En la jungla de asfalto <br>La vida en la ciudad es imposible <br>No entiendo que hacemos ahi <br>Y lo digo de verdad <br>Dejemos todo y escapemos <br><br>Viejo mar <br>Me vuelves mi fragilidad <br>Me abres las heridas y <br>Las otras cicatrices <br>Me haces convertirme en paz <br>Me Bendito mar <br>Que limpias toda la maldad <br>Retiras toda la ansiedad <br>Y alivias los sentidos <br>Me haces convertirme en paz <br>Me desinfectas la ciudad <br>Y se me calma el alma <br><br>Descansar <br>Al ritmo de esta perfeccion <br>El tiempo suele perdonar <br>En esos ratos de armonia <br>Mira como pinta el sol <br>Las nubes de felicidad <br>De purpura frecuencia <br><br>Cargar energia para sentirse bien <br>Agarrar sincronia con la naturaleza <br>No quiero perderme, no <br>En la jungla de asfalto <br>La vida en la ciudad es imposible <br>No entiendo que hacemos ahi <br>Y lo digo de verdad <br>Dejemos todo y escapemos <br><br>Viejo mar <br>Me vuelves mi fragilidad <br>Me abres las heridas y <br>Las otras cicatrices <br>Me haces convertirme en paz <br>Me desinfectas la ciudad <br>Y se me calma el alma <br><br>Cargar energia para sentirse bien <br>Agarrar sincronia con la naturaleza <br>No quiero perderme, no <br>En la jungla de asfalto <br>En la metropoli la vida es imposible <br>No entiendo que hacemos ahi <br>Y te pido por favor <br>Dejemos todo y escapemos <br><br>Un salto de boca a boca <br>Cambiamos el mundo, mi amor <br>Un salto de cama a hamaca <br>Tirando los muros, mi amor <br>Al ritmo de una cancion <br>Bailamos contentos, mi amor <br>Un salto de paso en paso <br>Pisando la suerte, mi amor <br>Un salto de boca a boca <br>Abrimos la mente, mi amor <br>Un salto de cama a hamaca <br>Tumbamos las puertas mi amor]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Mar (Live)" label="Mar (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Resistolux_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Resistolux (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Resistolux_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Resistolux (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tu sabes que hacer <br>Tu sabes que hacer por un mundo mejor <br>No hay destino real <br>Se trata de como lo viajas mi amor <br><br>Abre la puerta, el amor no se guarda <br>Un grito de luz <br>Marchando en el cielo del amanecer <br>Tu sabes de que hablo es el fuego del alma mi amor <br><br>Resistelos, tu tienes el poder <br>Resistelos mi amor <br>Resistelos, tu tienes el poder <br>Que caigan los tiranos <br><br>Tu sabes que hacer <br>Tienes que luchar por el sol que tu quieres <br>No hay destino real <br>Se trata de como lo viajas mi amor <br><br>Abre la puerta, el amor no se guarda <br>Tu sabes de que hablo es el fuego del alma mi amor <br>Resistelos, tu tienes el poder <br>Resiste a los tiranos <br>Resistelos, tu tienes el poder <br>Que caigan los tiranos]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Resistolux (Live)" label="Resistolux (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Visiones_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Visiones (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Visiones_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Visiones (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Despierto en medio de la noche con una vision del futuro <br>De civilizaciones enteras, enterradas bajo la arena <br>No tiene caso vivir temiendole a todo, no, a todos <br>Ya no me queda tanto tiempo como antes, no, ya no <br><br>Hoy con mas razon, porque hoy te tengo a ti <br>La vida no se vive con temor, esa es otra, y hay conflicto <br><br>No te dejes enganar, todo es un mismo organismo <br>Que comparte la misma conciencia e ilusion <br>No estamos separados el uno del otro, no, no es cierto <br>Somos diferentes versiones del mismo ser y algoritmo <br><br>Hoy con mas razon, porque hoy te tengo a ti <br>La vida, no se vive con temor <br>Y hoy con mas razon, porque hoy te tengo a ti <br>La vida se vive con amor, hay amor <br><br>Ya, no hay visiones del futuro, desplantes toxicos <br>Hay amor <br>o esperanza que no pueda confiar en contra del mundo <br>Ah <br>Con visiones del futuro, desplantes toxicos <br>Hay amor <br>o esperanza que se pueda ponerse en contra del mundo <br>Hmm <br>Con visiones del futuro, desplantes toxicos <br>Hay amor <br>o esperanza que pueda ponerse en contra del mundo <br>Con visiones del futuro, desplantes to]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Visiones (Live)" label="Visiones (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Visitantes_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Visitantes (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Visitantes_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Visitantes (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Los visitantes del amor <br>Llegan vestidos de promesas <br>Llegan brillando con candor <br>Con esa inocencia inmaculada <br><br>Si me miras titubear <br>Es porque no encuentro palabras <br><br>Belleza de la naturaleza <br>Y siento que estaba a punto de explotarme el corazon <br>Belleza, uh grandeza <br>Te digo que es mentira <br>No hay amores imposibles <br><br>Los visitantes del amor <br>Labran la historia de tu vida <br>Y cada visita trae su adios <br>Una que otra ensenanza que se queda <br><br>Si me miras titubear <br>Es porque no encuentro palabras <br><br>Belleza de la naturaleza <br>Siento que estaba a punto de explotarme el corazon <br>Belleza uhh, grandeza <br>Te digo que es mentira <br>No hay amores imposibles <br><br>Vienen y van como diamantes en el mar <br>Que navegan dejando huellas al andar <br>Vienen y van como diamantes en el mar <br>Que navegan dejando huellas al andar <br>Si tu te vas, te deseo mucha suerte amor <br>Y nunca mas, no nunca mires atras <br><br>Y cuando quieras, no dudes en visitarme <br>Te estare esperando]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Visitantes (Live)" label="Visitantes (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Birdie_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Birdie (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Birdie_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Birdie (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fue una tarde en Nueva York <br>Inesperada <br>Despues de largo tiempo <br>Encontre a mi amor <br><br>Y La distancia no importo <br>Y Florecio <br>Y en mi alma siempre supe que eras tu <br><br>Mi gran amor <br>Mi companera <br>Mi adoracion <br>Mi gran amor <br>Mi Mejor amiga <br>Mi ensonacion <br><br>Transparente y bella <br>Pura como el sol <br>Eres real <br>Y el espiritu mas dulce que hay <br>Bella <br>Pura como el sol <br>Eres real <br>Y el espiritu mas dulce que existe <br><br>Recuerdo el nervio que me dio <br>En la Boutique <br>Cuando te escondiste en el vestidor <br>La gloria eterna y el sabor <br>Del primer beso <br>Que nos dimos en la calle Broadway <br><br>Tu mi gran amor <br>Mi companera <br>Mi adoracion <br>Mi gran amor <br>Mi Mejor amiga <br>Mi ensonacion <br><br>Transparente y bella <br>Pura como el sol <br>Eres real <br>Y el espiritu mas dulce que hay <br>Bella <br>Pura como el sol <br>Eres real <br>Y el espiritu mas dulce que existe]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Birdie (Live)" label="Birdie (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Rue_Vieille_Du_Temple_Live_Feat_Mon_Laferte/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Rue Vieille Du Temple (Live) (Feat. Mon Laferte) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Rue_Vieille_Du_Temple_Live_Feat_Mon_Laferte/" title="Leon Larregui - Rue Vieille Du Temple (Live) (Feat. Mon Laferte) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Te vas moviendo y cambias de color <br>Marque tu nombre en la corteza de mi ser <br>Peleando con demonios otra vez <br>Siempre me atacan cuando mas cansado estoy <br><br>Y es cuando tu me miras desde alla <br>Y sonriendome me regresas hasta ti <br>Conoces bien mi habilidad de volar <br>De divagar, entre los mundos <br><br>Te vas borrando con la multitud <br>Puedo ver los puntitos contra el cielo <br>Y cuando aprieto los ojos veo tu voz <br>Fantastica, geometrica, multicolor <br><br>Y es cuando tu me miras desde alla <br>Y sonriendome me regresas hasta ti <br>Conoces bien mi habilidad de volar <br>De divagar <br><br>Me haces volar <br>Me haces sonar <br>Me haces sentir tranquilo en la obscuridad <br>Me haces sentir <br>Me haces llorar <br>Me haces sentir que ya no existe gravedad <br>Me haces reir <br>Me haces cantar <br>Me haces pisar el suelo de la realidad <br><br>Sentarnos frente a frente <br>Y encontrarnos <br><br>Me haces volar <br>Me haces sonar <br>Me haces sentir que hay esperanza una vez mas <br>Y cuando me siento mal <br>O cuando pierdo el camino <br>Me haces pisar el suelo de la realidad <br><br>Sentarnos frente a frente <br>Y encontrarnos nuevamente]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Rue Vieille Du Temple (Live) (Feat. Mon Laferte)" label="Rue Vieille Du Temple (Live) (Feat. Mon Laferte)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Lattice_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Lattice (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Lattice_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Lattice (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Un habitante y su melancolia <br>Observan el cielo, esperando el dia <br>Miro las sombras deshelando el frio <br>Nutren sinfonias, vibran fantasias <br><br>Se estremecio, se abrio el portal <br>Reencarnacion dimensional <br><br>No se muy bien a donde ire <br>Creo que es momento de pasar a otro tiempo <br><br>Un habitante estudia las neuronas <br>Inyecta realidades, y encuentra la inconsciencia <br>Y se da cuenta de que aqui no hay nadie <br>Ni tampoco nada <br>Solo proyecciones <br><br>Se estremecio, se abrio el portal <br>Reencarnacion dimensional <br><br>No se muy bien a donde ire <br>Creo que es momento de pasar a otro tiempo <br><br>Perdoname por no avisar <br>Pero no estabas lista para ese hasta pronto]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Lattice (Live)" label="Lattice (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Tiraste_A_Matar_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Tiraste A Matar (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Tiraste_A_Matar_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Tiraste A Matar (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Si te vas amor <br>Ya no queda nada bueno <br>Si te vuelvo a ver <br>Ya no se si volveremos <br>Tiraste a matar <br>Y me diste en pleno vuelo <br><br>Y tienes razon <br>Que pretendo ser perfecto <br>Y que no lo soy <br>Me porte como un pendejo <br>Perdoname <br>Yo no quise hacerte dano <br><br>Se lo que sientes <br>Pero no soy el mismo de antes <br>Cargaba penas <br>Un karma denso y algo torcido <br>Un diablo que ahora vive bajo el mar <br><br>Y me das amor <br>Y confias en mis delirios <br>Y eres lo mejor <br>Que me ha sucedido <br>Tiraste a matar <br>Y me diste en pleno vuelo <br><br>Que digan lo que quieran <br>Pero no soy el mismo de antes <br>Cargaba penas <br>Un karma denso y algo torcido <br><br>Ya no, ya no, me vuelvo a tropezar <br>Ya no, ya no, me vuelvo a equivocar <br>Ya no, ya no, ya no vuelvo a castigar <br>Ya nunca mas arriesgare este amor <br><br>Mejor bailemos, que todo esta bien <br>Somos humanos y a veces inhumanos <br>Nos queremos mas fuerte que ayer <br>Y el mundo gira al reves]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Tiraste A Matar (Live)" label="Tiraste A Matar (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Zombies_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Zombies (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:58:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:58:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Zombies_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Zombies (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Traes, malefica aromatica <br>Tendencia a burlarte de mi <br>Colgada de mi corazon <br><br>Vas, maniaca del telefono <br>Enferma informatica fe <br>Pegada con las micro ondas <br><br>Vives, en una sopa de palabras <br>Poniendo caritas estupidas <br>Charlando con gente virtual evita a la real <br><br>No voy a dejar <br>Que me mientas de nuevo <br>No voy a dejar <br>Que me cristalices el alma <br><br>Y ahi van <br>Los zombies del telefono <br>Enferma y elastica fe <br>Los Jonkis de la micro onda <br><br>Vives en una sopa de palabras <br>Poniendo caritas estupidas <br>Charlando con gente virtual evita a la real <br><br>No voy a dejar <br>Que me mientas de nuevo <br>No voy a dejar <br>Que me cristalices el alma <br><br>No voy a dejar <br>Que me mientas de nuevo <br>No voy a dejar <br>Que me cristalices el alma <br><br>Entre lineas se perdia la voz <br>Entre lineas se perdia todo <br>Entre lineas se perdia la voz <br>Entre lineas se perdia todo]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Zombies (Live)" label="Zombies (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Tremantra_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Tremantra (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:59:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:59:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Tremantra_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Tremantra (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh senor de las galaxias, rey del tiempo escucha mi voz, mi corazon <br>Con dulces palabras nos sentimos en el atardecer <br>Gran parecer <br><br>Nos metimos en la noche <br>Cuando dejamos atrapar <br>En el medio de los pensamientos <br>Nos convertimos en presente <br>Nos despedimos de las formas <br>Y al final lleno y se presento el silencio <br><br>Tu dices amar la tierra <br>Amar a mis raices al suelo <br>No me dejes ir <br><br>Con dulces palabras nos sentimos con <br>El amanecer y al parecer <br><br>Nos metimos en las nubes <br>Para dejarnos atrapar <br>Y con el tiempo de mis pensamientos <br>Nos convertimos en presente <br>Nos disfrutamos de las formas <br>Y al final llego y se presento el amor <br><br>Luz del amor <br>Llegaste a mi vida <br>Con pura armonia <br>Ser del amor <br>Llenas mi vida <br>Con pura alegria <br>Ser del amor <br>Eres fantastico <br>Mi agrades, cielo <br>Enciende la luz <br>Estas lleno de fuerza <br>Y de poderes magicos <br>Hijo de mi amor]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Tremantra (Live)" label="Tremantra (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Souvenir_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Souvenir (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:59:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:59:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Souvenir_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Souvenir (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Y asi fue que me olvide de mi <br>Tratando de hacerte feliz <br>Y en el intento, me perdi <br>Y me dio miedo la distancia <br>En no ser bueno para ti <br>Y a un precipicio, me tire <br><br>Oh, no existe el amor <br>No existe el amor <br>Oh <br>Oh, cuando le buscas <br>Siempre fuera de ti <br><br>Un vil souvenir <br>Tu tesoro <br>Un pedazo de ayer <br>Mejor, asi <br>Sin enganos ni mentiras <br><br>Y dices que no estabas lista <br>Que no debiste continuar <br>Ahora ya es tarde para volver <br>Y fueron tantas las palabras <br>Mil promesas a la vez <br>Habra ilusiones huerfanas <br><br>Oh, no existe el amor <br>No existe el amor <br>Oh, cuando depende de algo <br>Fuera de ti <br>Oh, me dices que soy <br>Un ser especial <br>Oh, pero me haces sentir <br>Como un vil souvenir <br><br>Un vil souvenir <br>Tu tesoro <br>Un pedazo de ayer <br>Mejor, asi <br>Sin enganos ni mentiras <br><br>Oh, no existe el amor <br>No existe el amor <br>Oh, cuando lo buscas siempre <br>Fuera de ti <br>Oh, me dices que soy <br>Un ser especial <br>Oh, pero me haces sentir <br>Como un vil souvenir <br><br>Un vil souvenir <br>Tu tesoro <br>Un pedazo de ayer <br>Mejor, asi <br>Sin enganos ni mentiras]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Souvenir (Live)" label="Souvenir (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Carmin_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Carmin (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:59:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:59:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Carmin_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Carmin (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No encuentro sentido amor <br>Que me alejes mas de ti <br>Yo se que me extranas <br>Y que te hace falta mi calor <br>Te hace falta mi calor <br>No encuentro sentido amor <br>Que me alejes mas de ti <br>Yo se que me amas <br>Y que te hace falta mi amor <br><br>Te extrano tanto <br>Que me vuelvo gris <br>Te extrano tanto <br>Que me ahogo en aguas de carmin <br>Te extrano tanto <br>Que me vuelvo gris <br>Te extrano tanto <br>Que me ahogo en aguas de carmin <br><br>No encuentro sentido amor <br>Que me alejes mas de ti <br>Se que me echas de menos <br>Y que te hace falta mi calor <br>Te hace falta mi calor <br><br>Te extrano tanto <br>Que me vuelvo gris <br>Te extrano tanto <br>Que me ahogo en aguas de carmin <br>Te extrano tanto <br>Que me vuelvo gris <br>Te extrano tanto <br>Que me ahogo en aguas de carmin <br><br>Y junto al rio me fui a llorar <br>Al mar le ensene las penas <br>Y junto al rio me fui a llorar <br>Al mar le ensene las penas <br>Y junto al rio me fui a llorar <br>El mar que se lleve las penas]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Carmin (Live)" label="Carmin (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Aurora_Boreal_Live/</id><title>Leon Larregui - Aurora Boreal (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:59:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:59:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leon_Larregui/Aurora_Boreal_Live/" title="Leon Larregui - Aurora Boreal (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tuviste tiempo para ver <br>Tuviste tiempo pa' pensar <br>Y espacio para meditar <br>Mirando la aurora boreal <br><br>Que facil se disuelve todo <br>Que rico se siente estar solo <br>Aunque te tengo muy presente <br>Mirando la aurora boreal <br><br>Un milagro en el cielo frio <br>Cauteriza tus lagrimas <br>Tranquilidad vestida de blanco <br>Y un par de planetas alineados <br><br>Fragilidad tu orquesta de luces <br>Respiras el aire mas tierno del mundo <br>Al ritmo de dios <br>Al ritmo del sol <br><br>Tuvimos tiempo para ver <br>Tuvimos tiempo pa' pensar <br>Y espacio para meditar <br>Mirando la aurora boreal <br><br>Un milagro en el cielo frio <br>Cauteriza tus lagrimas <br>Tranquilidad vestida de blanco <br>Y un par de planetas alineados <br><br>Fragilidad tu orquesta de luces <br>Respiras el aire mas tierno del mundo <br>Al ritmo de dios <br>Al ritmo del sol]]></content><category term="Leon Larregui" label="Leon Larregui"/><category term="Aurora Boreal (Live)" label="Aurora Boreal (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Show_Me_The_Body/Why_You_lying/</id><title>Show Me The Body - Why You lying - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T18:59:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T18:59:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Show_Me_The_Body/Why_You_lying/" title="Show Me The Body - Why You lying - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All I gave a fuck about was <br>yo <br>these mother fuckers aint jacking us they aint pulling us into no fucking alleyway i dont have to use this fuckin knife i got in my pocket i can jus go home and <br>write some fucking grafitti in a big ass book <br>try and do a fuckin piece stoned out of my mind with my mother knocking on my door be like <br>'what are you doing' <br>I'm like 'leave me alone, leave me alone, i dont feel well, leave me alone, I cant go to school today I dont feel well' <br><br>Why you lying to to your fans <br>your word is incredible why <br>shorty homegirls seen the show said <br>you was incredible damn <br>smoking on loud, know i'm not eating no edibles smokin' on gat <br>Eyes on my team, i feel like really incredible <br><br>Why you lyin' to to your fans <br>your word is incredible i know <br>shorty homegirls seen the show said <br>that shit was incredible thank you <br>smoking on loud, know i'm not eatin' no edibles loud <br>Eyes on my team, i feel like really incredible hey <br><br>Leave me alone, i don't want to speak to you <br>turn off my phone for a week or two that is unreasonable <br><br>These niggas translucent i see thru u see thru it <br>snakes in the grass you know i be peepin' you i see you <br><br>if Sagi not eatin' you know i'm not eatin' too <br>you is not there then you know there's no seat for you <br>this not a charity boy i cant eat with you <br>i got my own crib i don't got to sneak into <br><br>Why you lyin' to to your fans <br>your word is incredible it's not <br>shorty homegirls seen the show said <br>that you was incredible thank u <br>smoking on loud, know im not eatin no edibles gat <br>Eyes on my team, i feel like really incredible <br><br>why you lying to to your fans <br>your word is incredible i know <br>shorty homegirls seen the show said <br>that shit was incredible <br>smoking on loud, know i'm not eatin no edibles smokin on gat <br>Eyes on my team, i feel like really incredible]]></content><category term="Show Me The Body" label="Show Me The Body"/><category term="Why You lying" label="Why You lying"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Show_Me_The_Body/Im_On_it/</id><title>Show Me The Body - I`m On it - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Show_Me_The_Body/Im_On_it/" title="Show Me The Body - I`m On it - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The voices in my head say go get it <br>I'm on it <br>The noises, distorted <br>Sounds, imported <br>A change for me in mind <br>Is the only thing important <br>I'm on it <br>I'm on it <br>I'm on it <br>I'm on it <br><br>Go get it <br>I got it <br>As soon as I quote it <br>Lets get it <br>Who got it <br>Cause I'm coming for it <br>No fill top just just fill the whole swisher with the purest <br>If your in this shit is laden I'm the one to thank for it <br>I been on a roll ruin <br>Smoking on that Russian coolant <br>Ain't been home in the longest <br>Ain't no telling where I'm going <br>Ain't no telling where I'm headed <br>I can tell that thing ready <br>I'm a pull up on them heavy <br>In that all black chevy <br>Dressed in only that black <br>And my back is not black <br>And my steez is not black <br>Maybe twist my hat back <br>Imma bring the trap back <br>Lurking in the trap lap <br>You know where I trap at <br>If you know where that trap lap <br><br>They should check it that back <br>I'm on it <br>Tell me bring that trap back <br>I'm on it <br>Tell me run that check back <br>I'm on it <br>I know they respect that <br>I'm on it <br><br>I'm on the grind <br>It's morning time <br>I put in work <br>That's overtime <br>Life's a ride <br>You got a hanging <br>If you fall don't fall behind <br>Everybody got a thing <br>You just got to find your thing <br>I'm just trying find mine <br>You could look but never find <br>You could look but as you searching <br>You could pre <br>But as you lurking <br>Not gon' see behind the curtain <br>Not got work if you not working <br>I got work I hear supply <br>I gotta work to make you buy <br>Take a trip on wastin time <br>On my sick days had the grime <br><br>The voices in my head say go get it <br>I'm on it <br>The noises, distorted <br>The Sounds, imported <br>A change for me in mind <br>Is the only thing important <br>I'm on it <br>I'm on it <br>I'm on it <br>I'm on it <br><br>They say shaq get that back <br>I'm on it <br>Tell me bring the trap back <br>I'm on it <br>Tell me run that check back <br>I'm on it <br>I know they respect that <br>I'm on it <br><br>They say shaq get that back <br>I'm on it <br>Tell me bring the trap back <br>I'm on it <br>Tell me bring that check back <br>I'm on it <br>I know they respect that <br>I'm on it <br><br>I got the mic <br>I was like holding boom fight <br>Let me show you how we hick, night <br>When we start the fire know it <br>I'm not lying <br>Gotta keep it real <br>Gotta still <br>I ain't been home for real <br>Wait let me tell you what I'm really thinking <br>Probably gotta go ahead <br>Really started with <br>Y'all been drawling <br>I ain't really go the dro <br>I be getting all the clo <br>I'm on in out <br>I don't care what you talkin' bout <br><br>Words in my mind <br>A creature can't reach ya Ok <br>My accent's somethin I can't teach ya <br>Can't knock me out so sweet <br>Sound down with the beat <br>The heart beat <br>Nuff stinct <br>Make me wanna sing <br>Trap for couples in the week <br>Pling more fast side <br>Leave em rasping <br>Leave em laughing <br>While you trapping <br>A triple tasking <br>I sought the flat <br>I got the cake <br>So I baked it <br>Paddycake with cake <br>All you fakes <br>With the cake just wait <br>Wonder woman is that <br>Wouldn't hurt with third eye <br>I heard a cake wait <br>Get it]]></content><category term="Show Me The Body" label="Show Me The Body"/><category term="I`m On it" label="I`m On it"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Show_Me_The_Body/You_Thought_What_You_Saw_Was_It/</id><title>Show Me The Body - You Thought What You Saw Was It - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Show_Me_The_Body/You_Thought_What_You_Saw_Was_It/" title="Show Me The Body - You Thought What You Saw Was It - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Burning <br>I can taste it coming up <br>Venom drop <br>I can feel it burning up <br>Burning <br>I can taste it coming up <br>Venom drop <br>I can feel it burning up <br><br>Burning <br>I can taste it coming up <br>Venom drop <br>I can taste it burning up <br>Burning <br>I can taste it coming up <br>Venom drop <br>I can feel it burning up <br>Burning <br>I can taste it coming up <br>Venom drop <br>I can feel it burning up <br><br>I'm the needlepoint <br>Needlepoint <br>Needlepoint <br>Needlepoint <br>Cross stitch up over your lips <br><br>Who you gonna fight <br>Everybody Everybody's down with the team Motherfucker, this is personal I'm taking this shit personal I ain't on nobody's team I'm taking care of me, my little crew, fuck it]]></content><category term="Show Me The Body" label="Show Me The Body"/><category term="You Thought What You Saw Was It" label="You Thought What You Saw Was It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Show_Me_The_Body/Trash/</id><title>Show Me The Body - Trash - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Show_Me_The_Body/Trash/" title="Show Me The Body - Trash - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah you already know what time it is <br>Time is of the essence mothafucka <br><br>Take drugs when I need to <br>Get love when I need to, Fuck when I need to <br>Show love when I need to <br>Get rough if in need get up if I need to <br>Trust none when I need to <br>Feel done when I need to none when I need two <br>Abhorred when I need to <br>Good lord if I need take yours if I need to <br><br>Come up catch slip back <br>Coma shaft open gas <br><br>Don't know what I need <br>You keep telling me <br>Get away from me <br>Hundred ways to make me feel <br>Only one way to make me heal <br><br>Come up catch slip back <br>Coma shaft open gas <br><br>Take drugs when I need to <br>Get love when I need to, Fuck when I need to <br>Show love when I need to <br>Get rough if in need get up if I need to <br>Trust none when I need to <br>Feel done when I need to none when I need two <br>Abhorred when I need to <br>Good lord if I need take yours if I need to <br><br>One bottle when I need two <br>I sip when I need one bottle when I need two <br>I hit when I need to <br>Cut wrist when I need I lick when I need to <br>On the street when I need to <br>I bleed when I need to I eat when I need to <br>Fought cops when I need to <br>On the street when I need to eat when I need to <br><br>Come up catch slip back <br>Coma shaft open gas <br><br>Don't know what I need <br>You keep telling me <br>Get away from me <br>Hundred ways to make me feel <br>Only one way to make me heal]]></content><category term="Show Me The Body" label="Show Me The Body"/><category term="Trash" label="Trash"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Show_Me_The_Body/Intro/</id><title>Show Me The Body - Intro - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Show_Me_The_Body/Intro/" title="Show Me The Body - Intro - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't give a fuck what you do <br>just do whatever <br>Don't fucking make excuses <br>just do what you know how to do <br>and don't fucking make excuses <br>just do it]]></content><category term="Show Me The Body" label="Show Me The Body"/><category term="Intro" label="Intro"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/O_Sol_Nascera_A_Sorrir_Ao_Vivo___BIS/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - O Sol Nascera (A Sorrir) (Ao Vivo / BIS) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/O_Sol_Nascera_A_Sorrir_Ao_Vivo___BIS/" title="Ney Matogrosso - O Sol Nascera (A Sorrir) (Ao Vivo / BIS) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A sorrir <br>Eu pretendo levar a vida <br>Pois chorando <br>Eu vi a mocidade perdida <br><br>A sorrir <br>Eu pretendo levar a vida <br>Pois chorando <br>Eu vi a mocidade perdida <br><br>Finda a tempestade <br>O sol nascera <br>Finda esta saudade <br>Hei de ter outro alguem para amar <br><br>A sorrir <br>Eu pretendo levar a vida <br>Pois chorando <br>Eu vi a mocidade perdida <br><br>A sorrir <br>Eu pretendo levar a vida <br>Pois chorando <br>Eu vi a mocidade perdida <br><br>Levar a vida]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="O Sol Nascera (A Sorrir) (Ao Vivo / BIS)" label="O Sol Nascera (A Sorrir) (Ao Vivo / BIS)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Basta_De_Clamares_Inocencia_Ao_Vivo___BIS/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Basta De Clamares Inocencia (Ao Vivo / BIS) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Basta_De_Clamares_Inocencia_Ao_Vivo___BIS/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Basta De Clamares Inocencia (Ao Vivo / BIS) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Basta de clamares inocencia <br>Eu sei todo o mal que a mim voce fez <br>Voce desconhece consciencia <br>So deseja o mal a quem o bem te fez <br><br>Basta, nao ajoelhes, va embora <br>Se estas arrependida <br>Ve se chora <br>Quando voce partiu <br><br>Disseste chora, nao chorei <br>Caprichosamente fui esquecendo <br>Que te amei <br>Hoje me encontras tao alegre e diferente <br><br>Jesus nao castiga o filho que esta inocente <br>Basta, nao ajoelhes, va embora <br>Se estas arrependida <br>Ve se chora]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Basta De Clamares Inocencia (Ao Vivo / BIS)" label="Basta De Clamares Inocencia (Ao Vivo / BIS)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Peito_Vazio_Ao_Vivo___BIS/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Peito Vazio (Ao Vivo / BIS) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Peito_Vazio_Ao_Vivo___BIS/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Peito Vazio (Ao Vivo / BIS) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nada consigo fazer <br>Quando a saudade aperta <br>Foge me a inspiracao <br>Sinto a alma deserta <br>Um vazio se faz em meu peito <br>E de fato eu sinto <br>Em meu peito um vazio <br>Me faltando as tuas caricias <br>As noites sao longas <br>E eu sinto mais frio <br>Procuro afogar no alcool <br>A tua lembranca <br>Mas noto que e ridicula <br>A minha vinganca <br>Vou seguir os conselhos <br>De amigos <br>E garanto que nao beberei <br>Nunca mais <br>E com o tempo <br>Essa imensa saudade que sinto <br>Se esvai]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Peito Vazio (Ao Vivo / BIS)" label="Peito Vazio (Ao Vivo / BIS)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Preciso_Me_Encontrar_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Preciso Me Encontrar (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Preciso_Me_Encontrar_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Preciso Me Encontrar (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Deixe me ir preciso andar <br>Vou por ai a procurar <br>Rir pra nao chorar <br>Quero assistir o sol nascer <br>Ver as aguas dos rios correr <br>Ouvir os passaros cantar <br>Eu quero nascer quero viver <br>Deixe me ir preciso andar <br>Vou por ai a procurar <br>Rir pra nao chorar <br>Se alguem for vir perguntar <br>Diga que eu so vou voltar depois que eu me encontrar <br>Quero assistir o sol nascer <br>Ver as aguas dos rios correr <br>Ouvir os passaros cantar <br>Eu quero nascer quero viver <br>Deixe me ir preciso andar <br>Vou por ai a procurar <br>Rir pra nao chorar]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Preciso Me Encontrar (Ao Vivo)" label="Preciso Me Encontrar (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Nao_Quero_Mais_Amar_A_Ninguem_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Nao Quero Mais Amar A Ninguem (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Nao_Quero_Mais_Amar_A_Ninguem_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Nao Quero Mais Amar A Ninguem (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nao quero mais amar a ninguem <br>Nao fui feliz, o destino nao quis <br>O meu primeiro amor <br>Morreu como a flor, ainda em botao <br>Deixando espinhos que dilaceram meu coracao <br>Semente de amor sei que sou desde nascenca <br>Mas sem ter a vida e fulgor, heis minha sentenca <br>Tentei pela primeira vez um sonho vibrar <br>Foi beijo que nasceu e morreu, sem se chegar a dar <br>bisa a primeira parte <br>as vezes dou gargalhada ao lembrar do passado <br>Nunca pensei em amor, nunca amei nem fui amado <br>Se julgas que estou mentindo, jurar sou capaz <br>Foi simples sonho que passou e nada mais]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Nao Quero Mais Amar A Ninguem (Ao Vivo)" label="Nao Quero Mais Amar A Ninguem (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Desfigurado_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Desfigurado (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Desfigurado_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Desfigurado (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dizem que estou desfigurado, com razao <br>Estou cansado de pedir a Deus <br>E aos ceus enfim <br>Um amor, onde encontrarei, Senhor <br>Livrai me desta nostalgia <br>Confiante ainda espero um dia <br><br>Meu coracao e pobre e magoado <br>e infeliz como um menor abandonado <br>Viveu sempre nesta ilusao <br>Procurando um outro coracao]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Desfigurado (Ao Vivo)" label="Desfigurado (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Ensaboa_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Ensaboa (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Ensaboa_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Ensaboa (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ensaboa mulata, ensaboa <br>Ensaboa <br>To ensaboando <br>Ensaboa mulata, ensaboa <br>Ensaboa <br>To ensaboando <br>To lavando a minha roupa <br>La em casa estao me chamando Dondo <br>Ensaboa mulata, ensaboa <br>Ensaboa <br>To ensaboando <br><br>O filho que e meu <br>que e meu e que e dela <br>Rebenta a goela de tanto chora <br>O rio ta seco, o sol nao vem nao <br>Voltemos pra casa <br>Chamando Dondo]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Ensaboa (Ao Vivo)" label="Ensaboa (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Senoes_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Senoes (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Senoes_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Senoes (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nosso romance teve <br>senoes <br>e se separaram dois <br>coracoes <br>Posso chorar, ate esquecer <br>mas o meu desejo e viver <br>longe de voce <br><br>Meu interesse e viver sem voce <br>Nosso passado eu procuro esquecer <br>Ao grande protetor eu <br>peco em uma prece <br>Senhor, por piedade, ve se <br>ela me esquece <br>O nosso amor <br>um grande amor <br>termina assim <br>Todo o romance tem <br>principio e tem fim]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Senoes (Ao Vivo)" label="Senoes (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Peito_Vazio_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Peito Vazio (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Peito_Vazio_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Peito Vazio (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nada consigo fazer <br>Quando a saudade aperta <br>Foge me a inspiracao <br>Sinto a alma deserta <br>Um vazio se faz em meu peito <br>E de fato eu sinto <br>Em meu peito um vazio <br>Me faltando as tuas caricias <br>As noites sao longas <br>E eu sinto mais frio <br>Procuro afogar no alcool <br>A tua lembranca <br>Mas noto que e ridicula <br>A minha vinganca <br>Vou seguir os conselhos <br>De amigos <br>E garanto que nao beberei <br>Nunca mais <br>E com o tempo <br>Essa imensa saudade que sinto <br>Se esvai]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Peito Vazio (Ao Vivo)" label="Peito Vazio (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Amor_Proibido_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Amor Proibido (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Amor_Proibido_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Amor Proibido (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sabes que vou partir <br>Com os olhos rasos d'agua <br>E o coracao ferido <br>Quando lembrar de ti <br>Me lembrarei tambem <br>Deste amor proibido <br>Facil demais <br>Foi presa <br>Servir de pasto <br>Em tua mesa <br>Mas fique certa que jamais <br>Teras o meu amor <br>Pq nao tens pudor <br>Faco tudo para evitar o mal <br>Sou pelo mal perseguido <br>So o que faltava era esta <br>Fui trair meu grande amigo <br>Mas vou limpar a mente <br>Sei que errei <br>Errei inocente <br>Sabes que vou partir]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Amor Proibido (Ao Vivo)" label="Amor Proibido (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/O_Mundo_E_Um_Moinho_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - O Mundo E Um Moinho (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/O_Mundo_E_Um_Moinho_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - O Mundo E Um Moinho (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ainda e cedo amor <br>Mal comecaste a conhecer a vida <br>Ja anuncias a hora de partida <br>Sem saber mesmo o rumo que iras tomar <br><br>Preste atencao querida, embora eu saiba que estas resolvida <br>Em cada esquina cai um pouco a tua vida <br>Em pouco tempo nao seras mais o que es <br>Ouca me bem amor <br><br>Preste atencao, o mundo e um moinho <br>Vai triturar teus sonhos tao mesquinho <br>Vai reduzir as ilusoes a po <br>Preste atencao querida <br><br>De cada amor tu herdaras so o cinismo <br>Quando notares estas a beira do abismo <br>Abismo que cavaste com teus pes]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="O Mundo E Um Moinho (Ao Vivo)" label="O Mundo E Um Moinho (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Tive_Sim_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Tive Sim (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Tive_Sim_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Tive Sim (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tive sim outro grande amor antes do teu, tive sim <br>O que ela sonhava eram os meus sonhos e a assim <br>iamos vivendo em paz <br>Nosso lar em nosso lar sempre houve alegria <br>e eu vivia tao contente como contente ao teu lado estou <br>Tive sim, mas comparado ao teu amor seria o fim <br>Eu vou calar, pois nao pretendo amor te magoar <br><br>Tive sim outro grande amor antes do teu, tive sim <br>O que ela sonhava era os meus sonhos e a assim <br>iamos vivendo em paz <br>Nosso lar em nosso lar sempre houve alegria <br>e eu vivia tao contente como contente ao teu lado estou <br>Tive sim, mas comparar com teu amor seria o fim <br>E vou calar, pois nao pretendo amor te magoar <br><br>Ai, ai <br>Pois nao pretendo, amor, te magoar <br>Ai, ai Ai, ai <br>Pois nao pretendo, amor, te magoar <br>Ai, ai <br>Pois nao pretendo, amor, te magoar]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Tive Sim (Ao Vivo)" label="Tive Sim (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Autonomia_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Autonomia (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Autonomia_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Autonomia (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[e impossivel nesta primavera eu sei <br>Impossivel, pois longe estarei <br>Mas pensando em nosso amor <br>Amor sincero <br>Ai, se eu tivesse autonomia <br>Se eu pudesse, gritaria <br>Nao vou, nao quero <br>Escravizaram assim um pobre coracao <br>e necessario a nova abolicao <br>Pra trazer de volta a minha liberdade <br>Se eu pudesse, gritaria amor <br>Se eu pudesse, brigaria, amor <br>Nao vou, nao quero]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Autonomia (Ao Vivo)" label="Autonomia (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Basta_De_Clamares_Inocencia_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Basta De Clamares Inocencia (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Basta_De_Clamares_Inocencia_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Basta De Clamares Inocencia (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Basta de clamares inocencia <br>Eu sei todo o mal que a mim voce fez <br>Voce desconhece consciencia <br>So deseja o mal a quem o bem te fez <br><br>Basta, nao ajoelhes, va embora <br>Se estas arrependida <br>Ve se chora <br>Quando voce partiu <br><br>Disseste chora, nao chorei <br>Caprichosamente fui esquecendo <br>Que te amei <br>Hoje me encontras tao alegre e diferente <br><br>Jesus nao castiga o filho que esta inocente <br>Basta, nao ajoelhes, va embora <br>Se estas arrependida <br>Ve se chora]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Basta De Clamares Inocencia (Ao Vivo)" label="Basta De Clamares Inocencia (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Acontece_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Acontece (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Acontece_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Acontece (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Esquece nosso amor ve se esquece <br>Porque tudo no mundo acontece <br>E acontece que ja nao sei mais amar <br>Vai chorar vai sofrer <br>E voce nao merece <br>Mas isso acontece <br>Acontece que meu coracao ficou frio <br>E nosso ninho de amor esta vazio <br>Se eu ainda pudesse fingir que te amo <br>Ai se eu pudesse <br>Mas nao quero, nao devo faze lo <br>Isso nao acontece]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Acontece (Ao Vivo)" label="Acontece (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/As_Rosas_Nao_Falam_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - As Rosas Nao Falam (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:00:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:00:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/As_Rosas_Nao_Falam_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - As Rosas Nao Falam (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bate outra vez <br>Com esperancas o meu coracao <br>Pois ja vai terminando o verao enfim <br><br>Volto ao jardim <br>Com a certeza que devo chorar <br>Pois bem sei que nao queres voltar para mim <br><br>Queixo me as rosas, mas que bobagem <br>As rosas nao falam <br>Simplesmente as rosas exalam <br>O perfume que roubam de ti <br><br>Devias vir <br>Para ver os meus olhos tristonhos <br>E, quem sabe, sonhava meus sonhos <br>por fim]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="As Rosas Nao Falam (Ao Vivo)" label="As Rosas Nao Falam (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Corra_E_Olhe_O_Ceu_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Corra E Olhe O Ceu (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:01:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:01:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Corra_E_Olhe_O_Ceu_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Corra E Olhe O Ceu (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Linda te sinto mais bela <br>Te fico na espera <br>Me sinto tao so, mas <br>O tempo que passa <br>Em dor maior, bem maior <br>Linda no que se apresenta <br>O triste se ausenta <br>Fez se a alegria <br>Corra e olha o ceu <br>Que o sol vem trazer bom dia <br>Ah, corra e olha o ceu]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Corra E Olhe O Ceu (Ao Vivo)" label="Corra E Olhe O Ceu (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Cordas_De_Aco_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Cordas De Aco (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:01:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:01:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Cordas_De_Aco_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Cordas De Aco (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ah Estas cordas de aco <br>Este minusculo braco <br>Do violao que os dedos meus acariciam <br>Ah Este bojo perfeito <br>Que trago junto ao meu peito <br>So voce violao <br>Compreende porque perdi toda alegria <br>E no entanto meu pinho <br>Pode crer, eu adivinho <br>Aquela mulher <br>Ate hoje esta nos esperando <br>Solte o teu som da madeira <br>Eu voce e a companheira <br>A madrugada iremos pra casa <br>Cantando]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Cordas De Aco (Ao Vivo)" label="Cordas De Aco (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Sim_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - Sim (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:01:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:01:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/Sim_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - Sim (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sim <br>Deve haver o perdao <br>Para mim <br>Senao nem sei qual sera <br>O meu fim <br><br>Para ter uma companheira <br>Ate promessas fiz <br>Consegui um grande amor <br>Mas eu nao fui feliz <br>E com raiva para os ceus <br>Os bracos levantei <br>Blasfemei <br>Hoje todos sao contra mim <br><br>Todos erram neste mundo <br>Nao ha excecao <br>Quando voltam a realidade <br>Conseguem perdao <br>Porque e que eu Senhor <br>Que errei pela vez primeira <br>Passo tantos dissabores <br>E luto contra a humanidade inteira]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="Sim (Ao Vivo)" label="Sim (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/O_Sol_Nascera_A_Sorrir_Ao_Vivo/</id><title>Ney Matogrosso - O Sol Nascera (A Sorrir) (Ao Vivo) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:01:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:01:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ney_Matogrosso/O_Sol_Nascera_A_Sorrir_Ao_Vivo/" title="Ney Matogrosso - O Sol Nascera (A Sorrir) (Ao Vivo) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A sorrir <br>Eu pretendo levar a vida <br>Pois chorando <br>Eu vi a mocidade perdida <br><br>A sorrir <br>Eu pretendo levar a vida <br>Pois chorando <br>Eu vi a mocidade perdida <br><br>Finda a tempestade <br>O sol nascera <br>Finda esta saudade <br>Hei de ter outro alguem para amar <br><br>A sorrir <br>Eu pretendo levar a vida <br>Pois chorando <br>Eu vi a mocidade perdida <br><br>A sorrir <br>Eu pretendo levar a vida <br>Pois chorando <br>Eu vi a mocidade perdida <br><br>Levar a vida]]></content><category term="Ney Matogrosso" label="Ney Matogrosso"/><category term="O Sol Nascera (A Sorrir) (Ao Vivo)" label="O Sol Nascera (A Sorrir) (Ao Vivo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Harry_Styles/Sign_Of_The_Times_LG_V30_광고_삽입곡/</id><title>Harry Styles - Sign Of The Times (LG V30 광고 삽입곡) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:01:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:01:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Harry_Styles/Sign_Of_The_Times_LG_V30_%EA%B4%91%EA%B3%A0_%EC%82%BD%EC%9E%85%EA%B3%A1/" title="Harry Styles - Sign Of The Times (LG V30 광고 삽입곡) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just stop your crying <br>It’s a sign of the times <br>Welcome to the final show <br>Hope you’re wearing <br>your best clothes <br>You can't bribe the door <br>on your way to the sky <br>You look pretty good down here <br>But you ain't really good <br>If we never learn <br>we been here before <br>Why are we always stuck <br>and running from <br>The bullets <br>The bullets <br>We never learn <br>we been here before <br>Why are we always stuck <br>and running from <br>The bullets <br>The bullets <br>Just stop your crying <br>It’s a sign of the times <br>We gotta get away from here <br>We gotta get away from here <br>Just stop your crying <br>It will be alright <br>They told me that the end is near <br>We gotta get away from here <br>Just stop crying <br>Have the time of your life <br>Breaking through the atmosphere <br>And things are pretty good <br>from here <br>Remember everything <br>will be alright <br>We can meet again somewhere <br>Somewhere far away from here <br>If we never learn <br>we been here before <br>Why are we always stuck <br>and running from <br>The bullets <br>The bullets <br>We never learn <br>we been here before <br>Why are we always stuck <br>and running from <br>The bullets <br>The bullets <br>Just stop your crying <br>It’s a sign of the times <br>We gotta get away from here <br>We gotta get away from here <br>stop your crying <br>Baby it will be alright <br>They told me that the end is near <br>We gotta get away from here <br>If we never learn <br>we been here before <br>Why are we always stuck <br>and running from <br>The bullets <br>The bullets <br>We never learn <br>we been here before <br>Why are we always stuck <br>and running from <br>The bullets <br>The bullets <br>We don't talk enough <br>We should open up <br>Before it's all too much <br>Will we ever learn <br>We've been here before <br>It's just what we know <br>Stop your crying baby <br>It’s a sign of the times <br>We gotta get away <br>We got to get away <br>We got to get away <br>We got to get away <br>We got to get away <br>We got to we got to <br>We got to we got to <br>We got to we got to <br>]]></content><category term="Harry Styles" label="Harry Styles"/><category term="Sign Of The Times (LG V30 광고 삽입곡)" label="Sign Of The Times (LG V30 광고 삽입곡)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pentatonix/Cant_Help_Falling_In_Love/</id><title>Pentatonix - Can`t Help Falling In Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:01:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:01:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pentatonix/Cant_Help_Falling_In_Love/" title="Pentatonix - Can`t Help Falling In Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wise men say <br>only fools rush in <br>but I can't help <br>falling in love with you <br>Shall I stay <br>Would it be a sin <br>if I can't help <br>falling in love with you <br>Like a river flows <br>surley to the sea <br>darling so it goes <br>some thing are meant to be <br>Take my hand <br>take my whole life too <br>but I can't help <br>falling in love with you <br>Like a river flows <br>surely to the sea <br>darling so it goes <br>some things are meant to be <br>Take my hand <br>take my whole life too <br>for I can't help <br>falling in love with you <br>but I can't help <br>falling in love with you <br>]]></content><category term="Pentatonix" label="Pentatonix"/><category term="Can`t Help Falling In Love" label="Can`t Help Falling In Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pentatonix/Take_On_Me/</id><title>Pentatonix - Take On Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:01:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:01:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pentatonix/Take_On_Me/" title="Pentatonix - Take On Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're talking away <br>I don't know what <br>I'm to say I'll say it anyway <br>Today's another day to find you <br>Shying away <br>I'll be coming for your love okay <br>Take on me take on me <br>Take me on take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day or two <br>Take on me <br>So needless to say <br>I'm odds and ends <br>I'll be stumbling away <br>Slowly learning that life is OK <br>Say after me <br>It's no better to be safe than sorry <br>Take on me take on me <br>Take me on take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day or two <br>In a day or two <br>Take on me <br>Oh the things that you say <br>Is it live or <br>Just to play my worries away <br>You're all the things <br>I've got to remember <br>You're shying away <br>I'll be coming for you anyway <br>Take on me take on me <br>Take me on take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day <br>Take on me take on me <br>Take me on take on me <br>I'll be gone <br>In a day or two <br>]]></content><category term="Pentatonix" label="Pentatonix"/><category term="Take On Me" label="Take On Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pentatonix/Imagine/</id><title>Pentatonix - Imagine - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-10T19:01:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-10T19:01:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pentatonix/Imagine/" title="Pentatonix - Imagine - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine there's no heaven <br>It's easy if you try <br>no hell below us <br>above us only sky <br>Imagine all the people <br>living for today yeah- <br>Imagine there's no countries <br>It isn't hard to do <br>nothing to kill or die for oh- <br>and no religion too <br>imagine all the people <br>living life in peace as you <br>you may say I'm a dreamer (dreamer) <br>but I'm not the only one (not the only one) <br>I hope someday you'll join us <br>and the world will be as one <br>will be as one <br>imagine no posessions <br>I wonder if you can <br>no need for greed or hunger <br>a brotherhood of man <br>oh- imagine all the people <br>sharing all the world <br>you may say I'm a dreamer (dreamer) <br>but I am not the only one (not the only one) <br>I hope someday you'll join us <br>and the wolrd will live as one <br>(live as one) <br>(will live as one) <br>(will live as one) <br>live as one <br>Oneday all the world will live as one <br>you may say I'm a dreamer <br>but I'm not the only one (not the only one) <br>I hope someday you'll join us <br>and the world will live as one]]></content><category term="Pentatonix" label="Pentatonix"/><category term="Imagine" label="Imagine"/></entry></feed>