<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:06+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Down_In_It_Live/</id><title>Nine Inch Nails - Down In It (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:04:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Down_In_It_Live/" title="Nine Inch Nails - Down In It (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wimp. Wimp. <br><br>Kinda like a cloud I was up way up in the sky. <br>And I was feeling some feelings you wouldn't believe. <br>Sometimes I don't believe them myself and I decided I was never coming down. <br><br>Just then a tiny little dot caught my eye. <br>It was just about too small to see. <br>But I watched it way too long. <br>It was pulling down. <br><br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>Now I'm down in it <br><br>Shut up. <br>So what what does it matter now. <br>I was swimming in the hate now I crawl on the ground. <br>And everything I never liked about you is kind of seeping into me. <br>I try to laugh about it now but isn't it funny how everything works out. <br>I guess the jokes on me, she said. <br><br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>Now I'm down in it <br><br>I used to be so big and strong. <br>I used to know my right from wrong. <br>I used to never be afraid. <br>I used to be somebody. <br><br>I used to have something inside. <br>Now just this hole it's open wide. <br>I used to want it all. <br>I used to be somebody. <br><br>I'll cross my heart and hope to die. <br>But the needle's already in my eye. <br>And all the world's weight is on my back and I don't even know why. <br>And what I used to think was me is just a fading memory. <br>I looked him right in the eye and said "goodbye." <br><br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>Now I'm down in it <br><br>Rain rain go away. <br>Rain rain go away. <br>Rain rain go away. <br>Come again some other day. <br><br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>I was up above it. <br>Now I'm down in it <br><br>Na na na na na na na na.]]></content><category term="Nine Inch Nails" label="Nine Inch Nails"/><category term="Down In It (Live)" label="Down In It (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/The_Only_Time_Live/</id><title>Nine Inch Nails - The Only Time (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:04:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/The_Only_Time_Live/" title="Nine Inch Nails - The Only Time (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm drunk. <br>And right now I'm so in love with you. <br>And I don't want to think too much about what we should or shouldn't do. <br>Lay my hands on Heaven and the sun and the moon and the stars. <br>While the devil wants to fuck me in the back of his car. <br><br>Nothing quite like the feel of something new. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up in you. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up in you. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>This is the only time I really feel alive. <br>This is the only time I really feel alive. <br><br>I swear. <br>I just found everything I need. <br>The sweat in your eyes the blood in your veins are listening to me. <br>Well I want to wrap it up and swim in it until I drown. <br>My moral standing is lying down. <br><br>Nothing quite like the feel of something new. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up in you. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up in you. <br>Maybe I'm all messed up. <br>This is the only time I really feel alive. <br>This is the only time I really feel alive]]></content><category term="Nine Inch Nails" label="Nine Inch Nails"/><category term="The Only Time (Live)" label="The Only Time (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Burn_Live/</id><title>Nine Inch Nails - Burn (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:04:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Burn_Live/" title="Nine Inch Nails - Burn (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This world rejects me <br>This world threw me away <br>This world never gave me a chance <br>This world's gonna have to pay <br><br>I don't believe in your institutions <br>I did what you wanted me to <br>Like cancer in the system <br>I've got a little suprise for you <br><br>Something inside of me has opened up its eyes <br>Why did you put it there did you not realize <br>This thing inside of me it screams the loudest sound <br>Sometimes i think i could <br><br>Burn <br><br>I look down there where you're standing <br>Flock of sheep out on display <br>Saw your lives burned up around you <br>I can take it all away <br><br>Something inside of me has opened up its eyes <br>Why did you put it there did you not realize <br>This thing inside of me it screams the loudest sound <br>Sometimes i think i could <br><br>I'm gonna burn this whole world down <br><br>I never was a part of you burn <br><br>I am the agent i never was a part of you burn <br>I am corruption i never was a part of you burn <br>I am the angel i never was a part of you burn <br>Of your destruction i never was a part of you burn <br><br>I am subversion i never was a part of you burn <br>Secret desire i never was a part of you burn <br>I am your future i never was a part of you burn <br>Swallow down all that fire]]></content><category term="Nine Inch Nails" label="Nine Inch Nails"/><category term="Burn (Live)" label="Burn (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Reptile_Live/</id><title>Nine Inch Nails - Reptile (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:04:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Reptile_Live/" title="Nine Inch Nails - Reptile (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[she spread herself wide open to let the insects in <br>she leaves a trail of honey to show me where she's been <br>she has the blood of reptile just underneath her skin <br>seeds from a thousand others drip down from within <br><br>oh my beautiful liar <br>oh my precious whore <br>my disease my infection <br>I am so impure <br><br>get it <br><br>devils speak of the ways in which she'll manifest <br>angels bleed from the tainted touch of my caress <br>need to contaminate to alleviate this loneliness <br>I now know the depths I reach are limitless <br><br>oh my beautiful liar <br>oh my precious whore <br>my disease my infection <br>I am so impure]]></content><category term="Nine Inch Nails" label="Nine Inch Nails"/><category term="Reptile (Live)" label="Reptile (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Something_I_Can_Never_Have_Live/</id><title>Nine Inch Nails - Something I Can Never Have (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:04:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:04:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nine_Inch_Nails/Something_I_Can_Never_Have_Live/" title="Nine Inch Nails - Something I Can Never Have (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I still recall the taste of your tears. <br>Echoing your voice just like the ringing in my ears. <br>My favorite dreams of you still wash ashore. <br>Scraping through my head 'till I don't want to sleep anymore. <br><br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I'm down to just one thing. <br>And I'm starting to scare myself. <br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I just want something. <br>I just want something I can never have <br><br>You always were the one to show me how <br>Back then I couldn't do the things that I can do now. <br>This thing is slowly taking me apart. <br>Grey would be the color if I had a heart. <br><br>Come on tell me <br><br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I'm down to just one thing. <br>And I'm starting to scare myself. <br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I just want something. <br>I just want something I can never have <br><br>In this place it seems like such a shame. <br>Though it all looks different now <br>I know it's still the same <br>Everywhere I look you're all I see. <br>Just a fading fucking reminder of who I used to be. <br><br>Come on tell me <br><br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I'm down to just one thing. <br>And I'm starting to scare myself. <br>You make this all go away. <br>You make this all go away. <br>I just want something. <br>I just want something I can never have <br><br>I just want something I can never have]]></content><category term="Nine Inch Nails" label="Nine Inch Nails"/><category term="Something I Can Never Have (Live)" label="Something I Can Never Have (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Tush_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - Tush (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Tush_Live/" title="ZZ Top - Tush (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I been up, I been down. <br>Take my word, my way around. <br>I ain't askin' for much. <br>I said, Lord, take me downtown <br>I'm just lookin' for some tush. <br><br>I been bad, I been good <br>Dallas, Texas, Hollywood. <br>I ain't askin' for much. <br>I said, Lord, take me downtown <br>I'm just lookin' for some tush. <br><br>Take me back way back home <br>not by myself, not alone. <br>I ain't askin' for much. <br>I said, Lord, take me downtown <br>I'm just lookin' for some tush.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Tush (Live)" label="Tush (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Jailhouse_Rock_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - Jailhouse Rock (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Jailhouse_Rock_Live/" title="ZZ Top - Jailhouse Rock (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Goin' to a party in the county jail <br>Prison band was there and they began to wail. <br>Kid is shakin' and began to sing; <br>You should've heard them knocked out jailbirds sing. <br>Let's rock! Everybody, let's rock! <br>Everybody in the whole cell block <br>Was dancin' to the jailhouse rock. <br><br>Spider Murphy sittin' on a block of stone; <br>Little Joey blowin' on a slide trombone. <br>Come on, Silly Willy, don't you be no square. <br>If you cannot find a partner, use a wooden chair. <br>Let's rock! Everybody, let's rock! <br>Everybody in the whole cell block <br>Was dancin' to the jailhouse rock. <br><br>Shifty Henry said to Bugs,"For heaven's sake <br>No one's lookin'; now's our chance to make a break." <br>Bugsy turned to Shifty and he said, "Nix nix. I <br>Wanna stick around awhile and get my kicks." <br>Let's rock! Everybody, let's rock! <br>Everybody in the whole cell block <br>Was dancin' to the jailhouse rock.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Jailhouse Rock (Live)" label="Jailhouse Rock (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Dust_My_Broom_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - Dust My Broom (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Dust_My_Broom_Live/" title="ZZ Top - Dust My Broom (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm gonna get up in the morning <br>I believe I'll dust my broom. <br>I'm gonna get up in the morning <br>I believe I'll dust my broom. <br>Well my best gal I'll be leaving <br>So my friend, get out my room <br><br>I'm gonna write a letter to China <br>See if my baby's over there. <br>I'm gonna write a letter to China <br>See if my baby's over there. <br>If she ain't up in the Hawaiian Islands <br>Must be in Ethiopia somewhere <br><br>I believe believe my time alone <br>I believe believe my time alone <br>I've had to quit my baby and give up my happy home]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Dust My Broom (Live)" label="Dust My Broom (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Hi_Fi_Mama_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - Hi Fi Mama (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Hi_Fi_Mama_Live/" title="ZZ Top - Hi Fi Mama (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want your hi fi mama, won't you let me play it tonight <br>I want your hi fi mama, won't you let me play it tonight <br>I put the needle in the groove, baby while you douse the lights. <br><br>I play it on your dresser, play it upside your wall <br>I play it in your kitchen, even play it in your hall <br>I play it anywhere you want it, any old time at all. <br><br>Hi fi lo fi no fi's just fine with me. <br>Hi fi lo fi no fi's just fine with me. <br>And if you want to give me stereo first give me vitamin E. <br>I got your name and your number.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Hi Fi Mama (Live)" label="Hi Fi Mama (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/She_Loves_My_Automobile_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - She Loves My Automobile (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/She_Loves_My_Automobile_Live/" title="ZZ Top - She Loves My Automobile (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She don't love me, she love my automobile. <br>She don't love me, she love my automobile. <br>Well she would do anything just to slide behind the wheel. <br><br>She said what's it gonna take for you to lay your top on down? <br>She said what's it gonna take for you to lay your top on down? <br>I said honey why don't you ask me when we get to the outskirts of town. <br><br>Well now she don't care if I'm stoned or sloppy drunk. <br>Well she don't care if I'm stoned or sloppy drunk <br>Long as she got the keys and there's a spare wheel in her trunk.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="She Loves My Automobile (Live)" label="She Loves My Automobile (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Arrested_For_Driving_While_Blind_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - Arrested For Driving While Blind (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Arrested_For_Driving_While_Blind_Live/" title="ZZ Top - Arrested For Driving While Blind (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you're driving down the highway at night <br>And you're feelin' that wild turkey's bite <br>Don't give Johnny Walker a ride <br>Cause Jack Black is right by your side <br>You might get taken to the jailhouse and find <br>You've been arrested for driving while blind <br><br>Now just the other night with nothin' to do <br>We broke a case of proof 102 <br>And started itchin' for that wonderful feel <br>Of rollin' in an automobile <br>You could say we was out of our mind <br>And let me tell you we were flyin' while blind <br><br>Then they had us up against the wall <br>Hey it's only blood grain alcohol <br>And there ain't no cause for alarm <br>We ain't out to do nobody no harm <br>How could anyone be so unkind <br>To arrest a man for drivin' while blind]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Arrested For Driving While Blind (Live)" label="Arrested For Driving While Blind (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Cheap_Sunglasses_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - Cheap Sunglasses (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Cheap_Sunglasses_Live/" title="ZZ Top - Cheap Sunglasses (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you get up in the morning and the light is hurt your head <br>The first thing you do when you get up out of bed <br>Is hit that street a-runnin' and try to meet the masses <br>And go get yourself some cheap sunglasses <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah <br><br>Spied a little thing and I followed her all night <br>In a funky fine levis and her sweater's kind of tight <br>She had a west coast strut that was sweet as molases <br>But what really knocked me out was her cheap sunglasses <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah <br><br>Now go out and get yourself some thick black frames <br>With the glass so dark thay won't even know your name <br>And the choice is up to you cause they come in two classes <br>Rhinestone shades and cheap sunglasses <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Cheap Sunglasses (Live)" label="Cheap Sunglasses (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/A_Fool_For_Your_Stockings_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - A Fool For Your Stockings (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/A_Fool_For_Your_Stockings_Live/" title="ZZ Top - A Fool For Your Stockings (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Is it you again outside <br>Just banging on the front door? <br>You say you had enough <br>Now you're coming' back for more <br>But that's alright. <br>I said that that's alright. <br>I may not want to admit it <br>I'm just a fool for your stockings I believe. <br><br>Now I don't mind when you send money <br>and bring your girlfriends with you <br>But how could one be so thoughtless to try <br>and handle less than two? <br>But that's alright. <br>I said that that's alright, baby. <br>I may not want to admit it <br>I'm just a fool for your stockings I believe. <br><br>Now I'm tellin' everybody <br>It seems too good to be true: <br>Sweet things can always get sweeter. <br>I know mine did, how about you? <br>Yes, it's alright. <br>I said, yes it is, that's alright. <br>I may not want to admit it <br>I'm just a fool for your stockings I believe.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="A Fool For Your Stockings (Live)" label="A Fool For Your Stockings (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Low_Down_In_The_Street_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - Low Down In The Street (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Low_Down_In_The_Street_Live/" title="ZZ Top - Low Down In The Street (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well there comes Lola, out of control-a: <br>She just loves those rhythm and blues. <br>And miss Ivy will be arriving; <br>in leopard skin tights she's willing to cruise. <br><br>It's a fiend scene and it happens 'bout once a week. <br>So fork over some bread, it'll do your head to get low down in the street. <br><br>There's Jimmy and Jojo, there's Kim and Keith <br>Way outside the eyes of cool. <br>And sweet M.B., and there's little G.B. <br>Everybody wants to be their fool. <br><br>It's a fiend scene and it happens here ev'ry week. <br>Fork over some bread, it'll do your head to get low down in the street. <br><br>Some nights are lonely, some nights are lazy <br>but ain't nobody try and slip away. <br>They'll make you loose. They'll make you crazy. <br>Know what I mean, what you say, what you say. <br><br>It's a fiend scene and it happens 'bout once a week. <br>So roam on in, it ain't no sin to get low down in the street.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Low Down In The Street (Live)" label="Low Down In The Street (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Im_Bad_Im_Nationwide_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - I`m Bad I`m Nationwide (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Im_Bad_Im_Nationwide_Live/" title="ZZ Top - I`m Bad I`m Nationwide (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well I was rollin' down the road in some cold blue steel <br>I had a bluesman in the back, and a beautician at the wheel. <br>We're going downtown in the middle of the night <br>We was laughing and I'm jokin' and we feelin' alright. <br>Oh I'm bad, I'm nationwide. <br>Yes I'm bad, I'm nationwide. <br><br>Easin' down the highway in a new Cadillac <br>I had a fine fox in front, I had three more in the back. <br>They sportin' short dresses, wearin' spike-heeled shoes <br>They smokin' Lucky Strikes, wearing nylon too. <br>Welcome back, we're nationwide. <br>Yeah we bad, we're nationwide. <br><br>Well I was movin' down the road in my V-8 Ford <br>I had a shine on my boots, I had my sideburns lowered. <br>With my New York brim and my gold tooth displayed <br>Nobody give me trouble cause they know I got it made. <br>I'm bad, I'm nationwide. <br>Girl I'm bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, I'm nationwide.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="I`m Bad I`m Nationwide (Live)" label="I`m Bad I`m Nationwide (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Jesus_Just_Left_Chicago_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - Jesus Just Left Chicago (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Jesus_Just_Left_Chicago_Live/" title="ZZ Top - Jesus Just Left Chicago (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jesus just left Chicago and he's bound for New Orleans. <br>Well now, Jesus just left Chicago and he's bound for New Orleans. <br>Yeah, yeah. <br>Workin' from one end to the other and all points in between. <br><br>Took a jump through Mississippi, well, muddy water turned to wine. <br>Took a jump through Mississippi, muddy water turned to wine. <br>Yeah, yeah. <br>Then out to California through the forests and the pines. <br>Ah, take me with you, Jesus. <br><br>You might not see him in person but he'll see you just the same. <br>You might not see him in person but he'll see you just the same. <br>Yeah, yeah. <br>You don't have to worry 'cause takin' care of business is his name.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Jesus Just Left Chicago (Live)" label="Jesus Just Left Chicago (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Waitin_For_The_Bus_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - Waitin` For The Bus (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/Waitin_For_The_Bus_Live/" title="ZZ Top - Waitin` For The Bus (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Have mercy, been waitin' for the bus all day. <br>Have mercy, been waitin' for the bus all day. <br>I got my brown paper bag and my take-home pay. <br><br>Have mercy, old bus be packed up tight. <br>Have mercy, old bus be packed up tight. <br>Well, I'm glad just to get on and home tonight. <br><br>Right on, that bus done got me back. <br>Right on, that bus done got me back. <br>Well, I'll be ridin' on the bus till I Cadillac.]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="Waitin` For The Bus (Live)" label="Waitin` For The Bus (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/I_Thank_You_Live/</id><title>ZZ Top - I Thank You (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:05:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:05:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ZZ_Top/I_Thank_You_Live/" title="ZZ Top - I Thank You (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You didn't have to love me like you did <br>But you did, but you did. <br>And I thank you. <br>You didn't have to love me like you did <br>But you did, but you did. <br>And I thank you. <br>But you took your love to someone else <br>I wouldn't know what it meant to be loved to death <br><br>You made me feel like I've never felt <br>Kisses so good I had to holler for help <br>You didn't have to squeeze it but you did <br>But you did but you did <br>And I thank you. <br>You didn't have to hold it but you did <br>But you did but you did <br>And I thank you. <br><br>Every day was something new <br>You put on your bag and your fine to-do <br>You got me trying new things too <br>Just so I can keep up with you. <br><br>You didn't have to shake it but you did <br>But you did but you did <br>And I thank you. <br>You didn't have to make it like you did <br>but you did but you did <br>And I thank you. <br><br>All my life I've been shortchanged <br>Without your love baby it's a crying shame <br>But now I know what the fellas talking about <br>Hear me say that they been turned out <br>I want to thank you <br>I want to thank you <br>I want to thank you <br>Yes, I want to thank you]]></content><category term="ZZ Top" label="ZZ Top"/><category term="I Thank You (Live)" label="I Thank You (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Hey_Hey_My_My_Out_Of_The_Black_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Hey Hey, My My (Out Of The Black) (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Hey_Hey_My_My_Out_Of_The_Black_Live/" title="Neil Young - Hey Hey, My My (Out Of The Black) (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey hey, my my <br>Rock and roll can never die <br>There's more to the picture <br>Than meets the eye. <br>Hey hey, my my. <br><br>Out of the blue <br>and into the black <br>You pay for this <br>but they give you that <br>And once you're gone <br>you can't come back <br>When you're out of the blue <br>and into the black. <br><br>The king is gone <br>but he's not forgotten <br>Is this the story <br>of Johnny Rotten? <br>It's better to burn out <br>'cause rust never sleeps <br>The king is gone <br>but he's not forgotten. <br><br>Hey hey, my my <br>Rock and roll can never die <br>There's more to the picture <br>Than meets the eye.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Hey Hey, My My (Out Of The Black) (Live)" label="Hey Hey, My My (Out Of The Black) (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Like_A_Hurricane_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Like A Hurricane (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Like_A_Hurricane_Live/" title="Neil Young - Like A Hurricane (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Once I thought I saw you <br>in a crowded hazy bar <br>Dancing on the light <br>from star to star. <br>Far across the moonbeam <br>I know that's who you are <br>I saw your brown eyes <br>turning once to fire. <br><br>You are like a hurricane <br>There's calm in your eye. <br>And I'm gettin' blown away <br>To somewhere safer <br>where the feeling stays. <br>I want to love you but <br>I'm getting blown away. <br><br>I am just a dreamer <br>but you are just a dream <br>You could have been <br>anyone to me. <br>Before that moment <br>you touched my lips <br>That perfect feeling <br>when time just slips <br>Away between us <br>on our foggy trip. <br><br>You are like a hurricane <br>There's calm in your eye. <br>And I'm gettin' blown away <br>To somewhere safer <br>where the feeling stays. <br>I want to love you but <br>I'm getting blown away. <br><br>You are just a dreamer <br>and I am just a dream. <br>You could have been <br>anyone to me. <br>Before that moment <br>you touched my lips <br>That perfect feeling <br>when time just slips <br>Away between us <br>on our foggy trip. <br><br>You are like a hurricane <br>There's calm in your eye. <br>And I'm gettin' blown away <br>To somewhere safer <br>where the feeling stays. <br>I want to love you but <br>I'm getting blown away.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Like A Hurricane (Live)" label="Like A Hurricane (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Violent_Side_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Violent Side (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Violent_Side_Live/" title="Neil Young - Violent Side (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here comes the night <br>Here comes the anger <br>Hidden so deep inside <br>No one can see <br>Behind these eyes <br>There walks a stranger <br>Wandering through the dark <br>Following me. <br><br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side. <br><br>Electric light <br>Shining on your block <br>Sayin' to everyone <br>The power is on <br>While your alarm <br>Set up for safety <br>Keeps out invaders who come <br>But still can't control. <br><br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side <br>Control the violent side. <br><br>Got to fight to control <br>the violent side <br>Every day and night <br>I've got to fight <br>to control it.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Violent Side (Live)" label="Violent Side (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Computer_Age_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Computer Age (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Computer_Age_Live/" title="Neil Young - Computer Age (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cars and trucks <br>Fly by me on the corner <br>But I'm all right <br>Standin' proud <br>before the signal <br>When I see the light <br>I know I'm more <br>than just a number. <br>And I stand before you <br>Or else we <br>just don't see the other <br>Computer age computer age <br>Computer age. <br><br>Bikes and vans <br>Fly by me on the desert <br>But I'm all right <br>Standing out here <br>in the hot sun <br>When I see the light <br>I feel like <br>more than just a number <br>And I stand before you <br>Or else we <br>just don't see the other <br>Computer age computer age <br>Computer age. <br><br>Precious metal lines <br>Molded into highways <br>Running through me <br>So microscopically <br>Days and nights <br>Weeks and months and seasons <br>Rolling through me <br>So chronologically. <br>Computer age computer age <br>Computer age. <br><br>I need you <br>To let me know <br>that there's a heartbeat <br>Let it pound and pound <br>And I'll be <br>flying like a free bird <br>And you need me <br>Like ugly needs a mirror <br>And day by day <br>This horizon's getting clearer <br>Computer age computer age <br>Computer age.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Computer Age (Live)" label="Computer Age (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Sample__Hold_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Sample &amp; Hold (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Sample__Hold_Live/" title="Neil Young - Sample &amp; Hold (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sample and Hold <br>Hair: Blonde <br>Eyes: Blue <br>Weight: 110 <br>Disposition: Even <br>Mood Code: Rotary Adjustable <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold <br>But not the angry one <br>A new design, new design. <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold <br>But not the lonely one <br>A new design, new design. <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold <br>But not the lonely one <br>A new design, new design. <br><br>Sample and hold. <br><br>We'll send it out right away <br>Satisfaction guaranteed. <br>Please specify <br>The color of skin and eye <br>We know you'll be happy. <br><br>Don't hesitate to give us a call <br>We know you'll be satisfied <br>When you energize <br>And see your unit come alive <br>We know you'll be happy. <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold <br>But not the lonely one <br>the lonely one <br>the lonely one <br>Sample and hold. <br>Weight: 110. <br><br>Perfection in every details <br>Fabricated from <br>the curl of the hair <br>To the tip of the nail <br>Because our units never fail <br>We know you'll be happy. <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold. <br><br>Don't hesitate to give us a call <br>We know you'll be satisfied <br>When you energize <br>And see your unit come alive <br>We know you'll be happy. <br><br>I need a unit to sample and hold. <br><br>We know you'll be happy 110 <br>We know you'll be happy <br>We know you'll be happy. <br><br>But not the lonely one <br>A new design, new design <br>Perfection in every detail <br>new design <br>Sample and hold.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Sample &amp; Hold (Live)" label="Sample &amp; Hold (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/After_The_Goldrush_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - After The Goldrush (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/After_The_Goldrush_Live/" title="Neil Young - After The Goldrush (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I dreamed I saw the knights <br>In armor coming <br>Saying something about a queen. <br>There were peasants singing and <br>Drummers drumming <br>And the archer split the tree. <br>There was a fanfare blowing <br>To the sun <br>That was floating on the breeze. <br>Look at Mother Nature on the run <br>In the nineteen seventies. <br>Look at Mother Nature on the run <br>In the nineteen seventies. <br><br>I was lying in a burned out basement <br>With the full moon in my eyes. <br>I was hoping for replacement <br>When the sun burst thru the sky. <br>There was a band playing in my head <br>And I felt like getting high. <br>I was thinking about what a <br>Friend had said <br>I was hoping it was a lie. <br>Thinking about what a <br>Friend had said <br>I was hoping it was a lie. <br><br>Well, I dreamed I saw the silver <br>Space ships flying <br>In the yellow haze of the sun <br>There were children crying <br>And colors flying <br>All around the chosen ones. <br>All in a dream, all in a dream <br>The loading had begun. <br>They were flying Mother Nature's <br>Silver seed to a new home in the sun. <br>Flying Mother Nature's <br>Silver seed to a new home.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="After The Goldrush (Live)" label="After The Goldrush (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/The_Needle__The_Damage_Done_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - The Needle &amp; The Damage Done (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/The_Needle__The_Damage_Done_Live/" title="Neil Young - The Needle &amp; The Damage Done (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I caught you knockin' <br>at my cellar door <br>I love you, baby <br>can I have some more <br>Ooh, ooh, the damage done. <br><br>I hit the city and <br>I lost my band <br>I watched the needle <br>take another man <br>Gone, gone, the damage done. <br><br>I sing the song <br>because I love the man <br>I know that some <br>of you don't understand <br>Milk-blood <br>to keep from running out. <br><br>I've seen the needle <br>and the damage done <br>A little part of it in everyone <br>But every junkie's <br>like a settin' sun.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="The Needle &amp; The Damage Done (Live)" label="The Needle &amp; The Damage Done (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Sugar_Mountain_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Sugar Mountain (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Sugar_Mountain_Live/" title="Neil Young - Sugar Mountain (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>With the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon. <br><br>It's so noisy at the fair <br>But all your friends are there <br>And the candy floss you had <br>And your mother and your dad. <br><br>Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>With the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon. <br><br>There's a girl just down the aisle <br>Oh, to turn and see her smile. <br>You can hear the words she wrote <br>As you read the hidden note. <br><br>Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>With the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon. <br><br>Now you're underneath the stairs <br>And you're givin' back some glares <br>To the people who you met <br>And it's your first cigarette. <br><br>Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>With the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon. <br><br>Now you say you're leavin' home <br>'Cause you want to be alone. <br>Ain't it funny how you feel <br>When you're findin' out it's real? <br><br>Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>With the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon. <br><br>Oh, to live on Sugar Mountain <br>with the barkers and the colored balloons <br>You can't be twenty on Sugar Mountain <br>Though you're thinking that <br>you're leaving there too soon <br>You're leaving there too soon.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Sugar Mountain (Live)" label="Sugar Mountain (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Heart_Of_Gold_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Heart Of Gold (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Heart_Of_Gold_Live/" title="Neil Young - Heart Of Gold (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want to live <br>I want to give <br>I've been a miner for a heart of gold. <br>It's these expressions <br>I never give <br>That keep me searching for a heart of gold. <br><br>And I'm getting old. <br>Keep me searching for a heart of gold <br>And I'm getting old. <br><br>I've been to Hollywood <br>I've been to Redwood <br>I crossed the ocean for a heart of gold. <br>I've been in my mind <br>It's such a fine line <br>That keeps me searching for a heart of gold. <br><br>And I'm getting old. <br>Keeps me searching for a heart of gold <br>And I'm getting old. <br><br>Keep me searching for a heart of gold. <br>You keep me searching and I'm growing old. <br>Keep me searching for a heart of gold <br>I've been a miner for a heart of gold.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Heart Of Gold (Live)" label="Heart Of Gold (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Opera_Star_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Opera Star (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Opera_Star_Live/" title="Neil Young - Opera Star (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So your girlfriend <br>slammed the door shut <br>In your face tonight <br>but that's all right <br>Then she took off <br>to the opera <br>With some highbrow <br>from the city lights <br>Well, you grew up on a corner <br>You never missed a moonlit night. <br><br>Some things never change <br>they stay the way they are. <br>You were born to rock <br>you'll never be an opera star <br>Some things never change <br>they stay the way they are. <br><br>So you stay out all night <br>Gettin' fucked up <br>in that rock and roll bar <br>And you never get tired <br>'Cause your drugs <br>are in a little jar. <br><br>You were born to rock <br>you'll never be an opera star. <br>Some things never change <br>they stay the way they are. <br><br>I was born to rock! <br><br>So your girlfriend <br>slammed the door shut <br>In your face tonight <br>but that's all right <br>Then she took off <br>to the opera <br>With some highbrow <br>from the city lights <br>Well, you grew up on a corner <br>You never missed a moonlit night. <br><br>Some things never change <br>they stay the way they are. <br>You were born to rock <br>you'll never be an opera star.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Opera Star (Live)" label="Opera Star (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Drive_Back_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Drive Back (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Drive_Back_Live/" title="Neil Young - Drive Back (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whatever gets you <br>through the night <br>That's all right with me <br>When it's time to say goodbye <br>I have to make you see <br><br>You won't know me <br>I won't call you <br>I won't be there <br>To remind you <br>What you told me <br>When I showed you <br>In the morning <br>Let me know you'll <br><br>Drive back to your old town <br>I wanna wake up <br>with no-one around <br>Drive back to your old town. <br><br>If somebody <br>Is haunting your mind <br>Look in my eyes <br>Let me hide you <br>From yourself and <br>All your old friends <br>Every good thing <br>Comes to an end. <br><br>Drive back <br>drive back <br>drive back. <br><br>Drive back to your old town <br>I wanna wake up with no-one around <br>Drive back to your old town.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Drive Back (Live)" label="Drive Back (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Down_By_The_River_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Down By The River (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Down_By_The_River_Live/" title="Neil Young - Down By The River (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Be on my side <br>I'll be on your side <br>baby <br>There is no reason <br>for you to hide <br>It's so hard for me <br>staying here all alone <br>When you could be <br>taking me for a ride. <br><br>Yeah, she could drag me <br>over the rainbow <br>send me away <br>Down by the river <br>I shot my baby <br>Down by the river <br>Dead, oh, shot her dead. <br><br>You take my hand <br>I'll take your hand <br>Together we may get away <br>This much madness <br>is too much sorrow <br>It's impossible <br>to make it today. <br><br>Yeah, she could drag me <br>over the rainbow <br>send me away <br>Down by the river <br>I shot my baby <br>Down by the river <br>Dead, oh, shot her dead. <br><br>Be on my side <br>I'll be on your side <br>baby <br>There is no reason <br>for you to hide <br>It's so hard for me <br>staying here all alone <br>When you could be <br>taking me for a ride. <br><br>Yeah, she could drag me <br>over the rainbow <br>send me away <br>Down by the river <br>I shot my baby <br>Down by the river <br>Dead, oh, shot her dead.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Down By The River (Live)" label="Down By The River (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/When_You_Dance_I_Can_Really_Love_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - When You Dance I Can Really Love (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/When_You_Dance_I_Can_Really_Love_Live/" title="Neil Young - When You Dance I Can Really Love (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you dance <br>Do your senses tingle? <br>Then take a chance? <br>In a trance <br>While the lonely mingle <br>With circumstance? <br><br>I've got <br>something to tell you <br>you make it show. <br>Let me come over <br>I know you know <br>When you dance <br>I can really love. <br><br>I can love <br>I can really love <br>I can really love <br>I can love <br>I can really love <br>I can really love <br><br>Like a <br>mountain that's growing <br>a river that rolls <br>Let me come over <br>I know you know <br>When you dance <br>I can really love. <br><br>When you dance <br>Do your senses tingle? <br>Then take a chance? <br>In a trance <br>While the lonely mingle <br>With circumstance? <br><br>I've got <br>something to tell you <br>you make it show. <br>Let me come over <br>I know you know <br>When you dance <br>I can really love.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="When You Dance I Can Really Love (Live)" label="When You Dance I Can Really Love (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Cinnamon_Girl_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Cinnamon Girl (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Cinnamon_Girl_Live/" title="Neil Young - Cinnamon Girl (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanna live <br>with a cinnamon girl <br>I could be happy <br>the rest of my life <br>With a cinnamon girl. <br><br>A dreamer of pictures <br>I run in the night <br>You see us together <br>chasing the moonlight <br>My cinnamon girl. <br><br>Ten silver saxes <br>a bass with a bow <br>The drummer relaxes <br>and waits between shows <br>For his cinnamon girl. <br><br>A dreamer of pictures <br>I run in the night <br>You see us together <br>chasing the moonlight <br>My cinnamon girl. <br><br>Pa sent me money now <br>I'm gonna make it somehow <br>I need another chance <br>You see your baby loves to dance <br>Yeah... yeah... yeah.]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Cinnamon Girl (Live)" label="Cinnamon Girl (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Mr_Soul_Live/</id><title>Neil Young - Mr. Soul (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:13:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:13:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Young/Mr_Soul_Live/" title="Neil Young - Mr. Soul (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, hello Mr. Soul <br>I dropped by <br>to pick up a reason <br>For the thought that I caught <br>that my head <br>is the event of the season <br>Why in crowds just a trace <br>of my face <br>could seem so pleasin' <br>I'll cop out to the change <br>but a stranger <br>is putting the tease on. <br><br>I was down on a frown <br>when the messenger <br>brought me a letter <br>I was raised by the praise <br>of a fan <br>who said I upset her <br>Any girl in the world <br>could have easily <br>known me better <br>She said, You're strange <br>but don't change <br>and I let her. <br><br>In a while will the smile <br>on my face <br>turn to plaster? <br>Stick around while the clown <br>who is sick <br>does the trick of disaster <br>For the race of my head <br>and my face <br>is moving much faster <br>Is it strange I should change? <br>I don't know <br>why don't you ask her?]]></content><category term="Neil Young" label="Neil Young"/><category term="Mr. Soul (Live)" label="Mr. Soul (Live)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//_/</id><title> -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:21:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:21:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%9A%B0/%EB%82%B4%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C_%EB%B3%84%EA%B3%BC%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%B4/" title=" -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>  <br> <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>  <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>   <br> <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:21:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:21:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%9A%B0/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>  <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//_/</id><title> -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:21:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:21:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%9A%B0/%EC%B2%AD%EC%B6%98_%EA%B7%B8%EC%8B%9C%EC%A0%88/" title=" -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>  <br>  <br>     <br>     <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>  <br>  <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:21:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:21:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%EC%9A%B0/%EB%AC%BC%EB%A0%88%EB%B0%A9%EC%95%84/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lemonan_Studio/Ice_Cream/</id><title>Lemonan Studio - Ice Cream - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:21:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:21:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lemonan_Studio/Ice_Cream/" title="Lemonan Studio - Ice Cream - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>   oh <br>i know there is something <br>sweet in your mind <br>     <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>  <br>boy you are my ice cream <br>you are my ice cream <br>    <br>   <br> your eyes <br> whipped cream   <br>ice cream you are my ice cream <br>     <br>    <br>   ice cream <br>    <br>     <br>    <br> <br>boy you are my ice cream <br>you are my ice cream <br>    <br>   <br> your eyes <br> whipped cream  <br>ice cream you are my ice cream <br>     <br>    <br>   ice cream <br>bittersweet and strange <br>      <br>do you know how i feel <br>Ice cream you are my ice cream <br>    <br>   <br> your eyes <br> whipped cream  <br>ice cream you are my ice cream <br>     <br>    <br>   ice cream <br>]]></content><category term="Lemonan Studio" label="Lemonan Studio"/><category term="Ice Cream" label="Ice Cream"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:22:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:22:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%EC%A0%95%EC%9D%80/%EA%B5%AD%ED%99%94/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[  <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>  <br>     <br>  <br>      <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:22:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:22:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%EC%A0%95%EC%9D%80/%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1%ED%95%B4%EB%B4%90%EC%9A%94/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:22:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:22:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%EC%A0%95%EC%9D%80/%ED%95%9C%EB%B2%88%EC%AF%A4/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>   <br>   <br> <br>      <br>   <br>   <br> <br>      <br>    <br> <br>     <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>   <br> <br>      <br>   <br>   <br> <br>      <br>    <br> <br>     <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>  <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Call_Me/</id><title>NAV - Call Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Call_Me/" title="NAV - Call Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro] <br>Metro Boomin want some more, nigga <br><br>[Verse 1] <br>They tell me, "Don't forget where you came from" <br>I regret what I came from <br>In my old hood moving like I got a vest on me <br>I'ma keep on winning, you should place your bets on me <br>I could open up a bakery, baguettes on me <br>Walking through the mall, I got a check on me <br>Designer look the best on me <br>I got lots of pressure, lotsa stress on me <br>Independent, I got people that depend on me <br>Knew you was a fake, you can't pretend on me <br>What I used to spend on you, I spend on me <br>Somehow all these problems keep on landing on me <br>I went on a mission with a bad bitch <br>3AM, I'm getting Backwoods like I'm average <br>All this money turned me to a savage <br>My life was better when I didn't have shit <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Do you know how it feel to feel alone? <br>Bought myself a house, still feel like I ain't home <br>Driving by myself, ain't got nowhere to go <br>I just took two 30s, now I'm in my zone <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br><br>[Verse 2] <br>Me and Metro Boomin' want some more, yah <br>All this money made me bored, yah <br>But there's lots of drugs to explore, yah <br>I'm a boss, yeah, I could employ ya <br>Couldn't buy one, now I got four, yah <br>Used to pray feds don't kick down the door, yah <br>Running back the sack the trap feel like a sport, yah <br>Yeah I'm famous but I miss my life before, yah <br>Finally got some money, can't go to the store <br>I lose every girl I love when I'm on tour <br>My mama calling me and I ignore <br>Running from my problems 'til my feet get sore <br><br>[Chorus] <br>Do you know how it feel to feel alone? <br>Bought myself a house, still feel like I ain't home <br>Driving by myself, ain't got nowhere to go <br>I just took two 30s, now I'm in my zone <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br>Are you really here for me? I don't know <br><br>[Verse 3] <br>I got what you need, you feeling lonely? <br>I need, I need you to hold me <br>I hope you mean everything that you told me <br>I'll try to come back to you, girl, I'm sorry <br>If you miss me just call me <br>You try to diss me 'cause you salty <br>Did this on my own, it's all me <br>I just wish that you would call me <br><br>[Outro] <br>Call me <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>Wish that you would call me <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>Wish that you would call me <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>Wish that you would call me <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>Me up <br>Just wish that you would call me up <br>Me up, me up <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>(Me up, me up) <br>I just wish that you would call me up <br>Me up]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="Call Me" label="Call Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Both_Sides_Feat_21_Savage/</id><title>NAV - Both Sides (Feat. 21 Savage) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Both_Sides_Feat_21_Savage/" title="NAV - Both Sides (Feat. 21 Savage) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro: Future] <br>If Young Metro don't trust ya, I'm gon shoot ya <br><br>[Chorus: 21 Savage] <br>Get my Maybach washed at the studio <br>I'm passing out xans to the groupie hoes <br>I got five on a Lamb' like Coolio <br>Multi-millionaire, now I'm hanging with the shooters tho <br>Yeah, bust downs, got a few of those <br>Yeah, bitch stop calling my phone, I'm in the studio <br>Yeah, nigga we ain't doing no Twitter, lil nigga get supersoaked <br>Nigga we ain't playing both sides, lil nigga who you rooting for? <br><br>[Verse 1: NAV] <br>My life is a secret, everything confidential <br>Rollie presidential, working on my mental <br>Ready for the pressure (yeah) 38 special (yeah) <br>Aim it at your temple (yeah), shooters behind me driving in a rental <br>Told his mama, "Sorry for your loss, did you get the flowers that I sent you?" <br>Used to sell my beats for two bills, now you can't even get a sample <br>Mama found the work in a closet <br>I was making shoe box deposits <br>Ain't looking back, change the topic <br>Park a Bentley coupe in the projects <br>Told my ex bitch I'm doing great, yah <br>So much ice, I need some skates, yah <br>Playing two sides, my shooter put three in his face, yah <br>I just spent eleven on my waist, yah <br>I dress like a star, my closet running out of space, yah <br><br>[Chorus: 21 Savage] <br>Get my Maybach washed at the studio <br>I'm passing out xans to the groupie hoes <br>I got five on a Lamb' like Coolio <br>Multi-millionaire, now I'm hanging with the shooters tho <br>Yeah, bust downs, got a few of those <br>Yeah, bitch stop calling my phone, I'm in the studio <br>Yeah, nigga we ain't doing no Twitter, lil nigga get supersoaked <br>Nigga we ain't playing both sides, lil nigga who you rooting for? <br><br>[Verse 2: 21 Savage] <br>Woah, Gucci jacket, inside pocket hold the ratchet <br>OG kush I'm smoking on a potent package <br>Saint Laurent don on me <br>And I got a gun on me <br>Can't no infiltrators come around me <br>Told my son don't suck his thumb around me <br>Issa lotta bloodhounds around me <br>You could get gunned down around me <br>Yeah, all my friends bad guys <br>Search him at the door, he might be wearing a wire <br>In a foreign, drinking syrup, that's a DUI <br>Police ass nigga, you the FBI <br><br>[Chorus: 21 Savage] <br>Get my Maybach washed at the studio <br>I'm passing out xans to the groupie hoes <br>I got five on a Lamb' like Coolio <br>Multi-millionaire, now I'm hanging with the shooters tho <br>Yeah, bust downs, got a few of those <br>Yeah, bitch stop calling my phone, I'm in the studio <br>Yeah, nigga we ain't doing no Twitter, lil nigga get supersoaked <br>Nigga we ain't playing both sides, lil nigga who you rooting for? <br><br>[Outro: 21 Savage] <br>I'm sleeping where the killers at <br>I'm hanging on a fed block <br>Yeah, Glock 40 with a red dot <br>Ten racks for a hard shot]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="Both Sides (Feat. 21 Savage)" label="Both Sides (Feat. 21 Savage)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Held_Me_Down/</id><title>NAV - Held Me Down - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Held_Me_Down/" title="NAV - Held Me Down - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Metro Boomin want some more, nigga <br><br>I've been running from my problems <br>I've been running from you <br>Girl, all this money, all these things don't feel the same without you <br>I can't trust these others girls, I got a feeling 'bout you <br>Even though I'm doing well, I lose my touch without you <br>I hate to hurt you, cameras showing everything that I do <br>Piece of shit, I got a side bitch and I lie to her too <br>My mama asking 'bout you, and I'm finna lie to her too <br>I blew up and got lost in the sauce, and changed up on you <br><br>But when nobody else was around <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>Way before I found my sound <br>She kept my feet on the ground <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br><br>I've been living life on the road <br>Feeling lonely, heart is turning cold <br>I be covered up in sold out clothes <br>Feeling empty, doing sold out shows <br>Use the drugs to cover up my emotions (abusing drugs) <br>Every time you see me, I'm either rolling or smoking (I'm rollin' up) <br>Everybody love me now, only you make me feel important <br>When we settle down, everything you buy gon' be imported <br>All of your friends, they told you, "Don't fuck with a artist" <br>When I tell you what my body count is, that gon hit you the hardest <br><br>I've been running from my problems <br>I've been running from you <br>Girl, all this money, all these things don't feel the same without you <br>I can't trust these others girls, I got a feeling 'bout you <br>Even though I'm doing well, I lose my touch without you <br>I hate to hurt you, cameras showing everything that I do <br>Piece of shit, I got a side bitch and I lie to her too <br>My mama asking 'bout you, and I'm finna lie to her too <br>I blew up and got lost in a sauce, and changed up on you <br><br>But when nobody else was around <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>Way before I found my sound <br>She kept my feet on the ground <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br><br>Whenever they took my music for a joke <br>Whenever I ever had my back against the ropes <br>When I was down nand out with no hope <br>She was always down from the get-go <br>She was always down, stayed ten toes <br>Lost my girl, found a thousand hoes <br>She a good girl, don't work on a pole <br>If I need it, she would stash my pole <br>She paid for all the dinners when I was broke <br>If I needed, she would hide my dope <br>Girl, I know you still wearing my clothes <br>I know you think about me when you're alone <br>I know you think about texting my phone <br>I wish you would give in and just let go <br>I'm happy I found out you was at my show <br>You're more than my girl <br>You're part of my soul <br><br>I've been running from my problems <br>I've been running from you <br>Girl, all this money, all these things don't feel the same without you <br>I can't trust these others girls, I got a feeling 'bout you <br>Even though I'm doing well, I lose my touch without you <br>I hate to hurt you, cameras showing everything that I do <br>Piece of shit, I got a side bitch and I lie to her too <br>My mama asking 'bout you, and I'm finna lie to her too <br><br>I blew up and got lost in a sauce, and changed up on you <br><br>But when nobody else was around <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down <br>Way before I found my sound <br>She kept my feet on the ground <br>She always held me down <br>She always held me down]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="Held Me Down" label="Held Me Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/AAP_Ferg_Feat_Lil_Uzi_Vert/</id><title>NAV - A$AP Ferg (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/AAP_Ferg_Feat_Lil_Uzi_Vert/" title="NAV - A$AP Ferg (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If Young Metro don't trust you, I'm gon' shoot you <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br><br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>I came from the dirt, know I put in work <br>Like I'm A$AP Ferg, like I'm A$AP Ferg <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in work <br>Diamonds different colors, so my neck look like Starburst <br>Kicked it one time, with your girlfriend <br>And she fucked me for a purse <br>I could hit that thing forever, when I'm on the perc <br><br>I used to put in work <br>Now my young boys do the dirt (brown boy) <br>Fully automatic, pull up hit you with a burst <br>Put you on a shirt, you a lil' boy, you a smurf <br>She used to put me down, and now she lifting up her skirt <br>Pull up and I swerve, leave her feelings hurt <br>She fucked me for a purse, she fucked me for a XO shirt <br>I see you wearing Off-White, but you know, I bought it first <br>I seen you post a picture, and I had to change my shirt <br>I can't punch him in his face, he gonna sue me now <br>Took your bitch to Nobu, fuck me for some sushi now <br>I hit it once, and now I can't stand her now <br>They pay me fifty thousand, just to stand around <br><br>Yeah, what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>I came from the dirt, know I put in work <br>Like I'm A$AP Ferg, like I'm A$AP Ferg <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in work <br>Diamonds different colors, so my neck look like Starburst <br>Kicked it one time, with your girlfriend <br>And she fucked me for a purse <br>I could hit that thing forever, when I'm on the perc <br><br>Heard you got that AP swerve, that was my watch first <br>Heard you got that Lambo', skrt, that was my drive first <br>Chopper beat that bitch to spurs, clip hang to the curb <br>That girl know, I put in work, like I'm A$AP Ferg <br>Your girlfriend say, I'm handsome <br>Fuck any girl, so random <br>Rock any clothes, I'm random <br>I rock that Demna right on my sandal <br>Don't give me the top then cancel <br>My momma said these niggas can't stand you <br>And I'm laughing right to the bank <br>All my chains on like I'm Shabba Ranks <br><br>Tell me what it's worth <br>Tell me what it's worth <br>I came from the dirt, know I put in work <br>Like I'm A$AP Ferg, like I'm A$AP Ferg <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in work <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in, yeah <br>Know I put in work <br>Diamonds different colors, so my neck look like Starburst <br>Kicked it one time, with your girlfriend <br>And she fucked me for a purse <br>I could hit that thing forever, when I'm on the perc <br><br>I came up from the dirt, yeah <br>I came up from the dirt, yeah <br>Put in work like A$AP Ferg, yeah <br>You're getting on my nerves, yeah <br>No pancakes, I want syrup, yeah <br>Mix some molly with the percs, yeah <br>Diss me take you off this earth, yeah <br>I came up from the dirt, yeah <br>I came up from the dirt, yeah <br>Came up from the dirt, yeah <br>Came up from the dirt, yeah <br>Put in work like A$AP Ferg, yeah <br>I got Vs on all my shirts, yeah <br>No pancakes, I want syrup, yeah <br>Mix some molly with the percs, yeah <br>Diss me take you off this earth, yeah <br>I came up from the dirt, yeah <br>I came up from the dirt, yeah]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="A$AP Ferg (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert)" label="A$AP Ferg (Feat. Lil Uzi Vert)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Hit/</id><title>NAV - Hit - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Hit/" title="NAV - Hit - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Southside <br>If Young Metro don't trust you, I'm gon shoot you <br><br>Smoke a lot, got a permanent cough <br>Popping them pills again <br>Used to think you was my dog, now you are not my friend <br>Turn myself into a boss, I was born to win <br>Still know how to handle a loss <br>Me and Metro going in <br>Everything hit <br>All my songs hits <br>All my chains hit <br>I look like a lick <br>Everything hit <br>Diss me, you get hit <br>Southside got the stick <br>Everything hit <br><br>My shooter gave me a promise, said he won't miss <br>I'm rich, I'm just being honest, look at my wrist <br>You ain't shit, you ain't piss <br>20k ain't shit, spent that on my bitch <br>Roll up I smoke by the zip <br>Got gorillas, a jungle with me <br>Snakes and bees on my feet <br>Bought a Range 'cause I don't want a Jeep <br>Fucking your bitch for a week <br>I fuck your bitch right where you sleep <br>Leaving my nut in your sheets <br>Molly turned me into a beast <br>Working four days, no sleep <br><br>Smoke a lot, got a permanent cough <br>Popping them pills again <br>Used to think you was my dog, now you are not my friend <br>Turn myself into a boss, I was born to win <br>Still know how to handle a loss <br>Me and Metro going in <br>Everything hit <br>All my songs hits <br>All my chains hit <br>I look like a lick <br>Everything hit <br>Diss me, you get hit <br>Southside got the stick <br>Everything hit <br><br>Water on my wrist <br>Codeine when I piss <br>Got pills in my shit <br>Don't think I could quit <br>Taking xannies to sleep <br>Wake up and I sip <br>There's a girl in my bed, and I don't know the bitch <br>I'm sipping juice, I make the yellow Fanta orange <br>I was stuck inside my house and now I'm touring <br>I couldn't do it, had to get it, life got boring <br>And now my clothes, my whip, and all my bitches foreign <br><br>Smoke a lot, got a permanent cough <br>Popping them pills again <br>Used to think you was my dog, now you are not my friend <br>Turn myself into a boss, I was born to win <br>Still know how to handle a loss <br>Me and Metro going in <br>Everything hit <br>All my songs hits <br>All my chains hit <br>I look like a lick <br>Everything hit <br>Diss me, you get hit <br>Southside got the stick <br>Everything hit <br><br>I'm sipping juice, I make the yellow Fanta orange <br>I was stuck inside my house and now I'm touring <br>I couldn't do it, had to get it, life got boring <br>And I might close my whip, and all my bitches foreign]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="Hit" label="Hit"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/I_Dont_Care/</id><title>NAV - I Don`t Care - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/I_Dont_Care/" title="NAV - I Don`t Care - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Metro Boomin' want some more nigga <br><br>Metro Boomin said he got me, yeah <br>All these rappers try to copy, yeah <br>Stick to ice, don't play no hockey, yeah <br>My strap is black and hot like coffee, yeah <br>I'm goin' fast, you can't stop me, yeah <br>Heard your album, break weed on a copy, yeah <br>I used to want her, now she sloppy, yeah <br>Compare 'em to me, they can't top me, yeah <br><br>Yeah, I'ma put the money up for broski's bail, yeah <br>I just spent $200 on my nails, yeah <br>You wasn't there and now I'm outta here, yeah <br>You call my phone, I ignore and I don't care, yeah <br>You say you goin' broke and I don't care <br>Got 10 Gucci shoes, I flex on you and buy another pair <br>When I had no hope you wasn't there <br>So when you ask for help, no I don't care <br><br>You say you can't pay your bills, no I don't care <br>I'ma go and spend your rent on underwear <br>I'm in Saks Fifth, used to shop at Sears <br>I've been poppin' pills and poppin' seals <br>I removed the fakes and shit got real <br>My shooter got tech fleece on <br>He don't train, but he trained to kill <br>Remember when Cash hit me up on the phone, I was broke as hell <br>'Member when I used to wake up, I ain't wanna check the mail <br>I know some bitches whorin' but I won't kiss and tell <br>The same bitches that put Body in a cell <br>All we knew is rob and steal and sell <br>I'm eatin' cajun salmon, used to eat Taco Bell <br><br>Metro Boomin said he got me, yeah <br>All these rappers try to copy, yeah <br>Stick to ice, don't play no hockey, yeah <br>My strap is black and hot like coffee, yeah <br>I'm goin' fast, you can't stop me, yeah <br>Heard your album, break weed on a copy, yeah <br>I used to want her, now she sloppy, yeah <br>Compare 'em to me, they can't top me, yeah <br><br>Yeah, I'ma put the money up for broski's bail, yeah <br>I just spent $200 on my nails, yeah <br>You wasn't there and now I'm outta here, yeah <br>You call my phone, I ignore and I don't care, yeah <br>You say you goin' broke and I don't care <br>Got 10 Gucci shoes, I flex on you and buy another pair <br>When I had no hope you wasn't there <br>So when you ask for help, no I don't care <br><br>You ain't drinkin' real Act, I can tell by the smell <br>Your girl just text me, said she hope I've been doin' well <br>They was cold, but now when they see me all these bitches melt <br>I'm a wizard, my dick game got her under a spell <br>I pop some molly, I just might go and shoot at myself <br>Frost just passed it to me, I put it under my belt <br>Still hide the work behind my hats on top of the shelf <br>Used to hide from my mom smokin' blunts in the back of the house <br>Why would I give you a half? I'll take it myself <br>You be the type to pop pills and go sit on the couch <br>I heard that your man is a rat and your OG's a mouse <br>You think I fucked on your bitch, I just nutted in her mouth <br><br>Metro Boomin said he got me, yeah <br>All these rappers try to copy, yeah <br>Stick to ice, don't play no hockey, yeah <br>My strap is black and hot like coffee, yeah <br>I'm goin' fast, you can't stop me, yeah <br>Heard your album, break weed on a copy, yeah <br>I used to want her, now she sloppy, yeah <br>Compare 'em to me, they can't top me, yeah <br><br>Yeah, I'ma put the money up for broski's bail, yeah <br>I just spent $200 on my nails, yeah <br>You wasn't there and now I'm outta here, yeah <br>You call my phone, I ignore and I don't care, yeah <br>You say you goin' broke and I don't care <br>Got 10 Gucci shoes, I flex on you and buy another pair <br>When I had no hope you wasn't there <br>So when you ask for help, no I don't care]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="I Don`t Care" label="I Don`t Care"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Perfect_Timing_Intro/</id><title>NAV - Perfect Timing (Intro) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:23:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:23:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NAV/Perfect_Timing_Intro/" title="NAV - Perfect Timing (Intro) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If Young Metro don't trust you, I'm gon' shoot you <br>Metro Boomin want some more, nigga <br><br>Me and Metro don't need help <br>Mail a pint to myself <br>Flew a pornstar to ATL <br>Louis Goyard belt <br>5 star hotels <br>Buy everything on the rack (cash) <br>Buy everything on the shelf (cash) <br>I make you mad, I can tell <br><br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Watch full of diamonds, yeah (bling) <br>Chart climbing, yeah <br>Foreign car driving, yeah (skrt) <br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Diamonds shining, yeah <br>Stars aligning, yeah <br>It's perfect timing, yeah <br><br>Double styrofoam cup (lean) <br>Big dog, you a pup <br>Since me and Metro made "Up" <br>All these bitches acting like sluts <br>You're not the type I can trust <br>Feel your energy through your touch <br>Follow feelings in my gut <br>Choppa turn your body into dust <br>She don't wanna listen to you <br>Your girlfriend listening to me <br>She on the phone with you <br>While she sucking on me <br>Off-white and Supreme <br>VLONE Vs, double Gs <br>Molly, liquor, bush, weed <br>These bitches so easy to please <br><br>Me and Metro don't need help <br>Mail a pint to myself <br>Flew a pornstar to ATL <br>Louis Goyard belt <br>5 star hotels <br>Buy everything on the rack (cash) <br>Buy everything on the shelf (cash) <br>I make you mad, I can tell <br><br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Watch full of diamonds, yeah (bling) <br>Chart climbing, yeah <br>Foreign car driving, yeah (skrt) <br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Diamonds shining, yeah <br>Stars aligning, yeah <br>It's perfect timing, yeah <br><br>Bust down rollie, flood it with diamonds <br>Can't tell what the time is, still know it's perfect timing <br>See it, want it, then I buy it, yeah <br>Lambo roar like a lion, yeah <br>Private jets is what I'm flying, yeah <br>Watching rap careers dying, yeah <br>Won't come to your wedding 'cause I don't want to wear a suit <br>Walking through the snow, I'm wearing YSL boots <br>9AM I'm off the Addys, still up in the booth <br>These other brown boys corny <br>They love me 'cause I'm the truth <br><br>Me and Metro don't need help <br>Mail a pint to myself <br>Flew a pornstar to ATL <br>Louis Goyard belt <br>5 star hotels <br>Buy everything on the rack (cash) <br>Buy everything on the shelf (cash) <br>I make you mad, I can tell <br><br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Watch full of diamonds, yeah (bling) <br>Chart climbing, yeah <br>Foreign car driving, yeah (skrt) <br>Perfect timing, yeah <br>Diamonds shining, yeah <br>Stars aligning, yeah <br>It's perfect timing, yeah]]></content><category term="NAV" label="NAV"/><category term="Perfect Timing (Intro)" label="Perfect Timing (Intro)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//_Feat__/</id><title> -  (Feat. , ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:25:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:25:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EC%9C%A0%EC%A7%84/%EC%9A%B0%EB%91%94%EB%82%A8%EB%85%80_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%84%EC%95%84_%EA%B9%80%EC%9C%A0%ED%83%9C/" title=" -  (Feat. , ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>  <br>     <br>     <br>  <br>   <br>     <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>  <br>     <br>  <br>  <br>  <br>  <br>  <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>  <br>   <br>     <br>  <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" (Feat. , )" label=" (Feat. , )"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//_/</id><title> -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:25:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:25:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B8%EC%A0%95%EC%9B%90/%EC%9D%B8%EC%B2%9C%ED%95%AD_%EC%B0%A8%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98%ED%83%80%EC%9A%B4/" title=" -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[  <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//Rain/</id><title> - Rain - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:25:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:25:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%86%8C%ED%98%84/Rain/" title=" - Rain - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rain    <br>Rain      <br>       <br>     <br>Rain     <br>Rain    <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>Rain     <br>Rain      <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="Rain" label="Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//Bon_Bon_With_/</id><title> - Bon Bon (With ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:29:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:29:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%A7%80%ED%9A%A8/Bon_Bon_With_%EA%B9%80%EC%98%88%EB%A6%B0/" title=" - Bon Bon (With ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[       <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>  Just wanna chew <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>Sweet and bitter  <br>   <br>Sweet and bitter  <br>  <br>    <br>Im falling in Love <br>Im falling for you <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>Sweet and bitter  <br>   <br>Sweet and bitter  <br>  <br>    <br>Im falling in Love <br>Im falling for you <br>Would you love me oh baby <br>      <br>Would you love me oh baby <br>     <br>Sweet and bitter  <br>   <br>Sweet and bitter  <br>  <br>    <br>Im falling in Love <br>Im falling for you <br>Sweet and bitter  <br>   <br>Sweet and bitter  <br>  <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="Bon Bon (With )" label="Bon Bon (With )"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/_NAVID/_Inst/</id><title> (NAVID) -  (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:29:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:29:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84%EB%93%9C_NAVID/%EC%95%84%EC%9E%90%EC%95%84%EC%9E%90_Inst/" title=" (NAVID) -  (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>  <br>  <br>     <br>     <br>   <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>       <br>     <br>   <br>   Sweet My Life <br>    <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>       <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>       <br>     <br>   <br>   Sweet My Life <br>]]></content><category term=" (NAVID)" label=" (NAVID)"/><category term=" (Inst.)" label=" (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/_NAVID//</id><title> (NAVID) -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:29:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:29:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84%EB%93%9C_NAVID/%EC%95%84%EC%9E%90%EC%95%84%EC%9E%90/" title=" (NAVID) -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>  <br>  <br>     <br>     <br>   <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>       <br>     <br>   <br>   Sweet My Life <br>    <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>       <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>       <br>     <br>   <br>   Sweet My Life <br>]]></content><category term=" (NAVID)" label=" (NAVID)"/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:29:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:29:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%A8%EC%A0%95/%EC%A0%9C%EC%A3%BC%EB%B4%89%EB%B4%89/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>      <br>      <br>  Go <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>  Go <br>     <br>  <br>      <br>  <br>   <br>      <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//___Ver/</id><title> -   ( Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:32:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:32:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EA%B7%9C/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9D%B4%EB%AA%A8_%EC%86%90%EB%8B%98_Ver/" title=" -   ( Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>  <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>  Go <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>  Go <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="  ( Ver.)" label="  ( Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//___Ver/</id><title> -   ( Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:32:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:32:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EA%B7%9C/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9D%B4%EB%AA%A8_%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%B8_Ver/" title=" -   ( Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>  <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>  Go <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>  Go <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="  ( Ver.)" label="  ( Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/_/________/</id><title> () -  (   ,    ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:33:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:33:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%98%ED%9D%AC_%EC%97%85%ED%85%90%EC%85%98/%EC%82%AC%EC%A7%84_%ED%8F%89%EC%B0%BD%EC%9D%98_%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4%EC%BD%94%ED%8A%B8_%EB%82%98%EC%95%BC%EB%82%98_%EC%88%98%ED%98%B8%EB%9E%91_%EB%84%8C_%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EB%B0%98%ED%96%88%EC%96%B4_%EB%B0%98%EB%8B%A4%EB%B9%84/" title=" () -  (   ,    ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>     <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>    <br>     <br>      <br>   <br>My love    <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>       <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>   <br>     <br>      <br>   <br>My love    <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>       <br>      <br>    <br>My love    <br>       <br>       <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>]]></content><category term=" ()" label=" ()"/><category term=" (   ,    )" label=" (   ,    )"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//________/</id><title> -   (  ,    ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:33:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:33:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%86%8C%EC%9D%80/%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C_%EA%B3%BC%EC%A6%99%EB%AF%B8_%EB%BF%9C%EB%BF%9C_%EA%B3%BC%EC%9D%BC%EB%B9%99%EC%88%98_%ED%83%9C%EC%96%91%EC%9D%84_%ED%94%BC%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%96%B4_%ED%8C%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%86%94/" title=" -   (  ,    ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>   <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>       <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>       <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>       <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>       <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="  (  ,    )" label="  (  ,    )"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//_/</id><title> -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:35:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:35:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%86%B0%ED%86%B0/%EA%B3%A0%EB%A7%99%EB%8B%A4%EB%8A%94_%EB%A7%90%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4%EB%8A%94/" title=" -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>  <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thanksgiving_band/_______Vocal_Ver/</id><title>Thanksgiving band -        (Vocal Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:35:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:35:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thanksgiving_band/%EC%A3%BC_%EC%98%88%EC%88%98_%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%98%EC%97%90_%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%99%80_%EA%B3%84%EC%8B%A0_%ED%9B%84_Vocal_Ver/" title="Thanksgiving band -        (Vocal Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[       <br>    <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>]]></content><category term="Thanksgiving band" label="Thanksgiving band"/><category term="       (Vocal Ver.)" label="       (Vocal Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/_/Oh_Oh_Oh/</id><title>  - Oh Oh Oh - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%88%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8%EC%95%A4_%EB%A1%9C%EC%A6%88/Oh_Oh_Oh/" title="  - Oh Oh Oh - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh <br>  <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>   <br> <br>      <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>I'm missing you <br>    <br>I am sing of you <br>    <br>Oh you don't have to why <br>   <br>   oh baby <br>Oh you don't have to why <br>   <br>   oh baby <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>Oh Oh Oh <br>  <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>   <br> <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh <br>I'm missing you <br>    <br>I am sing of you <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>  Alright <br>I'm missing you <br>    <br>I am sing of you <br>    <br>Oh you don't have to why <br>   <br>   oh baby <br>Oh you don't have to why <br>   <br>   oh <br>]]></content><category term=" " label=" "/><category term="Oh Oh Oh" label="Oh Oh Oh"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/_//</id><title>  -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%88%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8%EC%95%A4_%EB%A1%9C%EC%A6%88/%EC%95%88%EC%A0%84%EB%B2%A8%ED%8A%B8/" title="  -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>  <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>   Gossip   <br>  Emotion <br>   <br>      <br>   Motion <br>Fasten your seat belt Hoo- <br>Fasten your seat belt Hah- <br>Fasten your seat belt Hoo- <br>Fasten your seat belt <br>God bless you girl Uah <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>Beautiful day Beautiful lady <br>Beautiful day Beautiful lady <br>Fasten your seat belt Hoo- <br>Fasten your seat belt Hah- <br>Fasten your seat belt Hoo- <br>Fasten your seat belt <br>God bless you girl Uah <br>   <br>   Gossip   <br>  Emotion <br>   <br>      <br>   Motion <br>]]></content><category term=" " label=" "/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_/_All_Day_Every_Day/</id><title>Dayday () -  (All Day Every Day) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/%EC%98%AC%EB%9D%BC%EC%95%BC%ED%95%B4_All_Day_Every_Day/" title="Dayday () -  (All Day Every Day) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All Day Every Day <br>Aint no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Dont you let it fade <br>      <br>    <br>Oh Oh   <br>Oh Oh   <br>All Day Every Day <br>Aint no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Dont you let it fade <br>Nineteen eighty three <br>     <br>Cuz Im livin life <br>like Im forever twenty three <br>MIC   <br>   Look at me <br>I'm high fivin  <br>      <br>   <br>   <br> daily routine <br> gym   <br>   club  <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>  flow <br>    <br>    <br>All Day Every Day <br>Aint no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Dont you let it fade <br>      <br>    <br>Oh Oh   <br>Oh Oh   <br>All Day Every Day <br>Aint no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Dont you let it fade <br>Twenty four seven <br>Three six five <br>Im above and beyond <br>bullshit just positive vibes <br>Still rap   <br>  EP <br>Yesterday   <br> Dayday  <br>like  yolo <br>I said put some respect <br>on my  uh oh <br>    <br>  no no <br>      <br>      <br>No  No  <br>Shout out to AOMG <br>Team Loco Jay Park <br>and GRAY Simon D <br>Holmes crew Dalmatian too <br>I got love for all of yall till I d i e <br>      <br>For my fam for my friends <br>  <br>All Day Every Day <br>Aint no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Dont you let it fade <br>      <br>    <br>Oh Oh   <br>Oh Oh   <br>All Day Every Day <br>Aint no time to waste <br>Every second every minute <br>Dont you let it fade <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday ()" label="Dayday ()"/><category term=" (All Day Every Day)" label=" (All Day Every Day)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_/__remix_Feat_Hash_Swan_Shupie_Silly_Boot_Y1ee/</id><title>Dayday () -   remix (Feat. Hash Swan, Shupie, Silly Boot, Y1ee) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/%EB%8F%BC%EC%A7%80_%EC%A0%80%EA%B8%88%ED%86%B5_remix_Feat_Hash_Swan_Shupie_Silly_Boot_Y1ee/" title="Dayday () -   remix (Feat. Hash Swan, Shupie, Silly Boot, Y1ee) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All Day Every Day <br>   <br>You know its my Dayday <br>  <br>    <br>Oh yea hell yea <br>s hate <br>when we gettin paid <br>    <br>bulldozer  <br>Imma keep hustlin <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>  rookie <br> restarted <br>Imma old boy with that young <br>   rap  <br>    <br>   <br>  <br> good energy <br>  <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>And I be on my grinding mode <br>   <br>    <br>   <br> diamond <br> <br> <br>      <br>  <br>    <br>  twenty five <br>   <br>     <br>If you know how I feel <br>You deserve to listen to my EP <br>Seoul city There is no hippy <br> new hippy <br>   <br>      <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>  AB   <br>   <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>  <br>Yeah right Silly Boot MZN <br>We work hard play hard <br>This rap game is a day job <br>    <br>  Dream Chaser <br>   <br>  Thirty four <br>     <br>Yo Get that   <br>  <br>  <br>Get that   <br>  <br>Get that   <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>Oh Oh     <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>  Yeah <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>  10 <br>  <br>   <br>   Dayday IMAC <br>   <br>   <br>     <br>Yeah    <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>keep just cut it <br>      <br>   <br>keep just cut it <br>    <br>     <br> <br>keep just cut it <br>If you have to be our enemy <br>    <br>and your lil dick <br>keep just cut it <br>   <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>Don't worry bruh <br>We've got a lot of time <br>Always keep it real   <br>      <br>push it <br>  fresh    <br>Let's make some money <br>Let's make some noise <br>      <br>     no no <br>  <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>We work hard play hard <br>This rap game is a day job <br>    <br>  Dream Chaser <br>   <br>  Thirty four <br>     <br>Yo Get that   <br>  <br>  <br>Get that   <br>  <br>Get that   <br>Get that mula get that doe <br>Get that paper get that  <br> Ain't no diet for my <br>  <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>Get that mula get that doe <br>Get that paper get that  <br> Ain't no diet for my <br>  <br>     <br>  <br>  High five with  <br>work hard play hard <br>rap game is a day job <br>   <br> Dream Chaser <br>   <br>  Thirty four <br>     <br>Yo Lets get   <br>  <br>  <br>Get that   <br>  <br>Get that   <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday ()" label="Dayday ()"/><category term="  remix (Feat. Hash Swan, Shupie, Silly Boot, Y1ee)" label="  remix (Feat. Hash Swan, Shupie, Silly Boot, Y1ee)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_/No_Tomorrow_Feat__of_/</id><title>Dayday () - No Tomorrow (Feat.  of ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/No_Tomorrow_Feat_%EB%A6%B4%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4_of_%EA%B8%B1%EC%8A%A4/" title="Dayday () - No Tomorrow (Feat.  of ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>      <br>Jay-z Problem    <br>Man I'm just workin <br>through this life <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>  role model <br>   <br>Chasin paper gotta make <br>doe like bakers <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>    <br> nothing <br>    rhymes <br>   punchlines <br>Dedication motivation <br>overcame tribulations <br>in my worst times <br>Writer's block <br>      <br>only only positive vibes <br>One day <br>Imma make it to the clouds and <br>One day <br>I'm gonna make my momma proud yea <br>Someday <br>I'll look back at this right now <br>But until then till then <br>Imma live like No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow Tomorrow Tomorrow <br>I think that we'll be better tomorrow <br>I think that we'll be better tomorrow <br>There will be a better tomorrow <br>Now everything gone yea <br>No Tomorrow   <br>   <br>    <br>Like no tomorrow <br>    <br> But maybe <br>I feel <br>We can make it happen <br>yeah we can make it happen <br>    <br>    <br>   prolly <br>    <br>  fuck apocalypse <br>    <br>Like we don't care bout rules boi <br>we don't care bout rules boi <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>That's what we die for <br>    <br>fuck that  <br>      <br> Live like no tomorrow <br>   <br>    <br>   no business here <br>    What a family <br>    <br>    <br>  there's only <br>positive vibes <br>But you motherfucker <br>       <br> No Tomorrow <br>       <br>      only one <br>Better keep that attitude <br>    <br>  Dayday  <br>    <br>Tommorow <br>One day <br>Imma make it to the clouds and <br>One day <br>I'm gonna make my momma proud yea <br>Someday <br>I'll look back at this right now <br>But until then till then <br>Imma live like No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow <br>No No Tomorrow Tomorrow Tomorrow <br>I think we'll have a better tomorrow <br>Think there'll be a better tomorrow yea <br>I think we'll have a better tomorrow <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday ()" label="Dayday ()"/><category term="No Tomorrow (Feat.  of )" label="No Tomorrow (Feat.  of )"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_/__Feat_GRAY_/</id><title>Dayday () -   (Feat. GRAY, ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:37:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:37:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EB%B6%88%EB%9F%AC_Feat_GRAY_%EB%B0%95%EC%9E%AC%EB%B2%94/" title="Dayday () -   (Feat. GRAY, ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>Hey girl      <br>      <br> solo <br>party    <br>What Just like  <br>Ay     <br>dress code <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>It's your Dayday-javu <br>Youre so bad and  <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>holla at me <br>Livin good feel hella great <br>  Celeb Celebrate <br>   <br>ceremony   <br>Tell em GRAY <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>I'll be your personal hotline <br>  what's on your mind <br>No I aint a baller <br>    <br>  VI MVP <br>      <br>       <br>        <br>   <br> I'm up in the club <br>   <br>Ready for love <br>So hit me on my line <br>hit me on my line <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>For you the one and only <br>   <br>yeah yeah yeah <br>I'm feelin good feelin hella great <br>Always on my grind <br>I do this shh like everyday <br>I'm your Big Sean you Jhene Aiko <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>   call me <br>   <br>when you want me <br>When you need me <br>whenever you call me <br>I'll be there oh <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>       <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>Yo     <br>     <br>Cuz tonight we gon celebrate <br>I said     <br>Call me any time or day <br>   Bae <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday ()" label="Dayday ()"/><category term="  (Feat. GRAY, )" label="  (Feat. GRAY, )"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_/Better_Days_Feat_G2_ELO_DJ_Wegun/</id><title>Dayday () - Better Days (Feat. G2, ELO, DJ Wegun) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/Better_Days_Feat_G2_ELO_DJ_Wegun/" title="Dayday () - Better Days (Feat. G2, ELO, DJ Wegun) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>Is it the number 1 spot <br>   <br>    <br>Only the strong survive <br>  <br>  <br>I dont do cuz you <br>only get one shot <br>but I dont lose <br>      <br>   <br>nah that's my truth <br>and fact I proved <br>but   <br>     <br>  <br>      <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>    Imma keep <br>on doin my thing so yea <br>I'm gon be the king <br>Pray for better days <br>       <br>Guide me through evil ways <br>Oh please <br>Oh Oh Oh Better Days <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh I pray for better days <br>  Birthday day <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>Gotta maintain <br>till everyday be my payday <br>    <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>Dang <br>     <br>  <br>gotta take advantage <br>   <br>    <br>until every song <br>on my album gettin airplay <br>       <br>      <br>      <br>     <br>Pray for better days <br>       <br>Guide me through evil ways <br>Oh please <br>Oh Oh Oh Better Days <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh I pray for better days <br>    <br> epiphany    <br>    <br>    <br>body and mind <br> real really recognize <br>positive vibes <br>      <br>Superstar    <br>  boost   No  <br>Oh Lordy I pray for the best <br>    <br>        <br>    <br>money power respect <br>Finally oh Lord <br>I pray for the rest <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>Im turnin up and away <br>Pray for better days <br>       <br>Guide me through evil ways <br>Oh please <br>Oh Oh Oh Better Days <br>Oh Oh Oh Oh I pray for better days <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday ()" label="Dayday ()"/><category term="Better Days (Feat. G2, ELO, DJ Wegun)" label="Better Days (Feat. G2, ELO, DJ Wegun)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_/_Feat__DJ_Wegun/</id><title>Dayday () -  (Feat. , DJ Wegun) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dayday_%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4/%EC%97%8E%EC%96%B4_Feat_%EA%B9%80%ED%9A%A8%EC%9D%80_DJ_Wegun/" title="Dayday () -  (Feat. , DJ Wegun) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I go by the name of Dayday <br>a.k.a rap  <br>  <br>    flow  <br>   style     <br>no nada    <br>    <br>   <br> rap    <br>    <br>  <br>Smooth rapper boom <br>bapper swag too dapper <br>I get stupid <br>when I spit call me boom babo <br>and I dont start battles <br> <br> Benjamin Button <br> Bruce Banner <br>Imma beast    <br>    <br>King Kong shit <br> rap crossfit    <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>    show no mercy <br>    <br> flow heavy microdot  <br>    <br>competition demolition  <br>       <br>    <br>  <br>I dont give a fuck   <br>      <br>  MR. Chu  <br>  MIC    <br>run for ya life <br>Its that beat knocker <br>head bopper <br>rap  emcee pen dropper <br>    <br>     <br>Its that beat knocker <br>head bopper <br>rap  emcee pen dropper <br>     <br>      <br>1      <br>     eh <br>     <br>       <br>  <br>    <br>       <br>       <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>    <br>  Vegas  <br>Yea Kenny raw <br>We in this bitch <br>spittin raw raw shit <br>no specific topics only bars <br>thats lit <br>only bars thats lit <br>Molotov rap kids <br>no tolerance for wackness <br>so be gone vanish <br>always underrated <br>never outdated Im just <br>patiently waitin <br>and no aint complainin <br>I stay elevated levitated <br>detonate to greatness <br>and I keep distance <br>from fuckboys <br>they contagious <br>    <br>       <br>Boy be ambitious <br>on these bustas man <br>bumrush'em to the floor <br>  anthem  <br>ambush for you hoes <br>Its that beat knocker <br>head bopper <br>rap  emcee pen dropper <br>    <br>     <br>Its that beat knocker <br>head bopper <br>rap  emcee pen dropper <br>     <br>      <br>]]></content><category term="Dayday ()" label="Dayday ()"/><category term=" (Feat. , DJ Wegun)" label=" (Feat. , DJ Wegun)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joypark_/_/</id><title>Joypark () -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joypark_%EC%A1%B0%EC%9D%B4%ED%8C%8C%ED%81%AC/%EC%BA%98%EB%A6%AC%ED%8F%AC%EB%8B%88%EC%95%84_%EC%98%A4%EB%A0%8C%EC%A7%80/" title="Joypark () -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Say you love me <br>     <br>Drip it baby <br> juice   <br>I'll squeeze it woo my lady <br>   <br> nothing to me honey so please <br>Kiss me for orange sky <br>Take a sip and surf to the top <br>  <br>Drinking in orange sky <br>Come and find <br>What we are <br>I'm a map <br>And you are my golden compass <br> <br>Don't be shy <br>No more no more <br>Take it easy <br>  beach wear <br>  <br> <br>  <br>It drive me crazy lady <br>I'll be a farmer  <br>    my baby <br>     <br>   uh uh <br>   <br> nothing to me honey so please <br>Kiss me for orange sky <br>Take a sip and surf to the top <br>  <br>Drinking in orange sky <br>Come and find <br>What we are <br>I'm a map <br>And you are my golden compass <br> <br>Don't be shy <br>No more no more <br>Come and find <br>Paradise <br>Here we are <br>Yeah we're in California <br> <br>Don't be shy <br>No more no more <br>]]></content><category term="Joypark ()" label="Joypark ()"/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joypark_/Alive_Feat_/</id><title>Joypark () - Alive (Feat. ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Joypark_%EC%A1%B0%EC%9D%B4%ED%8C%8C%ED%81%AC/Alive_Feat_%EC%A7%80%EC%95%A0%EB%A6%B0/" title="Joypark () - Alive (Feat. ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want you to notice <br>    <br>   <br>We've been panting runners <br>   <br>We never surrender <br>We never get older <br>  <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>We will be together <br>   <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>  young and alive <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>Sun will ignite us <br>And it will celebrate us <br>We never get older <br>  <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>We will be together <br>   <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>  young and alive <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>Now Just sing on <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>Will be together now <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Yeah now I feel young and alive <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>Just sing on <br>Don't say no no no <br>Girl stay oh <br>Don't say no <br>]]></content><category term="Joypark ()" label="Joypark ()"/><category term="Alive (Feat. )" label="Alive (Feat. )"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%98%81%EC%B2%A0/%ED%8C%8C%EB%8F%84/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[  <br>One Two One Two Three Four <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>  <br>       <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>   <br> <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>       <br>       <br>  <br>    <br>      <br> <br> <br>  <br>   <br>       <br>     <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//__/</id><title> -    - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:38:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:38:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EC%9E%AC%ED%9D%AC/%EC%96%B4%EC%A9%8C%EB%8B%A4_%EB%A7%88%EC%A3%BC%EC%B9%9C_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80/" title=" -    - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="  " label="  "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Twelve24/The_Book/</id><title>Twelve24 - The Book - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:40:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:40:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Twelve24/The_Book/" title="Twelve24 - The Book - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You got me going <br>you got me going crazy <br>Something about you <br>your love is so amazing <br>I know that youll be <br>everything I need <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>No matter where I go <br>I give you control <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Like a cloud by day <br>like a fire by night <br>Youre with me all the way <br>Youre with me all the way <br>Like a cloud by day <br>like a fire by night <br>Youre with me all the way <br>Youre with me all the way <br>They say nothing lasts forever <br>but that aint true <br>You can change the weather <br>but they cant change you <br>And I love it when you speak <br>coz you speak the truth <br>Your words bring me to life <br>and make me brand new <br>So oh my I know <br>you been there my whole life <br>And you got me acting <br>to crazy right now <br>You saved me right now <br>aint that the truth <br>I know that youll be <br>everything I need <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>No matter where I go <br>I give you control <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Like a cloud by day <br>like a fire by night <br>Youre with me all the way <br>Youre with me all the way <br>Like a cloud by day <br>like a fire by night <br>Youre with me all the way <br>Youre with me all the way <br>When I dont know what to say <br>and I dont know what to do <br>Everything is falling down <br>I know youll get me through <br>Even with my broken heart <br>when every bit is torn apart <br>I know I can look to you <br>I know that youll be <br>everything I need <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>No matter where I go <br>I give you control <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Your word brings me to life <br>Youre with me all the way <br>Youre with me all the way <br>]]></content><category term="Twelve24" label="Twelve24"/><category term="The Book" label="The Book"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//__Inst/</id><title> -   (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:41:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:41:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%94%EC%A1%B0/%EB%91%90%EA%B7%BC%EB%91%90%EA%B7%BC_%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84%EB%82%A0_Inst/" title=" -   (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>       <br>      <br>     <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="  (Inst.)" label="  (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//_/</id><title> -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:41:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:41:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%94%EC%A1%B0/%EB%91%90%EA%B7%BC%EB%91%90%EA%B7%BC_%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84%EB%82%A0/" title=" -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>       <br>      <br>     <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//_/</id><title> -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:41:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:41:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A3%A8%EB%85%B8/%EB%84%90_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A0%A4/" title=" -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>   <br>   <br>   <br> <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>       <br>  <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>       <br>  <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/_ChAN/_/</id><title> (ChAN) -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:41:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:41:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%AC_ChAN/%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B8%EB%8B%A4/" title=" (ChAN) -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>      <br>     <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>      <br>     <br>  <br>]]></content><category term=" (ChAN)" label=" (ChAN)"/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%84%B1/%EC%A7%80%EC%A7%80%EA%B3%A0%EB%B3%B6%EA%B3%A0/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>      <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%84%B1/%EB%84%8B%EB%91%90%EB%A6%AC/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/_Hi_to_him/_Duet_Ver/</id><title> (Hi to him) -  (Duet Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%88%AC%ED%9E%98_Hi_to_him/%EC%A0%80%EA%B8%B0_Duet_Ver/" title=" (Hi to him) -  (Duet Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>   <br>    <br>       <br>  <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>      <br>  <br>    <br>     <br>      <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>]]></content><category term=" (Hi to him)" label=" (Hi to him)"/><category term=" (Duet Ver.)" label=" (Duet Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/_Hi_to_him/_/</id><title> (Hi to him) -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%88%AC%ED%9E%98_Hi_to_him/%EC%A7%9D%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EC%99%88%EC%B8%A0/" title=" (Hi to him) -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>   <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>     <br>  <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>  <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>]]></content><category term=" (Hi to him)" label=" (Hi to him)"/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/_Hi_to_him/_/</id><title> (Hi to him) -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%88%AC%ED%9E%98_Hi_to_him/%EC%88%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%98_%EA%B0%90%EC%A0%95/" title=" (Hi to him) -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>    <br>      <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>  <br> <br> <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>  <br>  <br>]]></content><category term=" (Hi to him)" label=" (Hi to him)"/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/_Hi_to_him//</id><title> (Hi to him) -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:42:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:42:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%88%AC%ED%9E%98_Hi_to_him/%EC%A0%80%EA%B8%B0/" title=" (Hi to him) -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>   <br>    <br>       <br>  <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>      <br>  <br>    <br>     <br>      <br>      <br>   <br>    <br>]]></content><category term=" (Hi to him)" label=" (Hi to him)"/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%94%84%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EB%93%9C%EB%B0%B4%EB%93%9C/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>   <br>      <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>      <br>  I believe your dream <br>     <br>  <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>      <br>  I believe your dream <br>My dream is to be with you <br>My dream is to be with you <br>My dream is to be with you <br>My dream is to be with you <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>     <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>     <br>      <br>  I believe my dream <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//____Band_Ver/</id><title> -     (Band Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%84%A0%ED%95%9C_%EB%AA%A9%EC%9E%90%EB%90%98%EC%8B%A0_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC_Band_Ver/" title=" -     (Band Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[       <br>    <br> <br>       <br>   <br>  <br>       <br>    <br> <br>       <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>     <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>       <br>     <br>     <br>       <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="    (Band Ver.)" label="    (Band Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//__/</id><title> -    - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%8C%ED%95%9C_%EC%97%AC%EC%9D%B8%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title=" -    - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="  " label="  "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//___/</id><title> -     - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%95%84_%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%98_%EC%86%8D%EC%97%90/" title=" -     - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[       <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>     <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="   " label="   "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//__Reach_Out_To_Jesus/</id><title> -   (Reach Out To Jesus) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%A7%90%EC%9D%B4_%EB%AC%B4%EA%B1%B0%EC%9A%B0%EB%83%90_Reach_Out_To_Jesus/" title=" -   (Reach Out To Jesus) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>    <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="  (Reach Out To Jesus)" label="  (Reach Out To Jesus)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//___/</id><title> -     - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:43:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:43:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%97%AC%EB%9F%AC%EB%B6%84%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%ED%95%98%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EC%9D%80_%EB%A7%90/" title=" -     - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[  <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>      <br>      <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>   <br> <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="   " label="   "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//_/</id><title> -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%97%AC%ED%98%B8%EC%99%80_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A0%88/" title=" -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>     <br>     <br> <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>  <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%B0%A9%EA%B0%81/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[  <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>  <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>       <br>      <br>  <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>  <br>    <br>   <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>       <br>      <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//____Acoustic_Ver/</id><title> -     (Acoustic Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%95%84%EB%9E%80/%EC%84%A0%ED%95%9C_%EB%AA%A9%EC%9E%90%EB%90%98%EC%8B%A0_%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC_Acoustic_Ver/" title=" -     (Acoustic Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[      <br>    <br>  <br>      <br>     <br>      <br>    <br>  <br>      <br>     <br>     <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>     <br>      <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>    <br>    <br>      <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="    (Acoustic Ver.)" label="    (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//__/</id><title> -    - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8C%80%ED%95%9C%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EA%B5%90%EC%9E%A5%EB%A1%9C%ED%9A%8C%EC%B4%9D%ED%9A%8C/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%98_%EA%B0%80%EB%93%9D%ED%95%9C/" title=" -    - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>  <br>  <br>  <br>   . <br><br>  <br>  <br>   <br>  ]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="  " label="  "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//Jump_Jump/</id><title> - Jump Jump - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8C%80%ED%95%9C%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EA%B5%90%EC%9E%A5%EB%A1%9C%ED%9A%8C%EC%B4%9D%ED%9A%8C/Jump_Jump/" title=" - Jump Jump - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>   <br> jump  jump <br>    <br>  jump jump <br>  jump jump <br>  jump jump <br>  jump jump jump <br><br>     <br>   <br> jump  jump <br>    <br>  jump jump <br>  jump jump <br>  jump jump <br>  jump jump jump <br><br>  jump jump <br>  jump jump <br>  jump jump <br>  jump jump jump jump <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="Jump Jump" label="Jump Jump"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//____2016__/</id><title> -  (  ) (2016  ) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:44:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:44:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8C%80%ED%95%9C%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EA%B5%90%EC%9E%A5%EB%A1%9C%ED%9A%8C%EC%B4%9D%ED%9A%8C/%EB%AF%BF%EC%9D%8C%EC%97%90%EC%84%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EA%B9%8C%EC%A7%80%EB%B6%80%EC%A0%9C%EF%BC%9A%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C%EC%9D%98_%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC%EB%A5%BC_%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4%EB%B3%B4%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94_2016%EB%85%84_%EC%97%AC%EB%A6%84%EC%84%B1%EA%B2%BD%ED%95%99%EA%B5%90_%EC%B4%9D%EC%A3%BC%EC%A0%9C%EA%B0%80/" title=" -  (  ) (2016  ) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>      <br>      <br>     <br>    X2 <br><br>      <br>      <br>     <br>   ]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" (  ) (2016  )" label=" (  ) (2016  )"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//_/</id><title> -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:47:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:47:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A8%EC%9C%A0/%EC%9D%B4%EB%9F%AC%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title=" -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[     <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>       <br>   <br>     <br>   <br>    <br>   <br>     <br>    <br>   <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist///</id><title> -  - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:49:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:49:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%A6%AC%EC%95%84/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%BC%EC%97%90%EB%8F%84/" title=" -  - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[   <br>   <br>     <br> <br>    <br>     <br> <br>     <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>  <br> <br> <br>   <br>   <br>    <br> <br>  <br>    <br> <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>   <br>  <br>  <br>   <br>    <br>  <br>  <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term="" label=""/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist//_/</id><title> -   - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:49:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:49:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%82%98%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%98/%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B1_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title=" -   - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[    <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>      <br>So beautiful day <br>I feel so happy with you <br>    <br>   <br>    <br>    <br>     <br>     <br>    <br>     <br>      <br>So beautiful day <br>I feel so happy with you <br>    <br>   <br>so beautiful day <br>I feel so happy with you <br>   <br>   <br>    <br>]]></content><category term="" label=""/><category term=" " label=" "/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Talking_Heads/No_Compassion_Live/</id><title>Talking Heads - No Compassion (Live) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T22:52:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T22:52:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Talking_Heads/No_Compassion_Live/" title="Talking Heads - No Compassion (Live) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In a world <br>where people have problems <br>In this world <br>where decisions are a way of life <br>Other people's problems they overwhelm my mind <br>They say compassion is a virtue, but I don't have the time <br><br>So many peoplehave their problems <br>I'm not interestedin their problems <br>I guess I'veexperienced some problems <br>But now I'vemade some decisions <br>Takes a lot of time to push away the nonsense <br>Take my compassionPush it as far as it goes <br>My interest level's dropping, my interest level is dropping <br>I've heard all I want to, I don't want to hear any more <br><br>What are you, in love with your problems <br>I think you take ita little too far <br>It'snot so cool to have so many problems <br>But don't expect me to explain your indecisions <br>Gotalk to your analyst, isn't that what they're paid for <br>You walk, you talkYou still function like you used to <br>It's not a questionOf your personality or style <br>Be a little more selfish, it might do you some good <br><br>In a world where people have problems <br>In this world where decisions are a way of life <br>Other people's problems, they overwhelm my mind <br>They say compassion is a virtue, but I don't have the time <br>Here we go again]]></content><category term="Talking Heads" label="Talking Heads"/><category term="No Compassion (Live)" label="No Compassion (Live)"/></entry></feed>