<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:52:23+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬릭_SLEEQ/WTF_SLEEQ_Solo/</id><title>슬릭 (SLEEQ) - WTF (SLEEQ Solo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:52:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:52:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AD_SLEEQ/WTF_SLEEQ_Solo/" title="슬릭 (SLEEQ) - WTF (SLEEQ Solo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So tell me what the fuck <br>the fuck do you mean <br>그 순간에 대해서 <br>난 필요해 설명이 <br>겨우 하는 거라곤 <br>숨을 아껴 하루 종일 <br>시간이 모든 걸 <br>흐려놓을까 봐 나지 겁이 <br>So tell me what the fuck <br>the fuck do you mean <br>그 순간에 대해서 <br>난 필요해 설명이 <br>겨우 하는 거라곤 <br>숨을 아껴 하루 종일 <br>시간이 모든 걸 <br>흐려놓을까 봐 나지 겁이 <br>넌 아무렇지 않은 척 하지 <br>왜 여기서 더 가까워지면 <br>영원히 멀어질 것 같니 <br>Damn 맘이 가는 대로 하면 <br>누군가 너를 버릴 것 같니 <br>나쁜 말은 하기는 싫은 <br>너는 나쁜 것을 원하지 <br>넌 나의 나쁜 척을 원하지 <br>I know <br>난 너의 거짓말을 알아 <br>기억하지 못하고 싶어하지만 <br>날 보는 너의 눈이 <br>거짓말을 않아 <br>난 니가 바라는 대로 <br>하고 싶으니까 <br>이걸 다 거짓말로 알아 <br>나도 편하겠지 <br>이 모든 게 다 아무것도 <br>아니면 시간은 많아 <br>시간은 많아 많아 <br>So tell me what the fuck <br>the fuck do you mean <br>그 순간에 대해서 <br>난 필요해 설명이 <br>겨우 하는 거라곤 <br>숨을 아껴 하루 종일 <br>시간이 모든 걸 <br>흐려놓을까 봐 나지 겁이 <br>So tell me what the fuck <br>the fuck do you mean <br>그 순간에 대해서 <br>난 필요해 설명이 <br>겨우 하는 거라곤 <br>숨을 아껴 하루 종일 <br>시간이 모든 걸 <br>흐려놓을까 봐 나지 겁이 <br>So what the fuck do you mean <br>What is your mind <br>실은 다 알지만 듣고 싶어 난 <br>알아 이기적인 것도 <br>너무 많은걸 바라는 것도 <br>나만 이런 게 아니란 것도 <br>서로 많이 기다렸단 것도 <br>우린 서로 많이 기다렸지 <br>돌아갈만한 길은 <br>죄다 알아가듯이 <br>엇갈리기만 하다가 <br>다 알아버렸지 <br>서로가 아니면 <br>이 모든 건 다 <br>아무것도 아니라는걸 <br>다 알면서 달아나는 <br>척하는 너 uh <br>다 알면서 따라가는 <br>걸 나는 uh uh <br>다 알면서 그만할 <br>순 없다는 걸 <br>날 안았던 너가 <br>제일 잘 아는 걸 <br>다 가르쳐 줘 <br>알아 이기적인 것도 <br>너무 많은걸 바라는 것도 <br>나만 이런 거 <br>나만 이런 게 아니란 것도 <br>서로 많이 기다렸단 것도 <br>So tell me what the fuck <br>the fuck do you mean <br>그 순간에 대해서 <br>난 필요해 설명이 <br>겨우 하는 거라곤 <br>숨을 아껴 하루 종일 <br>시간이 모든 걸 <br>흐려놓을까 봐 나지 겁이 <br>So tell me what the fuck <br>the fuck do you mean <br>그 순간에 대해서 <br>난 필요해 설명이 <br>겨우 하는 거라곤 <br>숨을 아껴 하루 종일 <br>시간이 모든 걸 <br>흐려놓을까 봐 나지 겁이 <br>So tell me what the fuck <br>So tell me what the fuck <br>그 순간에 대해서 <br>난 필요해 설명이 <br>겨우 하는 거라곤 <br>숨을 아껴 하루 종일 <br>시간이 모든 걸 <br>흐려놓을까 봐 나지 겁이 <br>the fuck do you mean <br>그 순간에 대해서 <br>난 필요해 설명이 <br>겨우 하는 거라곤 <br>숨을 아껴 하루 종일 <br>시간이 모든 걸 <br>흐려놓을까 봐 나지 겁이 <br>]]></content><category term="슬릭 (SLEEQ)" label="슬릭 (SLEEQ)"/><category term="WTF (SLEEQ Solo)" label="WTF (SLEEQ Solo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬릭_SLEEQ/이륙/</id><title>슬릭 (SLEEQ) - 이륙 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:52:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:52:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AD_SLEEQ/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A5%99/" title="슬릭 (SLEEQ) - 이륙 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여긴 있을 곳이 아냐 <br>날아갈 곳을 찾아 <br>매 주말마다 도심 <br>한복판에서 불 나 활활 <br>그래 봤자 바뀌는 거 <br>하나 없는 거처럼 <br>느껴서 말해 <br>뭘 바래 난 떠날래 <br>Marijuana 맘대로 하고 <br>이런 얘기하고 <br>안 찔리는 곳 <br>햇볕 쬐며 태평해도 <br>집시나 히피도 <br>쉴 수 있고 <br>누군가에겐 바하마에서 봐 <br>하와이 and 카오산 <br>또 타이완 ay <br>눈치 안보고 취해 <br>술 섞어 약과 함께 <br>물담배 fuck it fuck all y’all <br>높아져가 멍청도 <br>비둘기들 점점 더 <br>뻔뻔스러워져 <br>더 난 고개 돌리고 <br>표 끊고 있네 <br>내 목에 잉크와 바늘을 <br>댄 순간이 내 항공티켓 <br>도망친 곳에 <br>낙원은 없다고들 해 <br>가만히 있는 곳 <br>불바닥 난 꼭 뜰래 <br>말리부 마음의 부 <br>둘 다 가고 가져볼게 <br>어쩜 한잔 아님 <br>한대 말고 마는 게 있어 <br>답이였을 때가 <br>다 비웠을 때가 <br>다 태웠을 때가 <br>다 비웠을 때가 <br>난 날아가 음 <br>나만 아는 그 paradise 음 <br>목 끝까지 닿아 <br>내려가는 술과 음 <br>좋은 음악 <br>음 눈을 감아 음 난 눈감아 <br>난 날아가 음 <br>나만 아는 그 paradise 음 <br>목 끝까지 닿아 <br>내려가는 술과 음 <br>좋은 음악 <br>음 눈을 감아 음 난 눈감아 <br>인천공항 삐뚤어진 <br>유리 너머 보이는 <br>비행기 날개 위에 올라 <br>앉아 마셔 넘기는 <br>Dry Martini 소름 <br>올라 머리끝까지 <br>나는 파일럿에 <br>무전을 하지 <br>3초만 세고 <br>출발을 알리라고 <br>머리카락 날리는 오후 <br>하늘 빛은 아름다워 <br>나는 빨대 물고 <br>창문으로 손 흔들어 <br>그럼 사람들은 wow <br>SLEEQ 어디가요 <br>이 노래 빨간 딱지 <br>안 붙는 곳 아는 데 있나요 <br>거기 내릴라고 <br>찾아보는 중인데 <br>물이 된 얼음 마셔버리고는 <br>다시 한 번 술로 채워 <br>뜨거운 해 <br>검은 sunglasses 가면처럼 <br>시야를 메워 <br>행복이 될까 독이 될까 <br>feelin’ high 그거면 될까 <br>발바닥 아래가 <br>많이 아득하네 <br>자유낙하 가만히 <br>난 날아가 음 <br>나만 아는 그 paradise 음 <br>목 끝까지 닿아 <br>내려가는 술과 음 <br>좋은 음악 <br>음 눈을 감아 음 난 눈감아 <br>난 날아가 음 <br>나만 아는 그 paradise 음 <br>목 끝까지 닿아 <br>내려가는 술과 음 <br>좋은 음악 <br>음 눈을 감아 음 난 눈감아 <br>]]></content><category term="슬릭 (SLEEQ)" label="슬릭 (SLEEQ)"/><category term="이륙" label="이륙"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬릭_SLEEQ/베르테_SLEEQ_Solo/</id><title>슬릭 (SLEEQ) - 베르테 (SLEEQ Solo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:52:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:52:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AD_SLEEQ/%EB%B2%A0%EB%A5%B4%ED%85%8C_SLEEQ_Solo/" title="슬릭 (SLEEQ) - 베르테 (SLEEQ Solo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 영원히 <br>볼 수 없는 내가 없는 <br>그대의 시간을 <br>궁금해하는 내 마음은 <br>영원히 만질 수 없는 그대를 <br>원하는 내 마음은 어쩌면 <br>내가 영원히 <br>볼 수 없는 내가 없는 <br>그대의 시간을 <br>궁금해하는 내 마음은 <br>영원히 만질 수 없는 그대를 <br>원하는 내 마음은 <br>어쩌면 너무 잔인해 <br>나 숨을 내려 놓고파 <br>그대의 품에 안긴 채 <br>품에 안긴 채 <br>난 영원히 그대에겐 <br>어떤 의미도 없이 존재해 <br>그럼 영원히 난 가까워질 수도 <br>멀어질 수도 없이 공전해 <br>그댄 영원히 나의 눈 닿는 <br>모든 세계 모든 시간에 존재해 <br>그렇다고 해도 여전히 <br>나는 답을 내릴 수 없는 <br>이 관계를 어찌하지 못하네 <br>만약에 그대가 나와 <br>똑같은 눈동자를 하고 <br>내가 절대로 알 수 없는 <br>어떤 얼굴로 <br>나와 마주하게 될 수 있다면 <br>나는 감당할 수 있을까 과연 <br>감히 나의 환상 밖으로 <br>발바닥을 딛는 아찔함을 <br>식은땀에 눈을 깜박여 <br>그렇다고 해도 어쩔 수 없는데 <br>내려놓고파 내가 만들어낸 <br>너의 모습들은 <br>아무 거리낌없이 나를 만지지 <br>나는 당연하다는 듯이 <br>그 손에 나를 맡겨 <br>몽롱히 가쁜 숨을 내쉬고 마시지 <br>누구도 알 수 없고 <br>누구도 알지 못하는 <br>나락으로 떨어질 때 <br>손을 잡아 간신히 <br>그 온기로 얼어붙었던 <br>온몸을 힘껏 녹여도 <br>여전히 모든 꿈은 <br>끝나고 사라지지 <br>전부 다 사라져 <br>내가 영원히 <br>볼 수 없는 내가 없는 <br>그대의 시간을 <br>궁금해하는 내 마음은 <br>영원히 만질 수 없는 그대를 <br>원하는 내 마음은 어쩌면 <br>어쩌면 난 두려워 한 거야 <br>전하지 못한 그 말까지도 다 <br>어쩌면 난 불안한 것 뿐야 <br>다 낫지 못한 상처까지도 다 <br>당신에게 묻은 나의 위태로움도 <br>때로는 날카롭게 반짝일 테지만 <br>내게로 온 당신의 찬란함도 <br>때로는 어둠을 머금지만 <br>내가 영원히 <br>볼 수 없는 내가 없는 <br>그대의 시간을 <br>궁금해하는 내 마음은 <br>영원히 만질 수 없는 그대를 <br>원하는 내 마음은 어쩌면 <br>내가 영원히 <br>]]></content><category term="슬릭 (SLEEQ)" label="슬릭 (SLEEQ)"/><category term="베르테 (SLEEQ Solo)" label="베르테 (SLEEQ Solo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬릭_SLEEQ/비켜/</id><title>슬릭 (SLEEQ) - 비켜 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:52:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:52:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AD_SLEEQ/%EB%B9%84%EC%BC%9C/" title="슬릭 (SLEEQ) - 비켜 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모두 무서워하지 <br>잠하고 사촌지간 <br>난 둘 다 등쳐먹잖아 <br>자 까먹지 말고 <br>내 이름 어서 적어둬 <br>벌어뒀던 돈 준비해 <br>그 사기친 시간으로 <br>만든 건 늘 죽이네 <br>내 친구도 그걸 아니까 <br>걔 정신병을 내게 맡겼지 <br>생색 내는 거 아냐 <br>난 누구에겐 삶을 <br>책임질 수 있는 <br>존재가 돼 어쩔 때엔 <br>감정은 날 죽이고 <br>다시 태어나지 내 랩에 <br>그래서 망가진 관계와 <br>잡스런 과거 흔적 <br>생각하며 울음이 많아졌어 부쩍 <br>이건 조금 다른 내 울음 소리 <br>도미노 같이 아슬한 단어들 <br>한 개 더 세워 그 옆에다가 <br>허나 날 괴롭히는 건 <br>이젠 없지 그건 다 너희 거 <br>난 넘어지더라도 발 붙이고 <br>또 금방 서 있어 <br>어쩔 거야 생각대로 <br>되는 거 없어도 <br>I’m always good <br>나만 잘함 돼 끝 <br>I’m always good <br>넌 그냥 내 앞에서 꺼져주면 돼 <br>내가 다 알아서 하니까 다물어 <br>You’d better get off of my way <br>비켜봐 넌 그냥 꺼져주면 돼 <br>걍 있어봐 get off of my way <br>옷 병원 집 아들이어도 <br>내 몸보다 큰 옷 <br>큰 야망 수선 안 해 <br>원하는 대로 집어 들고 <br>걸쳐 본 뒤에 내 걸로 <br>모두의 시선과 걱정 <br>한 움큼 삼켜 <br>또 걸어가는 vagabond <br>다들 개나 줬던 <br>자존심 다 주워 담고 <br>허리 펴보니 보였던 건 <br>너희 부적절한 꼴 <br>뭐 누구 탓 안 해 <br>각자의 입장은 전부 타당해 <br>난 그냥 그걸 이해 안 할래 <br>설마 했던 일들은 벌어지기 마련 <br>난 작은 무대의 <br>온기로 빙하기를 나며 <br>기록을 남기지 called that record <br>자유의 날이 머지 않았다 <br>손 잡고 주문을 외며 <br>노래를 불러 남들이 <br>보기엔 미친놈 같이 <br>북을 치고 다니며 기뻐하지 <br>그 얼굴은 가면도 <br>아니고 진심도 아닌 <br>내 안 무엇 중 하나 <br>나를 던지는 중 여기에 열중하며 <br>Get the fuck off my way <br>Get the fuck off my way <br>Get the fuck off my way <br>Get the fuck off my way <br>]]></content><category term="슬릭 (SLEEQ)" label="슬릭 (SLEEQ)"/><category term="비켜" label="비켜"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬릭_SLEEQ/Talk_About_Feat_Jerryk/</id><title>슬릭 (SLEEQ) - Talk About (Feat. Jerry.k) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:52:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:52:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AD_SLEEQ/Talk_About_Feat_Jerryk/" title="슬릭 (SLEEQ) - Talk About (Feat. Jerry.k) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리의 믿음은 트위터 <br>트렌드 보다 얄팍해 <br>그래서 난 쉽게 믿곤 해 <br>그건 속는단 얘기랑 <br>다른 게 없으니 <br>난 또 do it again <br>걔가 인스타에 찍어 <br>올린 옷 죽이던데 <br>같은 셔츠에 다른 삶 <br>그뿐인걸 왜 <br>난 또 까먹고 멋진 <br>옷을 입었네 <br>사고 초조히 기다리는 <br>은행의 초인종 벨 <br>황금을 든 손은 <br>내 목젖을 눌러 <br>다 토해내고 난 다음에 <br>바닥에 굴러다니는 건 <br>다름아닌 내 천국의 주소 <br>기분 더러워도 <br>꽁돈처럼 줏어 <br>아 맞아 이건 동전에 <br>관한 얘기 <br>하늘 위로 튕겨내고 <br>잡아낸 뒤에 <br>어느 쪽인지 맞추면 <br>둘 중 하나겠지 <br>항상 그렇게 흘러가는걸 <br>알아냈지 <br>앞이 위를 보면 뒤는 <br>손바닥을 봐 <br>뒷면은 늘 존재해 <br>내 손바닥을 봐 <br>Act and react Merovingian <br>Karma를 안다 해도 <br>늘 때묻지 쉽게 <br>이건 축복이자 <br>저주의 메커니즘이야 <br>맞지 Ebbinghaus <br>난 가끔 여기에 <br>반항하는 척 <br>소리치면서 살아 rebel life <br>Ya know about me <br>I know about u <br>우리들은 거의 똑같단 걸 <br>난 알아봤어 <br>아닌 줄 알던 생각의 <br>무게를 달아놨어 <br>그 숫자를 이 가사에다 <br>잡아놨어 <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout money <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout fame <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout love <br>I am talkin' 'bout man <br>man man man <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout money <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout fame <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout love <br>I am talkin' 'bout man <br>man man man <br>Recycling sign처럼 <br>꼬릴 무는 지분과 <br>그 한가운데 쓰인 <br>3이라는 숫자 <br>그건 만들어질 때부터 <br>재활용이 불가능하단 뜻이지 <br>회장님 노시게 모시던 <br>비밀의 집을 봐 <br>높고 넓은 지붕관 달리 <br>밑바닥인 entertain 지불방식 <br>반의 반은 욕 못하지 <br>Uh 삶과 죽음의 경계에 <br>속세의 위로 증발할 <br>숫자의 개수를 맞추느라 <br>호흡기를 못 떼 <br>봐 어차피 다 잔고의 노예 <br>황금빛의 사슬을 목에서 <br>푼 다음 여기서 같이 <br>자유롭게 놀래 <br>단어 몇 개만 장전해 놓은 채 <br>부를 때가 올 거야 <br>Django의 노래 yeah <br>Free at last <br>Thank God almighty <br>we are free at last <br>어차피 우린 전부 <br>닝겐데스 <br>부은 두 발을 잠시 <br>여기 쉬게 해 <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout money <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout fame <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout love <br>I am talkin' 'bout man <br>man <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout money <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout fame <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout love <br>I am talkin' 'bout man <br>man <br>나는 안 믿어 <br>money fame love man <br>등불이 나가면 서로에게 <br>총을 겨누네 다같이 <br>또 알면서 금고로 <br>손을 뻗어대 어차피 <br>오늘 또는 내일 <br>Yeah I'm talkin' 'bout peace <br>그 잠깐의 고요 <br>그림자들이 오르가즘을 <br>맞고 지나는 몇 초 <br>즐기지는 마 이마에 <br>빨간 불이 번쩍하고 나면 <br>삶이 설명되는 것도 몇 초 <br>그 삶을 설명할 수 있을까 <br>생에 마지막 식사를 <br>정할 수 없는 <br>생에 마지막 순간에 <br>신을 용서할 수 없는 <br>생에 마지막 고함도 <br>세상 앞에선 적막이 <br>돼버리고만 기억들 <br>생에 아픔과 쾌락을 <br>나눈 하나님에 대해 <br>아님 하나님 앞에 창살로 <br>임하는 돈에 대해 <br>아님 탄생과 동시에 <br>입에 문 숟가락에 대해 <br>그 투박함에 대해 <br>순수한 답을 묻고 싶은데 <br>눈물로도 깜짝 아무도 <br>모르게 퍼트리는 투고도 <br>음 누군가 들의 당연하지 <br>않은 죽음으로도 <br>물어보는 것에 대해 <br>완벽한 답을 내려주는 <br>수고로움은 없네 <br>그저 두려워하는 것뿐 <br>두려움은 곧 숭배로 연결 <br>찬양하고 아름다워하고 <br>숫자를 적어 <br>찬양하고 아름다워하고 <br>숫자를 적어 <br>무한한 숨의 마침표마저 <br>숫자로 적혀 <br>Yeah <br>I am talkin' 'bout money <br>Yeah <br>I am talkin' 'bout fame <br>I am talkin' 'bout love <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout man <br>Never <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout man <br>Never <br>Yeah <br>I am talkin' 'bout money <br>I am talkin' 'bout fame <br>I am talkin' 'bout love <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout man <br>Never <br>I ain't talkin' 'bout man <br>Never <br>]]></content><category term="슬릭 (SLEEQ)" label="슬릭 (SLEEQ)"/><category term="Talk About (Feat. Jerry.k)" label="Talk About (Feat. Jerry.k)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬릭_SLEEQ/Whats_Going_On_Don_Malik_Solo/</id><title>슬릭 (SLEEQ) - What`s Going On (Don Malik Solo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:52:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:52:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AD_SLEEQ/Whats_Going_On_Don_Malik_Solo/" title="슬릭 (SLEEQ) - What`s Going On (Don Malik Solo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리의 아이디어는 <br>미디어가 주고 <br>대학 과제가 가져가 <br>뛰어가는 곳이 <br>어디였는지도 까먹고 <br>기억은 잠들어 <br>위험을 인지하는 건 <br>위헌이 돼 <br>작은 걸 의심하는 것 조차 <br>안되고 금지어는 늘어 <br>Real은 없이도 <br>현실에서 살다가 죽고 <br>앞뒤 없는 삶을 영화로 <br>그린 걸 돈 주고 <br>보러 갔다가 나오면 <br>앞뒤 꽉 막혀있는 풍경 <br>그걸 구경하듯 가만히 <br>쭈뼛거리느라 붐벼 <br>그 주변도 마찬가지여도 <br>아닌 듯이 숨쉬어 <br>돈은 중력 같은 거라고 <br>거짓말들 치는 걸 <br>믿음은 광신도의 상징이고 <br>미친 도시에서 <br>약 없이도 멀쩡히 <br>살아가고 있는 그들 속 <br>난 비정상 딱지 붙여지고 <br>다 속으로 비웃어 <br>내 시각은 굴절되고 <br>휘어지지 저 거울 속 <br>나와 비슷한 이에게 <br>악수를 건네면 <br>나오는 손은 왼손이지 <br>다른 에너지 <br>나와 같은 친군 없네 <br>낮은 괴롭기에 밤을 새웠지 <br>신문 옆에 작게 달려있는 <br>비아그라 광곤 날 못 세워줘 <br>맘대로 슬퍼하지도 못해 <br>노란 뱃지와 세월호 <br>넘어진 다음 일어나라고 <br>엄마에게 배웠어 <br>근데 지금 내가 어떤지도 몰라 <br>어서 날 깨워줘 <br>]]></content><category term="슬릭 (SLEEQ)" label="슬릭 (SLEEQ)"/><category term="What`s Going On (Don Malik Solo)" label="What`s Going On (Don Malik Solo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬릭_SLEEQ/Wonderland_Feat_Rico_JerryK/</id><title>슬릭 (SLEEQ) - Wonderland (Feat. Rico, Jerry.K) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:52:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:52:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A6%AD_SLEEQ/Wonderland_Feat_Rico_JerryK/" title="슬릭 (SLEEQ) - Wonderland (Feat. Rico, Jerry.K) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 유모차를 타는 <br>Michael Jackson who ride <br>like Paul Walker <br>Christopher Wallace <br>와 같이 flexin' <br>But I wanna live like <br>2pac Shakur <br>난 너희들과 왼손으로 <br>악수 하고 싶어 <br>이건 심장 얘기야 Hendrix <br>나의 검은 별들 <br>피부 얘기는 또 아냐 <br>그르치 David <br>나도 지금 무슨 일이 <br>벌어지는 지 모를 때가 <br>많지 뭐 그럼 <br>그때나 지금이나 사랑을 <br>찾아 다녀 날 토닥여줘 <br>Marvin 처럼 <br>내가 슬퍼서 울고 있을 땐 <br>가끔은 보라색 비가 오지 <br>Prince <br>그럴 때마다 부숴진 욕조에서 <br>편하게 쉬고 있고 싶어 <br>Whitney <br>걱정 마 Heron <br>술병 속으로 들어가는 건 <br>내 방식 아냐 <br>집을 싫어하긴 해도 <br>다른 게 있지 <br>I'm addicted at Winehouse <br>Phife 와 빛나는 도넛을 <br>입에 물지 <br>이 모든 건 그냥 다 <br>시간문제 <br>We gonna move on <br>up to the Mayfield <br>걱정 마 <br>I got u like James B <br>이 느낌 <br>이 기분이 내 안에 계속 쌓여가 <br>Make me feel alright <br>alright alright <br>내가 보고 느낀 대로 <br>이 느낌 <br>이 기분이 내 안에 계속 쌓여가 <br>Make me feel alright <br>alright alright <br>내가 듣고 느낀 대로 <br>이 느낌 <br>이 기분이 내 안에 계속 쌓여가 <br>Make me feel alright <br>alright alright <br>내가 보고 느낀 대로 <br>이 느낌 <br>이 기분이 내 안에 계속 쌓여가 <br>Make me feel alright <br>alright alright <br>내가 듣고 느낀 대로 <br>난 리듬이 돌면 먹던 <br>숟가락도 놓고 <br>혓바닥을 씻지 <br>여지껏 내가 다듬은 <br>flow 중에 젤 이쁜 걸 <br>보여주고 싶지 <br>나는 세상의 빛 <br>나와 같이한 이들이 <br>어둠을 걷지 <br>아니하게 하고파 <br>우리를 다치게 한 <br>악마의 구마를 위해 <br>머리를 밀지 <br>나의 걸음은 로제타 아니면 <br>하담의 것처럼 불안하지만 <br>멋대로 새긴 발자국의 <br>모양만으로도 <br>나를 알아보지 다 <br>내겐 이 걸음은 뭘 겨루는 <br>rap competition 이 아닌걸 <br>걸어가고픈 대로만 <br>또 가고픈 데로 가 <br>내 목표는 걷기왕이 아닌 <br>Gump <br>You know I mean <br>right 아는 사람은 알지 right <br>우린 각자 점처럼 존재하지만 <br>또 연결되고는 하지 right <br>나를 꿈 꾸는 사람이 있다면 <br>나는 바람을 맞으며 <br>차가운 눈밭을 걸어가 <br>못 알아 듣는다면 <br>눈동자를 더 보여 <br>내 스케치북은 커 <br>다슬이 것만큼이나 <br>Um-ha the way I breathe <br>Um-ha the way I breathe <br>달려가 거꾸로 더 <br>커다란 녀석을 물러 <br>치켜 뜬 두 눈만은 지키는 중 <br>You don't see us <br>but we see you <br>손목엔 metronome <br>심장을 뛰어 엇박자로 <br>알 놈만 알아 둬 <br>If you don't know <br>now you know <br>임마 <br>Um-ha the way I breathe <br>알 놈만 알아 둬 <br>If you don't know <br>now you know 임마 <br>이 느낌 <br>이 기분이 내 안에 계속 쌓여가 <br>Make me feel alright <br>alright alright <br>내가 보고 느낀 대로 <br>이 느낌 <br>이 기분이 내 안에 계속 쌓여가 <br>Make me feel alright <br>alright alright <br>내가 듣고 느낀 대로 <br>이 느낌 <br>이 기분이 내 안에 계속 쌓여가 <br>Make me feel alright <br>alright alright <br>내가 보고 느낀 대로 <br>이 느낌 <br>이 기분이 내 안에 계속 쌓여가 <br>Make me feel alright <br>alright alright <br>내가 듣고 느낀 대로 <br>alright alright <br>]]></content><category term="슬릭 (SLEEQ)" label="슬릭 (SLEEQ)"/><category term="Wonderland (Feat. Rico, Jerry.K)" label="Wonderland (Feat. Rico, Jerry.K)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/무감각/처음이었지/</id><title>무감각 - 처음이었지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:54:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:54:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AC%B4%EA%B0%90%EA%B0%81/%EC%B2%98%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%B4%EC%97%88%EC%A7%80/" title="무감각 - 처음이었지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그저 조용하던 나의 마음에 <br>머물다 갔던 너 <br>낯설기만 했던 그 시간들을 <br>감당하는 건 참 버거웠었지 <br>모든 게 서투르고 느린 나라서 <br>눈치 없이 너를 붙잡았었지 <br>하루하루 당연히 <br>널 떠올리던 습관조차 <br>버릴 방법을 몰랐어 <br>모두 다 다 처음이었지 <br>누군가의 말을 <br>의미 있게 담아본 건 <br>늦은 밤 돌아선 헤어짐에 <br>아쉬워했던 건 <br>그만큼 불안했던 건 <br>처음으로 다 그대로 <br>계속 난 너의 맘을 안고 싶은데 <br>너무 어리숙했던 나의 추억처럼 <br>다 묻는다는 게 <br>아직은 어려운 건가 봐 <br>괜찮다 위롤 하던 내 친구들은 <br>너를 나쁘다며 소릴 쳤었지 <br>그럼에도 여전히 <br>널 생각하는 바보처럼 <br>화를 내기도 했어 <br>모두 다 다 처음이었지 <br>누군가의 말을 <br>의미 있게 담아본 건 <br>늦은 밤 돌아선 헤어짐에 <br>아쉬워했던 건 <br>그만큼 불안했던 건 <br>처음으로 다 그대로 <br>계속 난 너의 맘을 안고 싶은데 <br>너무 어리숙했던 나의 추억처럼 <br>다 묻는다는 게 내겐 처음이라서 <br>어려운 건가 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="무감각" label="무감각"/><category term="처음이었지" label="처음이었지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양심/잊지말아요/</id><title>양심 - 잊지말아요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:54:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:54:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%8B%AC/%EC%9E%8A%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="양심 - 잊지말아요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침 이른 아침 깨면 <br>어두운 방 안 <br>홀로 있는 너 <br>매일 반복되는 이 삶을 <br>의미 없이 걷고 있는 너 <br>문득 거울에 비친 <br>초라한 모습에 <br>너무 힘들어 <br>울고 싶을 때 <br>잊지 말아요 <br>내가 있단 걸 <br>그대 혼자가 아니죠 <br>잊지 말아요 <br>그대를 사랑하는 나를 <br>내가 있단 걸 <br>잊지 말아요 <br>알고 있나요 <br>언제나 그대 곁에 <br>한 사람 <br>단 한 사람 <br>내가 있단 걸 <br>오늘 하루도 <br>아무런 기대 <br>생각도 없이 <br>그저 멍하니 <br>하늘만 보다가 <br>문득 거울에 비친 <br>초라한 모습에 <br>너무 힘들어 <br>울고 싶을 때 <br>잊지 말아요 <br>내가 있단 걸 <br>그대 혼자가 아니죠 <br>잊지 말아요 <br>그대를 사랑하는 나를 <br>내가 있단 걸 <br>잊지 말아요 <br>알고 있나요 <br>언제나 그대 곁에 <br>한 사람 <br>단 한 사람 <br>내가 있단 걸 <br>알고 있나요 <br>언제나 그대 곁에 <br>한 사람 <br>단 한 사람 <br>내가 있단 걸 <br>그 한 사람 잊지 말아요 <br>]]></content><category term="양심" label="양심"/><category term="잊지말아요" label="잊지말아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양심/하늘나라/</id><title>양심 - 하늘나라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:54:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:54:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%8B%AC/%ED%95%98%EB%8A%98%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC/" title="양심 - 하늘나라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날 부르던 그대 모습 <br>더 이상 볼 수 없죠 <br>날 반기던 그 목소리 <br>이젠 들을 수 없죠 <br>저기요 어디에 있나요 <br>나 아직 그대에게 <br>사랑을 말 못했는데 <br>날 어루만지던 손 길 <br>더 이상은 없겠죠 <br>날 바라보며 짓던 <br>그 미소는 어디에 <br>밤새 그대 생각하며 <br>잠 못 이루는 나죠 <br>함께 했던 추억에 잠겨 <br>매일 꿈만 꾸네요 <br>그대로 와 <br>다시 내게 안겨 <br>사랑스런 눈빛으로 <br>날 봐요 <br>]]></content><category term="양심" label="양심"/><category term="하늘나라" label="하늘나라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양심/눈비/</id><title>양심 - 눈비 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:54:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:54:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%8B%AC/%EB%88%88%EB%B9%84/" title="양심 - 눈비 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우연히 마주친 너의 눈빛엔 <br>어느새 비가 내리고 있네 <br>꼭 잡은 두 손 그 위에 내린 <br>너의 눈비가 내 마음 적시네 <br>영원할 것만 같았던 <br>너의 미소 보이지 않아 <br>처음 보는 그런 모습에 <br>나 조심스레 다가가 <br>지긋이 감은 그 두려운 마음 <br>홀로 헤매다 또 서성이네 <br>빗 속 길 잃어 앞이 캄캄해 <br>어느새 내가 너와의 <br>이 길 걷고 있네 <br>영원할 것 같던 너의 미소 <br>이젠 보이지 않아 <br>처음 보는 너의 그 모습에 <br>조심스레 다가가 <br>나란히 이 길 걷는 우리 <br>나의 향기가 너에게 우산이길 <br>내 손 꼭 잡고 보는 눈빛엔 <br>여전히 비가 내리고 있네 <br>]]></content><category term="양심" label="양심"/><category term="눈비" label="눈비"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양심/여기있어요/</id><title>양심 - 여기있어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:54:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:54:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%8B%AC/%EC%97%AC%EA%B8%B0%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="양심 - 여기있어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음 봐요 그대 무심한 눈빛 <br>나를 더 이상 <br>사랑하지 않는다 말하죠 <br>음음 <br>그대만을 바라는 나인데 왜 <br>왜 날 떠나요 <br>난 여전히 그대론데 <br>다시 그 눈빛으로 날 <br>바라봐 줄 순 없나요 <br>뒤돌아 나를 봐요 <br>떠나간 발걸음 조차 <br>붙잡을 수 없네요 <br>날 사랑하지 않는 그대여 <br>홀로 남겨진 길 위에서 <br>또 하염없이 눈물 짓지만 <br>이제 다시 내게 올 순 없나요 <br>마음 돌려 내게 와 줘요 제발 <br>떠나버린 것 다 알고 있지만 <br>그대 나 여기 있어요 <br>처음 봐요 그대 무심한 눈빛 <br>]]></content><category term="양심" label="양심"/><category term="여기있어요" label="여기있어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/B_SKIT/Cant_Live_Without_You/</id><title>B:SKIT - Can`t Live Without You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:54:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:54:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/B_SKIT/Cant_Live_Without_You/" title="B:SKIT - Can`t Live Without You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 홀로 남겨진 오늘 <br>차가운 방안에 누워 <br>그대와 부르던 그 노랠 부르네 <br>나만 혼자 느낀 사랑이 싫어 난 <br>너를 보내주던 날 <br>내 세상이 무너지는 맘 <br>La La 노랠 불러 이 맘을 담아 <br>어디서부터 잊어야 하나 <br>니 기억을 <br>I won't forget you <br>You don't wanna let me down <br>Can't live without you <br>Only one is you <br>Come back to me right now <br>Can't live without you <br>노랠 부르는 밤 <br>so so so so sorry <br>You drive me crazy <br>Oh baby how you doin' now <br>I've been fine without you <br>I don't know how <br>Always thinking bout you <br>every single day and night <br>Thinking bout the old times <br>when we used to fight <br>It’s been a while and <br>I know it’s been so long <br>But I'm livin my life <br>tryna keep it strong <br>It all goes down its worth a try <br>But it all falls apart baby goodbye <br>안되겠어 나는 널 놓을 수가 없어 <br>Heres music on and on <br>난 노랠 부르네 <br>다시 너를 부르네 <br>다시 노랠 부르네 Like insane <br>Can't live without you <br>Only one is you <br>Come back to me right now <br>Can't live without you <br>너를 부르네 <br>so so so so sorry <br>You drive me crazy <br>Can't live without you <br>Only one is you <br>Come back to me right now <br>Can't live without you <br>노랠 부르는 밤 <br>so so so so sorry <br>You drive me crazy <br>Can't live without you <br>Only one is you <br>Come back to me right now <br>Can't live without you <br>Please come back right now <br>so so so so sorry <br>Hey turn it up la la <br>]]></content><category term="B:SKIT" label="B:SKIT"/><category term="Can`t Live Without You" label="Can`t Live Without You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/B_SKIT/불놀이야/</id><title>B:SKIT - 불놀이야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:54:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:54:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/B_SKIT/%EB%B6%88%EB%86%80%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="B:SKIT - 불놀이야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You are mine <br>모두 지난 일이야 다 <br>슬프지도 기억나지도 않아 <br>모두 버렸어 <br>어쩌다 우연히 <br>나타나지 마 난 <br>후회하지 않아 나는 괜찮아 <br>You and me alright <br>눈물이 나와 <br>가슴을 쳐봐도 <br>젖어버린 눈을 감아도 <br>나는 정말 너를 용서할 수 없어 <br>불놀이야 사랑 그뿐이야 모두 <br>한마디 말조차 내겐 소중했는데 <br>웃기지마 사랑 내겐 없어 <br>이젠 날 놓아줘 <br>우리 사랑 Intro <br>지날수록 밑으로 <br>지나왔던 추억 기억 <br>파고들어 Central <br>내 맘 밖에서 <br>차갑게 떤 love song <br>가슴에 울려 Megaphone <br>미치도록 아프도록 <br>떠들어대는 Rap session <br>My love nation 눈물 쏙 <br>들어가는 분노의 Situation <br>I don’t wanna know <br>You are mine <br>모두 지난 일이야 다 <br>슬프지도 기억나지도 않아 <br>모두 버렸어 <br>어쩌다 우연히 <br>나타나지 마 난 <br>후회하지 않아 나는 괜찮아 <br>You and me alright <br>눈물이 나와 <br>가슴을 쳐봐도 <br>젖어버린 눈을 감아도 <br>나는 정말 너를 용서할 수 없어 <br>불놀이야 사랑 그뿐이야 모두 <br>한마디 말조차 내겐 소중했는데 <br>웃기지마 사랑 내겐 없어 <br>이젠 날 놓아줘 <br>멈춰버린 건 끝나버린 건 <br>나를 힘들게 하는 건 <br>눈물 흘리게 하는 건 <br>그건 사랑이 아냐 사랑이 아냐 <br>그래 그저 불놀이야 <br>넌 내겐 너라는 사랑 <br>모두다 다 모두 지워 버릴게 <br>불놀이야 사랑 그뿐이야 모두 <br>한마디 말조차 내겐 소중했는데 <br>웃기지마 사랑 내겐 없어 <br>이젠 날 놓아줘 <br>불놀이야 사랑 그뿐이야 모두 <br>한마디 말조차 내겐 소중했는데 <br>웃기지마 사랑 내겐 없어 <br>이젠 날 놓아줘 <br>]]></content><category term="B:SKIT" label="B:SKIT"/><category term="불놀이야" label="불놀이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/B_SKIT/빠삐용/</id><title>B:SKIT - 빠삐용 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:54:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:54:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/B_SKIT/%EB%B9%A0%EC%82%90%EC%9A%A9/" title="B:SKIT - 빠삐용 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Drop it <br>I Don't wanna be <br>저 빛은 바로 위 Yeah <br>낡은 사슬은 던지고 <br>Drop drop the beat <br>Drop drop the beat <br>Ah Whoo Clap 치고 <br>Follow me <br>나 삶에 대한 방식이 변했어 <br>빠삐용 <br>빠삐용 <br>Party 빠삐용 <br>Rock your body <br>빠 빠 빠 빠삐용 <br>Yeah 모두 <br>Huh 집중 여기 <br>We here <br>That's right <br>yes I'm him <br>내게서 부러움을 쓱 하고 <br>담아 결제는 필요 없어 <br>그냥 방해만 말아 <br>남녀노소 할 것 없이 <br>놀라움을 금치 못하는 <br>내 모습을 보자면 자체발광 <br>날 가둬두고 싶은 사람들 <br>미치고 환장 <br>But I'm sorry <br>난 잘 나가잖아 <br>어둠 속에 늘 찾아 <br>헤매었던 빛이었나 봐 <br>거울 위에 비친 <br>상실감에 젖은 바보같이 <br>반복되는 욕망 위에 <br>자신을 찾고 싶나 <br>똑바로 직진 바로 직진 <br>바로 직진 바로 직진 <br>빠삐용 <br>빠삐용 <br>Party 빠삐용 <br>Rock your body <br>빠 빠 빠 빠삐용 <br>신사 분들 자리로 돌아가시고 <br>어줍잖은 녀석들은 <br>내 앞에서 모양 빠지고 <br>고개를 까딱 대면 터지는 환호성 <br>내 역할은 꽤 익숙해 <br>오늘밤도 여심을 바로 저격 <br>빵야 빵야 비트가 울려 퍼질 땐 <br>어 가만가만 고만고만한 <br>녀석들은 불안불안 할 때가 된 듯 <br>멋으로 평가를 한다면 <br>나 빼고 다 Guilty 신고접수 <br>저 빛은 바로 위 포기는 바로 밑 <br>순간의 판단만이 내가 살아갈 길 <br>숨이 막혀 니 기억에 지쳐 <br>매일 밤 악몽에 잠 설쳐도 <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah <br>빠삐용 <br>빠삐용 <br>빠삐용 <br>Rock your body <br>빠 빠 빠 빠삐용 <br>]]></content><category term="B:SKIT" label="B:SKIT"/><category term="빠삐용" label="빠삐용"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더블팀_Doubleteam/Sunday_금토금토토토토/</id><title>더블팀 (Doubleteam) - Sunday (금토금토토토토) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:55:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:55:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%ED%8C%80_Doubleteam/Sunday_%EA%B8%88%ED%86%A0%EA%B8%88%ED%86%A0%ED%86%A0%ED%86%A0%ED%86%A0/" title="더블팀 (Doubleteam) - Sunday (금토금토토토토) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[헤롱헤롱 뒤집어진 <br>속을 부여잡고 일어나 <br>기억나는 게 하나도 없는 와중 <br>책상 위엔 주말 동안에 <br>미뤄놨던 일들이 가득 <br>시계의 바늘은 <br>이미 숫자 1을 가리켜 <br>날카로운 햇살이 눈을 괴롭혀 <br>감정 소모와 <br>소주를 소모하며 <br>도모했던 토요일 <br>밤에 친목은 over <br>일요일은 내 기분을 베려 놔 <br>그리고 내게 월요일을 데려와 <br>나와 침대는 한 몸 <br>마치 내게 여긴 편한 감옥 <br>지옥 같은 sunday morning <br>내 아까운 주말은 하늘로 <br>멈춰버려 시간아 가지 말고 <br>꿈이라면 절대로 깨지 말고 <br>금토금토토토토 everyday <br>I wanna 금토금토토토토 <br>What the hell its monday <br>눈 깜짝할새 <br>월요일은 코앞에 <br>도망가버린 <br>매 주말이 똑같애 <br>내 주말은 어디에 <br>where u at <br>어디에 <br>where u at boy <br>뭐 한 것도 없이 <br>일요일에 끝에서 <br>정신 차렸더니 <br>좀비처럼 멍하니 <br>이미 난 일요일에 <br>where u at <br>일요일에 <br>where u at boy <br>뒹굴 거리다 보니 <br>해는 숨고 저녁이 오지 <br>벌써부터 들려오는 듯한 <br>징그러운 알람 소리 <br>내일 출근해서 먹을 <br>점심밥을 벌써 고민 <br>시계바늘이 숫자 8을 <br>향해서 달려오니 <br>조촐하게 한잔하자는 <br>친구의 전화와 함께 <br>순간 이동한 내 두 발은 <br>이미 삐까뻔쩍 번화가 <br>어차피 월요일은 <br>매주 오는 거고 <br>이번 일요일은 방황할 뻔하다 <br>그런 생각도 잠시 <br>우린 아쉬운 몸을 <br>커피숍으로 옮겨 <br>멈춰버려 시간아 가지 말고 <br>꿈이라면 절대로 깨지 말고 <br>금토금토토토토 everyday <br>I wanna 금토금토토토토 <br>What the hell its monday <br>눈 깜짝할새 <br>월요일은 코앞에 <br>도망가버린 <br>매 주말이 똑같애 <br>내 주말은 어디에 <br>where u at <br>어디에 <br>where u at boy <br>뭐 한 것도 없이 <br>일요일에 끝에서 <br>정신 차렸더니 <br>좀비처럼 멍하니 <br>이미 난 일요일에 <br>where u at <br>일요일에 <br>where u at boy <br>일상이라는 저 바다로 난 <br>항해를 해 <br>지긋지긋한 월요병이란 파도가 <br>방해를 해 <br>달력 위에 빨간 숫자들과 <br>줄다리기를 해 <br>매번 감쪽하게 <br>잠복하네 Sunday <br>]]></content><category term="더블팀 (Doubleteam)" label="더블팀 (Doubleteam)"/><category term="Sunday (금토금토토토토)" label="Sunday (금토금토토토토)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iosir/Metro-놈/</id><title>Iosir - Metro-놈 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:55:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:55:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iosir/Metro-%EB%86%88/" title="Iosir - Metro-놈 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지난 밤 동안 <br>꿀같은 잠을 잤지 <br>좋은 꿈도 꿨어 <br>하지만 이제 <br>일어날 시간이 왔지 <br>시끄러운 알람 소리에 <br>이내 인내심은 <br>바닥이 났지 <br>사실 오래전부터 <br>울렸던 알람소리 <br>모른 척 귀를 막고 <br>눈을 감았었지 <br>그러는 사이 <br>꾸준히 가까워진 <br>햇빛은 창문을 <br>뚫고 들어와 <br>방안은 무섭고 <br>빠르게 밝아졌지 <br>가까스로 일어나 비틀비틀 <br>억지로 씻고나서 <br>인상 찌푸리고 <br>나갈 준비를 하며 <br>나오는 신음 <br>시름시름 앓듯 <br>무기력하게 신을 신고 <br>현관문을 밀어 <br>내 의지는 잊어 <br>그냥 몸을 실어 <br>아스팔트 위로 흐르는 <br>사람들 속으로 <br>난 눈을 감고도 <br>똑바로 갈 수 있어 <br>누구는 서있는 상태로 <br>잠을 잘 수도 있어 <br>이 순간 모두가 <br>버스와 물아일체 <br>거역할 수 없는 <br>거대한 힘을 가진 시스템 <br>무슨 옷을 입었든 <br>너와 난 너무 비슷해 <br>얘랑 쟤랑 내가 짓는 <br>표정도 너무 익숙해 <br>바뀌는 건 옷가지 <br>코스는 오직 한가지 <br>버스와 전철처럼 <br>같은 곳만 왔다가지 <br>무한 루프 훌라후프 <br>케이블 재방송 <br>시작의 환희는 냄새처럼 <br>무뎌져 버렸지 <br>똑딱거리는 메트로 놈 난 <br>똑딱거리는 메트로 놈 <br>무한 루프 훌라후프 <br>케이블 재방송 <br>시작의 환희는 냄새처럼 <br>무뎌져 버렸지 <br>배짱 좋게 여유 부리는 삶 <br>은 고사하고 당장 <br>내팔도 꼼짝못하게 <br>좁은 열차 안 <br>그마저도 못해 항상 <br>한 대쯤은 쿨하게 <br>떠나보내고 나서야 <br>그때 올라 타 <br>누굴 탓하겠어 <br>내가 짠 시간표 <br>모두가 내 잘못 <br>그날 잤던 늦잠도 <br>불만이 쌓여도 <br>결국 누워서 침뱉기 <br>그래 따지고 들어봤자 <br>결국 내가 문제지 <br>생각할 틈도 없이 <br>넘실 거리는 파도와 <br>관성에 휩쓸려버린 <br>몸은 어깨 넓이만 <br>한 자리 하나 잠깐도 못지켜 <br>답답한 탁한 공기 <br>종착점은 멀었어 <br>핸드폰 없었으면 <br>어떻게 버텼어 <br>앞에 뒷통수는 <br>아직 젖어있어 <br>어깨 너머로 <br>한강이 펼쳐져있어 <br>감상에 빠질 때쯤 <br>다시 어두워져있어 <br>이순간 모두가 <br>전철과 물아일체 <br>거역할 수 없는 <br>거대한 힘을 가진 시스템 <br>무엇을 보든 너와 난 <br>눈빛이 너무 비슷해 <br>얘랑 쟤랑 내가 <br>내리는 곳도 너무 익숙해 <br>바뀌는 건 옷가지 <br>코스는 오직 한가지 <br>버스와 전철처럼 <br>같은 곳만 왔다가지 <br>무한 루프 훌라후프 <br>케이블 재방송 <br>시작의 환희는 냄새처럼 <br>무뎌져 버렸지 <br>똑딱거리는 메트로 놈 난 <br>똑딱거리는 메트로 놈 <br>무한 루프 훌라후프 <br>케이블 재방송 <br>시작의 환희는 냄새처럼 <br>무뎌져 버렸지 <br>집으로 돌아가는 <br>길은 더 힘들어 <br>밝았던 태양도 <br>나처럼 축 늘어졌어 <br>난 그대로 인데 <br>그림자 길이만 더 늘어났어 <br>이대로 집에 들어가선 <br>씻고 먹고 이것저것하다 <br>시간 되면 이불덮고 <br>조용히 잠들지 <br>거푸집으로 찍어낸 듯한 하루의 <br>끝은 입다문 <br>비명소리로 가득히 <br>그러다 몽롱해지고 <br>fade out <br>바뀌는 건 옷가지 <br>코스는 오직 한가지 <br>버스와 전철처럼 <br>같은 곳만 왔다가지 <br>무한 루프 훌라후프 <br>케이블 재방송 <br>시작의 환희는 냄새처럼 <br>무뎌져 버렸지 <br>똑딱거리는 메트로 놈 난 <br>똑딱거리는 메트로 놈 <br>무한 루프 훌라후프 <br>케이블 재방송 <br>시작의 환희는 냄새처럼 <br>무뎌져 버렸지 <br>지난 밤 동안 <br>꿀같은 잠을 잤지 <br>좋은 꿈도 꿨어 <br>하지만 이제 <br>일어날 시간이 왔지 <br>시끄러운 알람 소리에 <br>이내 인내심은 <br>바닥이 났지 <br>사실 오래전부터 <br>울렸던 알람소리 <br>]]></content><category term="Iosir" label="Iosir"/><category term="Metro-놈" label="Metro-놈"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iosir/나한테_첫눈에_반했음_좋겠어/</id><title>Iosir - 나한테 첫눈에 반했음 좋겠어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:55:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:55:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Iosir/%EB%82%98%ED%95%9C%ED%85%8C_%EC%B2%AB%EB%88%88%EC%97%90_%EB%B0%98%ED%96%88%EC%9D%8C_%EC%A2%8B%EA%B2%A0%EC%96%B4/" title="Iosir - 나한테 첫눈에 반했음 좋겠어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[총이라도 한 발 당긴것처럼 <br>네 가슴에 묵직한거 <br>박아 놨으면 <br>즉 니가 내 목소리에 <br>첫눈에 반했으면 <br>하지만 그게 <br>말처럼 쉽지안다는걸 <br>알지만 이게 <br>내 최대에 마캐팅 <br>내가 뭐가 더 있어서 <br>뭘더 하겠니 <br>큰 맘 먹고 나왔어 <br>이 소개팅 <br>소개팅은 거의 <br>첫인상이 다가 아니겠니 <br>이 노래가 내가 <br>첫번째로 부르는 트랙이야 <br>그래 맞아 어떻게 <br>첫 술에 배 부르겠냐 <br>그래 시작이 반이지 <br>많이 머뭇거렸어 <br>이자리에 나오기까지 <br>떨리고 또 설레고 <br>막막 가슴이 <br>얌전히 있질 못해 <br>실수라도 저지를 것처럼 <br>자꾸 벌렁대는데 <br>애써 부끄럼 벗고 <br>옷을 걸쳤네 <br>기왕 이렇게 된거 <br>애프터 신청도 걸게 <br>나한테 uh huh <br>첫눈에 uh huh <br>반했음 uh huh <br>좋겠어 what <br>이게 말처럼 쉽지 않지 하지만 <br>나는 너를 나는 너를 <br>나한테 uh huh <br>첫눈에 uh huh <br>반했음 uh huh <br>좋겠어 what <br>이게 말처럼 쉽지 않지 하지만 <br>너도 나를 너도 나를 <br>어쩌면 내 목소리를 듣고 <br>별로라는 생각에 <br>자리를 뜨고 <br>다신 날 찾지 <br>않을지도 모르지만 그걸로 <br>완전 끝이나는게 아니란것 <br>만이라도 알아줬으면 해 <br>이렇게 벌써부터 <br>겁부터 먹었어 괜히 <br>사실 아무도 <br>신경쓰지 않을 테지 <br>아무말이나 빽빽 <br>써놓고 꽥꽥 질러데도 <br>쟤 왜 저래 하고 <br>욕도 않할 텐데 <br>뭐라도 해야 되겠어 <br>큰소리 떵떵친건 아니었어도 <br>이러다 먼지라도 되겠어 <br>시간은 빠르게 <br>쌓여가고 무거워 <br>내가 별 얘기를 다하죠 <br>긴장했나 봐요 <br>다음에 또 봐요 하면 <br>받아줄건 가요 <br>솔직히 사는거 초조하고 <br>자신없는거 당신도 <br>마찬가지 맞죠 <br>우린 많이 닳았어 <br>나한테 uh huh <br>첫눈에 uh huh <br>반했음 uh huh <br>좋겠어 what <br>이게 말처럼 쉽지 않지 하지만 <br>나는 너를 나는 너를 <br>나한테 uh huh <br>첫눈에 uh huh <br>반했음 uh huh <br>좋겠어 what <br>이게 말처럼 쉽지 않지 하지만 <br>너도 나를 너도 나를 <br>나도 너무 빠른 건 <br>좋아하지 않아 <br>너에게 한 걸음 더 <br>다가가는 걸 <br>절대 쉽게 생각 안해 <br>게다가 우린 <br>오늘 처음 봤는 걸 <br>서로 오랜 시간 <br>동안 각자의 <br>생각과 삶을 갖고 <br>살다 만난 우리 <br>천천히 가자 천천히 <br>hey 천천히 천천히 baby <br>나한테 uh huh <br>첫눈에 uh huh <br>반했음 uh huh <br>좋겠어 what <br>이게 말처럼 쉽지 않지 하지만 <br>나는 너를 나는 너를 <br>나한테 uh huh <br>첫눈에 uh huh <br>반했음 uh huh <br>좋겠어 what <br>이게 말처럼 쉽지 않지 하지만 <br>너도 나를 너도 나를 <br>]]></content><category term="Iosir" label="Iosir"/><category term="나한테 첫눈에 반했음 좋겠어" label="나한테 첫눈에 반했음 좋겠어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이백길/아저씨라고_부르지마라/</id><title>이백길 - 아저씨라고 부르지마라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:56:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:56:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B0%B1%EA%B8%B8/%EC%95%84%EC%A0%80%EC%94%A8%EB%9D%BC%EA%B3%A0_%EB%B6%80%EB%A5%B4%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%88%EB%9D%BC/" title="이백길 - 아저씨라고 부르지마라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아저씨라고 부르지 마라 <br>마음은 영원한 20대 <br>스냅 모자에 반바지 입고 <br>오늘도 길을 나선다 <br>아저씨라고 부르지 마라 <br>아직은 총각이란다 <br>아직도 살아갈 날 창창하단다 <br>나는야 젊은 오빠다 <br>머리 숱 빠졌다고 욕하지 마라 <br>얼굴은 팽팽하단다 <br>나도 이젠 살아가련다 <br>나만의 젊은 인생을 <br>나만의 젊은 인생을 <br>아저씨라고 부르지 마라 <br>나는야 언제나 20대 <br>선글라스에 청바지 입고 <br>오늘도 길을 나선다 <br>아저씨라고 부르지 마라 <br>여지껏 총각이란다 <br>앞으로 살아갈 날 창창하단다 <br>오빠만 믿으면 된다 <br>걸그룹 모른다고 욕하지 마라 <br>멤버 중 한 명은 안다 <br>나도 이젠 살아가련다 <br>화려한 나의 인생을 <br>내 개그 재미없다 욕하지 마라 <br>잠잘 때 빵빵 터진다 <br>나도 이젠 살아가련다 <br>빵빵한 나의 인생을 <br>빵빵한 나의 인생을 <br>빵빵한 나의 인생을 <br>]]></content><category term="이백길" label="이백길"/><category term="아저씨라고 부르지마라" label="아저씨라고 부르지마라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/미드나잇_트립/Fall_4_Me/</id><title>미드나잇 트립 - Fall 4 Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:56:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:56:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AF%B8%EB%93%9C%EB%82%98%EC%9E%87_%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%BD/Fall_4_Me/" title="미드나잇 트립 - Fall 4 Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look at my dark eyes <br>Look at my pink lips <br>And come to me <br>and talk to me <br>Listen to my breath <br>Listen to my song <br>And come close to me <br>and be with me <br>Every day comes <br>every day goes <br>but you don't move at all <br>The lights in my eyes <br>are telling you <br>what is in my mind <br>Turn around look at me <br>Contact my dark eyes <br>And come to me <br>and fall for me <br>Listen to my breath again <br>Listen to my song again <br>And come close to me <br>and be with me <br>Every day comes <br>every day goes <br>but you don't move at all <br>The lights in my eyes <br>are telling you <br>what is in my mind <br>Every day comes <br>every day goes <br>but you don't move at all <br>The lights in my eyes <br>are telling you <br>what is in my mind <br>Every day comes <br>every day goes <br>but you don't move at all <br>The lights in my eyes <br>are telling you <br>what is in my mind <br>]]></content><category term="미드나잇 트립" label="미드나잇 트립"/><category term="Fall 4 Me" label="Fall 4 Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MiC_LOWRY/Oh_Lord_Swifta_Beater_Remix_Feat_Sneakbo_Boss_Man_Birdie_Tempa__Double_S/</id><title>MiC LOWRY - Oh Lord (Swifta Beater Remix) (Feat. Sneakbo, Boss Man Birdie, Tempa &amp; Double S) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-15T23:57:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-15T23:57:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MiC_LOWRY/Oh_Lord_Swifta_Beater_Remix_Feat_Sneakbo_Boss_Man_Birdie_Tempa__Double_S/" title="MiC LOWRY - Oh Lord (Swifta Beater Remix) (Feat. Sneakbo, Boss Man Birdie, Tempa &amp; Double S) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>There's just way too many temptations, oh Lord <br><br>T t tempted <br>I got my eyes on a peng ting <br>Take a look at her bredrins <br>They're all looking like a blessing <br>Get her in the bed, that's pending <br>Spread out your legs, come stretch it <br>She said be calm, I'm reckless <br>When I whack that, gyal get breathless <br>Tap, tap, tap, tap it up <br>I don't hit girls, but slap it up <br>Grab it up, let me come mash it up <br>No knife, but I still jook it up <br>Like wow, wow, wow, wow <br>I make good girls turn foul <br>Front way, then turn around <br>I ain't talking London when she's down the south <br><br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>There's just way too many temptations, oh Lord <br><br>Oh Lord, oh Lord <br>You can get this work, babe, no charge <br>Give me the thick girls, no margs <br>When I do my ting, no holds barred <br>I make girls wet like coastguard <br>I only go hard or I go yard <br>Tell your girlfriend she could costar <br>Man are like calm but I so can't <br>Mad ting, sad ting <br>Big back tings I'm attracting <br>Thick thighs, so distracting <br>Try tempt man, girl, stop acting <br>I don't play games, no ramping <br>All nighters, man's vamping <br>Stab it out but I ain't shanking <br>Turn a good girl straight to a bad ting <br><br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>There's just way too many temptations, oh Lord <br><br>Temptations, yeah <br>It's only right cuh my nickname Tempa <br>Bad yout, went from school to a centre <br>And still make ya girl wan' dance in the centre <br>Bare MC's wanna take man's flow <br>And run with the ting like I didn't invent it <br>It's cool though, tell them the king's come back <br>And just make sure they got man's drinks when we enter <br>Sexy gyal that's wan' whine with it <br>Tell her, tell her tek time with it <br>Ten out of ten, you're a diamond it <br>The way your body move, it's a crime, init <br>It's only right that you fuel temptation <br>Wanna know if you're single or taken <br>'Cause right now, if you're looking at a replacement <br>There's just way too many temptations, oh Lord <br><br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>I can feel it coming in the air tonight, oh Lord <br>When the rhythm hits, I'm not afraid to die <br>There's just way too many temptations, oh Lord <br><br>Ayy, ayy, it's the gyal dem protein <br>Hope you got enough stamina for your whole team <br>She really thought that I was cool when she phoned me <br>'Cause I'm a good brudda but I beat so mean <br>Uh, she should call me Swifta <br>Cuh the beating game is way off the Richter <br>Yeah, I drew her, but you'll never see her in the picture <br>She stays low, you will never see her on Insta <br>No, she don't do it for the 'Gram <br>But when I come through, yeah, she do it for the man <br>She can't wait for the farrda to land <br>Man, I do it how they didn't wanna do it cause I can <br>I'm like Eminem with it, you won't understand <br>You could die, though, if you play with the gang <br>I came for twelve figures, I came with a plan <br>Fashion week, yeah, I might fly to Milan <br><br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>Break you off, while I break you off <br>Don't you run from me while I take it off <br>Take it off, take it off <br>Tell me your name while I break you off <br>There's just way too many temptations, oh Lord]]></content><category term="MiC LOWRY" label="MiC LOWRY"/><category term="Oh Lord (Swifta Beater Remix) (Feat. Sneakbo, Boss Man Birdie, Tempa &amp; Double S)" label="Oh Lord (Swifta Beater Remix) (Feat. Sneakbo, Boss Man Birdie, Tempa &amp; Double S)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Everglow/</id><title>Starset - Everglow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Everglow/" title="Starset - Everglow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You come in waves <br>Till you're all I know <br>Then you fade away <br>Into nothing <br>Weighed down by dark matter inside <br>You leave me frozen <br>You leave me froze in time <br>In your <br><br>Everglow <br>You'll never know <br>The beauty I see when you open your shadows <br>Everglow <br>They'll never know <br>The worlds that I see in the darkness you don't show <br><br>Falling through a landslide <br>Feeling like the first time I felt you <br>Caught inside the field lines <br>That pull me to the land mines inside you <br>Black hole eyes won't gaze now <br>Drawn in just the same <br>You leave me frozen <br>You leave me frozen inside <br><br>Everglow <br>You'll never know <br>The beauty I see when you open your shadows <br>Everglow <br>They'll never know <br>The worlds that I see in the darkness you don't show <br>x2 <br><br>Come <br>I'll show every ghost in me <br>Take my pain into you]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Everglow" label="Everglow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Telepathic/</id><title>Starset - Telepathic - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Telepathic/" title="Starset - Telepathic - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And if I had my way <br>I would run to the rescue <br>It never works that way <br>When you call a bluff <br><br>Oh, all the fools rush in <br>It's a battle to surround you <br>And all the fools want in <br>But I'm not giving up <br><br>I don't wanna let you go <br>But I can't stand to watch this <br>I don't wanna let you know <br>But you can read my mind <br><br>I feel it all the time <br>Felt it all around you <br>You had me under spell right from the start <br>I don't have a telepathic heart <br>Telepathic <br><br>Blind, I fall into the line <br>That's waiting just to get you <br>But I don't ever know just what we are <br>I don't have a telepathic heart <br>Telepathic <br><br>Look inside my brain <br>You'd know what I want before I tell you <br>Give me the words to say to make it enough <br>Don't want your star crossed fate <br>You are the sun, I am the full moon <br>Don't leave me lost in vain <br>I can be what you want <br><br>I don't wanna let you go <br>But I can't stand to watch this <br>I don't wanna let you know <br>But you can read my mind <br><br>I feel it all the time <br>Felt it all around you <br>You had me under spell right from the start <br>I don't have a telepathic heart <br>Telepathic <br><br>Blind, I fall into the line <br>That's waiting just to get you <br>But I don't ever know just what we are <br>I don't have a telepathic heart <br>Telepathic <br>Telepathic <br>Telepathic <br><br>And you always turn away <br>Back to the start where I break through <br>You can run, you can run away <br>I will wait in the dark for you <br>Should've never felt this way <br>Cause you're the sun and I'm just a moon <br>I'm in the dark 'till you light the way <br>Cause I'm see through <br>You can read my mind <br><br>I feel it all the time <br>Felt it all around you <br>You had me under spell right from the start <br>I don't have a telepathic heart <br>Telepathic <br><br>Blind, I fall into the line <br>That's waiting just to get you <br>But I don't ever know just what we are <br>I don't have a telepathic heart <br>Telepathic <br>Telepathic <br>Telepathic]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Telepathic" label="Telepathic"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Monster/</id><title>Starset - Monster - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Monster/" title="Starset - Monster - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Under the knife I surrendered <br>The innocence your's to consume <br>You cut it away <br>And you filled me up with hate <br>Into the silence you sent me <br>Into the fire consumed <br>You thought I'd forget <br>But it's always in my head <br><br>You're the pulse in my veins <br>You're the war that I wage <br>Can you change me <br>Can you change me <br>You're the love that I hate <br>You're the drug that I take <br>Will you cage me <br>Will you cage me <br>You're the pulse in my veins <br>You're the war that I wage <br>Can you change me <br>Can you change me <br>From the monster you made me <br>The monster you made me <br><br>This is the world you've created <br>The product of what I've become <br>My soul and my youth <br>Seems it's all for you to use <br>If I could take back the moment <br>I'd let you get under my skin <br>Relent or resist <br>Seems the monster always wins <br><br>You're the pulse in my veins <br>You're the war that I wage <br>Can you change me <br>Can you change me <br>You're the love that I hate <br>You're the drug that I take <br>Will you cage me <br>Will you cage me <br>You're the pulse in my veins <br>You're the war that I wage <br>Can you change me <br>Can you change me <br>From the monster you made me <br>The monster you made me <br><br>My heart's an artifice, a decoy soul <br>I lift you up and then I let you go <br>I've made an art of digging shallow holes <br>I'll drop the tiniest seed and watch it grow <br>My heart's an artifice, a decoy soul <br>Who knew the emptiness could be so cold <br>I've lost the parts of me that make me whole <br>I am the darkness <br>I'm a monster <br><br>You're the pulse in my veins <br>You're the war that I wage <br>Can you change me <br>Can you change me <br>You're the love that I hate <br>You're the drug that I take <br>Will you cage me <br>Will you cage me <br>You're the pulse in my veins <br>You're the war that I wage <br>Can you change me <br>Can you change me <br>From the monster you made me <br>The monster you made me <br>The monster you made me <br>The monster you made me]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Monster" label="Monster"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Unbecoming/</id><title>Starset - Unbecoming - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Unbecoming/" title="Starset - Unbecoming - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I lost myself into the night <br>And I flew higher <br>Than I had ever <br>But I still felt small <br>I clipped my wings and fell from flight <br>To open water <br>And floated farther <br>Away from myself <br><br>And I swam in the wakes of imposters <br>Just to feel what it's like to pretend <br>There's no dreams in the lakes only monsters <br>And the monsters are my only friends <br><br>They're all that I was <br>And never could be <br><br>Eyes in the dead still water <br>Tried but it pushed back harder <br>Cauterized and atrophied <br>This is my unbecoming <br>Knives in the backs of martyrs <br>Lives in the burning fodder <br>Cauterized and atrophied <br>This is my unbecoming <br><br>You found me drifted out to sea <br>It's automatic <br>It's telepathic <br>You always knew me <br>And you laugh as I search for a harbor <br>As you point where the halo had been <br>But the light in your eyes has been squandered <br>There's no angel in you in the end <br><br>And all that I was <br>I've left behind me <br><br>Eyes in the dead still water <br>Tried but it pushed back harder <br>Cauterized and atrophied <br>This is my unbecoming <br>Knives in the backs of martyrs <br>Lives in the burning fodder <br>Cauterized and atrophied <br>This is my unbecoming <br><br>Now I wait <br>This metamorphosis <br>All that is left is the change <br>Selfish fate <br>I think you made me this <br>Under the water I wait <br><br>Eyes in the dead still water <br>Tried but it pushed back harder <br>Cauterized and atrophied <br>This is my unbecoming <br>Knives in the backs of martyrs <br>Lives in the burning fodder <br>Cauterized and atrophied <br>This is my unbecoming]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Unbecoming" label="Unbecoming"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Bringing_It_Down/</id><title>Starset - Bringing It Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Bringing_It_Down/" title="Starset - Bringing It Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I saw it in your eyes <br>I saw the creature deep inside <br>You opened up your cage <br>Pathetic insect <br>Drawn to flame <br>I'm falling apart <br>Inside your holographic heart <br>Lost souls dancing <br>And now the lie's collapsing <br><br>There's something inside you that isn't right <br>There's something that haunts your dreams at night <br>There's something that you have lost <br>And you're bringing it down <br>You're bringing it down <br>On top of us <br><br>I see the crimson thief <br>Hanging on heartstrings <br>Dripping bleach <br>Victim with hands in sleeves <br>Your lying swan sings <br>As I reach <br>I'm falling apart <br>Inside your holographic heart <br>Lost souls dancing <br>And now the lie's collapsing <br><br>There's something inside you that isn't right <br>There's something that haunts your dreams at night <br>There's something that you have lost <br>And you're bringing it down <br>You're bringing it down <br>On top of us <br><br>Silly me <br>I thought I had it <br>I came so close this time <br>I knew your heart was plastic <br>I still thought I could make it mine <br>Surrender you my mind <br>Your creature is inside <br>Devouring me alive <br><br>There's something inside you that isn't right <br>There's something that haunts your dreams at night <br>There's something that you have lost <br>And you're bringing it down <br>You're bringing it down <br>On top of us]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Bringing It Down" label="Bringing It Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Last_To_Fall/</id><title>Starset - Last To Fall - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Last_To_Fall/" title="Starset - Last To Fall - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And I fly <br>Further away <br>Than I've ever been before <br>It's safe to say <br>This sky <br>Is lonely and grey <br>But every night I feel your gravity waves <br><br>And the world is cold <br>But it's beautiful <br>I wish you were here now <br>I miss your soul <br>But you lost your light <br>When the darkness called <br>But I stand here waiting <br><br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br><br>And I fly <br>Above the enslaved <br>My soul is burning <br>Like an earth reclaimed <br>And I try <br>A final crusade <br>This world is changing <br>But I'm still the same <br><br>And will you be bold <br>Will you lose control <br>I could never desert you <br>I could never let go <br>If you fall in line <br>And the zenith calls <br>I'm standing waiting <br><br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br><br>It's your magnetic hold <br>A gravity pull <br>I can feel you in waves <br>When your melody comes <br>It falls from above <br>I will not be afraid <br><br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall <br>The last to fall]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Last To Fall" label="Last To Fall"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Back_To_The_Earth/</id><title>Starset - Back To The Earth - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Back_To_The_Earth/" title="Starset - Back To The Earth - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And the world <br>Pull me high, far above, wicked skies <br>Set me free <br>Set alive <br>I become, satellite <br><br>Isolated, I succumb to the weight of the world <br>Separated, I fall from the sky <br><br>Is this death or rebirth <br><br>Falling back to the earth <br><br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling <br><br>I ignite, engine call <br>Jettison, all I know <br><br>Isolated, I succumb to the weight of the world <br>Separated, I fall from the sky <br><br>Is this death or rebirth <br><br>Falling back to the earth <br><br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br>Falling, falling <br><br>Fall <br>Fall <br>Fall <br>Fall]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Back To The Earth" label="Back To The Earth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Gravity_Of_You/</id><title>Starset - Gravity Of You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Gravity_Of_You/" title="Starset - Gravity Of You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a silencing <br>As the machine arrives here <br>I feel it pulling me <br>I feel the past that's died there <br>I hear it calling me <br>You can come alive here <br>I hear it beckoning <br>Until I am inside <br><br>Riding the horizon <br>Falling into you <br>Feel the vessel tighten <br>I feel you pull me through <br>A new world is breaking <br>Your heart is unveiling <br>Breaking into pieces <br>In the gravity of you <br><br>I see the empty dreams <br>Race across the sky here <br>I see energy streams <br>Where the ashes lie here <br>I feel you here with me <br>When all the hope has died here <br>It's boring holes in me <br>Enough to get inside <br><br>Riding the horizon <br>Falling into you <br>Feel the vessel tighten <br>I feel you pull me through <br>A new world is breaking <br>Your heart is unveiling <br>Breaking into pieces <br>In the gravity of you <br><br>To fall in the star is to be nothingness <br>To escape is to be empty <br>Fall into the star and then we won't exist <br>Or escape into the nothing <br>x2 <br><br>Your sky <br>The beauty alone is worth it <br>I will risk it all to own it <br><br>Riding the horizon <br>Falling into you <br>Feel the vessel tighten <br>I feel you pull me through <br>A new world is breaking <br>Your heart is unveiling <br>Breaking into pieces <br>In the gravity of you]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Gravity Of You" label="Gravity Of You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Into_The_Unknown/</id><title>Starset - Into The Unknown - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Into_The_Unknown/" title="Starset - Into The Unknown - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dislocated <br>Self is fading <br>Falling back from what I was <br>Flying through existence <br>Tumbling towards a burning sun <br>Something screaming in the distance <br>Telling me to come <br>It's calling me <br><br>Are you out there waiting <br>I can hear it calling <br>It takes more than eyes to see <br>It's out in the energy but <br>I can hear it calling <br><br>Take the path less traveled <br>Face the darkness on my own <br>Into the starlight will I go <br>Until the end I will roam <br>Fate itself unraveled <br>Make the emptiness my home <br>Into the starlight will I go <br>Soaring into the unknown <br><br>Suffocated <br>Voice has faded <br>Is this real or in my mind <br><br>I can hear it calling <br>It takes more than eyes to see <br>It's out in the energy but <br>I can hear it calling <br><br>Take the path less traveled <br>Face the darkness on my own <br>Into the starlight will I go <br>Until the end I will roam <br>Fate itself unraveled <br>Make the emptiness my home <br>Into the starlight will I go <br>Soaring into the unknown]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Into The Unknown" label="Into The Unknown"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Starlight/</id><title>Starset - Starlight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Starlight/" title="Starset - Starlight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stardust <br>In you and in me <br>Fuse us <br>Into unity <br>Primeval <br>We're coupled <br>Born from the universe <br>Farewell <br>The void is calling <br>Don't fear <br>For futures and dreams <br>They're fleeting, retreating <br>It's ok <br>I promise <br><br>I don't know what to say <br>But I'm going to want you till the stars evaporate <br>We're only here for just a moment in the light <br>One day it shines for us the next we're in the night <br>So say the word and I'll be running back to find you <br>A thousand armies won't stop me I'll break through <br>I'll soar the endless skies for only one sight <br>Of your starlight <br><br>Tell me <br>Just tell me to stay <br>I'll turn <br>I won't look away <br>I'll stay here <br>I'll never go but you don't feel the same <br>Farewell <br>Farewell and godspeed <br>Light years <br>Between you and me <br>I'm fading <br>Your beauty conquers the darkness <br><br>At night the earth will rise <br>And I'll think of you each time I watch from distant skies <br>Whenever stars go down and galaxies ignite <br>I'll think of you each time they wash me in their light <br>And I'll fall in love with you again <br>I will find you <br>A thousand armies won't stop me I'll break through <br>I'll soar the endless skies for only one sight of your starlight <br><br>Don't leave me lost here forever <br>Show me your starlight and pull me through <br>Don't leave me lost here forever <br>I need your starlight and pull me through <br>Bring me back to you]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Starlight" label="Starlight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Ricochet/</id><title>Starset - Ricochet - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:00:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:00:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Ricochet/" title="Starset - Ricochet - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And we were bold <br>Over the world <br>We were flying through the satellites <br>We had ahold <br>Of the lightning strikes <br>When we should have been afraid of heights <br>And I was trying just to get you <br>And now I'm dying to forget you <br>Cause I knew I couldn't catch you <br>So I left the sky <br>And I fell behind <br><br>We were one in the same <br>Running like moths to the flame <br>You'd hang on every word I'd say <br>But now they only ricochet <br>We were falling away <br>You left me with a bittersweet taste <br>But when I send my heart your way <br>It bounces off the walls you made <br>Ricochet <br><br>If I was whole <br>I'd turn right now <br>I'd forget it and just walk away <br>Cause I've been told <br>That I'm dragging it out <br>But I've been dying just to see your face <br>And all I wanted was to say goodbye <br>Into the fortress and you're stuck behind <br>And in the silence now I realize <br>That after all I built the wall <br><br>We were one in the same <br>Running like moths to the flame <br>You'd hang on every word I'd say <br>But now they only ricochet <br>You were falling away <br>You left me with a bittersweet taste <br>But when I send my heart your way <br>It bounces off the walls you made <br>Ricochet <br><br>All these broken souls <br>They never make me whole <br>They don't, they don't know my heart <br>They don't know my heart <br><br>All these broken souls <br>Each one more beautiful <br>They don't, they don't know my heart <br>They don't know my heart <br><br>I'll send out my soul <br>To worlds more beautiful <br>But they won't, they won't know my heart <br>It's the darkest part <br><br>We were one in the same <br>Running like moths to the flame <br>You'd hang on every word I'd say <br>But now they only ricochet <br>You were falling away <br>You left me with a bittersweet taste <br>But when I send my heart your way <br>It bounces off the walls you made <br>Ricochet]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Ricochet" label="Ricochet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Die_For_You/</id><title>Starset - Die For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:01:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:01:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Die_For_You/" title="Starset - Die For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will run alone tonight <br>Without you by my side <br>I guess you had a place you had to get to <br>I know your eyes <br>I know inside <br>The walls you hide behind <br>And I saw the truth inside the real you <br>Because I know you're lost when you run away <br>Into the same black holes and black mistakes <br>Taking all my will just to run alone <br>When are you coming home <br><br>Even if the sky does fall <br>Even if they take it all <br>There's no pain that I won't go through <br>Even if I have to die for you <br><br>And when all the fires burn <br>When everything is overturning <br>There's no thing that I won't go through <br>Even if I have to die for you <br><br>One day the earth will open wide <br>And I'll follow you inside <br>Cause the only hell I know is without you <br>Some day when galaxies collide <br>We'll be lost on different skies <br>I will send my rocket ship to find you <br>Because I know you're lost when you run away <br>Into the same black holes and black mistakes <br>Taking all my will just to run alone <br>Until I bring you home <br><br>Even if the sky does fall <br>Even if they take it all <br>There's no pain that I won't go through <br>Even if I have to die for you <br><br>And when all the fires burn <br>When everything is overturning <br>There's no thing that I won't go through <br>Even if I have to die for you <br><br>And if the sun grows cold along the way <br>And if the stars don't line to light the way <br>And when you fall away and crash back down below <br>I'll search the skies for you and I'll follow <br>I'll be in your afterglow <br>And I'll bring you home <br><br>Even if the sky does fall <br>Even if they take it all <br>I can't see but I'll follow you <br>Even if I'd die <br><br>And when all the fires burn <br>When everything is overturning <br>There's no thing that I won't go through <br>Even if I have to die for you]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Die For You" label="Die For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Frequency/</id><title>Starset - Frequency - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:01:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:01:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Frequency/" title="Starset - Frequency - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was scanning through the skies <br>And missed the static in your eyes <br>Something blocking your reception <br>It's distorting our connection <br>With the distance amplified <br>Was it all just synthesized <br>And now the silence screams that you are gone <br>You've tuned me out <br>I've lost your frequency <br><br>There's something here that's broken <br>There's something here with no end <br>It's paralyzed <br>It's in your eyes <br>Cause I can feel your soul fade <br>I can feel your heart change <br>It falls out of phase with mine <br>While you oscillate inside <br>Or is it only in my head <br><br>Left inside a half life <br>Irradiated insides <br>These memories <br>They never leave <br>I bared my soul for you and all I got was static <br>My heart was bulletproof till you took off the jacket <br><br>There's something here that's broken <br>There's something here with no end <br>It's paralyzed <br>It's in your eyes <br>Cause I can feel your soul fade <br>I can feel your heart change <br>It falls out of phase with mine <br>While you oscillate inside <br>Or is it only in my head <br><br>Castaway <br>My cries are blocked by the horizon <br>Suffocate <br>I was doing this all for you <br><br>I'm in the shallows <br>Stuck in the gallows <br>I tried to save you now I'm swallowed <br>You wanted war <br>I am the war <br>I alone]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Frequency" label="Frequency"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Satellite/</id><title>Starset - Satellite - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:01:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:01:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Starset/Satellite/" title="Starset - Satellite - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Darkening skies, coming this way <br>Falling behind, into nothing <br><br>If you lead, I will follow <br>A thousand miles away <br>I will be, your Apollo <br>Alone in outer space <br><br>Satellite, shine on me tonight <br>I'll feel your gravity, I'll stay and never leave <br>My satellite, I'm here tonight <br>Shine your light and set me free <br>Take the darkness out of me <br>Shine on me <br><br>Shine on me <br><br>Blinded I wait, end if forming <br>You are my fate, give me warning <br><br>If you lead, I will follow <br>A thousand miles away <br>I will be, your Apollo <br>Alone in out <br><br>Satellite, shine on me tonight <br>I'll feel your gravity, I'll stay and never leave <br>My satellite, I'm here tonight <br>Shine your light and set me free <br>Take the darkness out of me <br>Shine on me <br><br>Shine on me <br><br>Fall across the emptiness, and walk the night <br>Deserves the silence in the dark, and left behind <br>I seek the stars above the world to be the guide <br>They are pale against the light in your eyes <br><br>In your eyes <br><br>And once I pass I know that you are too late <br>But I can feel you coursing through beyond the space <br>Just send your energy to me and I'll push on <br>Send your signal out, and bring me back to you <br><br>Satellite, shine on me tonight <br>I'll feel your gravity, I'll stay and never leave <br>My satellite, I'm here tonight <br>Shine your light and set me free <br>Take the darkness out of me <br>Shine on me <br><br>Shine on me]]></content><category term="Starset" label="Starset"/><category term="Satellite" label="Satellite"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/A_Little_Bit_Of_Love_Is_All_It_Takes_A_Cappella/</id><title>New Edition - A Little Bit Of Love (Is All It Takes) (A Cappella) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:02:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:02:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/A_Little_Bit_Of_Love_Is_All_It_Takes_A_Cappella/" title="New Edition - A Little Bit Of Love (Is All It Takes) (A Cappella) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Woo ooh ooh ooh <br><br>You say you want to be the one I need <br>You say you want to be the one for me <br>You say you want to be the one I need <br>But then you go and act so crazy <br><br>You say you never want to let me go <br>You say you want to be the one I hold <br>You say you never want to let me go <br>But then you go and leave me lonely <br><br>If you want to make things right <br>Love can make a way <br>If you want to take the time <br>Act like what you say, yeah <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>You want to be the one who makes me shy <br>The one who makes me laugh and makes me cry <br>You want to be the one to change my life <br>Then maybe you should treat me kindly <br><br>You want to make believe you never left <br>You want to make believe I never wept <br>You said you'd never ever leave again <br>Oh, baby, won't you quit pretendin' <br><br>If you want to make things right <br>Love can make a way <br>And if you want to take the time <br>Act like what you say, yeah <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely, oh <br><br>Oh <br><br>Oh, if you want to make things right <br>Love can make a way <br>And if you want to take the time <br>Act like what you say, yeah <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is all it takes Little bit of love <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br><br>Girl, you got to make things right <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>Girl, we got to take our time <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="A Little Bit Of Love (Is All It Takes) (A Cappella)" label="A Little Bit Of Love (Is All It Takes) (A Cappella)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Count_Me_Out_Single_Ver/</id><title>New Edition - Count Me Out (Single Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:02:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:02:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Count_Me_Out_Single_Ver/" title="New Edition - Count Me Out (Single Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Count me out <br>Count me out <br><br>Fellas want to hang <br>And save tonight just <br>For the gang <br>But you'll have to count me <br>Out tonight <br>If I can't bring my girl <br><br>Don't look surprised <br>When I tell you that <br>Gotta spend some time <br>With my baby, yes <br>So if that means <br>We're gonna rain on <br>Your parade <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count me <br>Out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I wanna be with my girlfriend <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>When she asked me please <br>Could I say no and feel at <br>Ease <br>If you count me out tonight <br>She's gonna be with me wherever <br>I go <br><br>She's got a sweet personality <br>She saves her kisses just for me <br>So if that means we're gonna rain on <br>Your parade <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I'm saving kisses for my baby <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>My baby wants to be with me <br>You'll have to count me out <br>That's the way it's gonna be <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>Count me out <br>Count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count me <br>Out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I wanna be with my girlfriend <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I'm saving all my loving for her <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>I love my baby but she's just a <br>Tease <br>And when I need her I say please <br>Please, please <br>Can I hold you <br>Squeeze you <br>Cause I need you <br>Count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>Don't count me out <br>Don't leave me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>Count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>Count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>Man, we're going to the movies <br>Then to the park, to play a little <br>Ball till it get dark <br>That's what being young is all about <br>Man, C O U N T me out <br><br>Well what about us <br>We're your friends <br>We wanna C O U N T <br>Me in <br>No not tonight <br>Where you going then <br>Tonight I wanna be with my girlfriend <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>Count me out <br>Count me out <br>Count me out <br><br>Don't count me out <br>Don't leave me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I'm saving kisses for my baby <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I wanna be with my girlfriend <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Count Me Out (Single Ver.)" label="Count Me Out (Single Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/A_Little_Bit_Of_Love_Is_All_It_Takes_Extended_Mix/</id><title>New Edition - A Little Bit Of Love (Is All It Takes) (Extended Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:02:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:02:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/A_Little_Bit_Of_Love_Is_All_It_Takes_Extended_Mix/" title="New Edition - A Little Bit Of Love (Is All It Takes) (Extended Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Woo ooh ooh ooh <br><br>You say you want to be the one I need <br>You say you want to be the one for me <br>You say you want to be the one I need <br>But then you go and act so crazy <br><br>You say you never want to let me go <br>You say you want to be the one I hold <br>You say you never want to let me go <br>But then you go and leave me lonely <br><br>If you want to make things right <br>Love can make a way <br>If you want to take the time <br>Act like what you say, yeah <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>You want to be the one who makes me shy <br>The one who makes me laugh and makes me cry <br>You want to be the one to change my life <br>Then maybe you should treat me kindly <br><br>You want to make believe you never left <br>You want to make believe I never wept <br>You said you'd never ever leave again <br>Oh, baby, won't you quit pretendin' <br><br>If you want to make things right <br>Love can make a way <br>And if you want to take the time <br>Act like what you say, yeah <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely, oh <br><br>Oh <br><br>Oh, if you want to make things right <br>Love can make a way <br>And if you want to take the time <br>Act like what you say, yeah <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is all it takes Little bit of love <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br><br>Girl, you got to make things right <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>Girl, we got to take our time <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="A Little Bit Of Love (Is All It Takes) (Extended Mix)" label="A Little Bit Of Love (Is All It Takes) (Extended Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Count_Me_Out_Extended_Ver/</id><title>New Edition - Count Me Out (Extended Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:02:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:02:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Count_Me_Out_Extended_Ver/" title="New Edition - Count Me Out (Extended Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Count me out <br>Count me out <br><br>Fellas want to hang <br>And save tonight just <br>For the gang <br>But you'll have to count me <br>Out tonight <br>If I can't bring my girl <br><br>Don't look surprised <br>When I tell you that <br>Gotta spend some time <br>With my baby, yes <br>So if that means <br>We're gonna rain on <br>Your parade <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count me <br>Out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I wanna be with my girlfriend <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>When she asked me please <br>Could I say no and feel at <br>Ease <br>If you count me out tonight <br>She's gonna be with me wherever <br>I go <br><br>She's got a sweet personality <br>She saves her kisses just for me <br>So if that means we're gonna rain on <br>Your parade <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I'm saving kisses for my baby <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>My baby wants to be with me <br>You'll have to count me out <br>That's the way it's gonna be <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>Count me out <br>Count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count me <br>Out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I wanna be with my girlfriend <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I'm saving all my loving for her <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>I love my baby but she's just a <br>Tease <br>And when I need her I say please <br>Please, please <br>Can I hold you <br>Squeeze you <br>Cause I need you <br>Count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>Don't count me out <br>Don't leave me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>Count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>Count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>Man, we're going to the movies <br>Then to the park, to play a little <br>Ball till it get dark <br>That's what being young is all about <br>Man, C O U N T me out <br><br>Well what about us <br>We're your friends <br>We wanna C O U N T <br>Me in <br>No not tonight <br>Where you going then <br>Tonight I wanna be with my girlfriend <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>Count me out <br>Count me out <br>Count me out <br><br>Don't count me out <br>Don't leave me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I'm saving kisses for my baby <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I wanna be with my girlfriend <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Count Me Out (Extended Ver.)" label="Count Me Out (Extended Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/All_For_Love/</id><title>New Edition - All For Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:02:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:02:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/All_For_Love/" title="New Edition - All For Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The girl next door has taste and style <br>She's lookin' so much better to me, yeah <br>Her flavor is hot as she passes by <br>Now I want her so much that it makes me scream, yeah <br><br>Our eyes collide, couldn't turn away <br>She licked her lips and smiled at me <br>When we find ourselves a little hideaway <br>I knew that I was in for somethin' sweet <br><br>All for love <br>I'm doin' things I've never done before <br>All for love <br>I'll try my best 'cause she's the one my heart beats for <br><br>We hold each other 'neath the starry skies <br>I feel the rhythm of our hearts <br>This is harder than the 4th of July <br>And I want more of what she's got <br><br>I tell her things I always keep inside <br>I let her look into my soul <br>She says she loves me, can I squeeze her tight <br>Tonight there ain't no letting go <br><br>All for love <br>I'm doin' things I've never done before <br>All for love <br>I'll try my best 'cause she's the one my heart beats for <br><br>In a daze all time <br>Dreaming about her day and night <br><br>All for love <br>I'm doin' things I've never done before <br>All for love <br>I'll try my best 'cause she's the one my heart beats for <br><br>All for love <br>All for love <br>All for love <br><br>All for love <br>I'm doin' things I've never done before <br>All for love <br>I'll try my best 'cause she's the one my heart beats for <br><br>All for love <br>I'm doin' things I've never done before <br>All for love]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="All For Love" label="All For Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/School/</id><title>New Edition - School - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:02:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:02:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/School/" title="New Edition - School - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Education <br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky, and Mike <br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky, and Mike <br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky, and Mike <br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky, and Mike, and Ralph <br><br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br>When the alarm clock bangs ring, ding, dong <br>We gotta stop our rap about this song <br>Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, the weekend's here <br><br>Well listen <br>When I was very young I used to sit around the house <br>Watching oil can Harry battle Mighty Mouse <br>Until my mother said, Son, that's not the way to be <br>You've got to go to school and learn your ABCs <br><br>I said, Is that it, mom <br>She said, That's not even half <br>You've got to go to school, you got to learn some math <br>You got to learn you to count 1, 2, 3 <br>And then get brushed up on the history <br><br>My first day of school I'll never forget <br>My teacher said, Recite the alphabet <br>I said, A E M E L R, and, as you can see <br>I didn't get very far <br><br>The teacher said, Son, there's nothing to it <br>Before the day's over, you'll learn how to do it <br>And not only that, you'll learn how to read <br>And that's one thing in life you'll always need <br><br>Well, school's not all work <br>There's fun things to do like gym, lunch, and recess, too <br>Kindergarten was easy, it was mostly play <br>What I was worried about was elementary <br><br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br>When the alarm clock bangs ring, ding, dong <br>We gotta stop our rap about this song <br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br>When the alarm clock bangs ring, ding, dong <br>We gotta stop our rap about this song <br><br>Ha Now something got wrong, I took another turn <br>I didn't want to study, didn't even want to learn <br>Didn't want to go to class, I was always late <br>Because school became something that I started to hate <br><br>Started hanging with my boys, didn't mean no harm <br>We was going around the school pulling fire alarms <br>I was a chilly homeboy, yes, I was down <br>Because I came to school just to mess around <br><br>I started hanging in the halls, writing on the walls <br>Until I got started playing basketball <br>But I didn't have a job so I couldn't get paid <br>And I couldn't play ball because of my grades <br><br>But I still used to practice each and every day <br>In case the coach decided to let me play <br>But it didn't work out the way I planned <br>So I ran to a man who said he can understand <br><br>The troubles I was going through <br>He said, Son it's all about going to school <br>So I shut up and shipped out to get my keys <br>And now I'm moving up to the big leagues, high school <br><br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br>When the alarm clock bangs ring, ding, dong <br>We gotta stop our rap about this song <br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br>When the alarm clock bangs ring, ding, dong <br>We gotta stop our rap about this song <br><br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky, and Mike <br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky, and Mike, and Ralph <br>Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, the weekend's here <br><br>So sticking out that chest, I'm feeling cool <br>'Cause I was going on to something they call high school <br>And I feel important, 'cause things aren't the same <br>Wondering why nobody knows my name <br><br>That became something that I started to miss <br>And now that I'm here it feels like a big dis <br>But, anyway, I had to leave <br>I had something to achieve <br><br>It was singing, yeah, that's what I wanted to do <br>So I got a tutor, because I'm no fool <br>Dropping out of school is quite absurd <br>And it's something New Edition just spread the word <br>Stay in school <br><br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br>S C H O O L, you got to go to school and beat that bell <br><br>Ronnie, Ronnie, Ronnie, Ronnie, Ronnie <br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky, and Mike <br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky, and Mike, and Ralph <br>Ronnie <br><br>S C H O O L, beat that bell <br>Go to school and beat that bell <br>S C H O O L, go to school and beat that bell <br>S C H O O L]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="School" label="School"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Who_Do_You_Trust/</id><title>New Edition - Who Do You Trust - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:03:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:03:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Who_Do_You_Trust/" title="New Edition - Who Do You Trust - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fire and ice <br>Why dont we just throw in the dice <br>Hot or cold <br>I never know which way you may go <br>Follow me follow me <br>I have waited too long to see <br>Problems are problems <br>The truth is our security <br><br>It's my life, I cant waste the time <br>I've made my decision, so let's lay it on the line oh baby <br><br>Who do you trust if you cant trust me <br>Im the one who loves you <br>Who do you trust if you cant trust me <br>Im the one who loves you <br><br>If you stay <br>Ill just try to make you aware Ill <br>Be gone, if it dont get no better <br><br>Human hearts can only take so much <br>Faith is my condition if you want to keep in touch oh baby <br><br>Who do you trust if you cant trust me <br>Im the one who loves you <br>Who do you trust if you cant trust me <br>Im the one who loves you <br><br>Who do you trust Who do you trust <br>If you cant trust me <br>Who do you trust who do you trust <br>If you cant trust me <br><br>Its my life, I cant waste the time <br>Ive made my decision <br>So lets lay it on the line oh baby]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Who Do You Trust" label="Who Do You Trust"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Whispers_In_Bed/</id><title>New Edition - Whispers In Bed - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:03:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:03:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Whispers_In_Bed/" title="New Edition - Whispers In Bed - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been livin' on the whispers in bed <br>And if you had a picture <br>Of what I've got in my head <br>Whispers in bed <br>Your voice is like an angel <br>And this boy wants to be left <br>Just an ordinary guy, uh huh <br><br>And you're the vision that this boy wants to carry <br>You're perfect, you're the one I'll marry <br>You and I, we just keep getting closer <br>Soon it will be alright It's gonna be alright <br><br>I've been livin' on your whispers in bed <br>So full of emotion <br>Over all the things you said <br>Whispers in bed <br>I wish that I could see you <br>But I'll hold this phone instead <br>I'm a victim of your eyes, uh huh <br><br>And endless pleasures we will have 'cause it's magic <br>And everything I have, girl, we will share <br>OhohohI can hardly disguise it <br>Girl, why should I deny it We have so much to share <br><br>Girl, every night when I'm home <br>And I'm sittin' around on my bed <br>And I pick up the phone and I dial your number <br>I always have these images of you <br>Running around inside my head <br>And I just wanna let you know <br>That I, Ralph T, will always love you <br><br>I've been livin' on the whispers in bed <br>And if you had a picture <br>Of what I've got in my head <br>Whispers in bed <br>Your voice is like an angel <br>And this boy wants to be left <br><br>Whispers in bed <br>So full of emotion <br>Over all the things you said <br>Whispers in bed <br>And if you had a picture <br>Of what I've got in my head]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Whispers In Bed" label="Whispers In Bed"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Tonights_Your_Night/</id><title>New Edition - Tonight`s Your Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:03:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:03:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Tonights_Your_Night/" title="New Edition - Tonight`s Your Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ahhh <br>Ahhh <br><br>Here we are <br>Just the two of us <br>Holding on to <br>Precious romance <br><br>Locked away in another world <br>There's nothing wrong <br>Love is with us <br><br>Sometimes it makes me wonder it makes me wonder <br>If anybody understands <br>How it feels to be <br>So ready for love girl <br>Now that you're with me <br><br>Tonight's your night tonight is your night, tonight <br>I want you to feel the power of our love <br>Tonight's your night tonight is your night, tonight <br>No one can stop us now <br><br>Wooooo ahhhh <br>Wooooo ahhhh <br><br>When we met <br>I might have known <br>No matter what <br>You'd be my first love <br><br>Now this feeling <br>Sure has grown <br>Into so much <br>More than I dreamed <br><br>This night was made for magic made for magic <br>We can't let go of what we feel <br>This one's ours alone <br>This time baby <br>All our own <br><br>Tonight's your night tonight is your night, tonight <br>I want you to feel <br>The power of our love <br>Tonight's your night tonight is your night, tonight <br>No one can stop us now <br><br>This night we will remember baby baby <br>All of our lives <br><br>Spoken <br>Our time has come <br>The night has arrived So that means all games must be put aside put aside <br>The magic is here and it's coming on strong and then nothing can stop us now <br><br>Sometimes it makes me wonder it makes me wonder <br>If anybody understands <br>How it feels to be <br>So ready for love girl <br>Now that you're with me <br><br>Tonight's your night tonight is your night, tonight <br>I want you to feel the power of our love <br>Tonight's your night tonight is your night <br>No one can stop us now no one can stop us now <br><br>Tonight's your night feel it girl, feel it girl <br>I want you to feel <br>The power of our love]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Tonight`s Your Night" label="Tonight`s Your Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Kickback/</id><title>New Edition - Kickback - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:03:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:03:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Kickback/" title="New Edition - Kickback - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I grabbed my pillow in the middle of the night <br>Shook in a ice cold sweat <br>Curious of what real love feels like <br>It hasn't hit me yet it hasn't hit me yet <br><br>You'll reach that stage in your life <br>You wonder what love will be <br>My mama told me that will be our find <br>You will find love in reality she said <br><br>Baby you don't have to wonder <br>Just kickback and love will come <br>Love will tap you on the shoulder <br>Kickback and love will grow <br><br>I see the look that's in a young girls eye <br>As I watch TV <br>This thing called love I gotta try <br>Leave his script for me <br><br>Its time to learn all about <br>True love without a doubt <br>Cant fight the feeling when it comes around <br>You will know when the girl you found, mama said <br><br>Baby you don't have to wonder <br>Just kickback and love will come <br>Love will tap you on the shoulder girl <br>Kickback and love will grow <br><br>My mama said, kickback and love will flow <br>Mama said, kickback and love will grow <br><br>Now I'm kinda young and I don't understand <br>What it is about love that attracts a man <br>Could it be you got to be of age <br>Or tell me Mike is love just a stage <br>Love when does it come how, when, and why <br>Does it bring happiness,does it make you cry <br>My mother told me one day I'll know <br>Just kickback and love will grow <br><br>Baby you don't have to wonder <br>Just kickback and love will come <br>Love will tap you on the shoulder girl <br>Kickback and love will grow <br>]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Kickback" label="Kickback"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Lets_Be_Friends/</id><title>New Edition - Let`s Be Friends - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:03:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:03:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Lets_Be_Friends/" title="New Edition - Let`s Be Friends - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I guess u want to no why I got to go <br>Knowing how I feel about ya bout ya <br>I can go all night sing my our love <br>But it's hard to fight this feeling feeling inside <br><br>Girl I can not do what I want to do momma said <br>That were movin movin to fast <br>If we hold on to and if love is true <br>I know the day will final come around <br><br>Let's be friends cause I don't want to hurt you <br>Let's be friends I don't want to let you down <br>Let's be friends na girl I don't want to hurt you <br>Lets be friends I don't want to let you down <br><br>Girl if we explain why we must refrain <br>Why we can't give in we can only just be friends <br>If you only new what im going through <br>I really want cha but I can't stick around <br><br>Girl I can not do what I want to do papa said <br>That were movin movin to fast <br>If we hold on to and if love is true <br>I know the day will come but in the mean time <br><br>Let's be friends cause I don't want to hurt you <br>Let's be friends I don't want to let you down <br>Let's be friends I don't want to hurt you <br>No you know you're the only one I need <br>Girl you're the only one I need girl <br><br>Want you be my friend we can work it out <br><br>Let's be friends let's be friends <br>So hard to turn love down friends doo doo dout it out <br>I just can't stick around <br><br>Friends no girl don't cha want be my friend <br>I don't want to let you down <br><br>Girl I know how you feel about me <br>And im not knocking the way you feel <br>But as you can see baby time is not on or side <br>And for that reason we can't be together <br>But I can assure you one day we would prove them all wrong <br>But in the meant time luve let's just walk away and be friend's <br><br>Friend's forever soon enough it will be just you and me <br>Ooh ooh we can work it put we can work it out yeah yeah oooh]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Let`s Be Friends" label="Let`s Be Friends"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/With_You_All_The_Way/</id><title>New Edition - With You All The Way - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:03:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:03:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/With_You_All_The_Way/" title="New Edition - With You All The Way - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girl, if ever the going got rough <br>You never <br>Were the type to think of backing down <br>So when you got more than your share <br><br>In a minute I knew your heart was in it <br>I knew that it would make you be your best <br>Put you to the test <br>But if sometimes it seems not worth the battle <br>That's when you'll see <br>You can count on me <br><br>'Cause I'm with you all the way <br>I'll never give up this dream <br>Although it may seem <br>There's no way out today Oh, girl <br><br>Yes, I'm with you all the way <br>Whatever places love might put us through <br>Remember I'm with you <br>With you all the way <br><br>When you see me <br>Your eyes say that you need me <br>But there's another feelin' they can't hide <br>And it hurts so deep inside <br>To think maybe before I'd let you down <br>Won't you hear me out now <br>Believe me somehow <br><br>'Cause I'm with you all the way <br>I'll never give up the dream <br>Although it may seem <br>There's no way out today Oh, girl <br><br>Yes, I'm with you all the way <br>Whatever places love might put us through <br>Remember I'm with you <br>With you all the way <br><br>I thought I'd never know just where to start <br>Delivering this promise from my heart <br>Holding you here in my arms <br>Has told me what to say, yeah <br><br>'Cause I'm with you all the way <br>I'll never give up the dream <br>Although it may seem <br>There's no way out today Oh, girl <br><br>Yes, I'm with you all the way <br>Whatever places love might put us through <br>Remember I'm with you <br>With you all the way]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="With You All The Way" label="With You All The Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Sweet_Thing/</id><title>New Edition - Sweet Thing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:03:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:03:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Sweet_Thing/" title="New Edition - Sweet Thing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well when she walks on by she's got that look in her eye <br>Drop and roll, funk and soul <br>And when she wants a guy you know she don't have to try <br>Can't say no, what boy would say no <br>Every since I saw her nothings ever been the same <br>I'm feeling like a brand new me <br>She's the one that I need, she could really make my life complete <br><br>Wish she were crazy bout me, sweet thing <br>I will hold you in my arms and make you feel apart of my dreams <br>sweet thing <br>I will hold you in my arms and make you feel apart of my dreams <br>Dreams <br><br>Well she can break your heart she can tear it apart <br>With her smile, with her smile <br>And when she starts to dance shes got you all in a trance <br>Girl so fine, woo woo its a crime <br>Everybody wants her, what am I to do <br>I know thay she don't notice me, wondering should I tell her <br>I would give her everything <br><br>Wish she were crazy bout me, sweet thing <br>I will hold you in my arms and make you feel apart of my dreams <br>sweet dreams <br>I will hold you in my arms and make you feel apart of my dreams <br>sweet dreams <br><br>Every since I saw her nothings ever been the same <br>I'm feeling like a brand new me <br>She's the one that I need, she could really make my life complete <br><br>Wish she were crazy bout me, sweet thing <br>I will hold you in my arms and make you feel apart of my dreams <br>sweet thing <br>I will finally make you mines and wrap you up inside of my dreams <br>sweet thing <br>I will kiss you in the night and love you til we both start to scream <br>sweet thing <br><br>Sweet thing <br>Sweet thing]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Sweet Thing" label="Sweet Thing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/A_Little_Bit_Of_Love/</id><title>New Edition - A Little Bit Of Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:03:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:03:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/A_Little_Bit_Of_Love/" title="New Edition - A Little Bit Of Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Woo ooh ooh ooh <br><br>You say you want to be the one I need <br>You say you want to be the one for me <br>You say you want to be the one I need <br>But then you go and act so crazy <br><br>You say you never want to let me go <br>You say you want to be the one I hold <br>You say you never want to let me go <br>But then you go and leave me lonely <br><br>If you want to make things right <br>Love can make a way <br>If you want to take the time <br>Act like what you say, yeah <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>You want to be the one who makes me shy <br>The one who makes me laugh and makes me cry <br>You want to be the one to change my life <br>Then maybe you should treat me kindly <br><br>You want to make believe you never left <br>You want to make believe I never wept <br>You said you'd never ever leave again <br>Oh, baby, won't you quit pretendin' <br><br>If you want to make things right <br>Love can make a way <br>And if you want to take the time <br>Act like what you say, yeah <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely, oh <br><br>Oh <br><br>Oh, if you want to make things right <br>Love can make a way <br>And if you want to take the time <br>Act like what you say, yeah <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is all it takes Little bit of love <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br><br>Girl, you got to make things right <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>Girl, we got to take our time <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way <br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love is lovely <br><br>A little bit of love is all it takes <br>A little bit of love goes a long, long way]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="A Little Bit Of Love" label="A Little Bit Of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Count_Me_Out/</id><title>New Edition - Count Me Out - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:03:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:03:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Count_Me_Out/" title="New Edition - Count Me Out - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Count me out <br>Count me out <br><br>Fellas want to hang <br>And save tonight just <br>For the gang <br>But you'll have to count me <br>Out tonight <br>If I can't bring my girl <br><br>Don't look surprised <br>When I tell you that <br>Gotta spend some time <br>With my baby, yes <br>So if that means <br>We're gonna rain on <br>Your parade <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count me <br>Out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I wanna be with my girlfriend <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>When she asked me please <br>Could I say no and feel at <br>Ease <br>If you count me out tonight <br>She's gonna be with me wherever <br>I go <br><br>She's got a sweet personality <br>She saves her kisses just for me <br>So if that means we're gonna rain on <br>Your parade <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I'm saving kisses for my baby <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>My baby wants to be with me <br>You'll have to count me out <br>That's the way it's gonna be <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>Count me out <br>Count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count me <br>Out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I wanna be with my girlfriend <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I'm saving all my loving for her <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>I love my baby but she's just a <br>Tease <br>And when I need her I say please <br>Please, please <br>Can I hold you <br>Squeeze you <br>Cause I need you <br>Count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>Don't count me out <br>Don't leave me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>Count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>Count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>Man, we're going to the movies <br>Then to the park, to play a little <br>Ball till it get dark <br>That's what being young is all about <br>Man, C O U N T me out <br><br>Well what about us <br>We're your friends <br>We wanna C O U N T <br>Me in <br>No not tonight <br>Where you going then <br>Tonight I wanna be with my girlfriend <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>Count me out <br>Count me out <br>Count me out <br><br>Don't count me out <br>Don't leave me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I'm saving kisses for my baby <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out <br><br>You'll have to count me out <br>You're gonna have to count <br>Me out <br>You'll have to count me out <br>I wanna be with my girlfriend <br>You'll have to count me out <br>This time <br>You'll have to count me out]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Count Me Out" label="Count Me Out"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Johnossi/Hands/</id><title>Johnossi - Hands - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:07:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:07:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Johnossi/Hands/" title="Johnossi - Hands - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Spread your legs and shut your mouth <br>Put your hands where I can see 'em <br>I know exactly what you're all about <br><br>So put your hands where I can see 'em <br>I believe that <br>It is people like you who deserves to be beaten by me black and blue <br>I believe in <br>Ooh ooh <br>Yeah <br>Ooh ooh <br>Sorry officer for driving through <br>I'll put my hands where you can see 'em <br>Don't want no trouble tell me what to do <br>I'll put my hands where you can see 'em <br>You should know that <br>I'm a family man, swear to god <br>I ain't done nothing wrong, understand <br>Please believe me <br>Boy I dare you act so innocent and juvenile <br>Sick and tired of you people doing drugs at night <br>I guess your father left you and your mom to her despair <br>Why do you think I'd even care <br>Put your hands up in the air <br>If you believe in love tonight <br>Then put your hands where I can see 'em <br>If you believe we could all unite <br>Then put your hands where I can see 'em <br>Try to believe that <br>We are one and the world is a beautiful pearl in this great universe <br>I believe in <br>Hey <br>In another life <br>Hey <br>I would prove I'm right <br>I would never let nobody tell me how to live <br>All I know is I feel better once I start again <br>Imperfection is a beauty everybody shares <br>Fuck the medias we don't care <br>Put your hands up in the air <br>I would never let nobody tell me how to live <br>All I know is I feel better once I start again <br>Imperfection is a beauty everybody shares <br>Fuck the medias we don't care <br>Put your hands up in the air <br>Fuck the medias we don't care <br>Put your hands up in the air <br>Ooh ooh <br>Fuck the medias we don't care <br>Put your hands up in the air]]></content><category term="Johnossi" label="Johnossi"/><category term="Hands" label="Hands"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Saint_Mesa/Jungle_Acoustic/</id><title>Saint Mesa - Jungle (Acoustic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:07:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:07:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Saint_Mesa/Jungle_Acoustic/" title="Saint Mesa - Jungle (Acoustic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Give me a sign <br>Whether you're coming home <br>Tell me, tell me why <br>These winds feel so cold <br><br>Oh, I can't keep with you now <br>Your lies turn my head around <br>Oh, oh it's a jungle <br>Oh, I can't keep with you now <br>My head's stuck up in the clouds <br>Oh, stuck in the jungle <br><br>I can't wait for you <br>Forever and ever in the dark <br>Oh, please, please let me go <br>These windows are calling out my name <br><br>Oh, I can't keep with you now <br>Your lies turn my head around <br>Oh, oh it's a jungle <br>Oh, I can't keep with you now <br>My head's stuck up in the clouds <br>Oh, stuck in the jungle <br><br>You got me spinning now <br>You tied my hands and chained me back <br>shut the door <br>you ask for more <br>I'm so tired and it's okay <br><br>I'm begging you, I'm begging you <br>I'm begging you, please let me go <br><br>Oh, I can't keep with you now <br>Your lies turn my head around <br>Oh, oh it's a jungle <br>Oh, I can't keep with you now <br>My head's stuck up in the clouds <br>Oh, stuck in the jungle <br><br>Oh, I can't keep with you now <br>Your lies turn my head around <br>Oh, oh it's a jungle]]></content><category term="Saint Mesa" label="Saint Mesa"/><category term="Jungle (Acoustic)" label="Jungle (Acoustic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박용민/Curtis___Tu_Ca_Nun_Chiagne_쿠르티스___넌_왜_울지_않고/</id><title>박용민 - Curtis : Tu Ca Nun Chiagne (쿠르티스 : 넌 왜 울지 않고) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:11:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:11:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9A%A9%EB%AF%BC/Curtis___Tu_Ca_Nun_Chiagne_%EC%BF%A0%EB%A5%B4%ED%8B%B0%EC%8A%A4___%EB%84%8C_%EC%99%9C_%EC%9A%B8%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EA%B3%A0/" title="박용민 - Curtis : Tu Ca Nun Chiagne (쿠르티스 : 넌 왜 울지 않고) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Comme bella a <br>muntagna stanotte <br>bella accussi nun <br>laggio vista maie <br>Nanema pare <br>rassignata e stance <br>sotto cuperta e <br>chesta luna janca <br>Tu che nun chiagne <br>e chiagnere me faie <br>tu stanotte addo staie <br>Voglio a te <br>Voglio a te <br>Chist uocchie te vonno <br>n ata vota vede <br>Comme calma a <br>muntagna stanotte <br>cchiu calma e mo nun <br>laggio vista maie <br>e tutto dorme <br>tutto dorme o more <br>e i sulo viglio <br>per che veglia Ammore <br>Tu che nun chiagne <br>e chiagnere me faie <br>tu stanotte addo staie <br>Voglio a te <br>Voglio a te <br>Chist uocchie te vonno <br>n ata vota vede <br>Voglio a te <br>Voglio a te <br>Chist uocchie te vonno <br>n ata vota vede <br>]]></content><category term="박용민" label="박용민"/><category term="Curtis : Tu Ca Nun Chiagne (쿠르티스 : 넌 왜 울지 않고)" label="Curtis : Tu Ca Nun Chiagne (쿠르티스 : 넌 왜 울지 않고)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하트_BHEART/실감나_Inst/</id><title>비하트 (B.HEART) - 실감나 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:12:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:12:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%ED%8A%B8_BHEART/%EC%8B%A4%EA%B0%90%EB%82%98_Inst/" title="비하트 (B.HEART) - 실감나 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘따라 평소와 <br>같은 하루가 <br>니가 없다고 <br>다르게 느껴져 <br>우연이라도 너를 <br>마주칠 수만 있다면 <br>나는 왜 조금씩 멀어지는 <br>우리를 또 힘들게 했을까 <br>이제야 조금씩 실감나 <br>니가 날 떠났다는 게 <br>난 자꾸만 실감나 <br>미칠 것 같아 <br>니가 없는 게 <br>왜 이리 나를 <br>힘들게 하는지 <br>그대는 왜 <br>나를 이렇게만 <br>힘들게 하고 <br>날 떠나려 하는지 <br>oh baby <br>니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby <br>내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 <br>볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 <br>안을 수가 없는 <br>oh baby <br>니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby <br>내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 <br>볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 <br>안을 수가 없는 <br>너라는 아름다운 꽃을 <br>나라는 화분이 담기엔 <br>넌 너무 내게 과분해서 <br>너무 힘들던 <br>너를 떼어내면 <br>홀가분해질 거라는 <br>내 생각은 <br>완전히 빗나가 <br>니 마음 속에서 <br>너를 위해서였다는 <br>내 행동이 <br>전부 거짓으로 들린대도 <br>내 마지막 진심이 <br>너에게 닿길 <br>내게 다시 꼭 돌아오길 <br>미칠 것 같아 <br>니가 없는 게 <br>왜 이리 나를 <br>힘들게 하는지 <br>그대는 왜 <br>나를 이렇게만 <br>힘들게 하고 <br>날 떠나려 하는지 <br>oh baby <br>니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby <br>내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 <br>볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 <br>안을 수가 없는 <br>제발 가지마 <br>제발 떠나지마 <br>너를 바라보고 있잖아 나 <br>제발 가지마 놓지마 <br>내 곁으로 돌아와 <br>나 너를 잊을 수 있을까 <br>oh baby <br>니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby <br>내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 <br>볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 <br>안을 수가 없는 <br>oh baby <br>니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby <br>내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 <br>볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 <br>안을 수가 없는 <br>]]></content><category term="비하트 (B.HEART)" label="비하트 (B.HEART)"/><category term="실감나 (Inst.)" label="실감나 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하트_BHEART/STAY/</id><title>비하트 (B.HEART) - STAY - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:12:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:12:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%ED%8A%B8_BHEART/STAY/" title="비하트 (B.HEART) - STAY - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바라는 게 더 있을까 <br>그저 니가 내 품에 안겨 <br>들리는 숨소리와 <br>너랑 내 웃음소리만 있으면 <br>모든 게 행복했는데 <br>이젠 아무 소용이 없더라고 <br>행복했던 우리 기억이 <br>꽤 지나칠 정도로 <br>자꾸만 내 목을 조이고 <br>죽음도 내놓을 수 있다던 <br>너를 위한 내 말도 <br>이젠 아무 소용이 없더라고 <br>우리같이 걷던 그 곳에서 <br>나 혼자 멍하니 <br>너만 또 생각하는데 <br>넌 뭐하고 있는지 <br>난 모르지만 또 아직 <br>너무 헷갈려 <br>나는 널 모르겠어 <br>니 맘 아직도 <br>베이베 why <br>난 너만 보면 그대론데 <br>도대체 너는 내 맘을 <br>왜 아직 모르냐고 <br>아직도 혼자 행복하냐고 <br>그냥 있어주면 된다고 <br>내 옆에 있어주면 된다고 <br>널 기다리고 있어 혼자 <br>니가 올 때까지 기다려 <br>baby <br>stay stay <br>내 옆에 <br>stay stay <br>내 곁에 <br>내 옆에 있어주면 된다는 말 <br>널 기다리고 있다는 말 <br>stay stay <br>내 옆에 <br>stay stay <br>너만을 난 기다리고 있어 <br>Baby <br>어서 내 곁으로 돌아와 <br>baby <br>Ay 말이 안 되잖아 이건 <br>니 옆에 내가 아닌 <br>다른 사람이라는 게 <br>단 한 순간에 이렇게 <br>또 멀어진다는 게 <br>이젠 돌이킬 수 없단 <br>것까지 잘 알고 있는데 <br>Ye 이젠 안을 수도 없어 <br>듣고 싶어도 들을 수 <br>조차 도 없고 <br>널 보고 싶어도 이젠 <br>볼 수 조차 없어 <br>아직도 내 모든 중심은 <br>전부다 너인데 <br>너와 함께 했던 그 추억들 <br>하나 둘 생각나 <br>너를 더 떠올리는데 <br>baby <br>난 못 잊고 있는데 <br>넌 잊었겠지 너 벌써 <br>아직 힘들어 나는 널 <br>잊을 수가 없어 아직도 <br>베이베 why <br>난 너만 보면 그대론데 <br>도대체 너는 내 맘을 <br>왜 아직 모르냐고 <br>아직도 혼자 행복하냐고 <br>그냥 있어주면 된다고 <br>내 옆에 있어주면 된다고 <br>널 기다리고 있어 혼자 <br>니가 올 때까지 기다려 <br>baby <br>stay stay <br>내 옆에 <br>stay stay <br>내 곁에 <br>내 옆에 있어주면 된다는 말 <br>널 기다리고 있다는 말 <br>stay stay <br>내 옆에 <br>stay stay <br>너만을 난 기다리고 있어 <br>Baby <br>어서 내 곁으로 돌아와 <br>베이베 <br>넌 나를 잊었겠지만 <br>난 아직 그대론데 <br>언제쯤 잊혀질까 <br>함께 했던 추억 <br>함께 걷던 거릴 <br>언젠간 다시 올까 <br>난 너를 또 기다려 <br>베이베 why <br>난 너만 보면 그대론데 <br>도대체 너는 내 맘을 <br>왜 아직 모르냐고 <br>아직도 혼자 행복하냐고 <br>그냥 있어주면 된다고 <br>내 옆에 있어주면 된다고 <br>널 기다리고 있어 혼자 <br>니가 올 때까지 기다려 <br>baby <br>stay stay <br>내 옆에 <br>stay stay <br>내 곁에 <br>내 옆에 있어주면 된다는 말 <br>널 기다리고 있다는 말 <br>stay stay <br>내 옆에 <br>stay stay <br>너만을 난 기다리고 있어 <br>Baby <br>어서 내 곁으로 돌아와 <br>베이베 <br>]]></content><category term="비하트 (B.HEART)" label="비하트 (B.HEART)"/><category term="STAY" label="STAY"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하트_BHEART/필요없어/</id><title>비하트 (B.HEART) - 필요없어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:12:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:12:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%ED%8A%B8_BHEART/%ED%95%84%EC%9A%94%EC%97%86%EC%96%B4/" title="비하트 (B.HEART) - 필요없어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[화려한 불빛 아래 서있는 너와 나 <br>이제는 니가 손을 놓으려 해 <br>그저 쳐다보는 나 <br>눈빛도 안 주는 너 Yeah <br>이제 모든 건 끝난 거 같아 <br>믿기 힘들 정도로 말이야 <br>끝이 없다 생각했었던 <br>내가 너무 바보 같아 하 <br>내 손을 잡고 아무 생각 마 <br>두려울 때 난 네가 생각나 <br>분명 힘들어하고 <br>후회가 남아 Oh Baby <br>I Gave You Everything But <br>넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Everything 난 <br>아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>차가운 인사말로 안녕 <br>시간을 되돌릴 수만 있다면 <br>I Gave You Everything but <br>넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Everything 난 <br>아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>아무 것도 필요 없어 <br>너만 있으면 필요 없어 <br>매일같이 널 또 울려 <br>마치 마지막인 것처럼 <br>늘 다그치던 나였지만 <br>오늘은 못 참아 걸 <br>사랑에 좋은 이별 따위 없다면서 <br>날 밀어내는 <br>널 보는 내 맘은 어떻겠어 <br>좋았었던 기억이 안 나는지 <br>그런데 왜 넌 아파하고만 있는지 <br>이미 끝난 듯이 <br>우리 사이 끝이 없는 로코 드라마 <br>감정이 다 무너져도 <br>날 보면 웃게 되잖아 <br>내 손을 잡고 아무 생각 마 <br>두려울 때 난 네가 생각나 <br>분명 힘들어하고 <br>후회가 남아 Oh Baby <br>I Gave You Everything But <br>넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Everything 난 <br>아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>차가운 인사말로 안녕 <br>시간을 되돌릴 수만 있다면 <br>I Gave You Everything but <br>넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Everything 난 <br>아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>아무 것도 필요 없어 <br>너만 있으면 필요 없어 <br>내 방안에 모든 것이 멈춘듯해 <br>내 중심은 온통 너였었는데 Girl <br>영원하자고 믿으라고 <br>운명이라 넌 말했었지 <br>이제 그만하자는 널 <br>끝내기엔 아직 사랑하는데 <br>I Gave You Everything But <br>넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Everything 난 <br>아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>차가운 인사말로 안녕 <br>시간을 되돌릴 수만 있다면 <br>I Gave You Everything but <br>넌 더 원하나 봐 <br>I Got No Everything 난 <br>아직 널 잘 몰라 <br>아무 것도 필요 없어 <br>너만 있으면 필요 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="비하트 (B.HEART)" label="비하트 (B.HEART)"/><category term="필요없어" label="필요없어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하트_BHEART/실감나_Acoustic_Ver/</id><title>비하트 (B.HEART) - 실감나 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:12:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:12:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%ED%8A%B8_BHEART/%EC%8B%A4%EA%B0%90%EB%82%98_Acoustic_Ver/" title="비하트 (B.HEART) - 실감나 (Acoustic Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oh baby 니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby 내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 안을 수가 없는 <br>오늘따라 평소와 같은 하루가 <br>니가 없다고 다르게 느껴져 <br>우연이라도 <br>너를 마주칠 수만 있다면 <br>나는 왜 조금씩 멀어지는 <br>우리를 또 힘들게 했을까 <br>이제야 조금씩 실감나 <br>니가 날 떠났다는 게 <br>난 자꾸만 실감나 <br>미칠 것 같아 니가 없는 게 <br>왜 이리 나를 힘들게 하는지 <br>그대는 왜 나를 이렇게만 <br>힘들게 하고 날 떠나려 하는지 <br>oh baby 니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby 내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 안을 수가 없는 <br>너라는 아름다운 꽃을 <br>나라는 화분이 담기엔 <br>넌 너무 내게 과분해서 <br>너무 힘들던 너를 떼어내면 <br>홀가분해질 거라는 내 생각은 <br>완전히 빗나가 니 마음 속에서 <br>너를 위해서였다는 내 행동이 <br>전부 거짓으로 들린대도 <br>내 마지막 진심이 너에게 닿길 <br>내게 다시 꼭 돌아오길 <br>미칠 것 같아 니가 없는 게 <br>왜 이리 나를 힘들게 하는지 <br>그대는 왜 나를 이렇게만 <br>힘들게 하고 날 떠나려 하는지 <br>oh baby 니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby 내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 안을 수가 없는 <br>제발 가지마 제발 떠나지마 <br>너를 바라보고 있잖아 나 <br>제발 가지마 놓지마 <br>내 곁으로 돌아와 <br>나 너를 잊을 수 있을까 <br>oh baby 니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby 내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 안을 수가 없는 <br>]]></content><category term="비하트 (B.HEART)" label="비하트 (B.HEART)"/><category term="실감나 (Acoustic Ver.)" label="실감나 (Acoustic Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하트_BHEART/실감나/</id><title>비하트 (B.HEART) - 실감나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:12:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:12:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%ED%8A%B8_BHEART/%EC%8B%A4%EA%B0%90%EB%82%98/" title="비하트 (B.HEART) - 실감나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘따라 평소와 <br>같은 하루가 <br>니가 없다고 <br>다르게 느껴져 <br>우연이라도 너를 <br>마주칠 수만 있다면 <br>나는 왜 조금씩 멀어지는 <br>우리를 또 힘들게 했을까 <br>이제야 조금씩 실감나 <br>니가 날 떠났다는 게 <br>난 자꾸만 실감나 <br>미칠 것 같아 <br>니가 없는 게 <br>왜 이리 나를 <br>힘들게 하는지 <br>그대는 왜 <br>나를 이렇게만 <br>힘들게 하고 <br>날 떠나려 하는지 <br>oh baby <br>니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby <br>내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 <br>볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 <br>안을 수가 없는 <br>oh baby <br>니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby <br>내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 <br>볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 <br>안을 수가 없는 <br>너라는 아름다운 꽃을 <br>나라는 화분이 담기엔 <br>넌 너무 내게 과분해서 <br>너무 힘들던 <br>너를 떼어내면 <br>홀가분해질 거라는 <br>내 생각은 <br>완전히 빗나가 <br>니 마음 속에서 <br>너를 위해서였다는 <br>내 행동이 <br>전부 거짓으로 들린대도 <br>내 마지막 진심이 <br>너에게 닿길 <br>내게 다시 꼭 돌아오길 <br>미칠 것 같아 <br>니가 없는 게 <br>왜 이리 나를 <br>힘들게 하는지 <br>그대는 왜 <br>나를 이렇게만 <br>힘들게 하고 <br>날 떠나려 하는지 <br>oh baby <br>니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby <br>내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 <br>볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 <br>안을 수가 없는 <br>제발 가지마 <br>제발 떠나지마 <br>너를 바라보고 있잖아 나 <br>제발 가지마 놓지마 <br>내 곁으로 돌아와 <br>나 너를 잊을 수 있을까 <br>oh baby <br>니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby <br>내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 <br>볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 <br>안을 수가 없는 <br>oh baby <br>니가 없단 게 난 실감나 <br>oh baby <br>내 옆에 없단 게 실감나 <br>보고파도 이제는 <br>볼 수 없는 <br>사랑해도 이젠 <br>안을 수가 없는 <br>]]></content><category term="비하트 (B.HEART)" label="비하트 (B.HEART)"/><category term="실감나" label="실감나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/비하트_BHEART/SAD/</id><title>비하트 (B.HEART) - SAD - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:12:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:12:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B9%84%ED%95%98%ED%8A%B8_BHEART/SAD/" title="비하트 (B.HEART) - SAD - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 니가 가진 <br>모든 것들을 <br>다 사랑한다고 <br>늘 말했잖아 <br>늘 그랬잖아 <br>난 그거면 충분한데 <br>아무리 생각해도 <br>이런 갑작스런 이별은 <br>말이 안 되잖아 <br>이해가 안 되잖아 <br>니가 날 떠나갈 리 없잖아 <br>대체 니가 나를 <br>왜 뿌리치며 <br>떠나가는 이유조차 <br>모른 채 <br>자고 일어나면 <br>평소처럼 나를 안아주겠지 <br>미친 듯이 사랑한 뒤에 <br>내려진 결론이 <br>이런 거라면 <br>난 다신 사랑 따위 <br>하지 못할 거야 <br>Baby I hate you <br>내가 아닌 다른 사람의 <br>옆이 돼버린 니가 <br>But I miss you <br>나를 떠나 얼마나 <br>행복해질지 기도할게 <br>Baby I hate you <br>내가 아닌 다른 사람의 <br>옆이 돼버린 니가 <br>But I miss you <br>나를 떠나 얼마나 <br>행복해질지 기도할게 <br>니가 없이 <br>텅 빈 내 맘에서 <br>가만히 몇 시간을 <br>생각해 봐도 <br>아무런 답이 <br>나오지 않는 건 <br>너무 멀리와 버린 <br>너와 내 사이를 <br>부정하고 있기 때문인 걸까 <br>I hate you but I miss you <br>꿈이라기 보단 <br>악몽이 돼버린 <br>추억을 안고 <br>얼마나 잘 사나 두고 볼게 <br>나 없이 잘 살길 기도해줄게 <br>대체 니가 나를 <br>왜 뿌리치며 <br>떠나가는 이유조차 <br>모른 채 <br>자고 일어나면 <br>평소처럼 나를 안아주겠지 <br>미친 듯이 사랑한 뒤에 <br>내려진 결론이 <br>이런 거라면 <br>난 다신 사랑 따위 <br>하지 못할 거야 <br>Baby I hate you <br>내가 아닌 다른 사람의 <br>옆이 돼버린 니가 <br>But I miss you <br>나를 떠나 얼마나 <br>행복해질지 기도할게 <br>Baby I hate you <br>내가 아닌 다른 사람의 <br>옆이 돼버린 니가 <br>But I miss you <br>나를 떠나 얼마나 <br>행복해질지 기도할게 <br>바보 같았어 이제 알았어 <br>너를 사랑했던 내가 <br>바보 같았어 이제 알았어 <br>너만 바라봤던 내가 <br>나를 떠나가려 하는 <br>사람 따위 잡지 않을게 <br>사랑 않는 사람 따위 <br>잡지 않을게 <br>나를 떠나 부디 <br>잘 살길 기도해 <br>I got ya pray ya <br>I love to all ya <br>Baby I hate you <br>내가 아닌 다른 사람의 <br>옆이 돼버린 니가 <br>But I miss you <br>나를 떠나 얼마나 <br>행복해질지 기도할게 <br>Baby I hate you <br>내가 아닌 다른 사람의 <br>옆이 돼버린 니가 <br>But I miss you <br>나를 떠나 얼마나 <br>행복해질지 기도할게 <br>Baby I hate you <br>내가 아닌 다른 사람의 <br>옆이 돼버린 니가 <br>But I miss you <br>나를 떠나 얼마나 <br>행복해질지 기도할게 <br>Baby I hate you <br>내가 아닌 다른 사람의 <br>옆이 돼버린 니가 <br>But I miss you <br>나를 떠나 얼마나 <br>행복해질지 기도할게 <br>]]></content><category term="비하트 (B.HEART)" label="비하트 (B.HEART)"/><category term="SAD" label="SAD"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Rise_Up/</id><title>Foxygen - Rise Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:17:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:17:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Rise_Up/" title="Foxygen - Rise Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rise up <br>See for yourself <br>You got to pull yourself up <br>From the fires of hell <br>Rise up <br>And see for yourself <br>What the all world's done <br>Nobody else's <br>And when the city spits itself out into that big ocean <br>The wonderful wisdom of thee <br><br>Quite a few shall wonder <br>Very few shall know <br>Everybody wants to change the world <br>Everybody wonders where the river goes <br>Everybody wants to save their souls <br>And everybody wonders <br>The very few shall know <br>Wonders where the river goes <br>And everybody wonders where the river goes <br><br>It's time to wake up early <br>Start taking care of your health <br>And start doing all the hard things <br>And believe in yourself <br>And follow your own heart <br>If nothing else <br>And listen to your own dreams <br>Nobody else's will do, will do <br><br>Everybody wonders <br>Very few shall know <br>Everybody wants to change the world <br>And everybody wonders where the river goes <br>Everybody wants to save their souls <br>You've been searching all your life for something till you realized that what you seek was with you all the time <br>And everybody wonders where the river grows <br><br>Sing the song for love <br>Sing the song for love <br>It's not to hard to tell <br>It's Christmas it's a hotel]]></content><category term="Foxygen" label="Foxygen"/><category term="Rise Up" label="Rise Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Trauma/</id><title>Foxygen - Trauma - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:17:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:17:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Trauma/" title="Foxygen - Trauma - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All you people who confuse and abuse <br>Be gone, throw your parapets into the fire <br>Trauma Trauma <br>Trauma Trauma <br>Trauma, yeah <br><br>Ooh, yeah so you free it from the trauma <br>Trauma Trauma <br>Trauma Trauma <br>Everyone has their own trauma trauma <br>Trauma Trauma <br>Trauma just like me <br>Oh, trauma <br>If I could get over this trauma trauma <br>Trauma, trauma <br>Oh, everyone, everyone has their own trauma <br>Oh, their own trauma <br>Some are big and some are much larger <br>Oh, but they come from our mothers and fathers <br>Among others <br><br>I got the paper from the lawn today <br>Don't get out that much these days <br>Anyway, but how can I tell you if I don't know what to say <br>Remember when we used to speak between the stars <br>And I see you with flamingos in the yard <br>But how can I love you if I don't know who you are, yeah <br>How can I love you if I don't know who you are <br><br>Caution <br>Cau caution <br>Cau caution <br>Cau cau cau caution <br>Caution, baby <br>Cau cau caution, baby]]></content><category term="Foxygen" label="Foxygen"/><category term="Trauma" label="Trauma"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Upon_A_Hill/</id><title>Foxygen - Upon A Hill - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:17:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:17:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Upon_A_Hill/" title="Foxygen - Upon A Hill - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I sit upon a hill <br>And through the windowsill, she slowly sings a song for me <br>And in her eyes, hands me my disguise <br>And served upon a plate, my heart will slowly rot and die and just be <br>And if I ever see the sun, free for everyone <br>Not just for me Not just for me <br><br>Someday I'm gonna sit myself right down that hillside there and see <br><br>And if our love shall die <br>Threw our souls up in the sky and candelabra in the sea <br>Sing a song for me <br>You wanna be so fine <br>And just be speaking with our minds <br>And just be laughing at the trees <br>And if you see me, give a sign <br>And just sing a song for me <br>Oh, the hills roll down and the silence <br>Every living creature's sound <br>Wild flamingos dance on spaceships with black fire in the mouth <br>Sing a song for me <br><br>If you see it then just sing a song for me <br>If you see it then just sing a song for me <br>If you see it then just sing a song for me]]></content><category term="Foxygen" label="Foxygen"/><category term="Upon A Hill" label="Upon A Hill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/On_Lankershim/</id><title>Foxygen - On Lankershim - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:17:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:17:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/On_Lankershim/" title="Foxygen - On Lankershim - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And it all but seems my lifetime dreams have ended <br>And I know some people hope they won't come true <br>On Lankershim, Lankershim <br>I can't start to live here anymore <br>And I can see from mango trees a memory <br>Of locked upon the pause of death of you <br><br>Well it just gets bigger till you can't seem to figure out <br>I walk away but I still can't seem to figure it out <br>I walk away, yeah <br>I walk away, I walk away <br>I walk away, I walk away <br><br>When someone loves you but you just can't figure it out <br>Just walk away, just walk away, just walk away <br>Oh, you walked away <br>You walked away <br><br>Well, we all spent time trying to make it <br>But you spent your money getting high <br>Well I know can make it back 'cause I'm only 25 <br>And my friend, she's only 20 <br>And she's an actress and so far <br>She said, you know, she said she can get me parts]]></content><category term="Foxygen" label="Foxygen"/><category term="On Lankershim" label="On Lankershim"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/America/</id><title>Foxygen - America - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:17:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:17:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/America/" title="Foxygen - America - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Merry Christmas from the pines <br>Hallelujah, and then <br>Just another wish, just another dream <br>Just a witch who comforts you when you're dying <br>When you're dying <br><br>America <br>America <br><br>I cry, Lord, to have used you <br>How could I, of all, to have used you <br><br>If you're already there <br>Then you're already dead <br>If you're living in America, whoa <br>Our heroes are bred <br>They just got nothing to lose <br>Because they're all living in America, whoa <br>In America, whoa <br><br>And the movie girl said <br>You walked in on set <br>But you only play yourself, you're Hollywood]]></content><category term="Foxygen" label="Foxygen"/><category term="America" label="America"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Mrs_Adams/</id><title>Foxygen - Mrs. Adams - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:17:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:17:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Mrs_Adams/" title="Foxygen - Mrs. Adams - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here I am <br>In this Hollywood bar <br>Press my face against the glass <br>Can't you see I'm making reservations <br>Ah, for her birthday <br>Hey, Mrs Adams <br>What you doing now with your gun in your mouth <br><br>You jokers and clowns you just feel down <br>Hey <br><br>Oh, I got to go with you <br>Don't you believe 'em <br>Do you seem 'em coming down <br>'Cause you'll end up in the ground <br>Ah hey, Jackie <br>Can't you seem 'em coming down from her attic <br>That's me and it doesn't feel down <br>You just feel down on your birthday <br>Yeah, go on Mrs Adams with your corpse in her attic on her birthday <br> to seventy <br>Oh, God, it's almost eleven <br>Whoa, you got to go <br>You got to go <br><br>Oh, I got to go <br><br>Poor Mrs Adams in the snow <br>Now I'm hanging from her robe <br><br>Huh <br>Just hang on, Mrs Adams <br>You spend your money now but you know you got to wait, yeah <br>Just hang on, Mrs Adams <br>Put the pieces back down and crack 'em together <br>Just hang on, Mrs Adams <br>You spend your money now but you know you got to wait, yeah <br>Just hang on, Mrs Adams <br>Put the pieces back down and crack 'em together <br><br>Mrs Adams]]></content><category term="Foxygen" label="Foxygen"/><category term="Mrs. Adams" label="Mrs. Adams"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Avalon/</id><title>Foxygen - Avalon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:17:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:17:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Avalon/" title="Foxygen - Avalon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They say that Avalon's playing a dream <br>Sometimes love just isn't what it seems <br>In the garden of love <br>Garden of love <br>In the garden of love <br>Ah, Sunset Boulevard, nightmare dreams <br>Take this candle off the porcelain scene <br>In the garden of love <br>Avalon <br>In the garden of love <br><br>Grab your favorite sweater, we're in for nasty weather <br><br>In the gardens of Avalon <br>It's in the garden of Avalon <br>Oh, in Avalon <br>It's in the garden of love with you <br>Oh, Avalon <br>It's in the garden of Avalon <br>Avalon, in the garden of love with you <br><br>Grab your favorite sweater, we're in for nasty weather <br><br>In the gardens of Avalon <br>It's in the garden of Avalon <br>The garden of love of Avalon <br>In the garden of love with you <br>Oh, Avalon <br>It's in the garden of Avalon <br>In Avalon <br>In the garden of love with you <br>Oh]]></content><category term="Foxygen" label="Foxygen"/><category term="Avalon" label="Avalon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Follow_The_Leader/</id><title>Foxygen - Follow The Leader - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:18:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:18:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Foxygen/Follow_The_Leader/" title="Foxygen - Follow The Leader - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey baby, you know it's true <br>I'm in love with you <br>Babe, but you never Never gonna be what I want <br>No, you're never gonna be Never gonna be what I want <br>Yeah, I was shotgunned lovers on the avenue <br>Yes, it's true, he's much too old for you <br>Babe, but you never Never gonna be what I want <br>No, you're never gonna be Never gonna be what I want <br><br>I know sometimes everyone wants to be someone else <br>So follow the leader <br>Follow the leader <br>Follow the leader <br>And the leader is you <br>Yeah, follow the leader <br>Follow the leader <br>And the leader is you, yeah <br><br>Hot flash Fun in the summertime <br>There's no better way to spend our time, baby <br>But that's never Never really what's it's about <br>No, no, no, no, that's never really what it's about <br>Oh yeah, I know what you're thinking <br>You could never get me to cheat on you <br>Babe, but it's never Never really what's it's about <br>Stop making me feel Never really what's it's about <br><br>I know sometimes everyone wants to be someone else <br>Oh, you people know that's true, yeah <br>So follow the leader <br>Follow the leader <br>Just follow the leader <br>And the leader is you <br>Yeah, you follow the leader <br>Follow, follow the leader <br>And the leader is you, yeah, you]]></content><category term="Foxygen" label="Foxygen"/><category term="Follow The Leader" label="Follow The Leader"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Munelin/Neon_Avatar/</id><title>Munelin - Neon Avatar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:18:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:18:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Munelin/Neon_Avatar/" title="Munelin - Neon Avatar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꿈에선 그런 일이 일어나곤 하지 <br>모습은 달라도 그게 바로 나래 <br>네온 빛 빛나는 몸 눈부시던 너 <br>초라한 날 일으켜 하늘을 나네 <br>그런 너 내 앞에 나타난 거야 <br>믿을 수 없게 같은 모습으로 오 <br>너도 날 좋아하게 될 거야 꿈처럼 <br>너도 날 사랑하게 될 거야 <br>한겨울 밤의 꿈처럼 <br>너도 날 좋아하게 될 거야 꿈처럼 <br>네온 불빛 아래 너의 그 환한 미소 <br>나를 미치게 해 <br>지금 이 순간만큼은 꿈이 아니길 <br>기도하고 있어 <br>너도 날 본 적 있을까 날 기억할까 <br>그날 밤 꿈처럼 <br>어서 와 내게로 널 바라보고 있어 <br>너를 기다려 <br>너도 날 좋아하게 될 거야 꿈처럼 <br>너도 날 사랑하게 될 거야 <br>한여름 밤의 꿈처럼 <br>너도 날 좋아하게 될 거야 꿈처럼 <br>너도 날 사랑하게 될 거야 <br>한겨울 밤의 꿈처럼 <br>네온 불빛 아래 너의 그 환한 미소 <br>나를 미치게 해 <br>지금 이 순간만큼은 꿈이 아니길 <br>기도하고 있어 <br>너도 날 본 적 있을까 날 기억할까 <br>그날 밤 꿈처럼 <br>어서 와 내게로 널 바라보고 있어 <br>너를 기다려 <br>너의 침대 머리맡 왕자님 <br>변신한 호두까기 인형처럼 <br>푸른 하늘 날으는 네온 빛 <br>아바타 토루쿠막토처럼 <br>너도 날 본 적 있을까 <br>날 기억할까 <br>그날 밤 꿈처럼 <br>어서 와 내게로 <br>널 바라보고 있어 <br>너를 기다려 <br>]]></content><category term="Munelin" label="Munelin"/><category term="Neon Avatar" label="Neon Avatar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬로우폴_Slowpaul/너에게_갈게/</id><title>슬로우폴 (Slowpaul) - 너에게 갈게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:19:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:19:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%ED%8F%B4_Slowpaul/%EB%84%88%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%EA%B0%88%EA%B2%8C/" title="슬로우폴 (Slowpaul) - 너에게 갈게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 몰랐었어 내가 누구였는지 <br>난 그저 널 찾아 헤매었던거야 <br>잘 몰랐었어 거울 볼 수 없었지 <br>바람에 사라질 순 없을까 <br>가을 향기에 우린 처음 만났지 <br>겨울 바다와 그토록 아름다운 <br>눈부신 너에게 갈게 <br>추억 속 너에게 갈게 <br>예전 그 모습으로 <br>넌 그대로겠지 <br>아련한 너에게 갈게 <br>추억 속 너에게 갈게 <br>이제서야 알게 된 <br>내 모습이라도 괜찮겠니 <br>눈부신 너에게 갈게 <br>추억 속 너에게 갈게 <br>함께 한 시간 속에 <br>난 알 수 없었지 <br>아련한 너에게 갈게 <br>추억 속 너에게 갈게 <br>다시 만난 너에게 <br>영원한 사랑을 약속할게 <br>]]></content><category term="슬로우폴 (Slowpaul)" label="슬로우폴 (Slowpaul)"/><category term="너에게 갈게" label="너에게 갈게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬로우폴_Slowpaul/사랑해_기도해/</id><title>슬로우폴 (Slowpaul) - 사랑해 기도해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:20:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:20:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%ED%8F%B4_Slowpaul/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84%ED%95%B4/" title="슬로우폴 (Slowpaul) - 사랑해 기도해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 없이 난 할 수 없다는 걸 <br>느꼈죠 알았죠 <br>그대 역시도 나와 같기만을 <br>바라요 원해요 <br>그대만큼 사랑할 수 있는 사람 <br>다시는 없겠죠 <br>사랑은 할수록 두려움도 커져요 <br>그대만 있어요 <br>그대 날 지켜줘요 <br>언제까지나 <br>그대 곁에 있어줘요 <br>언제까지나 <br>그대 날 지켜줘요 <br>언제까지나 <br>그대 곁에 있어줘요 <br>언제까지나 <br>사랑해 기도해 우리 영원을 <br>사랑해 기도해 우리 영원을 <br>사랑해 기도해 우리 영원을 <br>사랑해 기도해 우리 영원을 <br>사랑해 기도해 우리 영원을 <br>사랑해 기도해 우리 영원을 <br>사랑해 기도해 우리 영원을 <br>사랑해 기도해 우리 영원을 <br>]]></content><category term="슬로우폴 (Slowpaul)" label="슬로우폴 (Slowpaul)"/><category term="사랑해 기도해" label="사랑해 기도해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/슬로우폴_Slowpaul/숨/</id><title>슬로우폴 (Slowpaul) - 숨 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:20:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:20:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%ED%8F%B4_Slowpaul/%EC%88%A8/" title="슬로우폴 (Slowpaul) - 숨 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 돌아가고 싶어 <br>그 때 그 곳으로 <br>넌 너는 없겠지만 난 <br>지금 여길 떠나 널 찾아 헤매어 <br>어디든 달려가 <br>마음껏 숨쉬며 살 수 있어 <br>난 물어보지 않아도 <br>알 수 있을 것 같아 <br>좋은 사람 못됐던 <br>그 때로 돌아가 널 찾아 헤매어 <br>어디든 달려가 <br>마음껏 숨쉬며 살 수 있어 <br>보이지 않았던 너의 사랑과 <br>후회로 가득 찬 <br>우리의 시간 속으로 <br>그 때로 돌아가 모든걸 이해해준 <br>널 절대 놓지 않을게 <br>널 위한 눈물로 사랑할게 <br>]]></content><category term="슬로우폴 (Slowpaul)" label="슬로우폴 (Slowpaul)"/><category term="숨" label="숨"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도민/동암역_2번출구_Feat_김무성__성지영/</id><title>도민 - 동암역 2번출구 (Feat. 김무성 &amp; 성지영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:23:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:23:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EB%AF%BC/%EB%8F%99%EC%95%94%EC%97%AD_2%EB%B2%88%EC%B6%9C%EA%B5%AC_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EB%AC%B4%EC%84%B1__%EC%84%B1%EC%A7%80%EC%98%81/" title="도민 - 동암역 2번출구 (Feat. 김무성 &amp; 성지영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이별을 준비하는 사람의 <br>눈을 본 적 있나요 <br>아마 당신도 그 눈을 <br>쳐다보진 못했겠죠 <br>애꿎은 하늘만 바라보고 <br>내 손을 자꾸 만지작거리는 게 <br>아쉬운 건지 <br>아니면 마지막이라 <br>그대도 슬픈 건지 <br>이유를 알아도 안되겠죠 <br>이미 돌아선 그대 맘이기에 <br>이 손을 붙잡진 못하겠죠 <br>이 손을 놓아주면 끝이 날 텐데 <br>그래도 그댈 볼 수는 없고 <br>이렇게 시간이 흐르고 아프고 <br>널 보면 또 눈물이 흐를 텐데 <br>그러면 그대 미안할까봐 <br>이렇게 그대의 그림자 바라보다 <br>이젠 이 손을 좀 놓아줄래 <br>사람들이 자꾸만 쳐다보잖아 <br>힘들겠지만 날 좀 보내줄래 <br>우린 아니란 걸 너도 알고 있잖아 <br>마지막까지 난 <br>나만 생각해 <br>지금까지 많은걸 맞춰줬으니 <br>이번에도 내게 맞춰 주길 바래 <br>감정이란 게 참 무섭더라 <br>끝까지 갈 수 있을 거라 생각했지 <br>너의 아픔 <br>내가 안아주고 싶었는데 <br>생각보다 나는 어리더라 <br>미안하다 <br>더 이상 할 말 없다 <br>우리 이만 돌아서자 <br>사실은 이미 나는 보고 있었죠 <br>돌아선 그대의 마음을 <br>그 맘을 돌리기엔 늦고 말았죠 <br>이 손을 놓아주면 끝이 날 텐데 <br>그래도 그댈 볼 수는 없고 <br>이렇게 시간이 흐르고 아프고 <br>널 보면 또 눈물이 흐를 텐데 <br>그러면 그대 미안할까봐 <br>이렇게 그대의 그림자 바라보다 <br>내 앞에 더 이상 너는 없는데 <br>나 이제 울어도 되죠 <br>조금만 여기에 멈춰서 이렇게 <br>이별을 준비 했었나 봐요 <br>나도 너 없는 거릴 걷고 있네요 <br>이제는 나 혼자 <br>여전히 이렇게 <br>]]></content><category term="도민" label="도민"/><category term="동암역 2번출구 (Feat. 김무성 &amp; 성지영)" label="동암역 2번출구 (Feat. 김무성 &amp; 성지영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/당신이라는_사람_Feat_허진호/</id><title>Ryan - 당신이라는 사람 (Feat. 허진호) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:23:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:23:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC%EB%8A%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C_Feat_%ED%97%88%EC%A7%84%ED%98%B8/" title="Ryan - 당신이라는 사람 (Feat. 허진호) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[고마워 셀 수 없이 <br>늘 말해봐도 <br>안되는 걸 알죠 <br>미안하단 말 하지 말라 <br>날 다그쳐도 <br>맘은 그렇지 않죠 <br>늘 미안한 마음뿐인데 <br>그댄 매번 다시 또 <br>나를 안아주네요 <br>그댄 나룻배를 타고도 <br>내 방향이 되죠 <br>내가 비를 맞을 땐 <br>내 우산이 되고 <br>혹시 사람들이 뭐라 해도 <br>늘 내 편에 서서 <br>나의 침묵이 되죠 <br>그게 당신이라는 사람이죠 <br>당신에게 높고 <br>거친 파도 몰려와도 <br>늘 모른척했던 <br>추억 한순간 <br>주지 않았었던 <br>바보 같은 날 <br>왜 감싸주나요 <br>늘 감사한 마음뿐인데 <br>그댄 오늘 다시 또 <br>나를 안아주네요 <br>그댄 나룻배를 타고도 <br>내 방향이 되죠 <br>내가 비를 맞을 땐 <br>내 우산이 되고 <br>혹시 사람들이 뭐라 해도 <br>늘 내 편에 서서 <br>나의 침묵이 되죠 <br>그게 당신이라는 사람이죠 <br>수천 번을 나 되새겨 봐도 <br>매 순간을 추슬러 보지만 <br>어느새 그댈 <br>바라보고 있을 때면 <br>슬픈 표정만이 <br>지어져만 가는데 <br>비바람을 막아주고도 <br>날 향해 미소 짓네요 <br>내가 길을 나설 땐 <br>늘 햇빛이 되고 <br>항상 그러고도 <br>부족할까 걱정하면서 <br>나의 슬픔이 되죠 <br>그게 당신이라는 사람이죠 <br>]]></content><category term="Ryan" label="Ryan"/><category term="당신이라는 사람 (Feat. 허진호)" label="당신이라는 사람 (Feat. 허진호)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/Dont_Tell_Me_Why_Feat_Addy/</id><title>Ryan - Don`t Tell Me Why (Feat. Addy) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:23:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:23:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/Dont_Tell_Me_Why_Feat_Addy/" title="Ryan - Don`t Tell Me Why (Feat. Addy) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[행복한 듯이 <br>그렇게 웃지 좀 마요 <br>미소를 보는 일이 <br>오늘은 그저 달갑지만은 않네요 <br>그대가 없는 좁은 방 <br>한 켠에서 공허만 가득한 맘 <br>알 수 없는 정적만이 가득하지만 <br>but don’t tell me why <br>그냥 그대로 있어줘요 <br>내 마음은 그댈 위하고 <br>그대 미소 그대 향기 지켜야 해 <br>so I tell you why <br>나 떠나던 날 <br>아픔 끝났던 너였으니 <br>이 미소 이 향기 간직한 채로 <br>so don’t tell me why <br>그대 없는 곳에서 <br>바람이 따듯한 오늘 <br>내 마음만이 차가운 날 <br>잘못 내 마음을 <br>아직 그대 옆에 뒀나 봐요 <br>but don’t tell me why <br>그냥 그대로 있어줘요 <br>내 마음은 그댈 위하고 <br>그대 미소 그대 향기 지켜야 해 <br>so I tell you why <br>나 떠나던 날 <br>아픔 끝났던 너였으니 <br>이 미소 이 향기 간직한 채로 <br>그대 없는 어둠 익숙해지겠죠 <br>수많은 날이 지나면 <br>언제나 그랬듯이 너 보란 듯이 <br>나도 웃고 있을 테니 <br>so don’t tell me why <br>so I tell you why <br>나 떠나던 날 <br>아픔 끝났던 너였으니 <br>이 미소 이 향기 간직한 채로 <br>so don’t tell me why <br>]]></content><category term="Ryan" label="Ryan"/><category term="Don`t Tell Me Why (Feat. Addy)" label="Don`t Tell Me Why (Feat. Addy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/널_보고_있으면_Women_Ver_Feat_반미선/</id><title>Ryan - 널 보고 있으면 (Women Ver.) (Feat. 반미선) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:23:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:23:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/%EB%84%90_%EB%B3%B4%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9E%88%EC%9C%BC%EB%A9%B4_Women_Ver_Feat_%EB%B0%98%EB%AF%B8%EC%84%A0/" title="Ryan - 널 보고 있으면 (Women Ver.) (Feat. 반미선) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랜만에 길을 나서고 <br>반가운 바람이 나를 스치네 <br>혼자 있어야 할 곳 <br>또 우리 같이 걸으며 <br>수많은 기도 <br>들어주시고 날 향해서 <br>이젠 너란 축복을 <br>알듯이 내려주잖아 <br>따듯했던 네 목소리와 <br>내 옆에 있던 미소 <br>이 시간을 보낸다는 것마저 <br>난 싫어져 <br>서로가 아니면 <br>필요 없는 두 사람 <br>이젠 내 맘속에 가득해 <br>널 보고 있으면 <br>you are my everything <br>everything everything <br>나의 전부 너란 사람이죠 <br>날 보고 있으면 <br>있으면 있으면 <br>you are my everything <br>everything everything <br>나의 전부 너란 사람이죠 <br>차가운 공기마저도 <br>바꾸던 시간은 <br>내 맘속에 어둠이란 건 <br>모두 다 지워져 <br>서로가 아니면 <br>필요 없는 두 사람 <br>이젠 내 맘속에 가득해 <br>널 보고 있으면 <br>you are my everything <br>everything everything <br>나의 전부 너란 사람이죠 <br>날 보고 있으면 <br>있으면 있으면 <br>you are my everything <br>everything everything <br>나의 전부 너란 사람이죠 <br>]]></content><category term="Ryan" label="Ryan"/><category term="널 보고 있으면 (Women Ver.) (Feat. 반미선)" label="널 보고 있으면 (Women Ver.) (Feat. 반미선)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/널_보고_있으면_Man_Ver_Feat_장규철/</id><title>Ryan - 널 보고 있으면 (Man Ver.) (Feat. 장규철) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:23:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:23:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/%EB%84%90_%EB%B3%B4%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9E%88%EC%9C%BC%EB%A9%B4_Man_Ver_Feat_%EC%9E%A5%EA%B7%9C%EC%B2%A0/" title="Ryan - 널 보고 있으면 (Man Ver.) (Feat. 장규철) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랜만에 길을 나서고 <br>반가운 바람이 <br>나를 스치네 <br>혼자 있어야 할 곳 <br>또 우리같이 걸으며 <br>수많은 기도 들어주시고 <br>날 향해서 <br>이젠 너란 축복을 <br>알듯이 내려주잖아 <br>따듯했던 네 목소리와 <br>내 옆에 있던 미소 <br>이 시간을 보낸다는 <br>것마저 난 싫어져 <br>서로가 아니면 <br>필요 없는 두 사람 <br>이젠 내 맘속에 가득해 <br>널 보고 있으면 <br>you are my everything <br>everything everything <br>나의 전부 너란 사람이죠 <br>날 보고 있으면 <br>있으면 있으면 <br>you are my everything <br>everything everything <br>나의 전부 너란 사람이죠 <br>차가운 공기마저도 <br>바꾸던 시간은 <br>내 맘속에 어둠이란 건 <br>모두 다 지워져 <br>서로가 아니면 <br>필요 없는 두 사람 <br>이젠 이 맘속에 가득해 <br>예 워어어 워어어어 우 <br>you are my everything <br>everything everything <br>나의 전부 너란 사람이죠 <br>날 보고 있으면 <br>있으면 있으면 <br>you are my everything <br>everything everything <br>나의 전부 너란 사람이죠 <br>]]></content><category term="Ryan" label="Ryan"/><category term="널 보고 있으면 (Man Ver.) (Feat. 장규철)" label="널 보고 있으면 (Man Ver.) (Feat. 장규철)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/어른이_돼야_해_Feat_MyleD/</id><title>Ryan - 어른이 돼야 해 (Feat. Myle.D) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:23:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:23:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/%EC%96%B4%EB%A5%B8%EC%9D%B4_%EB%8F%BC%EC%95%BC_%ED%95%B4_Feat_MyleD/" title="Ryan - 어른이 돼야 해 (Feat. Myle.D) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[점점 할 일이 많아져 <br>자유롭게 놀던 우리가 <br>어느새 앞만을 보며 <br>달려가고 있는 걸 <br>누가 먼저라고 할 것 없이 <br>각자의 길들로 가기 시작했던 <br>그 어느 날에 혼자인 이 순간에 <br>내 맘은 공허해 <br>그래 우린 어른이 돼야 해 <br>밤의 밑에 나누던 <br>너와 나의 이야기들 <br>다 잊어버리는 <br>그런 어른이 돼야 해 <br>그래 그런 어른이 되갈게 <br>힘든 일마저도 모른 척 <br>그냥 미소 짓는 <br>그런 어른이 되갈게 <br>내겐 중요치 않은 <br>나 하는 이야기들 <br>어느 날 어른이 되면 <br>나도 편안할 텐데 <br>그래 이 순간은 하릴없이 <br>날 아무도 위로해주지 못했고 <br>이 어린 나만 추억의 한켠에 <br>늘 겉을 맴도네 <br>나는 이제 어른이 돼야 해 <br>모든 걸 알고 있는 <br>저기 보이는 모습처럼 <br>이런 어른이 돼야 해 <br>그래 이런 어른이 되갈게 <br>맘이 아파와 져도 <br>뭐든 배려하며 웃음 짓는 <br>이런 어른이 돼야 해 <br>]]></content><category term="Ryan" label="Ryan"/><category term="어른이 돼야 해 (Feat. Myle.D)" label="어른이 돼야 해 (Feat. Myle.D)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한울/하나님이_이_세상을/</id><title>한울 - 하나님이 이 세상을 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:23:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:23:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%9A%B8/%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%B4_%EC%9D%B4_%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81%EC%9D%84/" title="한울 - 하나님이 이 세상을 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나님이 이세상을 <br>이처럼 사랑 하셨으니 <br>이는 저를 믿는자 마다 <br>영생을 얻게하려 하심이라 <br>주께서 이땅에 오심은 <br>심판하려 하심이 아니요 <br>세상을 구원하려 하심이라 <br>빛으로 오신 예수님 <br>온세상을 비추시네 <br>어둠권세 물러가고 <br>영광의 빛 비추시네 <br>죽음이기신 예수님 <br>부활영광 나타내사 <br>사망권세 물러가고 <br>주님나라 임하시네 <br>할렐루야 <br>하나님이 이세상을 <br>이처럼 사랑 하셨으니 <br>이는 저를 믿는자 마다 <br>영생을 얻게하려 하심이라 <br>주께서 이땅에 오심은 <br>심판하려 하심이 아니요 <br>세상을 구원하려 하심이라 <br>빛으로 오신 예수님 <br>온세상을 비추시네 <br>어둠권세 물러가고 <br>영광의 빛 비추시네 <br>죽음이기신 예수님 <br>부활영광 나타내사 <br>사망권세 물러가고 <br>주님나라 임하시네 <br>할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>아아 <br>할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>아아 <br>할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>아아 <br>할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>할렐루야 <br>아아 <br>아멘 <br>할렐루야 <br>]]></content><category term="한울" label="한울"/><category term="하나님이 이 세상을" label="하나님이 이 세상을"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Crucial_Acapella/</id><title>New Edition - Crucial (Acapella) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Crucial_Acapella/" title="New Edition - Crucial (Acapella) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heart, beating strong <br>I was serious my love was furious <br>For you, only you, oh baby <br>Darling I don't know why <br>I can't leave you alone <br>You thrill me to the bone <br>You're the one <br>Obsession oh baby <br><br>Don't you know it was a crucial lovin' <br>Cru cial <br>Crucial lovin' <br>Cru cial <br><br>Chills, over me <br>Different from the rest <br>I won't settle for less <br>Hello, won't take no oh baby <br><br>From now on you and I <br>Stood the test of time <br>Yet still you're on my mind <br>Always, night and day oh baby <br><br>Don't you know it was a crucial lovinI never knew love could be so crucial <br>Cru cial oh, yeah <br>Crucial lovin' Girl, you are my last time, sugar <br>Cru cial baby, you're the one <br><br>Don't you know it was crucial lovin From now on, baby <br>Cru cial Don't you know it was crucial love <br>Crucial lovin Down to the, down to the bone <br>Cru cial heh heh heh <br><br>I have more than told you <br>Girl I've got to show you <br>Feelings over load extreme <br><br>For the very first time <br>Girl you are my last time <br>You have taken over me <br><br>Don't you know it was crucial lovin Baby, I don't know why, oh <br>Cru cial You're on my mind everyday <br>Crucial loving I never knew love could be so crucial <br>Cru cial Oh, girl Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>Don't you know it was crucial lovin If you could've heard me this way <br>Cru cial You're the one You're the one <br>Crucial lovin You're the one, you're the one, for me <br>Cru cial No one else <br><br>Don't you know it was crucial lovin' Girl this is my last chance <br>Cru cial So I'm begging you <br>Crucial lovin' It's crucial, It's crucial <br>Cru cial Girl <br><br>Don't you know it was crucial lovin' Down to the, down to the, down to the bone <br>Cru cial Down to the, down to the bone]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Crucial (Acapella)" label="Crucial (Acapella)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/NE_Heart_Break_Faux_Live_Ver/</id><title>New Edition - N.E. Heart Break (Faux Live Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/NE_Heart_Break_Faux_Live_Ver/" title="New Edition - N.E. Heart Break (Faux Live Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In store signing autographs at the mall <br>Next in line was a fly girl standing tall <br>Signed my name and said give me a call baby ya know <br><br>The girl screamed and fainted panic on the floor <br>The body gaurd pulled us the back door <br>I never saw her anymore it was an in store heartbreak <br><br>Live at five interview for Channel 2 <br>Saw a cutie thought she was on the TV cre <br>She said after the show I'll be waiting for you cool <br>After the show she got into the car and what a scence <br>Her dad was the driver of the limosuine <br>I didn't know she was only thirteen <br>It was a young girl heartbreak <br><br>People think we don't get lonely <br>But we're far away from home <br>One minute 20,000 people <br>But then they go home, we're alone <br><br>It's off to another city <br>Where everybody knows my name <br>But when I meet that perfect honey <br>Is it me she wants or is it my fame <br><br>Girlies and groupies and parties all night <br>Is the life that can lead you to a NE heartbreak <br>From city to city our friends and our fans <br>They're the ones who can keep us from having <br>NE heartbreak <br><br>Center stage NE was groovin' <br>The beatwas hard <br>And the girlies were movin' <br>There she was third row center coolin' <br>She was cold <br><br>Last note of the last song <br>House lights up they came on <br>When I looked she was gone <br>It was a 3rd row heartbreak <br><br>People think our life is easy <br>'cause they think we've got it made <br>But we're living underpressure <br>Just to be on top <br>And to give the best that we can give you <br>And to never let you down <br>We'll keep strivin' for perfection <br>NE heartbreak is coming to your town <br><br>Beware of NE heartbreak <br>Spreading fast and there's no cure <br>No need to run from heartache <br>It's gonna get you, get you for sure <br><br>Called up my girl and said <br>Meet me on the tour <br>I got a suite cold chillin' on the 50th floior <br>And I'll leave your ticket at the door <br>And baby don't forget the pumps <br><br>She lost her backstage pass and the room key <br>Then got stopped by hotel security <br>And I spent the whole night lonely <br>And it was a hotel heartbreak]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="N.E. Heart Break (Faux Live Ver.)" label="N.E. Heart Break (Faux Live Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Boys_To_Men_Extended_Vocal_Ver/</id><title>New Edition - Boys To Men (Extended Vocal Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Boys_To_Men_Extended_Vocal_Ver/" title="New Edition - Boys To Men (Extended Vocal Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up can be a pain <br>You're not an man until you come of age <br>We've given up our teenage years <br>In the effort to pursue our career <br>Who assumes responsibility <br>Of having to support our families <br>Who's protecting us from harm <br>Is there anyone around <br>That we can trust <br><br>So we search for answers to our questions <br>Looking for a answer <br>No answers but we're taught a lesson everytime <br>Through mistakes we've learned to gather wisdom <br>Cause lifes responsibility falls in our hand oh <br><br>Keep on learning <br>Keep on growing <br>'cause wisdom helps us understand <br>We're maturing <br>Without knowing <br>These are the things that change boys to men <br><br>Oh the goals we set may exceed reality <br>Cause failurealways is a possibility <br>Who can tell us that we're wrong <br>It's up to us to figure out <br>What life is all about <br><br>So we search for answers to questions <br>Looking for the answers <br>No answers but we're taught a lesson everytime <br>Through mistakes we've learned to gather wisdom <br>'cause wisdom helps us see our responsibility <br><br>I know it is hard sometimes growing up can be a pain <br>Know what I mean know what I mean <br>Is all you have to do is <br>All you have to do is hold on hold on hold on no no no no no baby]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Boys To Men (Extended Vocal Ver.)" label="Boys To Men (Extended Vocal Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Can_You_Stand_The_Rain_Extended_Ver/</id><title>New Edition - Can You Stand The Rain (Extended Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Can_You_Stand_The_Rain_Extended_Ver/" title="New Edition - Can You Stand The Rain (Extended Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On a perfect day I know that I can count on you when that's not possible tell <br>Me can you weather the storm <br><br>Cause I need some body who will stand by me through the good times and bad <br>Times she will always, always be right there <br><br>Sunny days everybody loves them tell me baby can you stand the rain storms <br>Will come this we know for sure this we know for sure can you stand the rain <br><br>yeah yeah love unconditional I'm not asking just of you and girl to make it <br>Last I'll do whatever needs to be done <br><br>But I need somebody who will stand by me, when it's tough she won't run she <br>Will always, be right there for me <br><br>Sunny days every body loves them tell me baby can you stand the rain storms <br>Will come ricky I know I know all the days won't be perfect this we know for <br>Sure but tell me can you stand it can you stand the rain <br><br>Can you stand the rain 4x <br><br>No pressure no pressure from me baby this we know for sure cause I want <br>You and I need you and I love you girl <br><br>Will you be there for me <br><br>Come on baby lets go get wet <br><br>Can you stand the rain 10x <br><br>Can you stand the rain <br>Will you be there girl <br>Storms will come for sure <br>Can you stand the rain <br><br>Yeah it's hard but I'll know I'll be right there baby yeah yeah yeah]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Can You Stand The Rain (Extended Ver.)" label="Can You Stand The Rain (Extended Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Youre_Not_My_Kind_Of_Girl_Extended_Ver/</id><title>New Edition - You`re Not My Kind Of Girl (Extended Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Youre_Not_My_Kind_Of_Girl_Extended_Ver/" title="New Edition - You`re Not My Kind Of Girl (Extended Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh girl I know that you're <br>Attracted to me <br>And I should feel the same <br>About you <br>There's just something wrong <br>I don't know what it is <br>That keeps us from becoming a two <br><br>It's not your looks, you're very pretty <br>It's not your style, the way you dress is oh so fresh <br>It's not the way that you carry yourself <br><br>Oh, girl I'm sorry <br>You're not my kind of girl <br>Case you're the kind of girl That a man's dreams are made of <br><br>Oh girl I'm sorry <br>You're not my kind of girl <br><br>Cause you're the kind of girl <br>That a man would be proud to call his own <br><br>Girl listen to me <br>You're so pretty <br>I wouldn't cgange a thing about you <br>But I've been in love before <br>So I know how it feels <br>And the chemistry just isn't there]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="You`re Not My Kind Of Girl (Extended Ver.)" label="You`re Not My Kind Of Girl (Extended Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Crucial_Dance_Remix/</id><title>New Edition - Crucial (Dance Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Crucial_Dance_Remix/" title="New Edition - Crucial (Dance Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heart, beating strong <br>I was serious my love was furious <br>For you, only you, oh baby <br>Darling I don't know why <br>I can't leave you alone <br>You thrill me to the bone <br>You're the one <br>Obsession oh baby <br><br>Don't you know it was a crucial lovin' <br>Cru cial <br>Crucial lovin' <br>Cru cial <br><br>Chills, over me <br>Different from the rest <br>I won't settle for less <br>Hello, won't take no oh baby <br><br>From now on you and I <br>Stood the test of time <br>Yet still you're on my mind <br>Always, night and day oh baby <br><br>Don't you know it was a crucial lovinI never knew love could be so crucial <br>Cru cial oh, yeah <br>Crucial lovin' Girl, you are my last time, sugar <br>Cru cial baby, you're the one <br><br>Don't you know it was crucial lovin From now on, baby <br>Cru cial Don't you know it was crucial love <br>Crucial lovin Down to the, down to the bone <br>Cru cial heh heh heh <br><br>I have more than told you <br>Girl I've got to show you <br>Feelings over load extreme <br><br>For the very first time <br>Girl you are my last time <br>You have taken over me <br><br>Don't you know it was crucial lovin Baby, I don't know why, oh <br>Cru cial You're on my mind everyday <br>Crucial loving I never knew love could be so crucial <br>Cru cial Oh, girl Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>Don't you know it was crucial lovin If you could've heard me this way <br>Cru cial You're the one You're the one <br>Crucial lovin You're the one, you're the one, for me <br>Cru cial No one else <br><br>Don't you know it was crucial lovin' Girl this is my last chance <br>Cru cial So I'm begging you <br>Crucial lovin' It's crucial, It's crucial <br>Cru cial Girl <br><br>Don't you know it was crucial lovin' Down to the, down to the, down to the bone <br>Cru cial Down to the, down to the bone]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Crucial (Dance Remix)" label="Crucial (Dance Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/If_It_Isnt_Love_Club_Mix/</id><title>New Edition - If It Isn`t Love (Club Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/If_It_Isnt_Love_Club_Mix/" title="New Edition - If It Isn`t Love (Club Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't love her <br>I tried to tell myself <br>But you could see it in my eyes <br>So don't deny, I can't fool no one else <br>The truth is in the tears I cried <br><br>Cuz if it isn't love <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why does she stay on my mind <br>And if it isn't love <br>Why does it hurt so bad <br>Make me feel so sad inside <br>If it isn't love <br><br>I told her I'd never fall in love <br>But now I know better <br><br>How does it feel <br>I can't describe this feeling <br>That came when I saw her last night Ohh <br>She got to me <br>I'll let you know the reason <br>I saw her with another guy <br><br>So if it isn't love <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why does she stay on my mind <br>And if it isn't love <br>Why does it hurt so bad <br>Make me feel so sad inside <br><br>And if it isn't love <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why does she stay on my mind <br>And if it isn't love <br>Why does it hurt so bad <br>Make me feel so sad inside <br>If it isn't love <br><br>Maybe she'll take me back <br>Hey girl, He's begging <br>I made a big mistake <br>Want you to forgive him girl <br>Now I can feel it <br>He's never felt before <br>I really love her <br>Love her What <br><br>It took my heart <br>Shattered in a thousand pieces <br>Before I'd ever dropped my pride <br>Ohh Ohh Ohh <br>Losing love, worrying about my image <br>Really helped me realize <br><br>If it isn't love <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why does she stay on my mind <br>And if it isn't love <br>Why does it hurt so bad <br>Make me feel so sad inside]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="If It Isn`t Love (Club Mix)" label="If It Isn`t Love (Club Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Supernatural_From_Ghostbusters_II_Soundtrack/</id><title>New Edition - Supernatural (From `Ghostbusters II` Soundtrack) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Supernatural_From_Ghostbusters_II_Soundtrack/" title="New Edition - Supernatural (From `Ghostbusters II` Soundtrack) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Interplanetary <br>Interplanetary <br>Supernatural <br>Supernatural <br>Supernatural <br><br>Lookin' for that perfect honey <br>You'll find only in a dream <br>I searched around and still can't find her <br>I guess my wants are too extreme <br>Turned around, she caught my eye <br>Tell me am I seeing things <br>Just might be imagination <br>Goes insane and hauntin' me <br><br>This woman Supernatural <br>The way she looks Supernatural <br>The way she moves her body Supernatural <br>Everything about this honey is so supernatural <br><br>Supernatural <br><br>As I watch her move in closer <br>Perfect beauty she exceeds <br>Never question Mother Nature <br>She's an angel without wings <br>Nervous tension fills my body <br>I reach out to hold her hand <br>Tried to grab, can't get a handle <br>The girl is gone, she was never here <br><br>This woman, yeah Supernatural <br>The way she looks, uh huh Supernatural <br>The way she moves her body Supernatural <br>Something about that woman that makes me feel so good <br>Supernatural <br>The way she looks Supernatural <br>Supernatural baby, yeah Supernatural <br>Everything about this honey is so supernatural <br><br>I'm tired of this cloud <br>Taking over the invisible force <br>Are they controlling me <br>Naw, that's a corny way of thinking <br>Take two beats out to rethink <br>I'm taking heed to my dream 'cause it's kind of extreme <br>Yo, Ron, help me out <br>You know what I mean <br>Yeah, Biv, it's not that deep <br>Come roll with me and put that ghost to sleep <br><br>I can't hate How she's possessing me <br>Unearthly She's metaphysical, super beautiful <br>Seeing things Might be imagination <br>Heart said 'hey' 'Cause everything about this honey I love <br>Alright <br><br>Supernatural The way that she moves, mmm <br>Supernatural There's no doubt about it, yeah, yeah <br>Supernatural Oh, I know heaven must have sent you from above <br>Supernatural Yeah <br>Supernatural Oohhoohooooh <br>Supernatural Say, baby, say, baby <br>If I'm dreamin', if I'm dreamin' please don't wake me up, yeah <br>Supernatural <br>Supernatural See, I just wanna keep dreamin' <br>Supernatural Everything I want in a woman <br>Supernatural And I love her, and I love her, and I love <br>Supernatural <br>Supernatural <br>Supernatural]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Supernatural (From `Ghostbusters II` Soundtrack)" label="Supernatural (From `Ghostbusters II` Soundtrack)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Helplessly_In_Love/</id><title>New Edition - Helplessly In Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Helplessly_In_Love/" title="New Edition - Helplessly In Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Never knew the closing of a door <br>Could open up a heart <br>Since the day we met I've needed you <br>Needed you <br>In my life <br><br>To do and say the things that I <br>Needed to feel and hear <br>I'm just <br><br>Helplessly in love <br>Ooh <br>Don't know what to do, I'm <br>Helplessly in love <br>And the love in my heart <br>Is for you <br><br>I've always been a man who took control <br>But now I'm so helpless <br>Can't find the nerve, I get emotional <br>When you're around <br><br>And it's hard for me to tell you or <br>To show you what I feel <br>I'm just <br><br>Helplessly in love <br>Helpless <br>Ooh <br>Don't know what to do, I'm <br>Helplessly in love <br>And the love in my heart <br>Is for you <br>Baby, baby <br><br>I just can't understand <br>No I don't understand <br>Why my feelings get so confused <br>Why I'm like that <br>Why I love you like I do <br><br>So I picked out these three words that best <br>Describe the way I feel <br><br>I'm just <br><br>Helplessly in love <br>Ooooh <br>Don't know what to do, I'm <br>Helplessly in love <br>Uh, oh <br>Don't know what to do, I'm <br>Helplessly in love <br>And the love in my heart <br>Is for you <br><br>Helplessly in love <br>Baby, baby <br>Ooh <br>Don't know what to do, I'm <br>Helplessly in love <br>And the love in my heart <br>Is for you]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Helplessly In Love" label="Helplessly In Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Boys_To_Men/</id><title>New Edition - Boys To Men - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Boys_To_Men/" title="New Edition - Boys To Men - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Growing up can be a pain <br>You're not an man until you come of age <br>We've given up our teenage years <br>In the effort to pursue our career <br>Who assumes responsibility <br>Of having to support our families <br>Who's protecting us from harm <br>Is there anyone around <br>That we can trust <br><br>So we search for answers to our questions <br>Looking for a answer <br>No answers but we're taught a lesson everytime <br>Through mistakes we've learned to gather wisdom <br>Cause lifes responsibility falls in our hand oh <br><br>Keep on learning <br>Keep on growing <br>'cause wisdom helps us understand <br>We're maturing <br>Without knowing <br>These are the things that change boys to men <br><br>Oh the goals we set may exceed reality <br>Cause failurealways is a possibility <br>Who can tell us that we're wrong <br>It's up to us to figure out <br>What life is all about <br><br>So we search for answers to questions <br>Looking for the answers <br>No answers but we're taught a lesson everytime <br>Through mistakes we've learned to gather wisdom <br>'cause wisdom helps us see our responsibility <br><br>I know it is hard sometimes growing up can be a pain <br>Know what I mean know what I mean <br>Is all you have to do is <br>All you have to do is hold on hold on hold on no no no no no baby]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Boys To Men" label="Boys To Men"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Im_Comin_Home/</id><title>New Edition - I`m Comin` Home - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:24:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:24:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Im_Comin_Home/" title="New Edition - I`m Comin` Home - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Save tomorrow for me <br>I'm comin' home to you <br>Oh girl my baby <br><br>I just called you up <br>Because you've been on my mind <br>So I can tell you what I feel <br>Ooh I'm missing you <br>I've been away too long <br>Now I'm coming home to you <br>It's been hard for me <br>To fall asleep at night my love <br>Because without you <br>I feel so alone <br>So I'm coming home <br><br>Save tomorrow for me <br>I'm comin' home to you <br>Oh girl my baby <br>Save tomorrow for me <br>I'm coming home to you <br>Oh girl my baby <br><br>Since the day I left <br>And you went on your own way <br>My life's just not the same <br>Ooh baby I'm needing you <br>And longing for your touch <br>Can I get a message through <br><br>I can hardly wait <br>To hold you in my arms <br>Oh girl <br>So don't be busy <br>Cancel everything <br>'Cause I'm <br>Cause tomorrow's my day <br><br>Save tomorrow for me aw baby <br>I'm comin' home to you and I want it all <br>Oh girl my baby my baby <br>Save tomorrow for me aw baby <br>I'm coming home to you girl, I'm comin' home <br>Oh girl my baby my baby <br><br>Save tomorrow for me missing you needing you <br>I'm comin' home to you wanting you each and every minute of the day <br>Oh girl my baby yeah <br>Save tomorrow for me I know you know Sugar, I know you know <br>I'm coming home to you I'm comin' home to you <br>Oh girl my baby <br><br>Away too long <br>Missing you so I'm comin' home <br>Save me tomorrow <br>Away too long <br>Missing you so I'm comin' home <br>Save me tomorrow <br><br>Save tomorrow <br>Baby save tomorrow 'cause I'm comin home <br>Because without you I feel so alone <br>Since the day I left <br>I was needing you <br>Now I'm comin' home <br>My baby to you <br>Can I get a message through <br>Because I'm comin' home <br>Home home home home <br>Home <br><br>I love you I love you, too]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="I`m Comin` Home" label="I`m Comin` Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Competition/</id><title>New Edition - Competition - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Competition/" title="New Edition - Competition - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I keep dreaming that one day the whole world <br>Will be together, will be together as one <br>And there's nothing I can do, but pray that <br>It comes true, and keep on searchin' for <br>That miracle, that some say will never be <br><br>Competition, is the world summarized in <br>Just one word, and you know what I mean <br>Friends competing with friends <br>Will it ever end <br>I'm losing all of my patience <br>I need a way out, and soon <br><br>Time and again we are fighting one another <br>Hurting our sisters and hurting our brothers <br>It's a shame, why do we play these games <br>But they'll come a time when we all will be together <br>Living as one in harmony forever <br>You and I, we will light the sky aaaaaaahhhhh <br><br>If we're ever gonna be as one <br>We'd better make some changes and fast <br>And this time make it last <br><br>Cause if we all just take the time <br>I'm sure that we will find, all of us <br>Shed blood of the same kind <br>And that's the bottom line so <br><br>Time and again we are fighting one another <br>Hurting our sisters and hurting our brothers <br>It's a shame, why do we play these games <br>But they'll come a time when we all will be together <br>Living as one in harmony forever <br>You and I, we will light the sky aaaaaaahhhhh <br>Time and again we are fighting one another <br>Hurting our sisters and hurting our brothers <br>It's a shame, why do we play these games <br>But they'll come a time when we all will be together <br>Living as one in harmony forever <br>You and I, we will light the sky aaaaaaahhhhh <br>Time and again we are fighting one another <br>Hurting our sisters and hurting our brothers <br>It's a shame, why do we play these games <br>But they'll come a time when we all will be together <br>Living as one in harmony forever <br>You and I, we will light the sky aaaaaaahhhhh <br><br>Together as one <br>Together harmony <br>Together harmony]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Competition" label="Competition"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Can_You_Stand_The_Rain/</id><title>New Edition - Can You Stand The Rain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Can_You_Stand_The_Rain/" title="New Edition - Can You Stand The Rain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On a perfect day I know that I can count on you when that's not possible tell <br>Me can you weather the storm <br><br>Cause I need some body who will stand by me through the good times and bad <br>Times she will always, always be right there <br><br>Sunny days everybody loves them tell me baby can you stand the rain storms <br>Will come this we know for sure this we know for sure can you stand the rain <br><br>yeah yeah love unconditional I'm not asking just of you and girl to make it <br>Last I'll do whatever needs to be done <br><br>But I need somebody who will stand by me, when it's tough she won't run she <br>Will always, be right there for me <br><br>Sunny days every body loves them tell me baby can you stand the rain storms <br>Will come ricky I know I know all the days won't be perfect this we know for <br>Sure but tell me can you stand it can you stand the rain <br><br>Can you stand the rain 4x <br><br>No pressure no pressure from me baby this we know for sure cause I want <br>You and I need you and I love you girl <br><br>Will you be there for me <br><br>Come on baby lets go get wet <br><br>Can you stand the rain 10x <br><br>Can you stand the rain <br>Will you be there girl <br>Storms will come for sure <br>Can you stand the rain <br><br>Yeah it's hard but I'll know I'll be right there baby yeah yeah yeah]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Can You Stand The Rain" label="Can You Stand The Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Superlady/</id><title>New Edition - Superlady - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Superlady/" title="New Edition - Superlady - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I'm alone with you <br>You know just what I wanna doooooo girrrl <br>To hold you in my arms <br>Lovin' you all over baby <br>Yeah yeah yeah <br><br>No pressure from me baby <br>No need to get excited <br>Because tonight was made for two lovers <br>And you were invited <br><br>Ordinary <br>Keep me runnin' <br>Superlady <br><br>Ordinary <br>Keep me runnin' <br>Superlady <br><br>Heaven must've sent you girl <br>To be with me for always <br>Sharin' all our fantasies ooooooh <br><br>Tell me that you'll always be around <br>Show me you care <br>I'll always be there]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Superlady" label="Superlady"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Youre_Not_My_Kind_Of_Girl/</id><title>New Edition - You`re Not My Kind Of Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Youre_Not_My_Kind_Of_Girl/" title="New Edition - You`re Not My Kind Of Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh girl I know that you're <br>Attracted to me <br>And I should feel the same <br>About you <br>There's just something wrong <br>I don't know what it is <br>That keeps us from becoming a two <br><br>It's not your looks, you're very pretty <br>It's not your style, the way you dress is oh so fresh <br>It's not the way that you carry yourself <br><br>Oh, girl I'm sorry <br>You're not my kind of girl <br>Case you're the kind of girl That a man's dreams are made of <br><br>Oh girl I'm sorry <br>You're not my kind of girl <br><br>Cause you're the kind of girl <br>That a man would be proud to call his own <br><br>Girl listen to me <br>You're so pretty <br>I wouldn't cgange a thing about you <br>But I've been in love before <br>So I know how it feels <br>And the chemistry just isn't there]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="You`re Not My Kind Of Girl" label="You`re Not My Kind Of Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Crucial/</id><title>New Edition - Crucial - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Crucial/" title="New Edition - Crucial - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heart, beating strong <br>I was serious my love was furious <br>For you, only you, oh babe <br>Darling I don't know why <br>Can't leave you alone <br>You thrill me to the bone <br>You're the one <br>Obsession oh babe <br><br>Don't you know it was a crucial lovin' <br>Cru cial <br>Crucial lovin' <br>Cru cial <br><br>Chills, over me <br>Different from the rest <br>I won't settle for less <br>Hello, won't take no oh babe <br><br>From now on you and I <br>Stood the test of time <br>Still you're on my mind <br>Always, night and day oh babe <br><br>Don't you know it was a crucial lovin' <br>Cru cial <br>Crucial lovin' <br>Cru cial <br><br>I have more than told you <br>Girl I've got to show you <br>Feelings over load extreme <br><br>For the very first time <br>Girl you are my last time <br>You have taken over me]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Crucial" label="Crucial"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/NE_Heart_Break/</id><title>New Edition - N.E. Heart Break - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/NE_Heart_Break/" title="New Edition - N.E. Heart Break - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In store signing autographs at the mall <br>Next in line was a fly girl standing tall <br>Signed my name and said give me a call baby ya know <br><br>The girl screamed and fainted panic on the floor <br>The body gaurd pulled us the back door <br>I never saw her anymore it was an in store heartbreak <br><br>Live at five interview for Channel 2 <br>Saw a cutie thought she was on the TV cre <br>She said after the show I'll be waiting for you cool <br>After the show she got into the car and what a scence <br>Her dad was the driver of the limosuine <br>I didn't know she was only thirteen <br>It was a young girl heartbreak <br><br>People think we don't get lonely <br>But we're far away from home <br>One minute 20,000 people <br>But then they go home, we're alone <br><br>It's off to another city <br>Where everybody knows my name <br>But when I meet that perfect honey <br>Is it me she wants or is it my fame <br><br>Girlies and groupies and parties all night <br>Is the life that can lead you to a NE heartbreak <br>From city to city our friends and our fans <br>They're the ones who can keep us from having <br>NE heartbreak <br><br>Center stage NE was groovin' <br>The beatwas hard <br>And the girlies were movin' <br>There she was third row center coolin' <br>She was cold <br><br>Last note of the last song <br>House lights up they came on <br>When I looked she was gone <br>It was a 3rd row heartbreak <br><br>People think our life is easy <br>'cause they think we've got it made <br>But we're living underpressure <br>Just to be on top <br>And to give the best that we can give you <br>And to never let you down <br>We'll keep strivin' for perfection <br>NE heartbreak is coming to your town <br><br>Beware of NE heartbreak <br>Spreading fast and there's no cure <br>No need to run from heartache <br>It's gonna get you, get you for sure <br><br>Called up my girl and said <br>Meet me on the tour <br>I got a suite cold chillin' on the 50th floior <br>And I'll leave your ticket at the door <br>And baby don't forget the pumps <br><br>She lost her backstage pass and the room key <br>Then got stopped by hotel security <br>And I spent the whole night lonely <br>And it was a hotel heartbreak]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="N.E. Heart Break" label="N.E. Heart Break"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/If_It_Isnt_Love/</id><title>New Edition - If It Isn`t Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/If_It_Isnt_Love/" title="New Edition - If It Isn`t Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't love her <br>I tried to tell myself <br>But you can see it in my eyes <br>So don't deny <br>I can't fool no one else <br>The truth is in the tears I cry cause <br><br>If it isn't love <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why does she stay on my mind <br>If it isn't love <br>Why does it hurt so bad <br>Make me feel so sad inside <br>Of it isn't love <br><br>I told her I'd never fall in love <br>But now I know better <br><br>How does it feel <br>I can't describe this feelin' <br>That came when I saw her last night <br>She got to me <br>I'll let you know the reason <br>I saw her with anohter guy so <br><br>If it isn't love <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why does she stay on my mind <br>If it isn't love <br>Why does it hurt so bad <br>Make me feel so sad inside <br>Of it isn't love <br><br>Maybe she'll take me back <br>Hey girl he's begging <br>I made a big mistake <br>Won't you forgive him girl <br>Now I can feel it <br>He's never felt before <br>I really love her <br>You love her, what <br><br>It took my heart <br>To shatter in a thousand pieces <br>Before I'd ever drop my pride <br>Losing love worrying about my image <br>Really helped me realize that <br><br>If it isn't love <br>Why do I feel this way <br>Why does she stay on my mind <br>If it isn't love <br>Why does it hurt so bad <br>Make me feel so sad inside <br>Of it isn't love]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="If It Isn`t Love" label="If It Isn`t Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Where_It_All_Started/</id><title>New Edition - Where It All Started - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Where_It_All_Started/" title="New Edition - Where It All Started - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Picture this where it all started was back in Boston, Mass <br>Some time ago believe that <br>and by reopening the doors to all youth <br>a little salt was thrown on me and my boys <br>you know what I'm sayin' <br>but now we're back picking up where we left off aw yeah <br>and through this song, process of elimination will be done <br>you better believe that <br><br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky and Mike <br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky and Mike <br><br>The beginning of a dream <br>Where our ideas were born <br>Tell em Ricky To understand what this really means <br>Let's set the record straight <br>Once and for all and I'll tell you <br><br>'Cause other people imitate <br>And try their best to recreate <br>This is where it all started from <br>So they only perpetrate <br>But they can never duplicate <br>This is where it all started from <br><br>Yo, it's on you Ron It's nice to be the original <br>That all the counterfeits like to bite off <br>We only take it as a compliment <br>When they copy some of our material <br><br>To stay the best among the rest <br>We work to keep our movements fresh <br>This is where it all started from <br>You listen up dap instead of being clones <br>Why don't you think of something on your own <br>This is where it all started from <br><br>Now there's one more thing we think you should know <br>Don't be a victim to the wanna be <br>This is where it all started from <br>A fake, a fake <br>'Cause no other's ever gonna be like us <br>This is where it all started from <br>Take that <br><br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky, and Mike <br>Ronnie, Bobby, Ricky, and Mike <br>We're cool Cool it coooool it now <br>Let's sweeten it up <br>Candy girl <br>Count it off 1 2 1 2 <br>But you better not, better not <br>Count me out <br><br>'Cause other people imitate <br>And try their best to recreate <br>This is where it all started from <br>So they only perpetrate <br>But they can never duplicate <br>This is where it all started from <br><br>To stay the best among the rest <br>We work to keep our movements fresh <br>This is where it all started from <br>You listen up dap instead of being clones <br>Why don't you think of something on your own <br>This is where it all started from <br><br>Yo wait a minute Hold up Wait Stop Huh <br>You didn't know we was coming back like this on 'em my brother]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Where It All Started" label="Where It All Started"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Thats_The_Way_Were_Livin/</id><title>New Edition - That`s The Way We`re Livin` - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Thats_The_Way_Were_Livin/" title="New Edition - That`s The Way We`re Livin` - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight <br>Tonight <br><br>Hey, what you're looking for is <br>Not so hard to find <br>It's in your eyes <br>Hurry <br>Don't hesitate you're running <br>Out of time yah yah <br>There's no need to be misled <br>There's no need to work <br>Oh no we'll show you the way tonight <br><br>We're working hard <br>We're striving for perfection cause <br>That's the way we're livin' <br>Perfection's hard, that's why we're <br>Working overtime <br>That's the way we're livin' for you <br><br>It's up to you, so don't you let nobody <br>Tell you what to do <br>Make up your mind <br>Cause life should be taken one day at a time <br><br>Step by step, one by one <br>We'll show you the way tonight <br><br>We're working hard <br>We're striving for perfection cause <br>That's the way we're livin' <br>Perfection's hard, that's why we're <br>Working overtime <br>That's the way we're livin' for you <br><br>Time, there's no better time 2x <br><br>We're working hard <br>We're striving for perfection cause <br>That's the way we're livin' <br>Perfection's hard, that's why we're <br>Working overtime <br>That's the way we're livin' for you <br><br>And time, there's no better time]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="That`s The Way We`re Livin`" label="That`s The Way We`re Livin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Intro/</id><title>New Edition - Intro - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Edition/Intro/" title="New Edition - Intro - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In our world all things must change <br>Just as New Edition has been rearranged <br>Emotionally hurt we shed a tear <br>But through your love our tears have disappeared <br>That's why this is dedicated to you <br>So just sit back and let us entertain you <br><br>Yeah Yeah We gone have some fun tonight <br>Come on Yeah Boston <br>Ladies and gentlemen, all the way from Boston, Mass <br>I bring you Ronnie, Johnny, Ricky, Mike and Ralph <br>The New Edition]]></content><category term="New Edition" label="New Edition"/><category term="Intro" label="Intro"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tone_Damli/Pinnacle/</id><title>Tone Damli - Pinnacle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T00:25:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T00:25:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tone_Damli/Pinnacle/" title="Tone Damli - Pinnacle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tie me up <br>'Cause I need to feel released <br>Tie me up <br>And then throw away the keys <br>Take me to the stars so you can see it on my face <br>Baby you're the pinnacle of my eye everyday <br>Gettin' so much closer now, and you know not to stop <br>Baby you're the pinnacle, you're the pinnacle <br><br>Touch my body <br>Take me down <br>Take all on me <br>Get closer <br>Touch my body <br>Take me down <br>Take all on me <br>Get closer <br><br>Take me to the stars so you can see it on my face <br>Baby you're the pinnacle of my eye everyday <br>Touch my body <br>Take me down <br>Take all on me <br>Get closer <br><br>We can play <br>Cover my eyes, show me pain <br>Yeah, we can play <br>Promise you'll do anything <br><br>Take me to the stars so you can see it on my face <br>Baby you're the pinnacle of my eye everyday <br>Gettin' so much closer now, and you know not to stop <br>Baby you're the pinnacle, you're the pinnacle <br>Touch my body <br>Take me down <br>Take all on me <br>Get closer <br>Touch my body <br>Take me down <br>Take all on me <br>Get closer <br><br>Take me to the stars so you can see it on my face <br>Baby you're the pinnacle of my eye everyday <br>Touch my body <br>Take me down <br>Take all on me <br>Get closer <br><br>Take me to the stars so you can see it on my face <br>Baby you're the pinnacle of my eye everyday <br>Touch my body <br>Take me down <br>Take all on me <br>Get closer]]></content><category term="Tone Damli" label="Tone Damli"/><category term="Pinnacle" label="Pinnacle"/></entry></feed>