<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:55:03+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/모양_탐험/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 모양 탐험 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%AA%A8%EC%96%91_%ED%83%90%ED%97%98/" title="핑크퐁 - 모양 탐험 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모양 탐험! <br>정글 속으로 정글 속으로 <br>모양 찾으러 가보자 <br>우우우 동그라미 <br>뱀 <br>우우우 동그라미 <br>사과 <br>우우우 동그라미 <br>눈? <br>호랑이다! 으악! <br>정글 속으로 정글 속으로 <br>모양 찾으러 가보자! <br>우우우 <br>가시 <br>우우우 세모 <br>부리 <br>우우우 세모 <br>이빨? <br>으악! 악어야! <br>쉿! <br>정글 속으로 정글 속으로 <br>모양 찾으러 가보자! <br>우우우 네모 <br>바위 <br>우우우 네모 <br>부엉이 <br>우우우 네모 <br>뭐지? <br>보물 상자다! <br>만세!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="모양 탐험" label="모양 탐험"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/네모_로봇/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 네모 로봇 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%84%A4%EB%AA%A8_%EB%A1%9C%EB%B4%87/" title="핑크퐁 - 네모 로봇 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네모 로봇 <br>변신 준비 <br>나는 네모네모 로봇 <br>네모난 눈 코 입 <br>강철 주먹 무쇠 다리 <br>출동! 네모 로봇 나가신다 <br>네모 로봇 <br>변신 준비 <br>Let’s go! <br>나는 네모네모 로봇 <br>네모난 눈 코 입 <br>강철 주먹 무쇠 다리 <br>출동! 네모 로봇 나가신다]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="네모 로봇" label="네모 로봇"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/세모의_바다_여행/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 세모의 바다 여행 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%84%B8%EB%AA%A8%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4_%EC%97%AC%ED%96%89/" title="핑크퐁 - 세모의 바다 여행 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Under the Sea! <br>뾰족뾰족 작은 세모 <br>뾰족뾰족 큰 세모 <br>흔들흔들 다리 열 개 <br>트랄랄랄랄라 <br>오징어 <br>나도 나도! <br>뾰족뾰족 큰 세모 <br>뾰족뾰족 작은 세모 <br>살랑살랑 지느러미 <br>트랄랄랄랄라 <br>물고기 <br>잠깐! <br>뾰족뾰족 큰 세모 <br>뾰족뾰족 작은 세모 <br>날카로운 세모 이빨 <br>트랄랄랄랄라 <br>상어]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="세모의 바다 여행" label="세모의 바다 여행"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/동글동글_동물/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 동글동글 동물 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%8F%99%EA%B8%80%EB%8F%99%EA%B8%80_%EB%8F%99%EB%AC%BC/" title="핑크퐁 - 동글동글 동물 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[동글동글 동그랗게 <br>동글동글 그려봐요 <br>동그라미 동그라미 <br>큰 동그라미 <br>동그라미 동그라미 <br>큰 동그라미 <br>세모 귀 세모 귀 <br>동그란 몸 <br>꿀꿀 꿀꿀 돼지 <br>동그라미 동그라미 <br>동그라미 <br>동그라미 동그라미 <br>큰 동그라미 <br>수염 쭉쭉 동그란 몸 <br>찍찍 찍찍 생쥐 <br>동그라미 동그라미 <br>거꾸로 세모 코 <br>길쭉길쭉 긴 동그라미 <br>동그란 얼굴 동그란 몸 <br>깡총깡총깡총 토끼 <br>동글동글 동그랗게 <br>동글동글 그려봐요]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="동글동글 동물" label="동글동글 동물"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/모양송/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 모양송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%AA%A8%EC%96%91%EC%86%A1/" title="핑크퐁 - 모양송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[동글 동그라미 <br>반듯반듯 네모 <br>뾰족뾰족 세모 <br>길쭉 긴네모 <br>동그라미 <br>동글동글 동그라미 <br>바퀴처럼 굴러가 <br>이리저리 데굴데굴 <br>나는야 동그라미 <br>네모 <br>반듯반듯 네모 <br>상자처럼 반듯해 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>선이 네 개, 네모 <br>동글 동그라미 <br>반듯반듯 네모 <br>뾰족뾰족 세모 <br>길쭉 긴네모 <br>세모 <br>뾰족뾰족 세모 <br>산처럼 뾰족해 <br>하나 둘 셋 <br>셋! <br>선이 세 개 <br>세모 <br>긴네모 <br>길쭉길쭉 긴네모 <br>길쭉한 문 같지 <br>두 갠 길고, 두 갠 짧은 <br>나는야 긴네모 <br>동글 동그라미 <br>반듯반듯 네모 <br>뾰족뾰족 세모 <br>길쭉 긴네모]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="모양송" label="모양송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/몽당연필/7월_28일_맑다_흐리다_맑음/</id><title>몽당연필 - 7월 28일 맑다 흐리다 맑음 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%AA%BD%EB%8B%B9%EC%97%B0%ED%95%84/7%EC%9B%94_28%EC%9D%BC_%EB%A7%91%EB%8B%A4_%ED%9D%90%EB%A6%AC%EB%8B%A4_%EB%A7%91%EC%9D%8C/" title="몽당연필 - 7월 28일 맑다 흐리다 맑음 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘의 일기 흐리다 맑음 <br>7월의 스물여덟 번째 날에 <br>유난히 더 밝은 햇살이 좋아 <br>밀렸던 빨래 청소도 하고 <br>아껴둔 새 신을 신고서 <br>친구들 만나 맛집도 가고 <br>예쁜 카페도 갔어 <br>눈을 떠 보니까 나는 내 방에 있고 <br>또르르 또르르 창가에 비 구르고 <br>일요일 밤 11시 <br>진정 잠이 들기 싫은 밤 <br>꿈은 달콤했다 <br>진짜 정말 완전 싫어 월요일 <br>다시 오긴 하는 걸까 토요일 <br>겨우 일어나 고양이 세수 <br>콩나물 버스에 올라타 <br>하루 종일 상사 눈치 보고 <br>오늘도 난 커피 셔틀 <br>눈을 떠 보니까 나는 내 방에 있고 <br>또르르 또르르 눈물은 또 흐르고 <br>화요일 새벽 세시 <br>정말 주말은 오긴 할런지 <br>잠은 다 잤구나 <br>월화 수요일은 거북이 거북이 <br>목금 토요일은 우사인 우사인 <br>일요일은 마치 사라지는 연기 마술 <br>친구들과 노는 날은 <br>술이 사라지는 마술 <br>눈을 떠 보니까 나는 내 방에 있고 <br>또르르 또르르 창가에 비 구르고 <br>일요일 밤 11시 <br>진정 잠이 들기 싫은 밤 <br>꿈은 달콤했다 <br>오늘의 일기 맑다가 흐리다 맑음 <br>]]></content><category term="몽당연필" label="몽당연필"/><category term="7월 28일 맑다 흐리다 맑음" label="7월 28일 맑다 흐리다 맑음"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Ten_in_a_Bed/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Ten in a Bed - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Ten_in_a_Bed/" title="핑크퐁 - Ten in a Bed - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[hew! I’m not sleepy. <br>Huh? <br>There were ten in a bed <br>and the little one said, <br>“Roll over, roll over.” <br>So they all rolled over and one fell out. <br>Nine! One! <br>There were nine in a bed <br>and the little one said, <br>“Roll over, roll over.” <br>So they all rolled over and one fell out. <br>Eight! Two! <br>There were eight in a bed <br>and the little one said, <br>“Roll over, roll over.” <br>So they all rolled over and one fell out. <br>Seven! Three! <br>There were seven in a bed <br>and the little one said, <br>“Roll over, roll over.” <br>So they all rolled over and one fell out. <br>Six! Four! <br>There were six in a bed <br>and the little one said, <br>“Roll over, roll over.” <br>So they all rolled over and one fell out. <br>Five! Five! <br>There were five in a bed <br>and the little one said, <br>“Roll over, roll over.” <br>So they all rolled over and one fell out. <br>Four! Six! <br>There were four in a bed <br>and the little one said, <br>“Roll over, roll over.” <br>So they all rolled over and one fell out. <br>Three! Seven! <br>There were three in a bed <br>and the little one said, <br>“Roll over, roll over.” <br>So they all rolled over and one fell out. <br>Two! Eight! <br>There were two in a bed <br>and the little one said, <br>“Roll over, roll over.” <br>So they all rolled over and one fell out. <br>One! Nine! <br>There was one in a bed <br>and that little one said, <br>“Good night!”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Ten in a Bed" label="Ten in a Bed"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Count_by_10s/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Count by 10s - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Count_by_10s/" title="핑크퐁 - Count by 10s - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Count by tens, count by tens, <br>count by tens! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Count by tens, count by tens, <br>count by tens! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Ten! <br>Twenty! <br>Thirty! <br>Forty! <br>Fifty! <br>Sixty! <br>Seventy! <br>Eighty! <br>Ninety! <br>One hundred! <br>Count by tens, count by tens, <br>count by tens! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Count by tens, count by tens, <br>count by tens! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Double time! <br>Ten! Twenty! Thirty! Forty! Fifty! <br>Sixty! Seventy! Eighty! Ninety! One hundred]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Count by 10s" label="Count by 10s"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Count_by_5s/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Count by 5s - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Count_by_5s/" title="핑크퐁 - Count by 5s - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Count by fives, count by fives, <br>count by fives! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Count by fives, count by fives, <br>count by fives! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Five! <br>Ten! <br>Fifteen! <br>Twenty! <br>Twenty five! <br>Thirty! <br>Thirty five! <br>Forty! <br>Forty five! <br>Fifty! <br>Count by fives, count by fives, <br>count by fives! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Count by fives, count by fives, <br>count by fives! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Double time! <br>Five! Ten! Fifteen! Twenty! Twenty five! <br>Thirty! Thirty five! Forty! Forty five! Fifty]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Count by 5s" label="Count by 5s"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Count_by_2s/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Count by 2s - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Count_by_2s/" title="핑크퐁 - Count by 2s - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Count by twos, count by twos, <br>count by twos! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Count by twos, count by twos, <br>count by twos! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Two! <br>Four! <br>Six! <br>Eight! <br>Ten! <br>Twelve! <br>Fourteen! <br>Sixteen! <br>Eighteen! <br>Twenty! <br>Count by twos, count by twos, <br>count by twos! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Count by twos, count by twos, <br>count by twos! <br>Won’t you sing along? <br>Double time! <br>Two! Four! Six! Eight! Ten! <br>Twelve! Fourteen! Sixteen! Eighteen! Twenty]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Count by 2s" label="Count by 2s"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Shape_Monsters/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Shape Monsters - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Shape_Monsters/" title="핑크퐁 - Shape Monsters - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Square! <br>Triangle! <br>Circle! <br>Shapes! <br>I’m a square. <br>I have four sides. <br>One, two, three, four. <br>I have four sides. <br>One, two, three, four. <br>I’m a square. <br>Wow! <br>Uh, uh, uh, yeah! <br>I’m a triangle. <br>I have three sides. <br>One, two, three. <br>I have three sides. <br>One, two, three. <br>I’m a triangle. <br>Wow! <br>Uh, uh, uh, yeah! <br>I’m a circle. <br>I go round and round. <br>Round and round. <br>I go round and round. <br>Round and round. <br>I’m a circle. <br>Wow!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Shape Monsters" label="Shape Monsters"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Counting_1_to_20/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Counting 1 to 20 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Counting_1_to_20/" title="핑크퐁 - Counting 1 to 20 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One, two, three, four, five jelly beans. <br>Six, seven, eight, nine, ten jelly beans. <br>They are too bored, yawn, yawn! <br>So ten jelly beans are going to find <br>something fun. <br>Eleven jelly beans drive <br>vroom, vroom, vroom. <br>Twelve jelly beans honk <br>beep, beep, beep. <br>Thirteen jelly beans row, <br>go, go, go. <br>Fourteen jelly beans dance <br>spin, spin, spin. <br>Waa! <br>Fifteen jelly beans jump <br>hop, hop, hop. <br>Sixteen jelly beans dive <br>splash, splash. <br>Seventeen jelly beans laugh <br>Ha, ha, ha. <br>Eighteen jelly beans sing <br>La, la, la, la, la. <br>Nineteen jelly beans nap <br>sleep, sleep, sleep. <br>Hush, they sleep deep, deep, deep. <br>But the alarm goes off <br>ring, ring, ring. <br>Twenty jelly beans run <br>dash, dash, dash. <br>One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, <br>eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve, thirteen, <br>fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, <br>eighteen, nineteen, twenty]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Counting 1 to 20" label="Counting 1 to 20"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Counting_1_to_5/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Counting 1 to 5 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Counting_1_to_5/" title="핑크퐁 - Counting 1 to 5 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One, one, number one. <br>Who’s gonna sing? <br>One little bear sings, tralalalala. <br>Two, two, number two. <br>Who’s gonna sing? <br>Two little birds sing, tralalalala. <br>Three, three, number three. <br>Who’s gonna sing? <br>Three little pigs sing, tralalalala. <br>Four, four, number four. <br>Who’s gonna sing? <br>Four little penguins sing, tralalalala. <br>Five, five, number five. <br>Who’s gonna sing? <br>Five little monkeys sing, tralalalala. <br>One, two, three, four, five! <br>One, one, number one. <br>Who’s gonna dance? <br>One little bear dances, hula, hula, hulala. <br>Two, two, number two. <br>Who’s gonna dance? <br>Two little birds dance, hula, hula, hulala. <br>Three, three, number three. <br>Who’s gonna dance? <br>Three little pigs dance, hula, hula, hulala. <br>Four, four, number four. <br>Who’s gonna dance? <br>Four little penguins dance, hula, hula, hulala. <br>Five, five, number five. <br>Who’s gonna dance? <br>Five little monkeys dance, hula, hula, yoohoo! <br>One, two, three, four, five!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Counting 1 to 5" label="Counting 1 to 5"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/The_Beaver_Song/</id><title>핑크퐁 - The Beaver Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/The_Beaver_Song/" title="핑크퐁 - The Beaver Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Are you ready to be a beaver? <br>Beaver! <br>Beaver hands and beaver teeth! <br>Beaver one, beaver all. <br>Let's all do the beaver call. <br>Fuh, fuh, fuh, <br>fuh, fuh, fuh, <br>fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh. <br>Beaver two, beaver three. <br>Let's all climb the beaver tree. <br>Fuh, fuh, fuh, <br>fuh, fuh, fuh, <br>fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh. <br>Beaver four, beaver five. <br>Let's all do the beaver jive. <br>Fuh, fuh, fuh, <br>fuh, fuh, fuh, <br>fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh. <br>Beaver six, beaver seven. <br>Let's all go to beaver heaven. <br>Fuh, fuh, fuh, <br>fuh, fuh, fuh, <br>fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh. <br>Beaver eight, beaver nine. <br>STOP! It's beaver time! <br>Fuh, fuh, fuh, <br>fuh, fuh, fuh, <br>fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh, fuh. <br>Beaver ten, beaver ten. <br>Let's be beavers once again! <br>Go beaver! Go beaver! <br>Go beaver! Go beaver!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="The Beaver Song" label="The Beaver Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Writing_Numbers/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Writing Numbers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Writing_Numbers/" title="핑크퐁 - Writing Numbers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah! Yeah! Write numebrs! <br>Yeah! Yeah! Write numebrs! <br>Go straight down and then you’re done. <br>Go straight down and then you’re done. <br>Go straight down and then you’re done. <br>I am number one. <br>One! <br>Curve around and slide to the right. <br>Curve around and slide to the right. <br>Curve around and slide to the right. <br>I am number two. <br>Two! <br>Curve around and around again. <br>Curve around and around again. <br>Curve around and around again. <br>I am number three. <br>Three! <br>Down across and cut it in half. <br>Down across and cut it in half. <br>Down across and cut it in half. <br>I am number four. <br>Four! <br>Neck and tummy, put on a hat. <br>Neck and tummy, put on a hat. <br>Neck and tummy, put on a hat. <br>I am number five. <br>Five! <br>Yeah! Yeah! Write numebrs! <br>Yeah! Yeah! Write numebrs! <br>Down and around and curl it up. <br>Down and around and curl it up. <br>Down and around and curl it up. <br>I am number six. <br>Six! <br>Slide to the right and slide it down. <br>Slide to the right and slide it down. <br>Slide to the right and slide it down. <br>I am number seven. <br>Seven! <br>Make an S and climb back up. <br>Make an S and climb back up. <br>Make an S and climb back up. <br>I am number eight. <br>Eight! <br>Make a ball and then a line. <br>Make a ball and then a line. <br>Make a ball and then a line. <br>I am number nine. <br>Nine! <br>Make a stick and then a ball. <br>Make a stick and then a ball. <br>Make a stick and then a ball. <br>I am number ten. <br>Ten! <br>Yeah! Yeah! <br>One to ten, done!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Writing Numbers" label="Writing Numbers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Finger_Plays/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Finger Plays - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Finger_Plays/" title="핑크퐁 - Finger Plays - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Doo-Bi-Doo-Ba! Play with numbers. <br>Doo-Bi-Doo-Ba! Play with numbers. <br>One, uh-huh! <br>Let’s think about it. <br>Two, uh-huh! <br>Um… scissors. <br>Three, uh-huh! <br>I am OK. <br>Four, uh-huh! <br>I can comb my hair. <br>Five, uh-huh! <br>Go high-five. <br>Doo-Bi-Doo-Ba! Play with numbers. <br>Doo-Bi-Doo-Ba! Play with numbers. <br>Five and one! <br>I can write numbers. <br>Five and two! <br>Cut it, cut it, oops! <br>Five and three! <br>Use a folk, umm. <br>Five and four! <br>Do make-up. <br>Five and five! <br>Clap your hands.]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Finger Plays" label="Finger Plays"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Finger_Animals/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Finger Animals - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Finger_Animals/" title="핑크퐁 - Finger Animals - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Finger animals, finger animals. <br>Which animals do you want to be? <br>One and one! <br>It’s a goat. <br>“Baa, baa.” <br>Two and two! <br>It’s a rabbit. <br>“Squeak, squeak.” <br>Three and three! <br>It’s a cat. <br>“Meow, meow.” <br>Four and four! <br>It’s a rooster. <br>“Cock-a-doodle-doo.” <br>Five and five! <br>It’s a monkey. <br>“Whoo-whoo-ha-ha.”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Finger Animals" label="Finger Animals"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/The_Magic_Number_World/</id><title>핑크퐁 - The Magic Number World - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/The_Magic_Number_World/" title="핑크퐁 - The Magic Number World - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Look around! <br>Magic Number World! <br>One, one, number one. <br>Hide and seek, number one. <br>Tree, tree, a tall tree <br>and a smiling snake. <br>Two, two, number two. <br>Hide and seek, number two. <br>Duck, duck, a swimming duck <br>and a crooked hanger. <br>Three, three, number three. <br>Hide and seek, number three. <br>Fly, fly, a butterfly <br>and a woo-woo-ha-ha monkey. <br>Four, four, number four. <br>Hide and seek, number four. <br>Yacht, yacht, a sailing yacht <br>and a flapping flag. <br>Five, five, number five. <br>Hide and seek, number five. <br>Mouth, mouth, a hippo’s mouth <br>and a yummy-yum banana. <br>Six, six, number six. <br>Hide and seek, number six. <br>Tail, tail, a pig’s tail <br>and an elephant’s nose. <br>Seven, seven, number seven. <br>Hide and seek, number seven. <br>Giraffe, giraffe, a tall giraffe <br>and a toot-toot-toot trumpet. <br>Eight, eight, number eight. <br>Hide and seek, number eight. <br>Snowman, Mr. Snowman <br>and my teddy bear. <br>Nine, nine, number nine. <br>Hide and seek, number nine. <br>Flower, flower, a pretty flower <br>and a lolli-lolli-lollipop. <br>Ten, ten, number ten. <br>Hide and seek, number ten. <br>Drum, drum, a boom-boom drum <br>and a spoon with a bowl. <br>See you again! <br>Bibbidi bobbidi boo! <br>The Magic Number World!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="The Magic Number World" label="The Magic Number World"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Number_Shapes/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Number Shapes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Number_Shapes/" title="핑크퐁 - Number Shapes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Number? Number! <br>La la la la! <br>Magic number! <br>Number? Number! <br>La la la la! <br>Yeah! <br>Tree, tree, a tall tree. <br>Number one, number one. <br>Quack, quack, little ducks. <br>Number two. <br>Flip, flap, butterflies. <br>Number three, number three. <br>Wobble, wobble, sailing yachts. <br>Number four. <br>Yummy yum, yum, bananas. <br>Number five. <br>Number? Number! <br>La la la la! <br>Magic number! <br>Number? Number! <br>La la la la! <br>Yeah! <br>Oink, oink, pig’s tails. <br>Number six, number six. <br>Toot, toot, toot, toot, trumpets. <br>Numebr seven. <br>Round and round snowmen. <br>Number eight, number eight. <br>Lolli-lolli-lollipop. <br>Number nine. <br>Boom, boom, tang, tang, <br>doong, doong, drums. <br>Number ten.]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Number Shapes" label="Number Shapes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/1_to_10_Penguins/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 1 to 10 Penguins - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:50:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:50:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/1_to_10_Penguins/" title="핑크퐁 - 1 to 10 Penguins - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Penguin march! <br>Left, right, left, right, go! <br>One, two, three little penguins, <br>four, five, six little penguins, <br>seven, eight, nine little penguins, <br>ten little penguins. <br>Bleat! Bleat! <br>One, two, three, <br>four, five, six, <br>seven, eight, nine, <br>ten little penguins. <br>Penguins! <br>Ten, nine, eight little penguins, <br>seven, six, five little penguins, <br>four, three, two little penguins, <br>one little penguin. <br>Bleat! Bleat! <br>Ten, nine, eight, <br>seven, six, five, <br>four, three, two, <br>one little penguin. <br>Penguin]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="1 to 10 Penguins" label="1 to 10 Penguins"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Ten_Flies/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Ten Flies - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:51:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:51:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Ten_Flies/" title="핑크퐁 - Ten Flies - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Number World! <br>Ten, ten, number ten. <br>Yippee! <br>------------------------------------------- <br>Shoo! Shoo away, flies! <br>Ten flies, don’t bother me. <br>Ten flies, don’t bother me. <br>Ten flies, don’t bother me. <br>Ten flies sit on my head. <br>Oh, I’ve got an idea! <br>I can, I can, I can catch them all. <br>I can, I can, I can catch them all. <br>Ten flies, don’t bother me. <br>Ten flies, don’t bother me. <br>Ten flies, don’t bother me. <br>Ten flies sit on my head. <br>Oh, I’ve got an idea! <br>I can, I can, I can catch them all. <br>I can, I can, I can catch them all. <br>One, two, three, four, five, <br>six, seven, eight, nine and ten! <br>I got them all.]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Ten Flies" label="Ten Flies"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Nine_Frogs/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Nine Frogs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:51:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:51:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Nine_Frogs/" title="핑크퐁 - Nine Frogs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Number World! <br>Nine, nine, number nine. <br>Wow! <br>-------------------------------------------- <br>Ribbit ribbit ribbit ribbit <br><br>There are one, two, three <br>hopping frogs. <br>Ribbit, ribbit! <br>There are four, five, six <br>hopping forgs. <br>Ribbit, ribbit! <br>There are seven hopping frogs. <br>There are eight hopping frogs. <br>There are nine, nine hopping frogs. <br>Ribbit, ribbit! <br>There are one, two, three <br>swimming frogs. <br>Ribbit, ribbit! <br>There are four, five, six <br>swimming forgs. <br>Ribbit, ribbit! <br>There are seven swimming frogs. <br>There are eight swimming frogs. <br>And me! <br>There are nine, nine swimming frogs. <br>Ribbit, ribbit!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Nine Frogs" label="Nine Frogs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Eight_Legs/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Eight Legs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:51:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:51:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Eight_Legs/" title="핑크퐁 - Eight Legs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Number World! <br>Eight, eight, number eight. <br>Yay! <br>----------------------------------------- <br>One! Two! <br>Itsy Bitsy <br>Three! Four! <br>Itsy Bitsy <br>Five! Six! <br>Itsy Bitsy <br>Seven! Eight! <br>Yeah! <br>The itsy bitsy spider <br>went up the waterspout. <br>Spout! <br>One, two, three, four, <br>five, six, seven, eight! <br>The itsy bitsy spider <br>went up the waterspout again. <br>Again? <br>One, two, three, four, <br>five, six, seven, eight! <br>Itsy bitsy! <br>Yeah! <br>The itsy bitsy spider <br>went up the waterspout. <br>Spout! <br>One, two, three, four, <br>five, six, seven, eight! <br>The itsy bitsy spider <br>went up the waterspout again. <br>Again? <br>One, two, three, four, <br>five, six, seven, eight! <br>One, two, three, four, <br>five, six, seven, eight]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Eight Legs" label="Eight Legs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Seven_Elves/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Seven Elves - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:51:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:51:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Seven_Elves/" title="핑크퐁 - Seven Elves - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Number World! <br>Seven, seven, number seven. <br>Whee! <br>--------------------------------------------- <br>Na na na na na na na! <br>We are seven little elves. <br>Na na na na na na na! <br>We are seven little elves. <br>Hey! <br>Seven little elves, seven little elves <br>dancing with great joy. <br>Hurray! <br>Seven little elves, seven little elves <br>dancing with great joy. <br>Great Joy! <br>Seven little elves are jumping. <br>Seven little elves are tapping. <br>Seven little elves are spinning. <br>And walking in a row. <br>In a row. <br>In a row. <br>In a row. <br>Na na na na na na na! <br>We are seven little elves. <br>Na na na na na na na! <br>We are seven little elves! <br>Bob bob bob bob bob, hurray]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Seven Elves" label="Seven Elves"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Six_Little_Ducks/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Six Little Ducks - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:51:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:51:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Six_Little_Ducks/" title="핑크퐁 - Six Little Ducks - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Number World! <br>Six, six, number six. <br>Oh, yeah! <br>--------------------------------------------- <br>Six little ducks went out one day. <br>Five fat ducks <br>and a skinny duck. <br>But the mother duck said, <br>“It’s time for lunch.” <br>Waddle, waddle! <br>Six little ducks went home. <br>One, two, three! <br>Three! <br>Four, five, six! <br>Six! <br>One, two, three! <br>Three! <br>Four, five, six! <br>Six! <br>Waddle, waddle! <br>Six little ducks went home. <br>Six little ducks went out one day. <br>Five fat ducks <br>and a skinny duck. <br>But the mother duck said, <br>“It’s time for lunch.” <br>Waddle, waddle! <br>Six little ducks went home. <br>One, two, three! <br>Three! <br>Four, five, six! <br>Six! <br>One, two, three! <br>Three! <br>Four, five, six! <br>Six! <br>Waddle, waddle! <br>Six little ducks went home]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Six Little Ducks" label="Six Little Ducks"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Five_Fingers/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Five Fingers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:51:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:51:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Five_Fingers/" title="핑크퐁 - Five Fingers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Number World! <br>Five, five, number five. <br>Yay! <br>-------------------------------------------- <br>Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle. <br>Wiggle your five fingers, freeze! <br>One, two, three, four, five. <br>Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle. <br>Wiggle your five fingers, freeze! <br>One, two, three, four, five. <br>Where are five fingers? <br>Where are five fingers? <br>Here we are. <br>Here we are. <br>One, two, three, four, five. <br>One, two, three, four, five. <br>Finger family. <br>Finger family. <br>Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle. <br>Wiggle your five toes, freeze! <br>One, two, three, four, five. <br>Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle. <br>Wiggle your five toes, freeze! <br>One, two, three, four, five. <br>Where are five toes? <br>Where are five toes? <br>Here we are. <br>Here we are. <br>One, two, three, four, five. <br>One, two, three, four, five. <br>Toe family. <br>Toe family. <br>Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, <br>wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, <br>FREEZE!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Five Fingers" label="Five Fingers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Four_Bears/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Four Bears - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:51:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:51:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Four_Bears/" title="핑크퐁 - Four Bears - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Number World! <br>Four, four, number four. <br>Hey! <br>-------------------------------------------------- <br>One and two and three and four and <br>one and two and three and four! <br>Four big bears singing together. <br>One, two, three, four! <br>One, two, three, four! <br>One, two, three, four! <br>The four big bears’ song. <br>One and two and three and four and <br>one and two and three and four! <br>Four big bears dancing together. <br>One, two, three, four! <br>One, two, three, four! <br>One, two, three, four! <br>The four big bears’ dance. <br>Oh, hula!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Four Bears" label="Four Bears"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Three_Little_Pigs/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Three Little Pigs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:51:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:51:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Three_Little_Pigs/" title="핑크퐁 - Three Little Pigs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Number World! <br>Three, three, number three. <br>Oh, yeah! <br>---------------------------------------- <br>Oink! <br>Oink, oink! <br>Oink, oink, oink! <br>We are three little pigs! <br>Three little pigs went to market. <br>One! Two! Three! <br>Three little pigs went to swim. <br>One! Two! Three! <br>Three little pigs built a snowman. <br>One! Two! Three! <br>Three little pigs went to skate. <br>Ouch! <br>And three little pigs cried, <br>“Wee, wee, wee, wee, wee.” <br>Three little pigs. <br>Three little pigs went to market. <br>One! Two! Three! <br>Three little pigs went to swim. <br>One! Two! Three! <br>Three little pigs built a snowman. <br>One! Two! Three! <br>Three little pigs went to skate. <br>Ouch! <br>And three little pigs cried, <br>“Wee, wee, wee, wee, wee.” <br>Let’s take a picture. <br>One, two, three! <br>Three little pigs]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Three Little Pigs" label="Three Little Pigs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Two_Eyes_Two_Ears/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Two Eyes Two Ears - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:51:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:51:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Two_Eyes_Two_Ears/" title="핑크퐁 - Two Eyes Two Ears - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Number World! <br>Two, two, number Two. <br>Yippee! <br>------------------------------------------ <br>Two, two little eyes and ears. <br>Two, two little hands and feet. <br>Two little eyes. <br>One! Two! <br>Two little ears. <br>One! Two! <br>Two little hands. <br>One! Two! <br>Two little feet. <br>One! Two! <br>My sweet heart, my little baby! <br>Two, two big eyes and ears. <br>Two, two big hands and feet. <br>Two big eyes. <br>One! Two! <br>Two big ears. <br>One! Two! <br>Two big hands. <br>One! Two! <br>Two big feet. <br>One! Two! <br>Peek-a-boo]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Two Eyes Two Ears" label="Two Eyes Two Ears"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/One_Elephant/</id><title>핑크퐁 - One Elephant - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:51:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:51:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/One_Elephant/" title="핑크퐁 - One Elephant - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magic Number World! <br>One, one, number one. <br>Oh, yeah! <br>---------------------------------------- <br>One big elephant. <br>One! <br>One big elephant. <br>One! <br>Boogie woogie! Dance with me. <br>One big elephant. <br>Ho! <br>One small mouse. <br>One! <br>One small mouse. <br>One! <br>Boogie woogie! Dance with me. <br>One small mouse. <br>Yeah! <br>One number one. <br>One! <br>One number one. <br>One! <br>Boogie woogie! Dance with me. <br>One more time! <br>Boogie woogie! Dance with me. <br>One number one]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="One Elephant" label="One Elephant"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Halloween_Shark/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Halloween Shark - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Halloween_Shark/" title="핑크퐁 - Halloween Shark - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Baby shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Baby shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Baby shark. <br>BOO! <br>Mommy shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Mommy shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Mommy shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Mommy shark. <br>BOO! <br>Daddy shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Daddy shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Daddy shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Daddy shark. <br>BOO! <br>Grandma shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Grandma shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Grandma shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Grandma shark. <br>BOO! <br>Grandpa shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Grandpa shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Grandpa shark, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Grandpa shark. <br>BOO! <br>Halloween, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Halloween, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Halloween, doo doo doo doo doo doo. <br>Halloween]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Halloween Shark" label="Halloween Shark"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Toy_Shop_at_Night/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Toy Shop at Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Toy_Shop_at_Night/" title="핑크퐁 - Toy Shop at Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It is dark! Tonight is Halloween, <br>Halloween, Halloween. <br>Wake up everyone. <br>Toy soldiers! Lion! Nutcracker! <br>Ballerina! Teddy Bear! <br>Clown and Train! <br>It is dark! Tonight is Halloween, <br>Halloween, Halloween. <br>Everyone is up. <br>Halloween night! <br>Halloween night! <br>Halloween night! <br>Now the party starts! <br>It is dark! Tonight is Halloween, <br>Halloween, Halloween. <br>The party keeps going on. <br>Toy soldiers! Lion! Nutcracker! <br>Ballerina! Teddy Bear! <br>Clown and Train! <br>It is dark! Tonight is Halloween, <br>Halloween, Halloween. <br>Until the sun rises. <br>Halloween night! <br>Halloween night! <br>Halloween night! <br>Shhhh, it’s a secret]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Toy Shop at Night" label="Toy Shop at Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Monster_Shuffle/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Monster Shuffle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Monster_Shuffle/" title="핑크퐁 - Monster Shuffle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Please get up! Let’s get moving! <br>Stand up, monsters! <br>Move it, monsters! <br>We’re monsters, make a spooky face. <br>Step, step, slide! <br>Step, step, slide! <br>It’s the vampire shuffle! <br>Stand up, monsters! <br>Move it, monsters! <br>We’re monsters, make a spooky face. <br>Stretch your arms! <br>Move them up and down! <br>It’s the mummy shuffle! <br>Stand up, monsters! <br>Move it, monsters! <br>We’re monsters, make a spooky face. <br>To the left and right, <br>dance as you please. <br>It’s the monster shuffle]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Monster Shuffle" label="Monster Shuffle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Creepy_Zombie/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Creepy Zombie - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Creepy_Zombie/" title="핑크퐁 - Creepy Zombie - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[La la la la la la la la! <br>La la la la la la la la! <br>La la la la la! <br>One creepy zombie <br>went out to trick or treat! <br>Everybody danced <br>to the spooky beat. <br>He had such enormous fun. <br>He called for another <br>creepy zombie to come. <br>Two creepy zombies <br>went out to trick or treat! <br>Everybody danced <br>to the spooky beat. <br>They had such enormous fun. <br>They called for another <br>creepy zombie to come. <br>La la la la la la la la! <br>La la la la la la la la! <br>Three creepy zombies <br>went out to trick or treat! <br>Everybody danced <br>to the spooky beat. <br>They had such enormous fun. <br>They called for another <br>creepy zombie to come. <br>Four creepy zombies <br>went out to trick or treat! <br>Everybody danced to the spooky beat. <br>They had such enormous fun. <br>They called for another <br>creepy zombie to come. <br>La la la la la la la la! <br>La la la la la!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Creepy Zombie" label="Creepy Zombie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Vampire_Wedding/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Vampire Wedding - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Vampire_Wedding/" title="핑크퐁 - Vampire Wedding - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My dear bride, <br>vampire bride. <br>We’re getting married <br>on spooky Halloween night. <br>My dear bride, <br>vampire bride. <br>You are beautiful, <br>my one and only bride. <br>Vampire wedding on Halloween. <br>“I love you so much!” <br>Vampire wedding on Halloween. <br>My dear groom, <br>vampire groom. <br>We’re getting married <br>on spooky Halloween night. <br>My dear groom, <br>vampire groom. <br>You are wonderful, <br>my one and only groom. <br>Vampire wedding on Halloween. <br>“I love you so much!” <br>Vampire wedding on Halloween.]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Vampire Wedding" label="Vampire Wedding"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Guess_Who_/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Guess Who? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Guess_Who_/" title="핑크퐁 - Guess Who? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Guess who? <br>Guess who? <br>Pointed hat and long nails. <br>Pointed nose and long broom. <br>Can you guess who I might be? <br>You are a witch! <br>Oh, yay-yay-yay-yay! <br>Bones, bones, bones and no skin. <br>Bony, bony, bony and so thin. <br>Can you guess who I might be? <br>You are a skeleton! <br>Oh, yay-yay-yay-yay! <br>Guess who? <br>Guess who? <br>Floating in the dark with bright eyes. <br>Round head and a white body. <br>Can you guess who I might be? <br>You are a ghost! <br>Oh, yay-yay-yay-yay! <br>Square head and square shoulders. <br>Pokey hair and green, green skin. <br>Can you guess who I might be? <br>You are Frankenstein! <br>Oh, yay-yay-yay-yay! <br>Happy Halloween! <br>We are Halloween friends!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Guess Who?" label="Guess Who?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Five_Little_Pumpkins/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Five Little Pumpkins - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Five_Little_Pumpkins/" title="핑크퐁 - Five Little Pumpkins - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Five little pumpkins <br>sitting on a gate. <br>The first one said, <br>"Oh my, it's getting late." <br>The second one said, <br>“There are witches in the air.” <br>The third one said, <br>"But we don’t care." <br>The fourth one said, <br>"Let’s run and run and run." <br>The fifth one said, <br>"We’re ready for some fun." <br>"Whooooo!" went the wind, <br>and out went the light. <br>And the five little pumpkins <br>rolled out of sight. <br>Five little pumpkins <br>sitting on a gate. <br>The first one said, <br>"Oh my, it's getting late." <br>The second one said, <br>“There are witches in the air.” <br>The third one said, <br>"But we don’t care." <br>The fourth one said, <br>"Let’s run and run and run." <br>The fifth one said, <br>"We’re ready for some fun." <br>"Whooooo!" went the wind, <br>and out went the light. <br>And the five little pumpkins <br>rolled out of sight]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Five Little Pumpkins" label="Five Little Pumpkins"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Three_Scarecrows/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Three Scarecrows - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Three_Scarecrows/" title="핑크퐁 - Three Scarecrows - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Three scarecrows, <br>they lost their hats. <br>And they began to cry. <br>Oh, witch, dear, we sadly fear, <br>our hats we have lost. <br>“Oh, poor guys. <br>But, you are not allowed to <br>come to the Halloween party <br>without hats! <br>Tease - ya , tease - ya !” <br>It’s Halloween night! <br>“We are here!” <br>Three scarecrows, <br>they went to party. <br>And they began to dance. <br>Oh, friends, dear, we’re finally here. <br>Let’s dance, it’s Halloween night! <br>“Oh, super cool hats! <br>Welcome to the Halloween party! <br>Tease - ya , tease - ya !” <br>It’s Halloween night]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Three Scarecrows" label="Three Scarecrows"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Halloween_Costume_Party/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Halloween Costume Party - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Halloween_Costume_Party/" title="핑크퐁 - Halloween Costume Party - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Halloween is back! Yay! <br>Let’s start <br>the Halloween costume party! <br>Ding-Dong! Trick-or-treat! <br>Who are you? <br>I am a Pirate! <br>A-hoy! <br>Welcome to the party! <br>You brought eyeballs. <br>Pirate! Pirate! <br>Happy Halloween! <br>Ding-Dong! Trick-or-treat! <br>Who are you? <br>I’m a Ballerina! <br>One-two, one-two! <br>Welcome to the party! <br>You brought bat-cake. <br>Ballerina! Ballerina! <br>Happy Halloween! <br>Ding-Dong! Trick-or-treat! <br>Who are you? <br>I’m a Cowboy! <br>Hee-haw! <br>Welcome to the party! <br>You brought ghost candies. <br>Cowboy! Cowboy! <br>Happy Halloween! <br>Ding-Dong! Trick-or-treat! <br>Who are you? <br>I’m a Refrigerator! <br>Whoooooong! <br>Welcome to the party! <br>You brought witches’ brew. <br>Refrigerator! <br>Happy Halloween! <br>Happy Halloween]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Halloween Costume Party" label="Halloween Costume Party"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/The_Spooky_Bus/</id><title>핑크퐁 - The Spooky Bus - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/The_Spooky_Bus/" title="핑크퐁 - The Spooky Bus - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“Hello, passengers! <br>Welcome aboard <br>the Halloween bus! <br>Fasten your seatbelts, please!” <br>The wheels on the bus go <br>round and round, <br>round and round, <br>round and round. <br>The wheels on the bus go <br>round and round <br>on Halloween. <br>The ghosts in a house go <br>boo, boo, boo, <br>boo, boo, boo, <br>boo, boo, boo, <br>The ghosts in a house go <br>boo, boo, boo <br>on Halloween. <br>The witch on a broom goes <br>vroom, vroom, vroom, <br>vroom, vroom, vroom, <br>vroom, vroom, vroom. <br>The witch on a broom goes <br>vroom, vroom, vroom <br>on Halloween. <br>“Hold on, please!” <br>The goblins in the dark go <br>stomp, stomp, stomp, <br>stomp, stomp, stomp, <br>stomp, stomp, stomp. <br>The goblins in the dark go <br>stomp, stomp, stomp <br>on Halloween. <br>The zombies on the road go <br>boom, boom, boom, <br>boom, boom, boom, <br>boom, boom, boom. <br>The zombies on the road go <br>boom, boom, boom <br>on Halloween]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="The Spooky Bus" label="The Spooky Bus"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Halloween_Party/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Halloween Party - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Halloween_Party/" title="핑크퐁 - Halloween Party - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Halloween party! <br>Let’s go! <br>If you’re Pumpkin <br>and you know it, roll and roll. <br>Jack-O’-Lantern <br>If you’re Pumpkin <br>and you know it, roll and roll. <br>Jack-O’-Lantern <br>If you’re Pumpkin <br>and you know it, <br>keep rolling, rolling, rolling. <br>If you’re Pumpkin <br>and you know it, roll and roll. <br>We love Halloween! <br>If you’re Witch <br>and you know it, ride your broom. <br>Vroom! Vroom! <br>If you’re Witch <br>and you know it, ride your broom. <br>Vroom! Vroom! <br>If you’re Witch <br>and you know it <br>keep riding, riding, riding. <br>If you are Witch <br>and you know it, ride your broom. <br>If you’re Black bat <br>and you know it fly high. <br>Flip! Flop! <br>If you’re Black bat <br>and you know it fly high. <br>Flip! Flop! <br>If you’re Black bat <br>and you know it <br>keep flying, flying, flying. <br>If you’re Black bat <br>and you know it fly high. <br>Flip! Flop!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Halloween Party" label="Halloween Party"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Knock_Knock_Trick-or-Treat/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Knock, Knock! Trick-or-Treat - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Knock_Knock_Trick-or-Treat/" title="핑크퐁 - Knock, Knock! Trick-or-Treat - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Trick-or-treat! <br>Happy Halloween! <br>Knock, knock! Trick-or-treat. <br>Give me something sweet to eat. <br>Here are candies, jellybeans. <br>Yummy, yummy Halloween! <br>Mm, so sweet! <br>Knock, knock! Trick-or-treat. <br>Give me something good to eat. <br>Here are apples, mangos, limes. <br>Yummy, yummy Halloween! <br>Wow, so good! <br>Knock, knock! Trick-or-treat. <br>Give me something sweet to eat. <br>Here are worms, yummy worms. <br>Yummy, yummy … … Oh, NO]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Knock, Knock! Trick-or-Treat" label="Knock, Knock! Trick-or-Treat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/The_Little_Ghost/</id><title>핑크퐁 - The Little Ghost - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/The_Little_Ghost/" title="핑크퐁 - The Little Ghost - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hello, everyone! <br>I like to play peek-a-boo! <br>Do you wanna join me? <br>This is the way a ghost plays, <br>peek-a-boo, peek-a-boo. <br>Wait for someone on a shelf. <br>Boo! <br>This is the way a ghost plays, <br>peek-a-boo, peek-a-boo. <br>Wait for someone in a shoe. <br>Boo! <br>This is the way a ghost plays, <br>peek-a-boo, peek-a-boo. <br>Wait for someone <br>behind the curtain. <br>Boo! <br>This is the way a ghost plays]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="The Little Ghost" label="The Little Ghost"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Who_Took_the_Candies/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Who Took the Candies - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Who_Took_the_Candies/" title="핑크퐁 - Who Took the Candies - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The candies are lost! <br>Who took cadies <br>from the big trick-or-treat bag? <br>Who’s this? <br>Who took cadies <br>from the big trick-or-treat bag? <br>Who’s this? <br>Oh, the cowboy took the candies <br>from the big trick-or-treat bag. <br>All right! <br>Let’s go find the cowboy right away. <br>Right away! <br>Who me? <br>Yes, you! <br>Not me. <br>Then who? <br>Maybe … the pirate! <br>Who took cadies <br>from the big trick-or-treat bag? <br>Who’s this? <br>Who took cadies <br>from the big trick-or-treat bag? <br>Who’s this? <br>Oh, the pirate took the candies <br>from the big trick-or-treat bag. <br>All right! <br>Let’s go find the pirate right away. <br>Right away! <br>Not me. <br>Then who? <br>Maybe … the fairy! <br>Who took cadies <br>from the big trick-or-treat bag? <br>Who’s this? <br>Who took cadies <br>from the big trick-or-treat bag? <br>Who’s this? <br>Oh, the fairy took the candies <br>from the big trick-or-treat bag. <br>All right! <br>Let’s go find the fairy right away. <br>Right away! <br>Who me? <br>Yes, you! <br>Yes, it was so yummy. <br>I’ll give you the fairy candies <br>in return! <br>La la la la la la la la la la <br>La la la la la la la la la la <br>La la la la la la la la la <br>La la la la la la la <br>La la la la la la la la]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Who Took the Candies" label="Who Took the Candies"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/The_Dark_House/</id><title>핑크퐁 - The Dark House - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/The_Dark_House/" title="핑크퐁 - The Dark House - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In a dark, dark wood, <br>there is a dark, dark castle. <br>And in that dark, dark castle, <br>who’s in there? <br>In the dark, dark castle, <br>there is a dark, dark room. <br>And in that dark, dark room, <br>there is a dark, dark coffin. <br>And in that dark, dark coffin, <br>there is a … … vampire! <br>In a dark, dark sky, <br>there is a dark, dark house. <br>And in that dark, dark house, <br>who’s in there? <br>In a dark, dark house, <br>there is a dark, dark room. <br>And in that dark, dark room, <br>there is a dark, dark box. <br>And in that dark, dark box, <br>there is a … … pumpkin!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="The Dark House" label="The Dark House"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/The_Skeleton_Band/</id><title>핑크퐁 - The Skeleton Band - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/The_Skeleton_Band/" title="핑크퐁 - The Skeleton Band - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dem bones! <br>Dem bones, dem bones, dem <br>oh, dancing bones. <br>Dem bones, dem bones, dem <br>oh, dancing bones. <br>Dem bones, dem bones, dem <br>oh, dancing bones. <br>Oh, dance with the skeleton band. <br>The foot bone’s connected to <br>the leg bone. <br>The leg bone’s connected to <br>the knee bone. <br>The knee bone’s connected to <br>the thigh bone. <br>Oh, dance with the skeleton band. <br>The thigh bone’s connected to <br>the hip bone. <br>The hip bone’s connected to <br>the back bone. <br>The back bone’s connected to <br>the neck bone. <br>Oh, dance with the skeleton band. <br>Dem bones, dem bones’ gonna <br>walk around. <br>Dem bones, dem bones’ gonna <br>walk around. <br>Dem bones, dem bones’ gonna <br>walk around. <br>Oh, dance with the skeleton band.]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="The Skeleton Band" label="The Skeleton Band"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Spooky_Pooky/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Spooky Pooky - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Spooky_Pooky/" title="핑크퐁 - Spooky Pooky - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It’s a special stage! <br>The witches! <br>You put your broom in. <br>You put your broom out. <br>You put your broom in. <br>And you shake it all about. <br>You do the spooky pooky, <br>and you turn yourself around. <br>Tonight is Halloween! <br>Wow! And the dancing mummies! <br>You put your bandage in. <br>You put your bandage out. <br>You put your bandage in. <br>And you shake it all about. <br>You do the spooky pooky, <br>and you turn yourself around. <br>Tonight is Halloween! <br>And last but not least. <br>The finale, the ghosts! <br>You put your head in. <br>You put your head out. <br>You put your head in. <br>And you shake it all about. <br>You do the spooky pooky, <br>and you turn yourself around. <br>Tonight is Halloween! <br>Tonight is Halloween. <br>Boo!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Spooky Pooky" label="Spooky Pooky"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Halloween_Is_Almost_Here/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Halloween Is Almost Here - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Halloween_Is_Almost_Here/" title="핑크퐁 - Halloween Is Almost Here - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to the Monster Club! <br>Are you ready? <br>Yeah! <br>Ok, let’s go! <br>Halloween is almost here <br>and I can hardly wait. <br>Halloween is almost here <br>and I can hardly wait. <br>When Halloween is here, <br>we will have a jolly time. <br>Halloween is almost here <br>and I can hardly wait. <br>This is Halloween night! <br>Ho ho! <br>Let’s sing and dance <br>to the beat! <br>Ha ha! <br>To the left! <br>To the left! <br>To the right! <br>To the right! <br>Oh, it’s Halloween! <br>Boo! (scream) <br>Halloween is almost here <br>and I can hardly wait. <br>Halloween is almost here <br>and I can hardly wait. <br>Happy, happy Halloween. <br>We will get some sweets to eat. <br>Halloween is almost here <br>and I can hardly wait]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Halloween Is Almost Here" label="Halloween Is Almost Here"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/미무스_친구들/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 미무스 친구들 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%AF%B8%EB%AC%B4%EC%8A%A4_%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC%EB%93%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 미무스 친구들 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[갈리미무스 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>스트루티오미무스 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>오르니토미무스 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>갈리! 스트루티오! 오르니토미무스! <br>오예! <br>갈리미무스 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>닭을 닮은 공룡! <br>갈리미무스 <br>스트루티오미무스 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>타조 닮은 공룡! <br>스트루티오미무스 <br>오르니토미무스 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>새를 닮은 공룡! <br>오르니토미무스 <br>달려라 달려 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>더 빨리 더 빨리 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>으악! 티라노다! <br>도망쳐 도망쳐 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>달려라 달려 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>무서워 무서워 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>숨어라 숨어 <br>미 미 미무스 <br>살았다! <br>어?]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="미무스 친구들" label="미무스 친구들"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/파라사우롤로푸스/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 파라사우롤로푸스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%ED%8C%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EB%A1%A4%EB%A1%9C%ED%91%B8%EC%8A%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 파라사우롤로푸스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[공룡 음악회에 오신 것을 환영합니다! <br>멋진 친구들을 만나볼까요? <br>머리에 커다란 볏, <br>파라사우롤로푸스 <br>파라! <br>나는야 멋진 음악가 <br>한번 들어 볼래? <br>트럼펫을 불어요 <br>빰빰 빠라빰 <br>모두 함께 불어요 <br>투투 투리타 <br>머리에 커다란 볏, <br>파라사우롤로푸스 <br>파라! <br>나는야 멋진 음악가 <br>한번 들어 볼래? <br>트럼펫을 불어요 <br>빰빰 빠라빰 <br>모두 함께 불어요 <br>투투 투리타 <br>트럼펫을 불어요 <br>빰빰 빠라빰 <br>모두 함께 불어요 <br>투투 투리타]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="파라사우롤로푸스" label="파라사우롤로푸스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/마이아사우라/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 마이아사우라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%84%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EB%9D%BC/" title="핑크퐁 - 마이아사우라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[굿! 굿! <br>구디 굿 구디 굿! <br>굿 맘! <br>우리는 마이아사우라 <br>마이아! <br>아기 공룡 언제나 지켜주죠 <br>아기 공룡이 나오려고 해 <br>와, 우리 아가! <br>우리는 따뜻한 엄마 <br>굿! 굿! <br>구디 굿 구디 굿! <br>굿 맘! <br>우리는 마이아사우라 <br>마이아! <br>엄마 공룡 언제나 함께하죠 <br>너무 졸려요 <br>크앙 배고파요! <br>우리는 행복한 아기! <br>우리는 행복한 가족]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="마이아사우라" label="마이아사우라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/엘라스모사우루스/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 엘라스모사우루스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%97%98%EB%9D%BC%EC%8A%A4%EB%AA%A8%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EB%A3%A8%EC%8A%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 엘라스모사우루스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[랄라랄라라 <br>엘라스모사우루스 <br>랄라랄라라 <br>깊은 바다 <br>헤엄을 치네 어푸어푸 <br>지느러미로 빨리빨리 <br>바닷속을 헤엄쳐요 <br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 <br>엘라스모사우루스 <br>랄라랄라라 <br>엘라스모사우루스 <br>랄라랄라라 <br>깊은 바다 <br>물고기 사냥 얌얌얌 <br>긴 목으로 휙휙휙 <br>바닷속을 헤엄쳐요 <br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 <br>엘라스모사우루스 <br>깊고 깊은 바닷속에 <br>엘라스모사우루스]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="엘라스모사우루스" label="엘라스모사우루스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/디플로도쿠스/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 디플로도쿠스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%94%94%ED%94%8C%EB%A1%9C%EB%8F%84%EC%BF%A0%EC%8A%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 디플로도쿠스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흔들흔들 <br>땅이 흔들 <br>디플로도쿠스! <br>큰 덩치 튼튼 다리 <br>디플로도쿠스 <br>발을 굴러 쿵쿵 쾅쾅쾅 <br>온몸이 흔들흔들 <br>땅도 흔들흔들 <br>큰 덩치 튼튼 다리 <br>디플로도쿠스 <br>모두 흔들! <br>흔들 흔들 흔들! <br>큰 덩치 긴 꼬리 <br>디플로도쿠스 <br>꼬리를 힘차게 휙휙 훅훅훅 <br>모두 다 같이 <br>꼬리 휙휙휙 <br>큰 덩치 긴 꼬리 디플로도쿠스]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="디플로도쿠스" label="디플로도쿠스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/파키케팔로사우루스/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 파키케팔로사우루스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%ED%8C%8C%ED%82%A4%EC%BC%80%ED%8C%94%EB%A1%9C%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EB%A3%A8%EC%8A%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 파키케팔로사우루스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[붐붐붐! <br>붐럼텀텀! <br>붐붐붐! <br>붐럼텀텀! <br>나는야 박치기 왕 <br>파키케팔로사우루스! <br>두꺼운 머리뼈로 <br>쿵쿵 박치기! <br>누구도 나를 <br>막을 순 없지 <br>자, 어디 한번 붙어볼까? <br>쿵쿵 박치기! <br>예! <br>붐붐붐! <br>붐럼텀텀! <br>붐붐붐! <br>붐럼텀텀! <br>나는야 박치기 왕 <br>파키케팔로사우루스! <br>두꺼운 머리뼈로 <br>쿵쿵 박치기! <br>누구도 나를 <br>막을 순 없지 <br>나는 박치기 왕 <br>파키케팔로사우루스! <br>쿵쿵 박치기! <br>예!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="파키케팔로사우루스" label="파키케팔로사우루스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/브라키오사우루스/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 브라키오사우루스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:52:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:52:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%ED%82%A4%EC%98%A4%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EB%A3%A8%EC%8A%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 브라키오사우루스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[헤이 호 브라키오! <br>레츠 고! 고고고! <br>헤이 호 브라키오! <br>레츠 고! 호호호! <br>난 브라키오사우루스 <br>덩치 큰 공룡 <br>긴 목 커다란 몸 <br>아기 공룡은 작아! <br>헤이 호 브라키오! <br>레츠 고! 고고고! <br>헤이 호 브라키오! <br>레츠 고! 호호호! <br>난 브라키오사우루스 <br>먹보 초식 공룡 <br>냠냠 쩝쩝 꿀꺽 꿀꺽 <br>엄청나게 먹어 치우지! <br>헤이 호 브라키오! <br>레츠 고! 고고고! <br>헤이 호 브라키오! <br>레츠 고! 호호호!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="브라키오사우루스" label="브라키오사우루스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/프테라노돈/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 프테라노돈 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%ED%94%84%ED%85%8C%EB%9D%BC%EB%85%B8%EB%8F%88/" title="핑크퐁 - 프테라노돈 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람에 몸을 맡긴 채 <br>왼쪽으로 슝 <br>오른쪽으로 슝 슝 <br>공룡 시대의 하늘을 누비는 <br>프테라노돈이라네! <br>커다란 날개를 쭉 펴고 <br>쭉쭉! <br>공룡 위를 나는 프테라노돈 <br>이쪽저쪽 자유롭게 비행하는 <br>나는야 멋쟁이 익룡 <br>슝슝 쌩쌩 프테라노돈 <br>슝슝 쌩쌩 프테라노돈 <br>슝슝 쌩쌩 프테라노돈 <br>나는야 멋쟁이 익룡 <br>커다란 날개를 쭉 펴고 <br>쭉쭉! <br>바다 위를 나는 프테라노돈 <br>휙휙 바다 사냥 즐기는 <br>나는야 멋쟁이 익룡 <br>슝슝 쌩쌩 프테라노돈 <br>슝슝 쌩쌩 프테라노돈 <br>슝슝 쌩쌩 프테라노돈 <br>나는야 멋쟁이 익룡]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="프테라노돈" label="프테라노돈"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/트리케라톱스/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 트리케라톱스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%BC%80%EB%9D%BC%ED%86%B1%EC%8A%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 트리케라톱스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나 둘 셋! <br>하나 둘 셋! <br>뿔이 세 개! <br>트리케라톱스! <br>깊고 깊은 공룡 숲속에 <br>트리케라톱스 살고 있었죠 <br>꺄악! <br>모두 모두 날 보고 도망가 <br>머리에 뿔 세 개 <br>뾰족 뿔 세 개! <br>난 무섭지 않아 <br>하나 둘 셋! <br>하나 둘 셋! <br>뿔이 세 개! <br>트리케라톱스! <br>깊고 깊은 공룡 숲속에 <br>트리케라톱스 살고 있었죠 <br>하하하하! <br>모두 모두 나를 좋아해 <br>머리에 큰 프릴 <br>왕관 같은 프릴! <br>정말 멋져! <br>최고야]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="트리케라톱스" label="트리케라톱스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/안킬로사우루스/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 안킬로사우루스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%95%88%ED%82%AC%EB%A1%9C%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EB%A3%A8%EC%8A%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 안킬로사우루스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[안킬로 앞으로! <br>하나 둘! 하나 둘! <br>안킬로 앞으로! <br>쿵쿵! 쾅쾅! <br>나는야 갑옷 공룡 <br>안킬로사우루스 <br>육식 공룡 티라노도 무섭지 않아 <br>탱크처럼 단단한 등 <br>다 덤벼 봐! <br>갑옷 공룡 안킬로사우루스 <br>안킬로 앞으로! <br>하나 둘! 하나 둘! <br>안킬로 앞으로! <br>쿵쿵! 쾅쾅! <br>나는야 힘센 공룡 <br>안킬로사우루스 <br>그 누구도 내 앞길을 막을 수 없어 <br>꼬리의 뼈 뭉치를 <br>힘차게 휙 휙! <br>힘센 공룡 안킬로사우루스 <br>안킬로사우루스! <br>으하하하]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="안킬로사우루스" label="안킬로사우루스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/아기_티라노/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 아기 티라노 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%95%84%EA%B8%B0_%ED%8B%B0%EB%9D%BC%EB%85%B8/" title="핑크퐁 - 아기 티라노 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아기 티티티 티라노 <br>아기 티티티 티라노 <br>아기 티티티 티라노사우루스 <br>엄마 티티티 티라노 <br>엄마 티티티 티라노 <br>엄마 티티티 티라노사우루스 <br>아빠 티티티 티라노 <br>아빠 티티티 티라노 <br>아빠 티티티 티라노사우루스 <br>할머니 티티티 티라노 <br>할머니 티티티 티라노 <br>할머니 티티티 티라노사우루스 <br>할아버지 티티티 티라노 <br>할아버지 티티티 티라노 <br>할아버지 티티티 티라노사우루스 <br>우리는 <br>티티 티라노 <br>힘이 센 <br>티티 티라노 <br>사냥꾼 <br>티티 티라노사우루스! <br>무서워! 티티 티라노 <br>도망쳐! 티티 티라노 <br>도망쳐! 티티 티라노 <br>숨자 <br>살았다 티티 티라노 <br>살았다 티티 티라노 <br>오늘도 티티 티라노 <br>살았다 <br>신난다 티티 티라노 <br>신난다 티티 티라노 <br>춤을 춰 티티 티라노 <br>노래 끝 <br>오예!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="아기 티라노" label="아기 티라노"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/스피노사우루스_VS_티라노사우루스/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 스피노사우루스 VS 티라노사우루스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%8A%A4%ED%94%BC%EB%85%B8%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EB%A3%A8%EC%8A%A4_VS_%ED%8B%B0%EB%9D%BC%EB%85%B8%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EB%A3%A8%EC%8A%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 스피노사우루스 VS 티라노사우루스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[공룡 왕은 누구? <br>나! 나! 스피노사우루스! <br>나! 나! 티라노사우루스! <br>기다란 턱 <br>큰 등뼈 <br>공룡 왕 스피노사우루스! <br>가장 큰 육식 공룡 <br>쿵쿵 쾅쾅 누구든 덤벼! <br>크앙! <br>나! 나! 스피노사우루스! <br>나! 나! 티라노사우루스! <br>강력한 턱 <br>뾰족 이빨 <br>공룡 왕 티라노사우루스! <br>가장 날쌘 육식 공룡 <br>쿵쿵 쾅쾅 누구든 덤벼! <br>크앙! <br>공룡 왕은 바로 나! <br>크아아앙]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="스피노사우루스 VS 티라노사우루스" label="스피노사우루스 VS 티라노사우루스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/최고_사냥꾼_티라노사우루스/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 최고 사냥꾼, 티라노사우루스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EC%B5%9C%EA%B3%A0_%EC%82%AC%EB%83%A5%EA%BE%BC_%ED%8B%B0%EB%9D%BC%EB%85%B8%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EB%A3%A8%EC%8A%A4/" title="핑크퐁 - 최고 사냥꾼, 티라노사우루스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[폭군 도마뱀! <br>티라노사우루스! <br>최고 사냥꾼! <br>티라노사우루스! <br>몸길이 12미터 <br>키는 5미터 <br>몸무게 8톤 <br>코끼리보다 무거워 <br>쿵쿵 휙휙! 최고 사냥꾼 <br>나는야 티라노사우루스 <br>크앙! <br>폭군 도마뱀! <br>티라노사우루스! <br>최고 사냥꾼! <br>티라노사우루스! <br>날카로운 이빨 <br>강력한 턱 <br>예리한 눈 <br>두 개의 앞발가락 <br>쿵쿵 휙휙! 최고 사냥꾼 <br>나는야 티라노사우루스 <br>나는야 티라노사우루스 <br>크앙!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="최고 사냥꾼, 티라노사우루스" label="최고 사냥꾼, 티라노사우루스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/날아라_잠자리/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 날아라 잠자리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%82%A0%EC%95%84%EB%9D%BC_%EC%9E%A0%EC%9E%90%EB%A6%AC/" title="핑크퐁 - 날아라 잠자리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[슝 슝 슝 <br>숑 숑 숑 <br>자리 자리 자리 자리 자리 잠자리 <br>슝 슝 슝 <br>숑 숑 숑 <br>자리 자리 자리 잠자리 <br>날아라 잠자리 <br>바람을 타고 <br>파란 가을 하늘 <br>높이 높이 날아 <br>비구름 내리면 <br>나뭇잎 아래서 <br>슝 슝 슝 <br>숑 숑 숑 <br>쉬어가라 <br>더 높이 <br>더 낮게 <br>자리 자리 자리 자리 잠자리 <br>날아라 잠자리 <br>바람을 타고 <br>그물 날개 네 개 <br>활짝 펴고 날아 <br>빙빙빙 뱅뱅 <br>종이 비행기처럼 <br>슝 슝 슝 <br>숑 숑 숑 <br>날아가라 <br>슝 슝 슝 <br>숑 숑 숑 <br>자리 자리 자리 자리 자리 잠자리]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="날아라 잠자리" label="날아라 잠자리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/내가_나비라면/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 내가 나비라면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84%EB%9D%BC%EB%A9%B4/" title="핑크퐁 - 내가 나비라면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우우우우 와와와와 <br>내가 곤충이라면 <br>우우우우 와와와와 <br>재밌는 상상 해보자 <br>내가 나비라면 <br>달콤한 꽃물 마실 거야 <br>내가 애벌레라면 <br>아삭한 잎 먹을 거야 <br>내가 쇠똥구리라면 <br>축구 선수될 거야 <br>내가 소금쟁이라면 <br>윈드서핑 할 거야 <br>내가 귀뚜라미라면 <br>멋진 사랑 노래할 거야 <br>내가 매미라면 <br>크게 외칠 거야 <br>“사랑해!”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="내가 나비라면" label="내가 나비라면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/100개의_지네_신발/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 100개의 지네 신발 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/100%EA%B0%9C%EC%9D%98_%EC%A7%80%EB%84%A4_%EC%8B%A0%EB%B0%9C/" title="핑크퐁 - 100개의 지네 신발 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“개미네 신발 가게로 오세요!” <br>메뚜기 양 <br>어서 오세요 <br>어떤 신발 찾나요 <br>하나 둘 셋 <br>넷 다섯 여섯 <br>여섯 개 신발 <br>발데리 발데라 <br>발데리 발데라 하 하 <br>“오, 맘에 들어요!” <br>“똑똑! 계세요?” <br>“네, 들어오세요!” <br>거미 씨 <br>어서 오세요 <br>어떤 신발 찾나요 <br>하나 둘 셋 넷 <br>다섯 여섯 일곱 여덟 <br>여덟 개 신발 <br>발데리 발데라 <br>발데리 발데라 하 하 <br>“저에게 꼭 맞아요!” <br>“개미 아저씨 저도 신발 주세요!” <br>지네 양 <br>어서 오세요 <br>어떤 신발 찾나요 <br>이십 사십 육십 팔십 백 <br>어마어마한 백 개 신발 <br>발데리 발데라 <br>발데리 발데라 하 하 <br>“정말 멋져요!” <br>“지네야, 아직도 못 신었어?”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="100개의 지네 신발" label="100개의 지네 신발"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/거미줄_파티/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 거미줄 파티 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EA%B1%B0%EB%AF%B8%EC%A4%84_%ED%8C%8C%ED%8B%B0/" title="핑크퐁 - 거미줄 파티 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[거미 <br>나는 멋쟁이 거미 <br>하지만 외로워 <br>하루 종일 심심해 <br>나는 멋쟁이 거미 <br>하지만 외로워 <br>하루 종일 심심해 <br>”재밌는 놀이가 생각났어!” <br>거미줄 <br>“거미줄!” <br>만들자 <br>“만들자!” <br>크고 멋진 거미줄 <br>친구들과 함께 <br>파티를 여는 거야 <br>퐁 퐁 거미줄 파티 <br>거미가 줄을 타고 아래 아래로 <br>거미가 줄을 타고 위로 위로 <br>나는 멋쟁이 거미 <br>외롭지 않아 <br>하루 종일 즐거워 <br>나는 멋쟁이 거미 <br>외롭지 않아 <br>하루 종일 즐거워 <br>거미줄 <br>“거미줄!” <br>만들자 <br>“만들자!” <br>크고 멋진 거미줄 <br>친구들과 함께 <br>파티를 여는 거야 <br>퐁 퐁 거미줄 파티]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="거미줄 파티" label="거미줄 파티"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/벌레들의_행진/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 벌레들의 행진 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%B2%8C%EB%A0%88%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%98_%ED%96%89%EC%A7%84/" title="핑크퐁 - 벌레들의 행진 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쿵따리 라바라 쿵따리 쿵 <br>우 우 우 <br>렛츠 고 <br>개미들이 행진을 <br>하나 둘 셋 <br>“착!” <br>하나 둘 셋 <br>“착!” <br>하나 둘 셋 <br>“착!” <br>개미들이 행진을 <br>하나 둘 셋 <br>“착!” <br>하루 종일 <br>벌들이 꿀 찾아 <br>붕 붕 붕 <br>“붕!” <br>붕 붕 붕 <br>“붕!” <br>붕 붕 붕 <br>“붕!” <br>벌들이 꿀 찾아 <br>붕 붕 붕 <br>“붕!” <br>하루 종일 <br>우 우 우 <br>렛츠 고 <br>깊은 밤 반딧불이 <br>깜빡 깜빡 <br>깜빡 깜빡 <br>깜빡 깜빡 <br>깊은 밤 반딧불이 <br>깜빡 깜빡 <br>밤새도록 <br>애벌레들 잎 찾아 <br>꼬물 꼬물 <br>“꼬물!” <br>꼬물 꼬물 <br>“꼬물!” <br>꼬물 꼬물 <br>“꼬물!” <br>애벌레들 잎 찾아 <br>꼬물 꼬물 <br>“꼬물!” <br>하루 종일 <br>쿵따리 라바라 쿵따리 쿵 <br>“예!’]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="벌레들의 행진" label="벌레들의 행진"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/꼬물꼬물_내_친구/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 꼬물꼬물 내 친구 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EA%BC%AC%EB%AC%BC%EA%BC%AC%EB%AC%BC_%EB%82%B4_%EC%B9%9C%EA%B5%AC/" title="핑크퐁 - 꼬물꼬물 내 친구 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[B! <br>U! <br>G! <br>S! Bugs! <br>꼬물꼬물 귀여운 내 친구 <br>“친구!” <br>꿈틀꿈틀 벌레는 내 친구 <br>“친구!” <br>꿀벌과 나비 꿀을 찾아 날죠 <br>귀뚜라미 날개 비벼 노래하죠 <br>개미와 메뚜기 동화 속 주인공 <br>벌레는 귀여운 내 친구 <br>애벌레 무당벌레도 난 좋아 <br>쉬지 않고 열심히 기어가지 <br>거미와 잠자리도 난 좋아 <br>벌레는 귀여운 내 친구 <br>꼬물꼬물 귀여운 내 친구 <br>“친구!” <br>꿈틀꿈틀 귀여운 내 친구 <br>“예!”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="꼬물꼬물 내 친구" label="꼬물꼬물 내 친구"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/반짝반짝_반딧불이/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 반짝반짝 반딧불이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%B0%98%EC%A7%9D%EB%B0%98%EC%A7%9D_%EB%B0%98%EB%94%A7%EB%B6%88%EC%9D%B4/" title="핑크퐁 - 반짝반짝 반딧불이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[반짝반짝 작은 별 <br>“우와, 반짝반짝 반딧불이다!” <br>반짝반짝 반딧불이 <br>아름답게 빛나네 <br>여름 밤의 별처럼 <br>엄마 자장가처럼 <br>반짝반짝 반딧불이 <br>아름답게 빛나네 <br>“우와아! 하늘에 반딧불이가 가득해!” <br>반짝반짝 반딧불이 <br>아름답게 빛나네 <br>여름 밤의 별처럼 <br>엄마 자장가처럼 <br>반짝반짝 반딧불이 <br>아름답게 빛나네]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="반짝반짝 반딧불이" label="반짝반짝 반딧불이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/무당벌레_안녕_/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 무당벌레, 안녕? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%AC%B4%EB%8B%B9%EB%B2%8C%EB%A0%88_%EC%95%88%EB%85%95_/" title="핑크퐁 - 무당벌레, 안녕? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[귀여운 무당벌레 <br>헤이 롤리 롤리 로 <br>“안녕?” <br>반갑게 인사해요 <br>헤이 롤리 롤리 로 <br>“안녕?” <br>푸른 하늘 높이 날아 <br>무당벌레 안녕 <br>향기론 꽃밭 사이 <br>무당벌레 안녕 <br>검은 점 무늬 콕콕 <br>무당벌레 안녕 <br>빠알간 날개 동글 <br>무당벌레 안녕 <br>귀여운 무당벌레 <br>헤이 롤리 롤리 로 <br>“안녕?” <br>반갑게 인사해요 <br>헤이 롤리 롤리 로 <br>“안녕?” <br>푸른 하늘 높이 날아 <br>무당벌레 안녕 <br>“안녕?” <br>향기론 꽃밭 사이 <br>무당벌레 안녕 <br>“안녕?” <br>검은 점 무늬 콕콕 <br>무당벌레 안녕 <br>“안녕?” <br>빠알간 날개 동글 <br>무당벌레 안녕 <br>“안녕?” <br>귀여운 무당벌레 <br>헤이 롤리 롤리 로 <br>“안녕?” <br>반갑게 인사해요 <br>헤이 롤리 롤리 로 <br>“안녕?”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="무당벌레, 안녕?" label="무당벌레, 안녕?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/나비의_왈츠/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 나비의 왈츠 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%82%98%EB%B9%84%EC%9D%98_%EC%99%88%EC%B8%A0/" title="핑크퐁 - 나비의 왈츠 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나풀나풀 고운 나비야 <br>어여쁜 장미 향기 맡고서 <br>날개 활짝 펴고 날아올라 <br>나풀나풀 나비야 <br>“ 얘들아! 우리 같이 날아볼까?” <br>나풀나풀 고운 나비야 <br>어여쁜 장미 향기 맡고서 <br>날개 활짝 펴고 날아올라 <br>나풀나풀 나비야]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="나비의 왈츠" label="나비의 왈츠"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/꿀벌의_비행/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 꿀벌의 비행 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EA%BF%80%EB%B2%8C%EC%9D%98_%EB%B9%84%ED%96%89/" title="핑크퐁 - 꿀벌의 비행 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[붕붕붕붕 더 높이 <br>날아라 붕붕 꿀벌 <br>꿀벌이 붕붕 <br>춤을 춰요 붕붕 <br>빙글뱅글 리본 춤 <br>“저쪽에 꿀이 있어!” <br>꿀벌이 붕붕 <br>춤을 춰요 붕붕 <br>친구와 함께 붕붕붕 <br>“오예!” <br>“맛있어!” <br>“달콤해!” <br>“더 크게!” <br>꿀벌이 붕붕 <br>춤을 춰요 붕붕 <br>빙글뱅글 리본 춤 <br>“저쪽에 꿀이 있어!” <br>꿀벌이 붕붕 <br>춤을 춰요 붕붕 <br>친구와 함께 붕붕붕 <br>붕붕붕붕 더 높이 <br>날아라 붕붕 꿀벌 <br>“붕붕붕!”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="꿀벌의 비행" label="꿀벌의 비행"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/배고픈_애벌레/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 배고픈 애벌레 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EB%B0%B0%EA%B3%A0%ED%94%88_%EC%95%A0%EB%B2%8C%EB%A0%88/" title="핑크퐁 - 배고픈 애벌레 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[냠냠냠 나뭇잎 <br>냠냠냠 나뭇잎 <br>맛있는 나뭇잎 <br>난 배고픈 <br>배고픈! <br>애벌레 <br>애벌레! <br>먹는 게 너무 좋아 <br>“냠냠!” <br>무럭무럭 자라나서 <br>어여쁜 나비 될 거야 <br>난 배고픈 애벌레 <br>먹는 게 너무 좋아 <br>“냠냠!” <br>무럭무럭 자라나서 <br>어여쁜 나비 될 거야 <br>냠 냠 냠 <br>“음~” <br>냠 냠 냠 <br>“오~” <br>냠 냠 냠 냠 나뭇잎 <br>“맛있어!” <br>우린 배고픈 애벌레 <br>“준비!” <br>어여쁜 나비 될 거야]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="배고픈 애벌레" label="배고픈 애벌레"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/개미가_바지_속에/</id><title>핑크퐁 - 개미가 바지 속에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/%EA%B0%9C%EB%AF%B8%EA%B0%80_%EB%B0%94%EC%A7%80_%EC%86%8D%EC%97%90/" title="핑크퐁 - 개미가 바지 속에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“으악! 개미다!” <br>개미가 여기 <br>“여기!” <br>개미가 저기 <br>“저기!” <br>개미가 여기저기 바지 속에서 <br>“어머!” <br>행진하며 간질간질 <br>춤추자고 간질간질 <br>개미와 신나는 댄스 <br>“댄스!” <br>“으악!” <br>개미가 여기 <br>“여기!” <br>개미가 저기 <br>“저기!” <br>개미가 여기저기 바지 속에서 <br>“어머!” <br>행진하며 간질간질 <br>춤추자고 간질간질 <br>개미와 신나는 댄스 <br>“댄스!” <br>다같이 씰룩 <br>“씰룩!” <br>다같이 쌜룩 <br>“쌜룩!” <br>다같이 씰룩쌜룩 <br>신나게 춤춰 봐 <br>이제 그만 <br>“그만!” <br>제발 그만 <br>“그만!” <br>개미와 신나는 댄스 <br>“예!”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="개미가 바지 속에" label="개미가 바지 속에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정경영/당신에게/</id><title>정경영 - 당신에게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:53:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:53:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EA%B2%BD%EC%98%81/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C/" title="정경영 - 당신에게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아주 오랜 만남이었죠 <br>아직 만날 날이 많지만 <br>그렇게 오랜 시간 속에서 <br>그댈 위한 시간은 너무도 짧았죠 <br>미안해요 고마워요 <br>당신을 처음 만난 그때와 달리 <br>나는 점점 커져가고 <br>그댄 아이가 돼요 <br>지금껏 받았던 사랑 <br>모두 다시 드려도 <br>부족한 걸요 <br>너무 부족하지만 모자라지만 <br>그대 등이 작아질수록 <br>더 크게 보답할게요 <br>이젠 나의 시간을 <br>당신을 위해 쓸게요 <br>나만 바라봐왔던 <br>나를 위해 살아왔던 <br>그대를 이제는 혼자 두지 않을게요 <br>사랑해요 그대를 사랑해요 <br>아무리 말해도 부족한 그 한마디 <br>그대가 잠들고 <br>우리의 시간이 남지 않아도 <br>잊지 않을게요 <br>]]></content><category term="정경영" label="정경영"/><category term="당신에게" label="당신에게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stimpack_스팀팩/Long_Night_Feat_Y1ee/</id><title>Stimpack_스팀팩 - Long Night (Feat. Y1ee) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Stimpack_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8C%80%ED%8C%A9/Long_Night_Feat_Y1ee/" title="Stimpack_스팀팩 - Long Night (Feat. Y1ee) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[we want the red bull yeah <br>we want the red bull yeah <br>우리의 생명 yeah <br>미친 밤에 난 늘 oh yeah <br>we criminal in club <br>나는 원해 여자들과 침대 all day <br>mri 찍어 brain <br>말 처럼 쉽진 않네 <br>너의 그 엉덩이 두개를 미친듯 <br>흔들면 돌아버리지 oh yeah <br>여기는 사람이 너무도 많아서 <br>기분이 이상해져 birth day <br>yeah yeah long night oh yeag <br>오늘 난 아쉬워져 all pass <br>다른건 접어 Double latex <br>지금 내 손엔 술 잔이 두개 <br>오늘 밤은 계속 red bulls <br>long night we gotta do <br>guest house we go malibu <br>we see the light some star on you <br>오늘 난 feel so fly <br>we go club &amp; bulls one shot <br>after 우리집 come all night <br>drivin' 침대 위 long all night <br>오늘 밤은 계속 red bulls <br>long night we gotta do <br>ready my night perfect your 나이 <br>오늘은 괜찮아 so that's alright <br>니가 내 몸에 니 몸을 밀착한 <br>지금 이 순간에 난 <br>always ya my baby <br>오늘 밤은 계속 되 forever ya <br>오늘 밤은 절대로 못 잊어 like <br>tokyo street takoyaki 매일 날 <br>먹고 싶진 않겠지만 다시 날 <br>분명 찾게 될꺼고 그때 다시 말 <br>하게 될꺼야 아 그래 이 맛이야 <br>special night we paradise <br>그래 미친듯이 부어 마셔 red bulls <br>yeah i m clean up hitter bitch <br>yeah i m clean up hitter ya <br>오늘 밤은 계속 red bulls <br>long night we gotta do <br>guest house we go malibu <br>we see the light some star on you <br>오늘 난 feel so fly <br>we go club &amp; bulls one shot <br>after 우리집 come all night <br>drivin' 침대 위 long all night <br>오늘 밤은 계속 red bulls <br>long night we gotta do <br>어깨만 스치고 가는거 <br>내가 돌아볼걸 알아 넌 <br>어쩌지 여기서 나 <br>어쩐지 여기서 너 <br>한두번 봤는게 아닌거 <br>볼테면 눈 마주치는 건 <br>어차피 여기서 나 <br>여기선 어차피 너 <br>말곤 안보여 아까부터 <br>니 빈 잔이 자꾸 맘에 걸려 <br>혹시나 하는 맘에 내 잔을 <br>또 내밀어 못 미더워 <br>하는게 귀여워 그래 여긴 더워 <br>밖으로 나가자 잘 안들려 yeah <br>오늘 밤은 계속 red bulls <br>long night we gotta do <br>guest house we go malibu <br>we see the light some star on you <br>오늘 난 feel so fly <br>we go club &amp; bulls one shot <br>after 우리집 come all night <br>drivin' 침대 위 long all night <br>오늘 밤은 계속 red bulls <br>long night we gotta do <br>]]></content><category term="Stimpack (스팀팩)" label="Stimpack (스팀팩)"/><category term="Long Night (Feat. Y1ee)" label="Long Night (Feat. Y1ee)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Twinkle_Twinkle_Little_Star/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Twinkle_Twinkle_Little_Star/" title="핑크퐁 - Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Twinkle, twinkle, little star, <br>How I wonder what you are! <br>Up above the world so high, <br>Like a diamond in the sky. <br>Twinkle, twinkle, little star, <br>How I wonder what you are! <br>When the blazing sun is gone, <br>When he nothing shines upon, <br>Then you show your little light, <br>Twinkle, twinkle, all the night. <br>Twinkle, twinkle, little star, <br>How I wonder what you are]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star" label="Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Sing_a_Song_of_Sixpence/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Sing a Song of Sixpence - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Sing_a_Song_of_Sixpence/" title="핑크퐁 - Sing a Song of Sixpence - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sing a song of sixpence, <br>a pocket full of rye. <br>Four and twenty blackbirds <br>baked in a pie. <br>When the pie was opened, <br>the birds began to sing. <br>Wasn’t that a dainty dish to set <br>before the king? <br>The king was in his counting house <br>counting out his money. <br>The queen was in the parlor <br>eating bread and honey. <br>The maid was in the garden <br>hanging out the clothes. <br>There came a little blackbird <br>and pecked off her nose]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Sing a Song of Sixpence" label="Sing a Song of Sixpence"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/This_Old_Man/</id><title>핑크퐁 - This Old Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/This_Old_Man/" title="핑크퐁 - This Old Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[“Hey, march with us!” <br>La-La-La-La. La-La-La. <br>La-La-La-La-La-La. La-La-La. <br>This old man. <br>He played one. One! <br>He played nick-nack on my thumb. <br>With a nick-nack paddy-whack, <br>give a dog a bone, <br>this old man came rolling home. <br>“ Join the parade!” <br>This old man. <br>He played two. Two! <br>He played nick-nack on my shoe. <br>With a nick-nack paddy-whack, <br>give a dog a bone, <br>this old man came rolling home. <br>“ Join the parade!” <br>This old man. <br>He played Three. Three! <br>He played nick-nack on my knee. <br>With a nick-nack paddy-whack, <br>give a dog a bone, <br>this old man came rolling home. <br>This old man came rolling home. <br>This old man came rolling home. <br>This old man came rolling home. <br>“Join the parade! Yeah!”]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="This Old Man" label="This Old Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Georgie_Porgie/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Georgie Porgie - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Georgie_Porgie/" title="핑크퐁 - Georgie Porgie - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Georgie Porgie, pudding and pie, <br>kissed the girls and made them cry. <br>When the boys came out to play, <br>Georgie Porgie ran away. <br>Georgie Porgie, pudding and pie, <br>kissed the girls and made them cry. <br>When the boys came out to play, <br>Georgie Porgie ran away. <br>Georgie Porgie! <br>Georgie Porgie]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Georgie Porgie" label="Georgie Porgie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Little_Miss_Muffet/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Little Miss Muffet - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Little_Miss_Muffet/" title="핑크퐁 - Little Miss Muffet - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Little Miss Muffet sat on a tuffet <br>eating her curds and whey. <br>Along came a spider, <br>who sat down beside her, <br>and frightened Miss Muffet away. <br>Little Miss Muffet sat on a tuffet <br>eating her curds and whey. <br>Along came a spider, <br>who sat down beside her, <br>and frightened Miss Muffet away! <br>Away! <br>And frightened Miss Muffet away]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Little Miss Muffet" label="Little Miss Muffet"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/John_Jacob_Jingleheimer_Schmidt/</id><title>핑크퐁 - John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/John_Jacob_Jingleheimer_Schmidt/" title="핑크퐁 - John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da! <br>Wow! <br>John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt! <br>That’s my name, too! <br>Oh, yeah! <br>Whenever I go out <br>the people always shout. <br>John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt! <br>Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da! <br>John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt! <br>That’s my name, too! <br>Oh, yeah! <br>Whenever I go out <br>the people always shout. <br>John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt! <br>Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da! <br>John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt! <br>That’s my name, too! <br>Oh, yeah! <br>Whenever I go out <br>the people always shout. <br>John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt! <br>Da, da, da, da, da, da, da, da! <br>Wow!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt" label="John Jacob Jingleheimer Schmidt"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/London_Bridge/</id><title>핑크퐁 - London Bridge - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/London_Bridge/" title="핑크퐁 - London Bridge - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Down, down, down, down. <br>Down, down, down, down. <br>London Bridge is falling down, <br>falling down, falling down. <br>London Bridge is falling down, <br>my fair lady. <br>Build it up with wood and clay. <br>Wood and clay, wood and clay. <br>Build it up with wood and clay, <br>my fair lady. <br>Everybody! <br>London Bridge is falling down, <br>falling down, falling down. <br>London Bridge is falling down, <br>my fair lady. <br>Down, down, down, down. <br>Down, down, down, down. <br>One more time! <br>Down, down, down, down. <br>Down, down, down, down. <br>My fair lady]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="London Bridge" label="London Bridge"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Little_Bo-Peep/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Little Bo-Peep - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Little_Bo-Peep/" title="핑크퐁 - Little Bo-Peep - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I lost my sheep! <br>Sheep! <br>Little Bo-Peep has lost her sheep, <br>and doesn’t know where to find them. <br>Leave them alone, and they’ll come home, <br>wagging their tails behind them. <br>Sheep! Sheep! <br>Little Bo-Peep fell fast asleep, <br>and dreamed she heard them bleating. <br>When she awoke, she found her sheep, <br>wagging their tails behind them. <br>Whew! <br>Sheep!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Little Bo-Peep" label="Little Bo-Peep"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/I’ve_Been_Working_on_the_Railroad/</id><title>핑크퐁 - I’ve Been Working on the Railroad - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/I%E2%80%99ve_Been_Working_on_the_Railroad/" title="핑크퐁 - I’ve Been Working on the Railroad - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been working on the railroad, <br>all the live long day. <br>I've been working on the railroad, <br>just to pass the time away! <br>I've been working on the railroad, <br>all the live long day. <br>I've been working on the railroad, <br>just to pass the time away. <br>Don't you hear the whistle blowing? <br>Rise up so early in the morning? <br>Don't you hear the captain shouting? <br>Dinah, blow your horn! <br>Dinah, won't you blow? <br>Dinah, won't you blow? <br>Dinah, won't you blow your horn, <br>your horn? <br>Dinah, won't you blow? <br>Dinah, won't you blow? <br>Dinah, won't you blow your horn? <br>Someone's in the kitchen with Dinah. <br>Someone's in the kitchen <br>I know, I know. <br>Oh, someone's in the kitchen <br>with Dinah, <br>strumming on the old banjo. <br>Fee fie fiddly-i-o. <br>Fee fie fiddly-i-o-i-o-i. <br>Fee fie fiddly-i-o, <br>strumming on the old banjo]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="I’ve Been Working on the Railroad" label="I’ve Been Working on the Railroad"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Pease_Porridge_Hot/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Pease Porridge Hot - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Pease_Porridge_Hot/" title="핑크퐁 - Pease Porridge Hot - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pease porridge hot, <br>pease porridge cold, <br>Pease porridge in the pot, <br>nine days old. <br>Some like it hot, <br>some like it cold, <br>some like it in the pot, <br>nine days old. <br>Pease porridge hot, <br>pease porridge cold, <br>Pease porridge in the pot, <br>nine days old. <br>Some like it hot, <br>some like it cold, <br>some like it in the pot, <br>nine days old.]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Pease Porridge Hot" label="Pease Porridge Hot"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/The_Mulberry_Bush/</id><title>핑크퐁 - The Mulberry Bush - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/The_Mulberry_Bush/" title="핑크퐁 - The Mulberry Bush - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here we go round the mulberry bush, <br>The mulberry bush, the mulberry bush. <br>Here we go round the mulberry bush, <br>So early in the morning. <br>Mom! <br>This is the way we wash our clothes, <br>wash our clothes, wash our clothes. <br>This is the way we wash our clothes, <br>so early in the morning. <br>Honey! <br>This is the way we sweep the floor, <br>sweep the floor, sweep the floor. <br>This is the way we sweep the floor, <br>so early in the morning. <br>Guys! <br>Here we go round the mulberry bush, <br>The mulberry bush, the mulberry bush. <br>Here we go round the mulberry bush, <br>So early in the morning]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="The Mulberry Bush" label="The Mulberry Bush"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Little_Jack_Horner/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Little Jack Horner - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Little_Jack_Horner/" title="핑크퐁 - Little Jack Horner - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, so cold! <br>I’d like to eat my Christmas pie! <br>Little Jack Horner sat in a corner, <br>eating a Christmas pie. <br>He put in his thumb <br>and pulled out a plum, <br>and said, “What a good boy am I!” <br>Oh! It’s a plum! <br>Mm, yummy! <br>Little Jack Horner sat in a corner, <br>eating a Christmas pie. <br>He put in his thumb <br>and pulled out a plum, <br>and said, “What a good boy am I!” <br>I’m full!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Little Jack Horner" label="Little Jack Horner"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/The_Farmer_in_the_Dell/</id><title>핑크퐁 - The Farmer in the Dell - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/The_Farmer_in_the_Dell/" title="핑크퐁 - The Farmer in the Dell - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heigh-ho! <br>The farmer in the dell. <br>The farmer in the dell. <br>Heigh-ho! <br>Heigh-ho! <br>The derry-O! <br>The farmer in the dell. <br>The farmer takes the child. <br>The farmer takes the child. <br>Heigh-ho! <br>Heigh-ho! <br>The derry-O! <br>The farmer takes the child. <br>The child takes the cat. <br>The child takes the cat. <br>Heigh-ho! <br>Heigh-ho! <br>The derry-O! <br>The child takes the cat. <br>Heigh-ho! <br>Heigh-ho! <br>The cat takes the rat. <br>The cat takes the rat. <br>Heigh-ho! <br>Heigh-ho! <br>The derry-O! <br>The cat takes the rat. <br>The rat takes the cheese. <br>The rat takes the cheese. <br>Heigh-ho! The derry-O! <br>The rat takes the cheese. <br>Heigh-ho! <br>Heigh-ho! <br>Heigh-ho! <br>Heigh-ho! <br>Yeah!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="The Farmer in the Dell" label="The Farmer in the Dell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Jack_and_Jill/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Jack and Jill - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Jack_and_Jill/" title="핑크퐁 - Jack and Jill - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jack! Jill! <br>Could you go and fetch me <br>a pail of water, please? <br>OK, Mom! <br>Jack and Jill went up the hill <br>to fetch a pail of water. <br>Jack fell down and broke his crown <br>and Jill came tumbling after. <br>Up Jack got and home did trot <br>as fast as he could caper, <br>went to bed to mend his head <br>with vinegar and brown paper. <br>Are you OK, Jack? <br>I’m OK, Mom]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Jack and Jill" label="Jack and Jill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Mary_Mary_Quite_Contrary/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Mary, Mary, Quite Contrary - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Mary_Mary_Quite_Contrary/" title="핑크퐁 - Mary, Mary, Quite Contrary - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is my garden! <br>Ta-da! <br>Mary, Mary, quite contrary, <br>how does your garden grow? <br>With silver bells and cockle shells <br>and pretty maids all in a row. <br>Mary, Mary, quite contrary, <br>how does your garden grow? <br>With silver bells and cockle shells <br>and pretty maids all in a row]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Mary, Mary, Quite Contrary" label="Mary, Mary, Quite Contrary"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Hey_Diddle_Diddle/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Hey, Diddle, Diddle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Hey_Diddle_Diddle/" title="핑크퐁 - Hey, Diddle, Diddle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey, diddle, diddle, <br>the cat and the fiddle, <br>the cow jumped over the moon. <br>The little dog laughed <br>to see such sport, <br>and the dish ran away <br>with the spoon. <br>Hey, diddle, diddle, <br>the cat and the fiddle, <br>the cow jumped over the moon. <br>The little dog laughed <br>to see such sport, <br>and the dish ran away <br>with the spoon. <br>Hey, diddle, diddle, <br>the cat and the fiddle, <br>the cow jumped over the moon. <br>The little dog laughed <br>to see such sport, <br>and the dish ran away <br>with the spoon.]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Hey, Diddle, Diddle" label="Hey, Diddle, Diddle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/There’s_a_hole_in_the_Middle_of_the_Sea/</id><title>핑크퐁 - There’s a hole in the Middle of the Sea - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/There%E2%80%99s_a_hole_in_the_Middle_of_the_Sea/" title="핑크퐁 - There’s a hole in the Middle of the Sea - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a hole <br>in the middle of the sea. <br>Clap! Clap! <br>There's a hole <br>in the middle of the sea. <br>Clap! Clap! <br>There's a hole. <br>There's a hole. <br>There's a hole <br>in the middle of the sea. <br>Clap! Clap! <br>There's a log in the hole <br>in the middle of the sea. <br>Blup! Blup! <br>There's a log in the hole <br>in the middle of the sea. <br>Blup! Blup! <br>There's a log. <br>There's a log. <br>There's a log in the hole <br>in the middle of the sea. <br>Blup! Blup! <br>There's a frog on the log <br>in the hole <br>in the middle of the sea. <br>Ribbit! Ribbit! <br>There's a frog on the log <br>in the hole <br>in the middle of the sea. <br>Ribbit! Ribbit! <br>There's a frog. <br>There's a frog. <br>There's a frog on the log <br>in the hole <br>in the middle of the sea. <br>Ribbit! Ribbit]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="There’s a hole in the Middle of the Sea" label="There’s a hole in the Middle of the Sea"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Pussy_Cat_Pussy_Cat/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Pussy Cat, Pussy Cat - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Pussy_Cat_Pussy_Cat/" title="핑크퐁 - Pussy Cat, Pussy Cat - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pussy cat, pussy cat, <br>where have you been? <br>I’ve been to London <br>to visit the queen. <br>Pussy cat, pussy cat, <br>what did you there? <br>I frightened a little mouse <br>under her chair. <br>Meow! Meow! <br>Pussy cat, pussy cat, <br>where have you been? <br>I’ve been to London <br>to visit the queen. <br>Pussy cat, pussy cat, <br>what did you there? <br>I frightened a little mouse <br>under her chair. <br>Meow! Meow]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Pussy Cat, Pussy Cat" label="Pussy Cat, Pussy Cat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Hot_Cross_Buns/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Hot Cross Buns - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Hot_Cross_Buns/" title="핑크퐁 - Hot Cross Buns - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hot cross buns! <br>Hot cross buns! <br>Hot cross buns! <br>Hot cross buns! Hot cross buns! <br>One a penny, two a penny, <br>hot cross buns! <br>Give them to your daughters, <br>give them to your sons. <br>One a penny, two a penny, <br>hot cross buns! <br>Hot cross buns! Hot cross buns! <br>One a penny, two a penny, <br>hot cross buns! <br>Give them to your daughters, <br>give them to your sons. <br>One a penny, two a penny, <br>hot cross buns!]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Hot Cross Buns" label="Hot Cross Buns"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Yankee_Doodle/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Yankee Doodle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Yankee_Doodle/" title="핑크퐁 - Yankee Doodle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yankee Doodle went to town <br>riding on a pony. <br>Stuck a feather in his hat <br>and called it macaroni. <br>Yankee Doodle, keep it up! <br>Yankee doodle, dandy! <br>Mind the music and the step, <br>and with the girls be handy. <br>Yankee Doodle went to town <br>riding on a pony. <br>Stuck a feather in his hat <br>and called it macaroni. <br>Yankee Doodle, keep it up! <br>Yankee doodle, dandy! <br>Mind the music and the step, <br>and with the girls be handy]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Yankee Doodle" label="Yankee Doodle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Skip_to_My_Lou/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Skip to My Lou - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Skip_to_My_Lou/" title="핑크퐁 - Skip to My Lou - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Skip, <br>skip, <br>skip, <br>skip. <br>Skip to my Lou~! <br>Lost my partner, what'll I do? <br>Lost my partner, what'll I do? <br>Lost my partner, what'll I do? <br>Skip to my Lou, my darling. <br>Go, go, go! <br>Skip, skip, skip to my Lou. <br>Skip, skip, skip to my Lou. <br>Skip, skip, skip to my Lou. <br>Skip to my Lou, my darling. <br>Lost my partner, what'll I do? <br>Lost my partner, what'll I do? <br>Lost my partner, what'll I do? <br>Skip to my Lou, my darling. <br>Go, go, go! <br>Skip, skip, skip to my Lou. <br>Skip, skip, skip to my Lou. <br>Skip, skip, skip to my Lou. <br>Skip to my Lou, my darling]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Skip to My Lou" label="Skip to My Lou"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Humpty_Dumpty/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Humpty Dumpty - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Humpty_Dumpty/" title="핑크퐁 - Humpty Dumpty - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall. <br>Humpty Dumpty had a great fall. <br>All the king’s horses <br>and all the king’s men <br>couldn’t put Humpty together again. <br>Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall. <br>Humpty Dumpty had a great fall. <br>All the king’s horses <br>and all the king’s men <br>couldn’t put Humpty together again]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Humpty Dumpty" label="Humpty Dumpty"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/To_Market_to_Market/</id><title>핑크퐁 - To Market, to Market - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:54:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:54:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/To_Market_to_Market/" title="핑크퐁 - To Market, to Market - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[To market, to market <br>to buy a fat pig. <br>Home again, home again, jiggety-jig. <br>To market, to market <br>to buy a fat hen. <br>Home again, home again, rickety-ren. <br>To market, to market <br>to buy a white cake. <br>Home again, home again, <br>never was baked. <br>To market, to market <br>to buy a plum bun. <br>Home again, home again, <br>market is done]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="To Market, to Market" label="To Market, to Market"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/Row_Row_Your_Boat/</id><title>핑크퐁 - Row, Row, Your Boat - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:55:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:55:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/Row_Row_Your_Boat/" title="핑크퐁 - Row, Row, Your Boat - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Row, row, row your boat, <br>gently down the stream. <br>Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily, <br>life is but a dream. <br>One, two! <br>One, two, three, four! <br>Row, row, row your boat, <br>gently down the stream. <br>Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily, <br>life is but a dream. <br>Merrily, merrily, merrily, merrily, <br>life is but a dream.]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="Row, Row, Your Boat" label="Row, Row, Your Boat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑크퐁/One_Two_Buckle_My_Shoe/</id><title>핑크퐁 - One, Two, Buckle My Shoe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-03T15:55:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-03T15:55:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%ED%81%AC%ED%90%81/One_Two_Buckle_My_Shoe/" title="핑크퐁 - One, Two, Buckle My Shoe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do it! Bucklie my shoe. <br>Do it! Bucklie my shoe. <br>Do it! <br>Do it! <br>One, two! Buckle my shoe. <br>Three, four! Open the door. <br>Five, six! Pick up sticks. <br>Seven, eight! Lay them straight. <br>Nine, ten! A big fat hen. <br>Do it again. <br>Do it! Bucklie my shoe. <br>Do it! Bucklie my shoe. <br>Do it! <br>Do it! <br>One, two! Buckle my shoe. <br>Three, four! Open the door. <br>Five, six! Pick up sticks. <br>Seven, eight! Lay them straight. <br>Nine, ten! A big fat hen. <br>That’s the end! <br>One, two, three]]></content><category term="핑크퐁" label="핑크퐁"/><category term="One, Two, Buckle My Shoe" label="One, Two, Buckle My Shoe"/></entry></feed>