<feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:05:50+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/허밍라운지/그리움의_하루/</id><title>허밍라운지 - 그리움의 하루 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:05:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:05:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%88%EB%B0%8D%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4%EC%A7%80/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9B%80%EC%9D%98_%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8/" title="허밍라운지 - 그리움의 하루 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[불어오네요 저 바람에 그대오네요 <br>내게 고이 맺힌 눈물 <br>싸늘히 가져가는 그대가 오네요 <br>흘러가네요 저 빗물에 그대가네요 <br>나의 자그마한 침묵을 <br>요란히 가져가는 그대가 가네요 <br>나무 의자에 걸터앉아 <br>조용한 노래를 들으며 <br>애써 태연한 웃음 지으며 우네 <br>온종일 귀를 틀어 막아도 <br>미친 듯이 웃어봐도 <br>그대의 온기를 잊을 수 없어 <br>슬픔에 나를 밀어 내봐도 <br>미친 듯이 울어봐도 <br>그대의 기억을 놓을 수 없어 <br>웃고 있나요 아니면 <br>울고 있나요 아무렇지도 않게 <br>나를 떠난 그댄 지금 웃나요 <br>나무 의자에 걸터앉아 <br>조용한 노래를 들으며 <br>애써 태연한 웃음 지으며 우네 <br>온종일 귀를 틀어 막아도 <br>미친듯이 웃어봐도 <br>그대의 온기를 잊을 수 없어 <br>슬픔에 나를 밀어 내봐도 <br>미친듯이 울어봐도 <br>그대의 기억을 놓을 수 없어 <br>노을 하늘에 또 너를 올려도 <br>이내 달빛에 떠내려가고 <br>어둠에 가리네 <br>온종일 귀를 틀어 막아도 <br>미친듯이 웃어봐도 <br>그대의 온기를 잊을 수 없어 <br>슬픔에 나를 밀어 내봐도 <br>미친듯이 울어봐도 <br>그대의 기억을 놓을 수 없어 <br>그대의 기억을 놓을 수 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="허밍라운지" label="허밍라운지"/><category term="그리움의 하루" label="그리움의 하루"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오은지/별/</id><title>오은지 - 별 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:05:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:05:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%9D%80%EC%A7%80/%EB%B3%84/" title="오은지 - 별 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예쁘네 오늘도 어제만큼 <br>오늘은 더 빛나 보여 <br>옆에 다른 별들보다 더 <br>자꾸 내 눈에 들어와 <br>너 환하게 비춰주는 그런 너라서 <br>I think I need you <br>I think I love you <br>손 내밀면 닿을 것 같은 <br>꿈만 같은 너인데 <br>I think I need you <br>I think I love you <br>내가 가는 곳 어디든 <br>항상 있어 주면 돼 <br>오늘 밤엔 너와 함께 있었으면 해 <br>밤하늘엔 항상 네가 있었으면 해 <br>I need you I want you oh oh <br>잠 못 드는 밤 네 옆에 별이 될래 <br>보고 싶어 오늘도 어제만큼 <br>더 보고싶어 <br>수많은 별들 중 딱 너 하나 <br>자꾸 내 맘에 들어와 <br>너 환하게 비춰주는 그런 너라서 <br>I think I need you <br>I think I love you <br>손 내밀면 닿을 것 같은 <br>꿈만 같은 너인데 <br>I think I need you <br>I think I love you <br>내가 가는 곳 어디든 <br>항상 있어 주면 돼 <br>오늘 밤엔 너와 함께 있었으면 해 <br>밤하늘엔 항상 네가 있었으면 해 <br>I need you I want you oh oh <br>잠 못 드는 밤 네 옆에 별이 될래 <br>너는 곁에 없지만 <br>그저 바라만 봐도 좋은 너 <br>하루종일 네 생각에 밤 잠을 설치며 <br>너만 바라보고 있는 나 <br>오늘 밤엔 너와 함께 있었으면 해 <br>밤하늘엔 항상 니가 있었으면 해 <br>I need you I want you <br>잠 못드는 밤 니 옆에 별이 될래 <br>]]></content><category term="오은지" label="오은지"/><category term="별" label="별"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HANAMALOO/안경잽이_Feat_MACDADDY_KCDP_MOLDY/</id><title>HANAMALOO - 안경잽이 (Feat. MACDADDY, KCDP, MOLDY) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:05:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:05:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HANAMALOO/%EC%95%88%EA%B2%BD%EC%9E%BD%EC%9D%B4_Feat_MACDADDY_KCDP_MOLDY/" title="HANAMALOO - 안경잽이 (Feat. MACDADDY, KCDP, MOLDY) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I just wanna lay down <br>그 자리는 1인석 <br>특급 찍지 k-2 <br>이젠 필요해 ak-47 <br>내 입 안에 뱀 <br>내 경쟁자들 피리불어 <br>동시에 my finger <br>on the trigger ak-47 <br>올라간 눈썹 금색 어금니 <br>내 금색 어금니는 없어 버릇이 <br>내 맘속 어장 안에 <br>유일한 물고기 selfish <br>너네와는 다르지 그래서 <br>내가 여자한테 잘 먹혀 <br>잘 먹고 난 너네한테 <br>전혀 경쟁심 못 느껴 macdaddy <br>그래 내 아이디 lesburrrn <br>무슨 뜻이냐면 let’s burn <br>니 여잔 내 뒤에 태워 <br>내 소갠 이 정도면 됐고 <br>난 갈길 갈게 <br>다음에 봐 <br>내 여자친구의 남자친구 <br>이게 무슨 말이냐면 <br>니 여자 휴대폰 뒤져봐 <br>그럼 난 먼저 갈게 친구 <br>I just wanna lay down <br>그 자리는 1인석 <br>특급 찍지 k-2 <br>이젠 필요해 ak-47 <br>내 입 안에 뱀 <br>내 경쟁자들 피리불어 <br>동시에 my finger <br>on the trigger ak-47 <br>뭘 원해 뭘 원해 <br>뭘 원해 뭘 원해 <br>나에게서 도대체 뭘 원해 <br>베풀 수 있는 건 오직 하나 <br>날 보면 복통이 번져 yeah <br>매일 매일 병신 넌 <br>나는 댄스 댄스 <br>난 지금 비보호 <br>니 얼굴 위로 똥을 싸 <br>네 애인과 속옷차림으로 facetime <br>캡쳐 후 저장해 엔드라이브 <br>해줄 리가 없잖아 위로 <br>단지 너를 겨누고 있어 <br>oh my AK-47 <br>말했잖아 지금 난 비보호 <br>엉덩이들 조심해 <br>oh my AK-47 <br>질질 짜 좌절하고 또 질질 짜 <br>거기 누구 아무나 <br>저기 고추 작은 새끼 <br>엉덩이 좀 걷어차 볼기짝 <br>나는 언제든 전부 쏴버릴 준비 <br>오줌 쌀 때마다 확인 해 <br>oh my AK-47 <br>I just wanna lay down <br>그 자리는 1인석 <br>특급 찍지 k-2 <br>이젠 필요해 ak-47 <br>내 입 안에 뱀 <br>내 경쟁자들 피리불어 <br>동시에 my finger <br>on the trigger ak-47 <br>탭탭 치고 인스타에 해쉬태그 <br>페이스타임 네이쳐 보이와 <br>에이케이 너의 삶에 <br>나의 미소를 대입해 <br>한가지로는 날 가두지를 못해 <br>깽깽거리지 새끼들 왜 <br>그랙다니 하나마루 <br>안경잽이 갱 <br>내 어깨의 무게 누구의 비해 <br>서도 그래 다시 그래 <br>존나 가볍지 공감을 얻기엔 <br>어깨에 가방 하나 메고 있지 않지 <br>정기를 정기를 받다가 보니 <br>내 존재는 공기와 같지 <br>너와 우리는 같이 <br>함께 할 수 없어 개 느린 속도 <br>속에서 통곡 하다가 <br>멋이 죄라면 난 무기징역 <br>넌 훈방조치 머퍼커 사칠 <br>에케 머퍼커 사칠 에헤이 <br>밖을 뒤져봐야 나야 갓디 <br>무지함이 아냐 거북해 넌 <br>모지람을 뭘로 채울래 먼 <br>산만 바라봐야 잡히지 않지 <br>나를 앞서 세워두고 앞길이 봬 <br>I just wanna lay down <br>그 자리는 1인석 <br>특급 찍지 k-2 <br>이젠 필요해 ak-47 <br>내 입 안에 뱀 <br>내 경쟁자들 피리불어 <br>동시에 my finger <br>on the trigger ak-47 <br>]]></content><category term="HANAMALOO" label="HANAMALOO"/><category term="안경잽이 (Feat. MACDADDY, KCDP, MOLDY)" label="안경잽이 (Feat. MACDADDY, KCDP, MOLDY)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HANAMALOO/얼마해_Feat_WONJAEWONJAE_KCDP_BLOODY_CODEINE/</id><title>HANAMALOO - 얼마해 (Feat. WONJAEWONJAE, KCDP, BLOODY CODEINE) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:05:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:05:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HANAMALOO/%EC%96%BC%EB%A7%88%ED%95%B4_Feat_WONJAEWONJAE_KCDP_BLOODY_CODEINE/" title="HANAMALOO - 얼마해 (Feat. WONJAEWONJAE, KCDP, BLOODY CODEINE) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 손목은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 손목은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 손목 다음에는 옷 다음에는 <br>브라 속 가슴은 꽤 <br>커지는 동공 콧대는 높고 <br>단맛에 돈 침이 돌게 해 <br>싼값의 노도 맥주 맛은 <br>low low <br>조선에선 못하게 하는 게 <br>너무 많어 <br>bonjour 프랑스서 태어났어 <br>간석1동 동사무소 가면 알어 <br>등본을 떼라 마 엄마는 <br>이혼해서 행복하게 살어 <br>못 가는 내 고향 프렌치 <br>바게트를 씹으면서 참아 <br>저기 쟤 학위도 허위 <br>난 그냥 눈감아주는 거지 <br>이런 랩이 Conscious 라고 <br>너희 머중이들 빨아대는 거지 <br>관심이 더 필요 하다구 <br>난 악플을 달아달라고 i love it <br>멜론에 내 랩을 레이업 해야 <br>회음부에 HNML 박아대야 <br>NO CD NO NO DOWNLOAD <br>SEED 를 불러줄게 <br>넌 당장 토렌트를 켜 <br>THUG LIFE IS WEB MEME <br>으로만 존재하는걸 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 손목은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 손목은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>너의 지갑에 <br>몇 장이나 있어 지폐 yeah <br>눈 앞에 들이밀어 flavor <br>oh yeah 핥아 baby <br>바짝 벌어놔 나에게 물어봐 <br>what 제시하지 금액 <br>씨발 너는 뻔해 <br>타고 브리또 내 입안에 위로 <br>꺼내먹어 나의 콩팥 <br>다 들어내고 let's dance 하 <br>다 신체포기 도장 찍고 <br>사채업자한테 돈을 빌려 <br>나는 미래가 보여 복채 내고 <br>내가 써준 부적하나 질러 <br>봄 여름 가을 겨울 <br>싹 다 쓸어 모아 <br>여기 자루 안에 담아 <br>호주머니에 짤랑짤랑 <br>동전은 너의 콧구멍에 전부 박아 <br>계좌번호를 외로웁게 해 <br>나의 망할 돈을 빨아가 <br>뭐 땜에 for sale <br>나는 하자 있어도 <br>귀찮아서 그냥 사곤 해 <br>니 수준 how much yah <br>니 친구 how much yah <br>니 음악 how much yah <br>니 현금 how much yah <br>forgive me forgive me <br>forgive me forgive me <br>i can’t feel your cash <br>내 지갑은 입을 errday <br>벌려 벌려 돈을 향해 <br>bitch gonna 기부 지를 위해 <br>너랑 같은 피를 섞진 않네 <br>대신 money 넣어 세탁기에 <br>쟤네 것까지 다 널어 ay <br>미안한데 돈만 join해 yah yah <br>니 수준 how much <br>니 손목 how much <br>니꺼는 how much <br>니 여친 날 믿지 <br>너도 해 어여 trust me <br>니 인생 얼마 해 <br>수지 맞춰 와줄래 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 손목은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>니 손목은 얼마 해 <br>니 삶은 얼마 해 <br>]]></content><category term="HANAMALOO" label="HANAMALOO"/><category term="얼마해 (Feat. WONJAEWONJAE, KCDP, BLOODY CODEINE)" label="얼마해 (Feat. WONJAEWONJAE, KCDP, BLOODY CODEINE)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HANAMALOO/오천만원_Feat_WONJAEWONJAE_QWER_MACDADDY/</id><title>HANAMALOO - 오천만원 (Feat. WONJAEWONJAE, QWER, MACDADDY) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:05:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:05:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HANAMALOO/%EC%98%A4%EC%B2%9C%EB%A7%8C%EC%9B%90_Feat_WONJAEWONJAE_QWER_MACDADDY/" title="HANAMALOO - 오천만원 (Feat. WONJAEWONJAE, QWER, MACDADDY) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떨어져 널 내려보는걸 난 즐기지 <br>내가 혀로 하는걸 너도 즐기지 <br>하 입술을 부비지 <br>니가 좋아하는걸 다 해주고 <br>파서 인터넷 속을 헤집어놔 <br>걔넨 더 이상 보여줄게 없을걸 <br>왜 거의 다 훔쳐왔어 <br>술에 취해 민망한 말 마구 <br>쏟아내기 아직 우린 이십 대니 <br>돈 낭비 시간을 마구 써버려 <br>아직 우린 이십 대니 <br>숙박비 내게 오천만 원이 <br>떨어지면 몇 년간 임대해 <br>너를 위해 우리 유흴 위해 해 <br>나는 다른 인종에 비해 미안해 <br>가만히 가마니가 되라 넌 <br>느껴지면 소리만 내주면 돼 <br>에어컨이 없으면 이방은 타버릴걸 <br>내 말을 곧이곧대로 들으면 돼 <br>움찔거리는 발가락은 귀여워 <br>다리에 힘을 빼고 벌렸으면 해 <br>이걸 보는 게 내 낙 어딜 가도 <br>이런 뷰는 쉽게 찾아 볼 수 없을 거야 <br>고민할 필요 없어 do that she <br>무례하게 놀자 우리 둘이 <br>고민할 필요 없어 do that she <br>무례하게 놀자 우리 둘이 <br>입을 대지 위 위아래로 <br>search high high high low <br>너의 하얀 다리 사이로 <br>손을 대면 문이 열리지 절로 <br>다리부터 팔로 <br>올라가지 이미 너의 많은 팔로워 <br>내가 널 바닥으로 떨어뜨려 <br>빵빵 그 위에 내 하나를 세워줘 <br>네 무게를 줄여줘 <br>내 위에 올라올 땐 <br>가벼운 게 좋아 더 <br>내가 말했잖아 <br>넌 뭘 입어도 예뻐 <br>내가 말했잖아 <br>넌 다 벗을 때 제일 예뻐 <br>고민할 필요 없어 do that she <br>입을 갖다 대도 돼 <br>네 기분이 좋을 대로 <br>맘껏 해도 돼 <br>돈을 필요 없어 페이백 <br>돌려주고 싶을 거야 베이베 <br>내가 결제한 here어때 <br>hello white skinny jean bitches <br>내 말 들어 그건 위험해 <br>날 위험하게 만들고 있어 <br>널 더럽히고 싶지 <br>my tungue just wanna lick it yo <br>술은 치워 내 앞에 널 들어올리고 <br>목마를 태워 난 뒤돌고 yo <br>니 눈빛에 fuck me sign <br>난 읽고 읽씹 해 말 대신 행동을 yo <br>넌 지금 막 태어난 것 같아 <br>하얀 피부가 참 야해 <br>불 끄고 led flexible <br>니 몸에 색칠할 때 난 감상해 <br>red green blue <br>그래 위험해 <br>너무 위험해 <br>그런 표정 위험해 <br>5천만원 5천만원 <br>5천만원 5천만원 <br>stackin’ 적립 <br>money to the ceilling 야놀자 <br>5천만원 5천만원 <br>누구랑 쓸지 한번 봐봐 <br>내일이면 내 취향이 <br>바뀔지도 모르지 <br>쟤 피부는 구릿빛 <br>]]></content><category term="HANAMALOO" label="HANAMALOO"/><category term="오천만원 (Feat. WONJAEWONJAE, QWER, MACDADDY)" label="오천만원 (Feat. WONJAEWONJAE, QWER, MACDADDY)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HANAMALOO/담배연기_Feat_QWER_WONJAEWONJAE_MACDADDY_KCDP/</id><title>HANAMALOO - 담배연기 (Feat. QWER, WONJAEWONJAE, MACDADDY, KCDP) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HANAMALOO/%EB%8B%B4%EB%B0%B0%EC%97%B0%EA%B8%B0_Feat_QWER_WONJAEWONJAE_MACDADDY_KCDP/" title="HANAMALOO - 담배연기 (Feat. QWER, WONJAEWONJAE, MACDADDY, KCDP) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 네 얼굴에 <br>뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 네 얼굴에 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 <br>뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 <br>뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>네 얼굴에 쏟아 붓지 <br>그림이 아주 보기 좋지 <br>눈물은 흘리지 마 얼굴에 다 <br>내가 대신 쏟아줄게 들이붓지 <br>우리 둘이 담밸 물리고 불을 붙이고 <br>알몸을 붙이고 다른 걸 물리곤 해 <br>서로 얼굴에 흰색을 묻히고 <br>샤워를 끝내고 담배 연기 <br>뱉어도 괜찮을까 네 얼굴에 <br>뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 네 얼굴에 <br>뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 네 얼굴에 <br>뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 네 얼굴에 <br>하이파이브 나의 다리 사이는 <br>im fine 넌 멀쩡하니 <br>담배 라이터는 나의 friend <br>타 들어가 나의 폐 속에 <br>산이 쌓임 온몸에 다 <br>성교 때문이니 참아야지 <br>아이들이 말하길 <br>나의 발기력은 전혀 무관하지 <br>담배연기 들이마시지 <br>매 순간 난 every time <br>동어 반복해도 모잘라 <br>엄마와 담배 친구 사이 <br>엄마의 보그 열정이 <br>느껴져 질 수 없지 내 말보로 <br>엄마의 의식은 쿨 담배 <br>때문이겠지 난 새겨둬 <br>재지 팩트 앨범을 들으며 <br>엄마와 드라이브 맞담해 <br>smoke that shit smoke that shit <br>빈지노는 흡연 권장해 <br>엄마들의 맘은 불안해 <br>CD태워야해 분서갱 <br>분서갱 분서갱 이젠 <br>묻어야 할 걸 인터넷 <br>all of my <br>all of my time 당연히 <br>내 구역은 늘 뿌옇지 <br>앞이 흐려 안보여 <br>창문 닫고 꺼 환풍기 <br>stackin’ time <br>넌 이게 싫으면 <br>우린 남이 되고 내겐 <br>너보다 훨씬 더 필요해 내 재떨이 <br>알다시피 i’m not your daddy <br>내 빅맥을 니 여자 입에 <br>물릴 수도 있겠지 <br>조심해 내 금단현상을 <br>곡엔 늘 19금 달아 <br>치과에서 스케일링하고 <br>나와서 난 커피와 담배를 <br>동시에 빨아 i’m good <br>뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 네 얼굴에 <br>뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 네 얼굴에 <br>내 담배 어디 있어 내 담배 <br>왜 밖에 나가서 피냐 왜 <br>인상을 찌푸려 손으로 <br>허공을 휘저어 <br>빌려간 라이터 내놔 <br>내 마이애미 라이타 <br>간접흡연 당하지 나한테 <br>청결한 폐 지녔니 딱 말해 <br>어차피 신경도 안 쓰고 <br>나는 만들지 도넛도넛 물레방아 <br>1mm 3mm 6mm catch me <br>난 몰래 담배를 쌔비지 <br>우리는 충분히 즐겁지 <br>we gonna party <br>졸리면 덮어 내 담배 연기를 <br>연기로 시 한편 써줄 테니 <br>열심히 옆에서 받아 적어 <br>안 빠질 꺼야 니 옷에 내 담배 냄새 <br>섬유 유연제 한 통을 다 써야 해 <br>그러면 거기다 재를 털게 <br>뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 네 얼굴에 <br>뱉어 하얀색 담배 연기 <br>뱉어 하얀색 땀 네 얼굴에 <br>]]></content><category term="HANAMALOO" label="HANAMALOO"/><category term="담배연기 (Feat. QWER, WONJAEWONJAE, MACDADDY, KCDP)" label="담배연기 (Feat. QWER, WONJAEWONJAE, MACDADDY, KCDP)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HANAMALOO/하나마루_Feat_KCDP_MACDADDY_WONJAEWONJAE/</id><title>HANAMALOO - 하나마루 (Feat. KCDP, MACDADDY, WONJAEWONJAE) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HANAMALOO/%ED%95%98%EB%82%98%EB%A7%88%EB%A3%A8_Feat_KCDP_MACDADDY_WONJAEWONJAE/" title="HANAMALOO - 하나마루 (Feat. KCDP, MACDADDY, WONJAEWONJAE) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[many many how many many how <br>many many how many many how <br>랜선 잡고 날아가 누가 따라와 <br>천국 간다 다 함께 how many how <br>many many how many many how <br>many many how many many how <br>랜선 잡고 날아가 누가 따라와 <br>천국 간다 다 함께 how many how <br>달려가지 나의 홈 <br>최고로 피곤하지 오 <br>혀가 꼬여 아마도 <br>키스는 내가 챔피언 <br>바라봐 눈꺼풀을 보며 걸어가 <br>잡아가 누구든 날 얼른 업어가 <br>매일 매일 나의 귀가 시간은 <br>늘 새카매 <br>베개가 낯설지 상태는 단명 하이패스 <br>날이 밝기 전에 <br>다가왔던 어둠 가기 전에 <br>발걸음을 옮겨 <br>바라보며 아이폰 <br>접속해 HNML 상태는 다 똑같아 <br>이쯤 되면 줄초상 각 <br>전부다 가기 전에 <br>터뜨려 샴페인 <br>망해도 샴페인 <br>엎드려 삽입 <br>뒷문에다 삽입 <br>many many how many many how <br>many many how many many how <br>랜선 잡고 날아가 누가 따라와 <br>천국 간다 다 함께 how many how <br>many many how many many how <br>many many how many many how <br>랜선 잡고 날아가 누가 따라와 <br>천국 간다 다 함께 how many how <br>pull off the key <br>just pull off the key <br>이번 달은 꽤나 바빠졌지 <br>지구촌 편집 마무리 <br>아마 이 곡을 듣기 전에 내겠지 <br>근데 이젠 곡을 쓰네 직접 <br>나는 누가 봐도 많아 욕심이 <br>하던걸 멈춰 다른 걸 시작 <br>대체 어디 있어 쉴 틈이 <br>always on the move <br>그래서 늘 켜져 있어 <br>뜨거워 내 맥북이 <br>다음달엔 이사 홍대로 가지 <br>다음달엔 여행가야 돼 <br>돈을 모아 빨리 <br>지갑 안에 parking <br>채워지면 떠날 거야 <br>아마 돌아오지 않을지도 모르지 <br>조또마떼 조또마떼 <br>와따시 일본어도 배워 <br>단어들을 외워 <br>머리 안에 채워두고 <br>다시 잠이 들면 서울에서 <br>깨어나고 다시 working <br>하루가 부족해 <br>하루가 부족해 나는 늘 <br>내 시간은 비싸 <br>내 시간은 비싸 audemars <br>many many how many many how <br>many many how many many how <br>랜선 잡고 날아가 누가 따라와 <br>천국 간다 다 함께 how many how <br>many many how many many how <br>many many how many many how <br>랜선 잡고 날아가 누가 따라와 <br>천국 간다 다 함께 how many how <br>엄마가 사준 FILA <br>내가 사줄 친칠라 코트 <br>지불했으니까 살고 있는 빌라도 <br>누군 나를 비난 너는 <br>도를 넘은 마마보이 <br>그래 나는 피망 흘려 <br>호불호의 심판도 <br>too many 호 too many 호 <br>난 호가 많지 too many 호 <br>조센인 만큼 달리지 또 알바야 <br>내가 노비일 건 <br>HNML이고 뭔 말인지 넌 모르지 또 <br>LOVE 모든 걸 사랑해 <br>그게 또 여자라면 <br>이럴 땐 엄마가 고마워 <br>미인을 엄마로 둬 <br>이런 말하면 또 흘겨 <br>너희들 사고는 후져 <br>너희들 랜선을 끊어 <br>올가밀 만들어 줄 걸 <br>LOVE X PEACE MINOR <br>아무 말이나 함 예 예 <br>many many how many many how <br>many many how many many how <br>랜선 잡고 날아가 누가 따라와 <br>천국 간다 다 함께 how many how <br>many many how many many how <br>many many how many many how <br>랜선 잡고 날아가 누가 따라와 <br>천국 간다 다 함께 how many how <br>]]></content><category term="HANAMALOO" label="HANAMALOO"/><category term="하나마루 (Feat. KCDP, MACDADDY, WONJAEWONJAE)" label="하나마루 (Feat. KCDP, MACDADDY, WONJAEWONJAE)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Edith_Piaf/Lhymne_A_Lamour_사랑의_찬가/</id><title>Edith Piaf - L`hymne A L`amour (사랑의 찬가) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Edith_Piaf/Lhymne_A_Lamour_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%98_%EC%B0%AC%EA%B0%80/" title="Edith Piaf - L`hymne A L`amour (사랑의 찬가) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Le ciel bleu sur nous peut s'effondrer <br>Et la terre peut bien s'ecrouler <br>Peu m'importe si tu m'aimes <br>Je me fous du monde entier <br>Tant qu'l'amour inond'ra mes matins <br>Tant que mon corps fremira sous tes mains <br>Peu m'importe les problemes <br>Mon amour puisque tu m'aimes <br>J'irais jusqu'au bout du monde <br>Je me ferais teindre en blonde <br>Si tu me le demandais <br>J'irais decrocher la lune <br>J'irais voler la fortune <br>Si tu me le demandais <br><br>Je renierais ma patrie <br>Je renierais mes amis <br>Si tu me le demandais <br>On peut bien rire de moi <br>Je ferais n'importe quoi <br>Si tu me le demandais <br><br>Si un jour la vie t'arrache a moi <br>Si tu meurs que tu sois loin de moi <br>Peu m'importe si tu m'aimes <br>Car moi je mourrais aussi <br>Nous aurons pour nous l'eternite <br>Dans le bleu de toute l'immensite <br>Dans le ciel plus de problemes <br>Mon amour crois tu qu'on s'aime <br>Dieu reunit ceux qui s'aiment]]></content><category term="Edith Piaf" label="Edith Piaf"/><category term="L`hymne A L`amour (사랑의 찬가)" label="L`hymne A L`amour (사랑의 찬가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Delfonics/La_La_Means_I_Love_You/</id><title>The Delfonics - La La Means I Love You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Delfonics/La_La_Means_I_Love_You/" title="The Delfonics - La La Means I Love You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Many guys have come to you <br>With a line that wasn't true <br>And you passed them by <br>Now you're in the center ring <br>And their lines don't mean a thing <br>Why don't you let me try <br>Now I don't wear a diamond ring <br>I don't even know a song to sing <br>All I know is <br><br>La la la la la la la la la means <br>I love you <br>Oh, baby please now <br>La la la la la la la la la means <br>I love you <br><br>If I ever saw a girl <br>That I needed in this world <br>You are the one for me, one for me <br>Let me hold me in my arms <br>Girl, and thrill you with my charms <br>I'm sure you will see, you will see <br>The things I am sayin' are true <br>And the way I explain them to you <br>Listen to me <br><br>La la la la la la la la la means <br>I love you <br>Oh, baby baby <br>La la la la la la la la la means <br>I love you <br><br>The things I am sayin' are true <br>And the way I explain them to you, yes to you <br>Listen to me <br><br>La la la la la la la la la means <br>I love you <br>Oh, you'll have to understand now <br>La la la la la la la la la means <br>I love you <br>Come on and take my hand <br>La la la la la la la la la means]]></content><category term="The Delfonics" label="The Delfonics"/><category term="La La Means I Love You" label="La La Means I Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Patti_Page/Changing_Partners/</id><title>Patti Page - Changing Partners - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Patti_Page/Changing_Partners/" title="Patti Page - Changing Partners - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We were waltzin' together to a dreamy melody <br>When they called out Change partners <br>And you waltzed away from me <br>Now my arms feel so empty as I gaze around the floor <br>And I'll keep on changing partners <br>Till I hold you once more <br><br>Though we danced for one moment and too soon we had to part <br>In that wonderful moment somethin' happened to my heart <br>So I'll keep changing partners till you're in my arms and then <br>Oh, my darlin' I will never change partners again <br><br>Though we danced for one moment and too soon we had to part <br>In that wonderful moment somethin' happened to my heart <br>So I'll keep changing partners till you're in my arms and then <br>Oh, my darlin' I will never change partners again]]></content><category term="Patti Page" label="Patti Page"/><category term="Changing Partners" label="Changing Partners"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Cooke/You_Send_Me/</id><title>Sam Cooke - You Send Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Cooke/You_Send_Me/" title="Sam Cooke - You Send Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Darling you send me <br>I know you send me <br>Darling you send me <br>Honest you do, honest you do <br>Honest you do, whoa <br><br>You thrill me <br>I know you, you, you thrill me <br>Darling you, you, you, you thrill me <br>Honest you do <br><br>At first I thought it was infatuation <br>But wooh, it's lasted so long <br>Now I find myself wanting <br>To marry you and take you home, woah <br><br>You, you, you, you send me <br>I know you send me <br>I know you send me <br>Honest you do <br><br>Whoa, whenever I'm with you <br>I know, I know, I know when I'm near you <br>Mmm hmm, mmm hmm, honest you do, honest you do <br>Whoa, I know <br><br>I know, I know, I know, when you hold me <br>Whoa, whenever you kiss me <br>Mmm hmm, mmm hmm, honest you do <br><br>At first I thought it was infatuation <br>But wooh, it's lasted so long <br>Now I find myself wanting <br>To marry you and take you home <br><br>I know, I know, I know, you send me <br>I know you send me <br>Whoa, you you you you send me <br>Honest you do]]></content><category term="Sam Cooke" label="Sam Cooke"/><category term="You Send Me" label="You Send Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pat_Boone/April_Love/</id><title>Pat Boone - April Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pat_Boone/April_Love/" title="Pat Boone - April Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[April love is for the very young <br>Every stars a wishing star that shines for you <br>April love is all the seven wonders <br>One little kiss can tell you this is true <br><br>Sometimes an april day will suddenly bring showers <br>Rain to grow the flowers for her first bouquet <br>But april love can slip right through your fingers <br>So if she's the one don't let her run away <br><br>Sometimes an april day will suddenly bring showers <br>Rain to grow the flowers for her first bouquet <br>But april love can slip right through your fingers <br>So if she's the one don't let her run away]]></content><category term="Pat Boone" label="Pat Boone"/><category term="April Love" label="April Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Phillips/Sea_Of_Love/</id><title>Phil Phillips - Sea Of Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Phillips/Sea_Of_Love/" title="Phil Phillips - Sea Of Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come with me, my love <br>To the sea, the sea of love <br>I want to tell you how much I love you <br><br>Do you remember when we met <br>That's the day I knew you were my pet <br>I want to tell you how much I love you <br><br>Come with me to the sea of love <br><br>Do you remember when we met <br>That's the day I knew you were my pet <br>I want to tell you how much I love you <br><br>Come with me to the sea of love <br><br>Do you remember when we met <br>That's the day I knew you were my pet <br>I want to tell you how much I love you <br><br>I want to tell you how much I love you <br>I want to tell you how much I love you]]></content><category term="Phil Phillips" label="Phil Phillips"/><category term="Sea Of Love" label="Sea Of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wayne_Fontana/A_Groovy_Kind_Of_Love/</id><title>Wayne Fontana - A Groovy Kind Of Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wayne_Fontana/A_Groovy_Kind_Of_Love/" title="Wayne Fontana - A Groovy Kind Of Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I'm feelin' blue, all I have to do is take a look at you <br>Then I'm not so blue <br>When you're close to me I can feel you heart beat <br>I can hear you breathing in my ear <br>Wouldn't you agree, baby, you and me got a groovy kind of love <br>We got a groovy kind of love <br>Any time you want to you can turn me on to anything you want to <br>Any time at all <br>When I taste your lips <br>Oh, I start to shiver can't control the quivering inside <br>Wouldn't you agree, baby, you and me got a groovy kind of love <br>We got a groovy kind of love <br>When I'm in your arms nothing seems to matter <br>If the world would shatter I don't care <br>Wouldn't you agree, baby, you and me got a groovy kind of love <br>We got a groovy kind of love <br>We got a groovy kind of love <br>We got a groovy kind of love]]></content><category term="Wayne Fontana" label="Wayne Fontana"/><category term="A Groovy Kind Of Love" label="A Groovy Kind Of Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Drifters/Save_The_Last_Dance_For_Me/</id><title>The Drifters - Save The Last Dance For Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Drifters/Save_The_Last_Dance_For_Me/" title="The Drifters - Save The Last Dance For Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You can dance <br>Every dance with the guy <br>Who gave you the eye <br>Let him hold you tight <br><br>You can smile <br>Every smile for the man <br>Who held your hand <br>'Neath the pale moonlight <br><br>But don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br><br>Oh I know <br>That the music is fine <br>Like sparkling wine <br>Go and have your fun <br><br>Laugh and sing <br>But while we're apart <br>Don't give your heart <br>To anyone <br><br>But don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br><br>Baby don't you know I love you so <br>Can't you feel it when we touch <br>I will never, never let you go <br>I love you oh so much <br><br>You can dance <br>Go and carry on <br>Till the night is gone <br>And it's time to go <br><br>If he asks <br>If you're all alone <br>Can he take you home <br>You must tell him no <br><br>'Cause don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me <br><br>'Cause don't forget who's taking you home <br>And in whose arms you're gonna be <br>So darlin' <br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br><br>Save the last dance for me, mmm <br>Save the last dance for me]]></content><category term="The Drifters" label="The Drifters"/><category term="Save The Last Dance For Me" label="Save The Last Dance For Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Shirelles/Will_You_Still_Love_Me_Tomorrow/</id><title>The Shirelles - Will You Still Love Me Tomorrow - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Shirelles/Will_You_Still_Love_Me_Tomorrow/" title="The Shirelles - Will You Still Love Me Tomorrow - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight you're mine, completely <br>You give your love so sweetly <br>Tonight the light of love is in your eyes <br>But will you love me tomorrow <br><br>Is this a lasting treasure <br>Or just a moment's pleasure <br>Can I believe the magic in your sighs <br>Will you still love me tomorrow <br><br>Tonight with words unspoken <br>You say that I'm the only one <br>But will my heart be broken <br>When the night meets the morning sun <br><br>I'd like to know that your love <br>Is a love I can be sure of <br>So tell me now and I won't ask again <br>Will you still love me tomorrow <br><br>So tell me now and I won't ask again <br>Will you still love me tomorrow <br>Will you still love me tomorrow <br>Will you still love me tomorrow]]></content><category term="The Shirelles" label="The Shirelles"/><category term="Will You Still Love Me Tomorrow" label="Will You Still Love Me Tomorrow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Ronettes/Be_My_Baby/</id><title>The Ronettes - Be My Baby - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Ronettes/Be_My_Baby/" title="The Ronettes - Be My Baby - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The night we met I knew I needed you so <br>And if I had the chance I'd never let you go <br>So won't you say you love me <br>I'll make you so proud of me <br>We'll make 'em turn their heads every place we go <br><br>So won't you, please <br>Be my, be my baby <br>Be my little baby <br>My one and only baby <br>Say you'll be my darlin' <br>Be my, be my baby <br>Be my baby now <br>Wha oh oh oh <br><br>I'll make you happy, baby, just wait and see <br>For every kiss you give me, I'll give you three <br>Oh, since the day I saw you <br>I have been waiting for you <br>You know I will adore you 'til eternity <br><br>So won't you, please <br>Be my, be my baby <br>Be my little baby <br>My one and only baby <br>Say you'll be my darlin' <br>Be my, be my baby <br>Be my baby now <br>Wha oh oh oh <br><br>So comm'on and be <br>Be my, be my baby <br>Be my little baby <br>My one and only baby <br>Say you'll be my darlin' <br>Be my, be my baby <br>Be my baby now <br>Wha oh oh oh <br><br>Be my, be my baby <br>Be my little baby <br>My one and only baby <br>Oh oh oooooh <br>Be my, be my baby <br>Ooooooooooh <br>Wha oh oh oh oh <br><br>Be my, be my baby <br>Oh oh oooooh <br>My one and only baby <br>Ooooooooooh <br>Be my, be my baby <br>Be my baby now <br>Wha oh oh oh]]></content><category term="The Ronettes" label="The Ronettes"/><category term="Be My Baby" label="Be My Baby"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mickey_Gilley/Susie_Q/</id><title>Mickey Gilley - Susie Q - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mickey_Gilley/Susie_Q/" title="Mickey Gilley - Susie Q - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Suzie Q <br>Oh Suzie Q <br>Oh Suzie Q Baby I love you <br>Suzie Q <br><br>I like the way you walk <br>I like the way you talk <br>I like the way you walk I like the way you talk <br>Suzie Q <br><br>Oh say that you'll be true <br>Oh say that you'll be true <br>Oh say that you'll be true and never leave me blue <br>Suzie Q <br><br>Oh say that you'll be mine <br>Oh say that you'll be mine <br>Oh say that you'll be mine Baby all the time <br>Suzie Q <br><br>Oh, Suzie Q <br>Oh, Suzie Q <br>Oh, Suzie Q, Baby, I love you <br>Suzie Q <br><br>I like the way you walk <br>I like the way you talk <br>I like the way you walk, I like the way you talk <br>Suzie Q <br><br>Oh, Suzie Q <br>Oh, Suzie Q <br>Oh, Suzie Q, Baby, I love you <br>Suzie Q]]></content><category term="Mickey Gilley" label="Mickey Gilley"/><category term="Susie Q" label="Susie Q"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Paul_Anka/Diana/</id><title>Paul Anka - Diana - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Paul_Anka/Diana/" title="Paul Anka - Diana - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm so young and you're so old <br>This, my darling, I've been told <br>I don't care just what they say <br>Cause forever I will pray <br>You and I will be as free <br>As the birds up in the trees <br>Oh, please stay by me, Diana <br><br>Thrills I get when you hold me close <br>Oh, my darling, you're the most <br>I love you but do you love me <br>Oh, Diana, can't you see <br>I love you with all my heart <br>And I hope we will never part <br>Oh, please stay with me, Diana <br><br>Oh, my darlin', oh, my lover <br>Tell me that there is no other <br>I love you with my heart <br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh <br>Only you can take my heart <br>Only you can tear it apart <br>When you hold me in your loving arms <br>I can feel you giving all your charms <br>Hold me, darling, ho ho hold me tight <br>Squeeze me baby with a all your might <br>Oh, please stay with me, Diana <br>Oh, please, Diana <br>Oh, please, Diana <br>Oh, please, Diana]]></content><category term="Paul Anka" label="Paul Anka"/><category term="Diana" label="Diana"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bay_City_Rollers/I_Only_Wanna_Be_With_You/</id><title>Bay City Rollers - I Only Wanna Be With You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bay_City_Rollers/I_Only_Wanna_Be_With_You/" title="Bay City Rollers - I Only Wanna Be With You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know what it is that makes me love you so <br>I only know I never want to let you go <br>Cause you started something <br>Oh can't you see <br>Ever since we met you've had a hold on me <br>It happens to be true <br>I only want to be with you <br><br>It doesn't matter where you go or what you do <br>I want to spend each moment of the day with you <br>Look what has happened with just one kiss <br>I never knew that I could be in love like this <br>It's crazy but it's true <br>I only want to be with you <br><br>You stopped and smiled at me <br>And asked me if I cared to dance <br>I fell into open arms <br>And I didn't stand a chance <br><br>Now listen honey <br>I just want to be beside you everywhere <br>As long as we're together, honey I don't care <br>Cause you started something <br>Oh can't you see <br>Ever since we met you've had a hold on me <br>No matter what you do <br>I only want to be with you <br><br>You stopped and smiled at me <br>And asked me if I cared to dance <br>I fell into open arms <br>And I didn't stand a chance <br><br>Now hear it honey <br>I just want to be beside you everywhere <br>As long as we're together honey I don't care <br>Cause you started something <br>Oh can't you see <br><br>Ever since we met you've had a hold on me <br>No matter what you do <br>I only want to be with you <br>Oh no matter, no matter what you do <br>I only want to be with you]]></content><category term="Bay City Rollers" label="Bay City Rollers"/><category term="I Only Wanna Be With You" label="I Only Wanna Be With You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daniel_Boone/Beautiful_Sunday/</id><title>Daniel Boone - Beautiful Sunday - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daniel_Boone/Beautiful_Sunday/" title="Daniel Boone - Beautiful Sunday - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sunday morning, up with the lark <br>I think I'll take a walk in the park <br>Hey hey hey, it's a beautiful day <br>I've got someone waiting for me <br>And when I see her I know that she'll say <br>Hey hey hey, what a beautiful day <br><br>Hi hi hi, beautiful Sunday <br>This is my my my beautiful day <br>When you said said said said that you loved me <br>Oh my my my its a beautiful day <br><br>Birds are singing, you by my side <br>Lets take a car and go for a ride <br>Hey hey hey, it's a beautiful day <br>We'll drive on and follow the sun <br>Making Sunday go on and on <br>Hey hey hey it's a beautiful day <br>Hi hi hi, beautiful Sunday <br>This is my my my beautiful day <br>When you said said said said that you loved me <br>Oh my my my its a beautiful day <br><br>Hi hi hi, beautiful Sunday <br>This is my my my beautiful day <br>When you said said said said that you loved me <br>Oh my my my its a beautiful day <br><br>Hi hi hi, beautiful Sunday]]></content><category term="Daniel Boone" label="Daniel Boone"/><category term="Beautiful Sunday" label="Beautiful Sunday"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Johnny_Tillotson/Poetry_In_Motion/</id><title>Johnny Tillotson - Poetry In Motion - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Johnny_Tillotson/Poetry_In_Motion/" title="Johnny Tillotson - Poetry In Motion - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I see my baby <br>What do I see <br>Poetry <br>Poetry in motion <br><br>Poetry in motion, walkin' by my side <br>Her lovely locomotion keeps my eyes open wide <br>Poetry in motion, see her gentle sway <br>A wave out on the ocean could never move that way <br><br>I love every movement <br>There's nothing I would change <br>She doesn't need improvement <br>She's much too nice to rearrange <br><br>Poetry in motion, dancing close to me <br>A flower of devotion a swaying gracefully <br><br>Oh, a whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa <br>A whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa <br>A whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa <br>Whoa <br><br>Poetry in motion, see her gentle sway <br>A wave out on the ocean could never move that way <br><br>I love every movement <br>There's nothing I would change <br>She doesn't need improvement <br>She's much too nice to rearrange <br><br>Poetry in motion, all that I adore <br>No number nine love potion could make me love her more <br><br>Oh, a whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa <br>A whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa <br>A whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa <br>A whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa]]></content><category term="Johnny Tillotson" label="Johnny Tillotson"/><category term="Poetry In Motion" label="Poetry In Motion"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/My_Girl/</id><title>The Temptations - My Girl - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Temptations/My_Girl/" title="The Temptations - My Girl - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've got sunshine on a cloudy day <br>When it's cold outside I've got the month of May <br>I guess you'd say <br>What can make me feel this way <br><br>My girl, my girl, my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl, my girl <br><br>I've got so much honey, the bees envy me <br>I've got a sweeter song, than the birds in the trees <br>Well, I guess you'd say <br>What can make me feel this way <br><br>My girl, my girl, my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl, my girl <br><br>Hey, hey, hey <br>Hey, hey, hey <br>Ooh, yeah <br><br>I don't need no money, fortune, or fame <br>I've got all the riches baby, one man can claim <br>Well, I guess you'd say <br>What can make me feel this way <br><br>My girl, my girl, my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl, my girl <br><br>I've got sunshine on a cloudy day <br>With my girl <br>I've even got the month of May <br>With my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout, talkin' 'bout, talkin' 'bout my girl]]></content><category term="The Temptations" label="The Temptations"/><category term="My Girl" label="My Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Andy_Williams/Love_Is_A_Many_Splendored_Thing/</id><title>Andy Williams - Love Is A Many Splendored Thing - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Andy_Williams/Love_Is_A_Many_Splendored_Thing/" title="Andy Williams - Love Is A Many Splendored Thing - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love is a many splendored thing <br>It's the April rose that only grows in the early Spring <br>Love is nature's way of giving a reason to be living <br>The golden crown that makes a man a king <br>Once on a high and windy hill, In the morning mist <br>Two lovers kissed and the world stood still <br>Then your fingers touched my silent heart and taught it how to sing <br>Yes, true love's a many splendored thing <br>Love is a many splendored thing <br>It's the April rose that only grows in the early Spring <br>Love is nature's way of giving a reason to be living <br>The golden crown that makes a man a king <br>Once on a high and windy hill, In the morning mist <br>Two lovers kissed and the world stood still <br>Then your fingers touched my silent heart and taught it how to sing <br>Yes, true love's a many splendored thing]]></content><category term="Andy Williams" label="Andy Williams"/><category term="Love Is A Many Splendored Thing" label="Love Is A Many Splendored Thing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Elvis_Presley/Love_Me_Tender/</id><title>Elvis Presley - Love Me Tender - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Elvis_Presley/Love_Me_Tender/" title="Elvis Presley - Love Me Tender - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love me tender <br>love me sweet <br>never let me go <br>You have made my life complete <br>and I love you so <br><br>Love me tender <br>love me true <br>all my dreams fulfilled <br>For my darlin' I love you <br>and I always will <br><br>Love me tender <br>love me long <br>take me to your heart <br>For it's there that I belong <br>and we'll never part <br><br>Love me tender <br>love me dear <br>tell me you are mine <br>I'll be yours through all the years <br>till the end of time <br><br>When at last my dreams come true <br>Darling this I know <br>Happiness will follow you <br>Everywhere you go]]></content><category term="Elvis Presley" label="Elvis Presley"/><category term="Love Me Tender" label="Love Me Tender"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brian_Hyland/Sealed_With_Kiss/</id><title>Brian Hyland - Sealed With Kiss - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brian_Hyland/Sealed_With_Kiss/" title="Brian Hyland - Sealed With Kiss - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Though we gotta say goodbye for the summer <br>Darling I promise you this <br>I'll send you all my love every day in a letter <br>Sealed with a kiss <br><br>Yes it's gonna be a cold lonely summer <br>But I'll fill the emptiness <br>I'll send you all my dreams every day in a letter <br>Sealed with a kiss <br><br>I'll see you in the sunlight <br>I'll hear your voice everywhere <br>I'll run to tenderly hold you <br>But darling you won't be there <br><br>I don't want to say goodbye for the summer <br>Knowing the love we'll miss <br>Oh let us make a pledge to meet in September <br>And seal it with a kiss <br><br>Yes it's gonna be a cold lonely summer <br>But I'll fill the emptiness <br>I'll send you all my love every day in a letter <br>Sealed with a kiss <br>Sealed with a kiss <br>Sealed with a kiss]]></content><category term="Brian Hyland" label="Brian Hyland"/><category term="Sealed With Kiss" label="Sealed With Kiss"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_E_King/Stand_By_Me/</id><title>Ben E. King - Stand By Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ben_E_King/Stand_By_Me/" title="Ben E. King - Stand By Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the night has come <br>And the land is dark <br>And the moon is the only light we'll see <br>No I won't be afraid <br>Oh, I won't be afraid <br>Just as long as you stand, stand by me <br><br>So darling, darling <br>Stand by me, oh stand by me <br>Oh stand, stand by me <br>Stand by me <br><br>If the sky that we look upon <br>Should tumble and fall <br>Or the mountain should crumble to the sea <br>I won't cry, I won't cry <br>No, I won't shed a tear <br>Just as long as you stand, stand by me <br><br>And darling, darling <br>Stand by me, oh stand by me <br>Oh stand now, stand by me <br>Stand by me <br><br>So darling, darling <br>Stand by me, oh stand by me <br>Oh stand now, stand by me, stand by me <br>Whenever you're in trouble won't you stand by me <br>Oh stand by me, won't you stand now, oh, stand <br>Stand by me]]></content><category term="Ben E. King" label="Ben E. King"/><category term="Stand By Me" label="Stand By Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Sedaka/You_Mean_Everything_To_Me/</id><title>Neil Sedaka - You Mean Everything To Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neil_Sedaka/You_Mean_Everything_To_Me/" title="Neil Sedaka - You Mean Everything To Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You are the answer to my lonely prayer <br>You are an angel from above <br>I was so lonely till you came to me <br>With the wonder of your love <br>I don't know how I ever lived before <br>You are my life, my destiny <br>Oh my darling, I love you so <br>You mean everything to me <br>If you should ever, ever go away <br>There would be lonely tears to cry <br>The sun above would be never shine again <br>There would be teardrops in the sky <br>So hold me close and never let me go <br>And say our love will always be <br>Oh, my darling, I love you so <br>You mean everything to me <br>So hold me close and never let me go <br>And say our love will always be <br>Oh, my darling, I love you so <br>You mean everything to me]]></content><category term="Neil Sedaka" label="Neil Sedaka"/><category term="You Mean Everything To Me" label="You Mean Everything To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Percy_Sledge/When_A_Man_Loves_A_Woman/</id><title>Percy Sledge - When A Man Loves A Woman - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Percy_Sledge/When_A_Man_Loves_A_Woman/" title="Percy Sledge - When A Man Loves A Woman - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When a man loves a woman <br>Can't keep his mind on nothin' else <br>He'd change the world for the good thing he's found <br>If she is bad, he can't see it <br>She can do no wrong <br>Turn his back on his best friend if he put her down <br><br>When a man loves a woman <br>He'll spend his very last dime <br>Tryin' to hold on to what he needs <br>He'd give up all his comforts <br>And sleep out in the rain <br>If she said that's the way <br>It ought to be <br><br>Well, this man loves you, woman <br>I gave you everything I had <br>Tryin' to hold on to your heartless love <br>Baby, please don't treat me bad <br><br>When a man loves a woman <br>Down deep in his soul <br>She can bring him such misery <br>If she is playin' him for a fool <br>He's the last one to know <br>Lovin' eyes can never see <br><br>When a man loves a woman <br>He can do her no wrong <br>He can never want <br>Some other girl <br><br>Yes when a man loves a woman <br>I know exactly how he feels <br>Cause baby, baby, you're my world <br><br>When a man loves a woman]]></content><category term="Percy Sledge" label="Percy Sledge"/><category term="When A Man Loves A Woman" label="When A Man Loves A Woman"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Zombies/Time_Of_The_Season/</id><title>The Zombies - Time Of The Season - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:06:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:06:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Zombies/Time_Of_The_Season/" title="The Zombies - Time Of The Season - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's the Time Of the Season <br>When love runs high <br>In this time, give it to me easy <br>And let me try with pleasured hands <br><br>To take you in the sun to promised lands <br>To show you every one It's the time of <br>The season for loving <br><br>What's your name Who's your daddy <br>Is he Rich Is he rich like me <br>Has he taken any time <br>To show To show you what you need to live <br><br>Tell it to me slowly tell you what <br>I really want to know It's the time of <br>The season for loving <br><br>What's your name Who's your daddy <br>Is he Rich, is he rich like me <br>Has he taken any time <br>To show To show you what you need to live <br><br>Tell it to me slowly tell you what <br>I really want to know It's the time of <br>The season for loving]]></content><category term="The Zombies" label="The Zombies"/><category term="Time Of The Season" label="Time Of The Season"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Badfinger/Without_You/</id><title>Badfinger - Without You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Badfinger/Without_You/" title="Badfinger - Without You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well, I can't forget this evening <br>And your face when you were leaving <br>But I guess that's just the way the story goes <br>You always smile, but in your eyes your sorrow shows <br>Yes it shows <br><br>Well I can't forget tomorrow <br>When I think of all my sorrow <br>I had you there, but then I let you go <br>And now it's only fair that I should let you know <br>What you should know <br><br>I can't live <br>If living is without you <br>I can't live <br>I can't give anymore <br>I can't live <br>If living is without you <br>I can't live <br>I can't give anymore <br><br>Well, I can't forget this evening <br>And your face when you were leaving <br>But I guess that's just the way the story goes <br>You always smile, but in your eyes your sorrow shows <br>Yes it shows <br><br>I can't live <br>If living is without you <br>I can't live <br>I can't give anymore <br>I can't live <br>If living is without you <br>I can't live <br>I can't give anymore <br><br>I can't live <br>If living is without you <br>I can't live <br>I can't give anymore <br>I can't live <br>If living is without you <br>I can't live <br>I can't give anymore]]></content><category term="Badfinger" label="Badfinger"/><category term="Without You" label="Without You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jerry_Butler/Let_It_Be_Me/</id><title>Jerry Butler - Let It Be Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jerry_Butler/Let_It_Be_Me/" title="Jerry Butler - Let It Be Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I bless the day I found you <br>I want to stay around you <br>And so I beg you, let it be me <br><br>Don't take this heaven from one <br>If you must cling to someone <br>Now and forever, let it be me <br><br>Each time we meet love <br>I find complete love <br>Without your sweet love what would life be <br><br>So never leave me lonely <br>Tell me you love me only <br>And that you'll always let it be me <br><br>Each time we meet love <br>I find complete love <br>Without your sweet love what would life be <br><br>So never leave me lonely <br>Tell me you love me only <br>And that you'll always, let, it, be, me]]></content><category term="Jerry Butler" label="Jerry Butler"/><category term="Let It Be Me" label="Let It Be Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Paul_Anka/Put_Your_Head_On_My_Shoulder/</id><title>Paul Anka - Put Your Head On My Shoulder - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Paul_Anka/Put_Your_Head_On_My_Shoulder/" title="Paul Anka - Put Your Head On My Shoulder - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Put your head on my shoulder <br>Hold me in your arms, baby <br>Squeeze me oh so tight <br>Show me that you love me too <br><br>Put your lips next to mine, dear <br>Won't you kiss me once, baby <br>Just a kiss goodnight, maybe <br>You and I will fall in love you and I will fall in love <br><br>People say that love's a game <br>A game you just can't win <br>If there's a way <br>I'll find it somebody <br>And then this fool will rush in <br><br>Put your head on my shoulder <br>Whisper in my ear, baby <br>Words I want to hear <br>Tell me, tell me that you love me too tell me that you love me too <br><br>Put your head on my shoulder <br>Whisper in my ear, baby <br>Words I want to hear, baby <br>Put your head on my shoulder]]></content><category term="Paul Anka" label="Paul Anka"/><category term="Put Your Head On My Shoulder" label="Put Your Head On My Shoulder"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Troggs/Love_Is_All_Around/</id><title>The Troggs - Love Is All Around - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Troggs/Love_Is_All_Around/" title="The Troggs - Love Is All Around - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel it in my fingers, I feel it in my toes <br>Love is all around me and so the feeling grows <br>It's written on the wind, it's everywhere I go <br>So if you really love me, come on and let it show <br><br>You know I love you I always will <br>My mind's made up by the way that I feel <br>There's no beginning, there'll be no end <br>Cause on my love you can depend <br><br>I see your face before me, as I lay on my bed <br>I kinda get to thinking of all the things we said <br>You gave a promise to me, and I gave mine to you <br>I need someone beside me in everything I do <br><br>You know I love you I always will <br>My mind's made up by the way that I feel <br>There's no beginning, there'll be no end <br>Cause on my love you can depend <br><br>It's written on the wind, it's everywhere I go <br>So if you really love me, come on and let it show <br>Come on and let it show]]></content><category term="The Troggs" label="The Troggs"/><category term="Love Is All Around" label="Love Is All Around"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gladys_Knight__The_Pips/Every_Beat_Of_My_Heart/</id><title>Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips - Every Beat Of My Heart - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gladys_Knight__The_Pips/Every_Beat_Of_My_Heart/" title="Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips - Every Beat Of My Heart - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Through these misty eyes I see lonely skies <br>Lonely road to Babylon <br>Where's my family <br>And my country <br>Heaven knows where I belong <br><br>Pack my bags tonight <br>Here's one Jacobite <br>Who must leave or surely die <br>Put me on a train <br>In the pouring rain say farewell <br>But don't say goodbye <br><br>Seagull carry me, over land and sea <br>To my own folk, that's where I want to be <br>Every beat of my heart <br>Tears me further apart <br>I'm lost and alone in the dark <br>I'm going home <br><br>One more glass of wine <br>Just for auld lang syne <br>And the girl I left behind <br>How I miss her now In my darkest hour <br><br>And the way our arms entwine <br><br>Seagull carry me, over land and sea <br>To my own folk, that's where I want to be <br>Every beat of my heart <br>Tears me further apart <br>I'm lost and alone in the dark <br>I'm going home <br><br>And we'll drink a toast <br>To the blood red rose <br>Cheer a while the <br>Emerald Isle <br>And to the northern lights <br>And the swirling pipes <br>How they make a grown man cry <br><br>Seagull carry me, over land and sea <br>To my own folk, that's where I want to be <br>Every beat of my heart <br>Tears me further apart <br>I'm lost and alone in the dark <br>I'm going home]]></content><category term="Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips" label="Gladys Knight &amp; The Pips"/><category term="Every Beat Of My Heart" label="Every Beat Of My Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Three_Degrees/When_Will_I_See_You_Again/</id><title>The Three Degrees - When Will I See You Again - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Three_Degrees/When_Will_I_See_You_Again/" title="The Three Degrees - When Will I See You Again - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hoo, hah <br>Hah, hoo <br>Precious moments <br><br>When will I see you again <br>When will we share precious moments <br>Will I have to wait forever <br>Will I have to suffer suffer <br>And cry the whole night through <br><br>When will I see you again <br>When will our hearts beat together <br>Are we in love or just friends <br>Is this my beginning or is this the end <br>Is this the end <br><br>When will I see you again <br>When will I see you again <br>When will I see you again <br><br>Hah, hoo <br>Precious moments <br><br>Are we in love or just friends <br>Is this my beginning or is this the end <br>Is this the end <br><br>When will I see you again <br>When will I see you again <br>Sweet sweet love of mine <br>When will I see you again <br>Come, come <br>When will I see you again <br>Tell me, yeah <br>When will I see you again <br>My sweet lover, yeah <br>When will I see you again <br>Ooh yeah <br>When will I see you again <br>Come on, come on <br>When will I see you again <br>When will I see you again <br>Ooh yeah <br>When will I see you again]]></content><category term="The Three Degrees" label="The Three Degrees"/><category term="When Will I See You Again" label="When Will I See You Again"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Drifters/Under_The_Boardwalk/</id><title>The Drifters - Under The Boardwalk - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Drifters/Under_The_Boardwalk/" title="The Drifters - Under The Boardwalk - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, when the sun beats down and burns the tar up on the roof <br>And your shoes get so hot, you wish your tired feet were fireproof <br>Under the boardwalk, down by the sea <br>On a blanket with my baby is where I'll be <br><br>Under the boardwalk Out of the sun <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be havin' some fun <br>Under the boardwalk People walking above <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be making love <br>Under the boardwalk, boardwalk <br><br>From the park you hear the happy sound of a carousel <br>Mmm, you can almost taste the hot dogs and French fries they sell <br>Under the boardwalk, down by the sea, yeah <br>On a blanket with my baby is where I'll be <br><br>Under the boardwalk Out of the sun <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be havin' some fun <br>Under the boardwalk People walking above <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be making love <br>Under the boardwalk, boardwalk <br><br>Oh, under the boardwalk, down by the sea, yeah <br>On a blanket with my baby is where I'll be <br><br>Under the boardwalk Out of the sun <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be havin' some fun <br>Under the boardwalk People walking above <br>Under the boardwalk We'll be falling in love <br>Under the boardwalk, boardwalk]]></content><category term="The Drifters" label="The Drifters"/><category term="Under The Boardwalk" label="Under The Boardwalk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sandy_Posey/I_Will_Follow_Him/</id><title>Sandy Posey - I Will Follow Him - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sandy_Posey/I_Will_Follow_Him/" title="Sandy Posey - I Will Follow Him - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love him, I love him, I love him <br>And where he goes I'll follow, I'll follow, I'll follow <br><br>I will follow him, follow him wherever he may go <br>There isn't an ocean too deep <br>A mountain so high it can keep me away <br><br>I must follow him, ever since he touched my hand I knew <br>That near him I always must be <br>And nothing can keep him from me <br>He is my destiny <br><br>I love him, I love him, I love him <br>And where he goes I'll follow, I'll follow, I'll follow <br>He'll always be my true love, my true love, my true love <br>From now until forever, forever, forever <br><br>I will follow him, follow him wherever he may go <br><br>There isn't an ocean too deep <br>A mountain so high it can keep, keep me away <br>Away from my love <br><br>I love him, I love him, I love him <br>And where he goes I'll follow, I'll follow, I'll follow <br>He'll always be my true love, my true love, my true love <br>From now until forever, forever, forever <br><br>I will follow him, follow him wherever he may go <br>There isn't an ocean too deep <br>A mountain so high it can keep, keep me away <br>Away from my love <br><br>Do do do do do do do do and where he goes <br>I'll follow, I'll follow, I'll follow <br>I know I'll always love him]]></content><category term="Sandy Posey" label="Sandy Posey"/><category term="I Will Follow Him" label="I Will Follow Him"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Van_Morrison/Brown_Eyed_Girl/</id><title>Van Morrison - Brown Eyed Girl - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Van_Morrison/Brown_Eyed_Girl/" title="Van Morrison - Brown Eyed Girl - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey where did we go <br>Days when the rains came <br>Down in the hollow <br>Playin' a new game <br>Laughing and a running hey, hey <br>Skipping and a jumping <br>In the misty morning fog with <br>Our hearts a thumpin' and you <br>My brown eyed girl <br>You, my brown eyed girl <br><br>Whatever happened <br>To Tuesday and so slow <br>Going down the old mine <br>With a transistor radio <br>Standing in the sunlight laughing <br>Hiding behind a rainbow's wall <br>Slipping and sliding <br>All along the waterfall, with you <br>My brown eyed girl <br>You, my brown eyed girl <br><br>Do you remember when we used to sing <br>Sha la la la la la la la la la la te da <br>Just like that <br>Sha la la la la la la la la la la te da la te da <br><br>So hard to find my way <br>Now that I'm all on my own <br>I saw you just the other day <br>My, how you have grown <br>Cast my memory back there, Lord <br>Sometimes I'm overcome thinking 'bout <br>Making love in the green grass <br>Behind the stadium with you <br>My brown eyed girl <br>You, my brown eyed girl <br><br>Do you remember when we used to sing <br>Sha la la la la la la la la la la te da <br>Sha la la la la la la la la la la te da la te da <br>Sha la la la la la la la la la la te da la te da]]></content><category term="Van Morrison" label="Van Morrison"/><category term="Brown Eyed Girl" label="Brown Eyed Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Archies/Sugar_Sugar/</id><title>The Archies - Sugar Sugar - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Archies/Sugar_Sugar/" title="The Archies - Sugar Sugar - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sugar, ah honey honey <br>You are my candy girl <br>And you've got me wanting you <br>Honey, ah sugar sugar <br>You are my candy girl <br>And you've got me wanting you <br><br>I just can't believe the loveliness of loving you <br>I just can't believe it's true <br>I just can't believe the one to love this feeling to <br>I just can't believe it's true <br><br>Ah sugar, ah honey honey <br>You are my candy girl <br>And you've got me wanting you <br>Ah honey, ah sugar sugar <br>You are my candy girl <br>And you've got me wanting you <br><br>When I kissed you, girl, I knew how sweet a kiss could be <br>I know how sweet a kiss can be <br>Like the summer sunshine pour your sweetness over me <br>Pour your sweetness over me <br><br>Sugar, pour a little sugar on it honey <br>Pour a little sugar on it baby <br>I'm gonna make your life so sweet, yeah yeah yeah <br>Pour a little sugar on it oh yeah <br>Pour a little sugar on it honey <br>Pour a little sugar on it baby <br>I'm gonna make your life so sweet, yeah yeah yeah <br>Pour a little sugar on it honey <br><br>Ah sugar, ah honey honey <br>You are my candy girl <br>And you've got me wanting you <br>Oh honey, honey, sugar sugar <br>You are my candy girl]]></content><category term="The Archies" label="The Archies"/><category term="Sugar Sugar" label="Sugar Sugar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Searchers/Love_Potion_No9/</id><title>The Searchers - Love Potion No.9 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Searchers/Love_Potion_No9/" title="The Searchers - Love Potion No.9 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I took my troubles down to Madame Ruth <br>You know that gypsy with the gold capped tooth <br>She's got a pad down on Thirty Fourth and Vine <br>Selling little bottles of love potion number nine <br><br>I told her that I was a flop with chics <br>I've been this way since 1956 <br>She looked at my palm and she made a magic sign <br>She said What you need is love potion number nine <br><br>She bent down and turned around and gave me a wink <br>She said I'm gonna make it up right here in the sink <br>It smelled like turpentine, it looked like Indian ink <br>I held my nose, I closed my eyes, I took a drink <br><br>I didn't know if it was day or night <br>I started kissing everything in sight <br>But when I kissed a cop down on Thirty Fourth and Vine <br>He broke my little bottle of Love Potion Number Nine <br><br>I held my nose, I closed my eyes, I took a drink <br><br>I didn't know if it was day or night <br>I started kissing everything in sight <br>But when I kissed a cop down on Thirty Fourth and Vine <br>He broke my little bottle of Love Potion Number Nine <br>Love potion number nine <br>Love Potion number nine <br>Love Potion number nine]]></content><category term="The Searchers" label="The Searchers"/><category term="Love Potion No.9" label="Love Potion No.9"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hermans_Hermits/Theres_A_Kind_Of_Hush/</id><title>Herman`s Hermits - There`s A Kind Of Hush - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hermans_Hermits/Theres_A_Kind_Of_Hush/" title="Herman`s Hermits - There`s A Kind Of Hush - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a kind of hush all over the world tonight <br>All over the world you can hear the sounds of lovers in love <br>You know what I mean <br>Just the two of us and nobody else in sight <br>There's nobody else and I'm feelin' good just holdin' you tight <br><br>So listen very carefully <br>Closer now and you will see what I mean <br>It isn't a dream <br>The only sound that you will hear <br>Is when I whisper in your ear <br>I love you forever and ever <br><br>There's a kind of hush all over the world tonight <br>All over the world you can hear the sound of lovers in love <br>La la la la la la la <br>La la la la la la la la <br>La la la la la la la la la la <br>La la la la la <br><br>So listen very carefully <br>Closer now and you will see what I mean <br>It isn't a dream <br>The only sound that you will hear <br>Is when I whisper in your ear <br>I love you forever and ever <br><br>There's a kind of hush all over the world tonight <br>All over the world, people just like us are falling in love <br>Yeah, they're falling in love <br>They're falling in love]]></content><category term="Herman`s Hermits" label="Herman`s Hermits"/><category term="There`s A Kind Of Hush" label="There`s A Kind Of Hush"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maxine_Nightingale/Lead_Me_On/</id><title>Maxine Nightingale - Lead Me On - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maxine_Nightingale/Lead_Me_On/" title="Maxine Nightingale - Lead Me On - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I have often heard you say <br>You love me as a friend <br>But I love you more than anyone <br>You know I can't pretend no longer <br>I would give you anything <br>I could throw my world away <br>But you don't want to hear that anymore <br>And you want to hear me say <br><br>Come on and lead me on <br>Come on and tease me all night long <br>Loving you I know it's right <br>I'll always need you <br>I'll never leave you <br>Come on and lead me on <br>Tease me all night long <br>I'd rather be a fool with a broken heart <br>Than someone who never had a part of you <br><br>You know I told you from the start <br>Exactly how I feel <br>Time goes on, seems nothing's changed <br>I'm in love for real <br>We have never played the games <br>That real lovers do <br>So maybe we are better off <br>Baby, I'd still like this from you <br><br>Come on and lead me on <br>Come on and tease me all night long <br>Loving you I know it's right <br>I'll always need you <br>I'll never leave you <br>Come on and lead me on <br>Tease me all night long <br>I'd rather be a fool with a broken heart <br>Than someone who never had a part of you]]></content><category term="Maxine Nightingale" label="Maxine Nightingale"/><category term="Lead Me On" label="Lead Me On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Edison_Lighthouse/Love_Grows/</id><title>Edison Lighthouse - Love Grows - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Edison_Lighthouse/Love_Grows/" title="Edison Lighthouse - Love Grows - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She ain't got no money <br>Her clothes are kinda funny <br>Her hair is kinda wild and free <br>Oh, but love grows where my Rosemary goes <br>And nobody knows like me <br><br>She talks kinda lazy <br>And people say she's crazy <br>And her life's a mystery <br>Oh, but love grows where my Rosemary goes <br>And nobody knows like me <br><br>There's something about her hand holding mine <br>It's a feeling that's fine <br>And I just gotta say, hey <br>She's really got a magical spell <br>And it's working so well <br>That I can't get away <br><br>I'm a lucky fella <br>And I just got to tell her <br>That I love her endlessly <br>Because love grows where my Rosemary goes <br>And nobody knows like me <br><br>There's something about her hand holding mine <br>It's a feeling that's fine <br>And I just gotta say, hey <br>She's really got a magical spell <br>And it's working so well <br>That I can't get away <br><br>I'm a lucky fella <br>And I just got to tell her <br>That I love her endlessly <br>Because love grows where my Rosemary goes <br>And nobody knows like me <br><br>Oh my love grows where my Rosemary goes <br>And nobody knows like me <br>Love grows where my Rosemary goes <br>And nobody knows like me <br><br>It keeps growing every place she's been <br>And nobody knows like me <br>If you've met her, you'll never forget her <br>And nobody knows like me <br>La la la, believe it when you've seen it <br>Nobody knows like me]]></content><category term="Edison Lighthouse" label="Edison Lighthouse"/><category term="Love Grows" label="Love Grows"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Orbison/Oh_Pretty_Woman/</id><title>Roy Orbison - Oh, Pretty Woman - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_Orbison/Oh_Pretty_Woman/" title="Roy Orbison - Oh, Pretty Woman - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Pretty woman, walkin' down the street <br>Pretty woman the kind I like to meet <br>Pretty woman I don't believe you, you're not the truth <br>No one could look as good as you, mercy <br><br>Pretty woman won't you pardon me <br>Pretty woman I couldn't help but see <br>Pretty woman that you look lovely as can be <br>Are you lonely just like me <br><br>Pretty woman stop awhile <br>Pretty woman talk awhile <br>Pretty woman give your smile to me <br>Pretty woman yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Pretty woman look my way <br>Pretty woman say you'll stay with me <br>'Cause I need you, I'll treat you right <br>Come with me baby, be mine tonight <br><br>Pretty woman don't walk on by <br>Pretty woman don't make me cry <br>Pretty woman don't walk away, hey, OK <br>If that's the way it must be, OK <br>I guess I'll go on home, it's late <br>There'll be tomorrow night, but wait <br>What do I see <br>Is she walkin' back to me <br>Yeah, she's walkin' back to me <br>Oh, oh, pretty woman]]></content><category term="Roy Orbison" label="Roy Orbison"/><category term="Oh, Pretty Woman" label="Oh, Pretty Woman"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Turtles/Happy_Together/</id><title>The Turtles - Happy Together - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Turtles/Happy_Together/" title="The Turtles - Happy Together - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine me and you, I do <br>I think about you day and night, it's only right <br>To think about the girl you love and hold her tight <br>So happy together <br><br>If I should call you up, invest a dime <br>And you say you belong to me and ease my mind <br>Imagine how the world could be, so very fine <br>So happy together <br><br>I can't see me lovin' nobody but you <br>For all my life <br>When you're with me, baby the skies'll be blue <br>For all my life <br><br>Me and you and you and me <br>No matter how they toss the dice, it had to be <br>The only one for me is you, and you for me <br>So happy together <br><br>I can't see me lovin' nobody but you <br>For all my life <br>When you're with me, baby the skies'll be blue <br>For all my life <br><br>Me and you and you and me <br>No matter how they toss the dice, it had to be <br>The only one for me is you, and you for me <br>So happy together <br><br>Ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba <br>Ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba <br><br>Me and you and you and me <br>No matter how they toss the dice, it had to be <br>The only one for me is you, and you for me <br>So happy together <br><br>So happy together <br>How is the weather <br>So happy together <br>We're happy together <br>So happy together <br>Happy together <br>So happy together <br>So happy together ba ba ba ba ba ba ba ba]]></content><category term="The Turtles" label="The Turtles"/><category term="Happy Together" label="Happy Together"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Vee/More_Than_I_Can_Say/</id><title>Bobby Vee - More Than I Can Say - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Vee/More_Than_I_Can_Say/" title="Bobby Vee - More Than I Can Say - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wo oh yay yay <br>Love you more than I can say <br>I'll love you twice as much tomorrow <br>Wo oh, love you more than I can say <br><br>Wo oh yay yay <br>I miss you every single day <br>Why must my life be filled with sorrow <br>Wo oh, love you more than I can say <br><br>Don't you know I need you so <br>Tell me please, I gotta know <br>Do you mean to make me cry <br>Am I just another guy <br><br>Wo oh yay yay <br>Love you more than I can say <br>I'll love you twice as much tomorrow <br>Wo,oh, love you more than I can say <br><br>Don't you know I need you so <br>Tell me please, I gotta know <br>Do you mean to make me cry <br>Am I just another guy <br><br>Wo oh yay yay <br>I love you more than I can say <br>I'll love you twice as much tomorrow <br>Wo oh, love you more than I can say]]></content><category term="Bobby Vee" label="Bobby Vee"/><category term="More Than I Can Say" label="More Than I Can Say"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ritchie_Valens/Donna/</id><title>Ritchie Valens - Donna - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ritchie_Valens/Donna/" title="Ritchie Valens - Donna - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, Donna <br>Oh, Donna <br>Oh, Donna <br>Oh, Donna <br><br>I had a girl <br>Donna was her name <br>Since she left me <br>I've never been the same <br><br>'Cause I love my girl <br>Donna, where can you be <br>Where can you be <br><br>Now that you're gone <br>I'm left all alone <br>All by myself <br>To wander and roam <br><br>'Cause I love my girl <br>Donna, where can you be <br>Where can you be <br><br>Oh, darlin', now that you're gone <br>I don't know what I'll do <br>All the time and all my love <br>For you <br><br>I had a girl <br>Donna was her name <br>Since she left me <br>I've never been the same <br><br>'Cause I love my girl <br>Donna, where can you be <br>Where can you be <br><br>Oh, Donna <br>Oh, Donna <br>Oh, Donna <br>Oh, Donna]]></content><category term="Ritchie Valens" label="Ritchie Valens"/><category term="Donna" label="Donna"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lynn_Anderson/When_I_Dream/</id><title>Lynn Anderson - When I Dream - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lynn_Anderson/When_I_Dream/" title="Lynn Anderson - When I Dream - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I could build a mansion that is higher than the trees <br>I could have all the gifts I want and never ask please <br>I could fly to Paris, it's at my beck and call <br>Why do I live my life alone with nothing at all <br>But when I dream, I dream of you <br>Maybe someday you will come true <br>When I dream, I dream of you <br>Maybe someday you will come true <br>I can be the singer or the clown in any room <br>I can call up someone to take me to the moon <br>I can put my makeup on and drive the men insane <br>I can go to bed alone and never know his name <br>But when I dream, I dream of you <br><br>Maybe someday you will come true <br>When I dream, I dream of you <br>Maybe someday you will come true]]></content><category term="Lynn Anderson" label="Lynn Anderson"/><category term="When I Dream" label="When I Dream"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lobo/Id_Love_You_To_Want_Me/</id><title>Lobo - I`d Love You To Want Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lobo/Id_Love_You_To_Want_Me/" title="Lobo - I`d Love You To Want Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When I saw you standing there <br>I bout fell out my chair <br>And when you moved your mouth to speak <br>I felt the blood go to my feet <br><br>Now it took time for me to know <br>what you tried so not to show <br>Now something in my soul just cries <br>I see the want in your blue eyes <br><br>Baby, I'd love you to want me <br>The way that I want you <br>The way that it should be <br>Baby, you'd love me to want you <br>The way that I want to <br>If you'd only let it be <br><br>You told yourself years ago <br>You'd never let your feeling show <br>The obligation that you made <br>For the title that they gave]]></content><category term="Lobo" label="Lobo"/><category term="I`d Love You To Want Me" label="I`d Love You To Want Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Platters/Only_You/</id><title>The Platters - Only You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Platters/Only_You/" title="The Platters - Only You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Only you can make all this world seem right <br>Only you can make the darkness bright <br>Only you and you alone can thrill me like you do <br>And fill my heart with love for only you <br><br>Only you can make all this change in me <br>For it's true, you are my destiny <br>When you hold my hand I understand the magic that you do <br>You're my dream come true, my one and only you <br><br>Only you can make this change in me <br>For it's true, you are my destiny <br>When you hold my hand I understand the magic that you do <br>You're my dream come true, my one and only you]]></content><category term="The Platters" label="The Platters"/><category term="Only You" label="Only You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Righteous_Brothers/Unchained_Melody/</id><title>The Righteous Brothers - Unchained Melody - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Righteous_Brothers/Unchained_Melody/" title="The Righteous Brothers - Unchained Melody - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, my love, my darling <br>I've hungered for your touch <br>A long, lonely time <br>Time goes by so slowly <br>And time can do so much <br>Are you still mine <br>I need your love <br>I need your love <br>God speed your love to me <br><br>Lonely rivers flow <br>To the sea, to the sea <br>To the open arms of the sea <br>Lonely rivers sigh <br>Wait for me, wait for me <br>I'll be coming home, wait for me <br><br>Oh, my love, my darling <br>I've hungered, for your touch <br>A long, lonely time <br>Time goes by so slowly <br>And time can do so much <br>Are you still mine <br>I need your love <br>I need your love <br>God speed your love to me]]></content><category term="The Righteous Brothers" label="The Righteous Brothers"/><category term="Unchained Melody" label="Unchained Melody"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Elvis_Presley/Cant_Help_Falling_In_Love/</id><title>Elvis Presley - Can`t Help Falling In Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Elvis_Presley/Cant_Help_Falling_In_Love/" title="Elvis Presley - Can`t Help Falling In Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wise men say only fools rush in <br>But I can't help falling in love with you <br>Shall I stay <br>Would it be a sin <br>If I can't help falling in love with you <br><br>Like a river flows surely to the sea <br>Darling so it goes <br>Some things are meant to be <br>Take my hand, take my whole life too <br>For I can't help falling in love with you <br><br>Like a river flows surely to the sea <br>Darling so it goes <br>Some things are meant to be <br>Take my hand, take my whole life too <br>For I can't help falling in love with you <br>For I can't help falling in love with you]]></content><category term="Elvis Presley" label="Elvis Presley"/><category term="Can`t Help Falling In Love" label="Can`t Help Falling In Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Valntn/Fantasies_Feat_Lexxi_Saal/</id><title>Valntn - Fantasies (Feat. Lexxi Saal) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:07:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:07:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Valntn/Fantasies_Feat_Lexxi_Saal/" title="Valntn - Fantasies (Feat. Lexxi Saal) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Last night <br>I saw myself in reflections from the light <br>Could not find my own face <br><br>광고 <br><br>Past times <br>I kept on going in spite of the bad times <br>Now that fire is fading <br><br>I might fall into the notion that I am bright <br>But you find my weakness <br>Tired eyes from work I do for you it's never right <br>So I'll find my own way <br><br>I'll change directions <br>These expectations take it all from me <br>No more deceptions <br>I can't go on living a fantasy anymore <br><br>I've tried to keep moving with no reward in sight <br>Pretending time stopped ticking <br>This lie has kept me wide awake at night <br>And it defies all reason <br><br>But I'll change directions <br>These expectations take it all from me <br>No more deceptions <br>I can't go on living a fantasy anymore <br><br>I can't go on living a fantasy <br>I can't go on living your fantasy anymore]]></content><category term="Valntn" label="Valntn"/><category term="Fantasies (Feat. Lexxi Saal)" label="Fantasies (Feat. Lexxi Saal)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레페_LEPE/SWISH/</id><title>레페 (LEPE) - SWISH - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:08:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:08:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%ED%8E%98_LEPE/SWISH/" title="레페 (LEPE) - SWISH - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[IT GOES LIKE <br>IT GOES LIKE <br>내 250의 발은 <br>너무 자연스레 <br>원하던 길 위에 둔 <br>채로 호흡을 유지해 늘 <br>GRIDIN' AND STAY TUNED <br>급하기도 싫고 <br>뭐 급하지도 않지 <br>즐거움을 잊은 채로 <br>숨 안 쉬며 달리는 건 NAH <br>CHILL한 느낌이 안나 <br>헐떡임과 손 잡은 <br>빈혈뿐이지 아마 <br>굳이 꾸미지 않아도 <br>이젠 내 가치를 알지 <br>다신 잡아 먹힐 뻔 했던 <br>그 나락으로 <br>가지 않길 원해 <br>틈을 찾기 힘든 세상은 어지러워 <br>계속 갇혀있다간 내 자신 조차 <br>모두 잃어버릴 걸 <br>너 자체로 빛이 나길 <br>우린 너무 젊어 아직 알지 <br>걱정하지마 우린 가장 높이 <br>떠 오를 거야 <br>IT GOES LIKE SWISH <br>IT GOES LIKE SWISH <br>IT GOES LIKE SWISH <br>IT GOES LIKE SWISH <br>IT GOES LIKE IT GOES LIKE <br>IT GOES LIKE <br>WE JUST WANNA SIT BACK AND RELAX <br>한치 앞도 모를 미래에 비해 <br>빡센 싸움보단 여율 원하지만 <br>늘 그랬듯 <br>일 봐주지 않는 시간 위로 <br>다시 바삐 걸음을 옮기지 <br>마찬 가지야 <br>사실 내일 당장 죽어도 <br>누구 한 사람 <br>안 이상할 현재에 사는 우린데 <br>먼 미래를 굳이 <br>걱정하는 것이 웃기네 <br>그냥 현재를 살아 <br>대체 누가 정확히 인생을 알아 <br>생을 마감할 때 기억되는 날 안에 <br>후회라는 감정이 <br>최대한 남지 않게 <br>DIRECTION BETTER THAN THE SPEED <br>깨닫고 나니 <br>상당히 해소 된 느낌을 <br>나누고 싶어서 가져왔어 <br>너도 가져가 <br>함께 나누고 싶어 너도 가져가 <br>틈을 찾기 힘든 세상은 어지러워 <br>계속 갇혀있다간 내 자신 조차 <br>모두 잃어버릴 걸 <br>너 자체로 빛이 나길 <br>우린 너무 젊어 아직 알지 <br>다시 말해 확실하게 살길 바래 <br>아쉬움에 잠길 바엔 <br>그냥 미련 없이 <br>오르자고 SWISH <br>IT GOES LIKE SWISH <br>IT GOES LIKE SWISH <br>IT GOES LIKE SWISH <br>IT GOES LIKE IT GOES LIKE <br>IT GOES LIKE <br>]]></content><category term="레페 (LEPE)" label="레페 (LEPE)"/><category term="SWISH" label="SWISH"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/은하수/뚝뚝뚝/</id><title>은하수 - 뚝뚝뚝 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:08:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:08:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%80%ED%95%98%EC%88%98/%EB%9A%9D%EB%9A%9D%EB%9A%9D/" title="은하수 - 뚝뚝뚝 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 괜찮다고 해도 <br>이렇게 눈물이 흘러서 <br>숨겨왔던 아픔이 너를 불러내 <br>한동안 힘들 것 같아 <br>난 아무 일 없다고 <br>시간이 해결해 줄 거라지만 <br>여기까지가 우리 끝이라면 <br>너무 아쉬워 난 어떡해 <br>지나간 우리 추억이 <br>한편의 영화처럼 기억에 남아 <br>아무도 모르게 하늘 보며 <br>입술을 깨물며 뚝뚝뚝 <br>난 아무 일 없다고 <br>시간이 해결해 줄 거라지만 <br>여기까지가 우리 끝이라면 <br>너무 아쉬워 난 어떡해 <br>지나간 우리 추억이 <br>한편의 영화처럼 기억에 남아 <br>아무도 모르게 하늘 보며 <br>입술을 깨물며 뚝뚝뚝 <br>이런 일 하루 이틀에 <br>쉽게 잊을 수가 없어서 <br>힘들 것 같아 <br>아플 것 같아 <br>지나간 우리 추억이 <br>한편의 영화처럼 <br>남을 수 있을까 <br>아무도 모르게 하늘 보며 <br>입술을 깨물며 뚝뚝뚝 <br>다시 서둘러 돌아간다면 <br>아무 일 없던 <br>그때로 갈 수 있을까 <br>너무나 멀리도 가버린 널 <br>얼마나 불러야 올까요 <br>아프지만 널 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="은하수" label="은하수"/><category term="뚝뚝뚝" label="뚝뚝뚝"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeremy_Passion/Stephanie/</id><title>Jeremy Passion - Stephanie - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:13:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:13:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jeremy_Passion/Stephanie/" title="Jeremy Passion - Stephanie - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She strums her guitar <br>The rosewood is stained with the tears from her eyes <br>Her phone said 20 missed calls <br>She didn't realize she's been crying all night <br>She said she's too young <br>Always rushed to get older <br>Now she's running out of time <br>Don't wanna believe the doctor's orders <br>Just awhile ago things were fine <br>Stephanie beautiful, beautiful Stephanie <br>She smiles for the world <br>Though she knows that sometimes life's not fair <br>Stephanie, stronger than anyone thought she'd be <br>She closes her eyes <br>Lifts her head to the skies <br>Lord, are you there <br>Are you there <br>Are you there <br>She keeps a diary of all that she feels <br>And hides from the world all her pain <br>She's speaking to Jesus <br>Though, she doesn't know <br>Whether to trust or to blame <br>She faces a wall and just wants to get over <br>But her body is too tired to climb <br>Rest in His arms and cry on His shoulders <br>The battle is not yours to fight <br>Stephanie beautiful, beautiful Stephanie <br>She smiles for the world <br>Though she knows that sometimes life's not fair <br>Oh, Stephanie stronger than anyone thought she'd be <br>She closes her eyes <br>Lifts her head to the skies <br>Lord, are you there <br>I don't know the answers to all of my questions <br>Why this had to happen to me <br>But my heart is trusting in you <br>Can you set me free <br>Stephanie beautiful, beautiful Stephanie <br>You smile for the world <br>Though you know that sometimes life's not fair <br>Oh, Stephanie stronger than anyone thought she'd be <br>She closes her eyes <br>Lifts her head to the skies <br>Lord, are you there <br>I am here <br>I've been here <br>My child, my child I've been here <br>I'll never leave you <br>Nor forsake you <br>I feel your pain <br>I've been here]]></content><category term="Jeremy Passion" label="Jeremy Passion"/><category term="Stephanie" label="Stephanie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/311/Too_Late/</id><title>311 - Too Late - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:13:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:13:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/311/Too_Late/" title="311 - Too Late - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been spinning in circles <br>Stuck in a state of contemplate <br>By the time that you hear this it will be too late <br>May not do a bit of good <br>But I can't stay in a hopeless way <br>By the time that you hear this it will be too late, too late <br>Pressing in the darkness <br>Maybe in our past we'd go along <br>By the world we need this <br>By the time you read this it will be too late <br><br>Made our way but we were way too long <br>Made our way but we were way too long <br><br>It's human nature, the tragic and danger <br>You look around but you won't see rangers <br>There's crazy acting strangers act in a major <br>Act in a major <br><br>A river cuts its way through stone <br>Obstacle course no persistence <br>At the end of the day the relentless always win <br>If they wanted to stop us <br>Opportunity passed 'cause they hesitate <br>By the time that you hear this it will be too late, too late <br>Left me in the darkness <br>Maybe in our past we'd go along <br>By the world we need this <br>By the time you read this it will be too late <br><br>Made our way but we were way too long <br>Made our way but we were way too long <br><br>The only thing that stopped us was coming in softer <br>The road at a tow, the end it will drop off <br>The universe explodes, new galaxies pop up <br>New galaxies pop up <br><br>Blowing gas going fast in the passing lane <br>On the line In the tunnel was an oncoming train <br>Out of sight, out of mind, now I'm stuck in a bind <br>That was the end of the line <br><br>Headshot <br>King of the block <br>It's going down <br>Another hard knock <br>That's all you got <br>Well turn it up in the mix <br>You'll hear it loud in the sticks <br>Relay the message from the downtown <br>With our sounds <br>We expound <br>It will be too late]]></content><category term="311" label="311"/><category term="Too Late" label="Too Late"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김도현/나의_가는_길/</id><title>김도현 - 나의 가는 길 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:13:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:13:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EB%8F%84%ED%98%84/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EA%B0%80%EB%8A%94_%EA%B8%B8/" title="김도현 - 나의 가는 길 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 가는 길 <br>오직 그 분은 아시니 <br>지친 내 영혼 <br>갈 곳 몰라 <br>헤매일 때 <br>나를 품어주시고 <br>절망에서 소망으로 <br>인도하셨네 <br>내게 새 힘 주셨네 <br>나 이제 가네 <br>나 이제 가네 <br>나의 상하고 지친 마음 버리고 <br>주 십자가 보혈의 능력 힘입어 <br>담대하게 나아가리라 <br>나 이제 서리라 <br>나 이제 서리라 <br>반석 위에 나를 굳게 세우리라 <br>허리에 진리에 띠를 띠고서 <br>담대히 말씀 가운데 서리라 <br>나를 품어주시고 <br>절망에서 소망으로 <br>인도하셨네 <br>내게 새 힘 주셨네 <br>나 이제 가네 <br>나 이제 가네 <br>나의 상하고 지친 마음 버리고 <br>주 십자가 보혈의 능력 힘입어 <br>담대하게 나아가리라 <br>나 이제 서리라 <br>나 이제 서리라 <br>반석 위에 나를 굳게 세우리라 <br>허리에 진리에 띠를 띠고서 <br>담대히 말씀 가운데 서리라 <br>나 이제 가네 <br>나 이제 가네 <br>나의 상하고 지친 마음 버리고 <br>주 십자가 보혈의 능력 힘입어 <br>담대하게 나아가리라 <br>나 이제 서리라 <br>나 이제 서리라 <br>반석 위에 나를 굳게 세우리라 <br>허리에 진리에 띠를 띠고서 <br>담대히 말씀 가운데 서리라 <br>그 길 위에 내가 서리라 <br>]]></content><category term="김도현" label="김도현"/><category term="나의 가는 길" label="나의 가는 길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/J_Brown/마리오네트/</id><title>J Brown - 마리오네트 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:13:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:13:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/J_Brown/%EB%A7%88%EB%A6%AC%EC%98%A4%EB%84%A4%ED%8A%B8/" title="J Brown - 마리오네트 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 걸 보여줄게 <br>가식 없는 art <br>태워줄게 열정을 <br>가요계에 널려 있는 <br>인형들의 폐기를 <br>길거리 음악인들의 <br>열정과 패기를 <br>JD는 간지 나지 <br>길거리 artist 패기를 <br>무대 위 꼭두각시 <br>주인공은 fake <br>구린내 나게 풍기지 <br>지독한 스멜 <br>가면 속 가려진 어둠 속 그림자 <br>네 모습은 역겨운 똥 냄새보다도 <br>더럽게 폼만 재 <br>지고 싶지 않아 <br>그림에 속지 않아 <br>창작을 버리지 않아 <br>실력은 뒤지지 않아 <br>어차피 가는 거 끝까지 가는 거 <br>예술에 고통을 아는 자뿐인걸 <br>JD는 그림자 없이도 창작에 <br>예술의 무대를 꾸미고 <br>보고 싶은 무대의 내 모습 그리고 <br>정상에 오르는 내 모습뿐이고 <br>창작의 고통은 아픔을 부르고 <br>무대 위 인형은 죽음을 부르고 <br>동규와 진용이 환영에 <br>진명아 J Brown JD Music 크루 후 <br>인지도 없이도 음악은 계속해 <br>실력은 언제나 조금씩 성장해 <br>노력의 결과는 배신은 없던데 <br>결과를 알기 전 심장은 쿵쾅대 <br>정상에 오르는 기분은 상쾌해 <br>오늘의 성장이 나를 더 키우네 <br>정상에 한걸음 오늘도 일을 내 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>슬픔에 울지 못해 <br>아픔에 울지 못해 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>나 우물 안 개구리지 <br>내 음악은 개 구리지 <br>음악의 완성이 100이면 <br>내 음악은 3이나 4겠지 <br>싱글을 낼 때면 오르는 <br>성장이 1이면 내 음원 <br>100개면 음원의 완성은 <br>100보다 더 높은 <br>가치가 있겠지 <br>언젠가 우물 안 개구리가 다 <br>삼켜버릴 거야 이 바닥을 <br>주변에 응원이 나를 더 키우네 <br>정상에 한걸음 오늘도 일을 내 <br>변하는 시스템 없지 난 아이템 <br>새로운 창작의 고통은 <br>예술을 창조해 <br>변화는 새로운 시작을 알리네 <br>난 전설이 되겠지 <br>무하마드 알리 예 <br>내 도전에 불만 가진 <br>사람이 많아졌어 <br>댓글로 디스가 취미인 <br>사람이 많아졌어 <br>무명 예술쟁이들 <br>전문가인 척하는 <br>사람이 많아졌어 <br>누군가 말했지 <br>도토리 키재기하면서 <br>너와 나 멀어졌어 <br>빠르게 변하는 세상은 마치 <br>누군가 조종해 게임어 같이 <br>기획사 가수들 상품의 가치 <br>메이커 상품과 다를 바가 없지 <br>지금의 음악은 <br>유행하는 악세사리 같지 <br>시간이 지나면 사라져 <br>음악이란 상품의 가치 <br>예술쟁이들도 마찬가지 <br>사라져 먼지처럼 <br>망가진 인형들의 <br>마지막 최후에 모습처럼 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>슬픔에 울지 못해 <br>아픔에 울지 못해 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>마리오네트 마리오네트 <br>]]></content><category term="J Brown" label="J Brown"/><category term="마리오네트" label="마리오네트"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Horse_Jumper_Of_Love/Ugly_Brunette/</id><title>Horse Jumper Of Love - Ugly Brunette - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:14:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:14:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Horse_Jumper_Of_Love/Ugly_Brunette/" title="Horse Jumper Of Love - Ugly Brunette - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[funeral expense commercial <br>kids cutting bday cake I am the jealous one <br><br>I remember that shirt I got a bunch of bleach on it <br>I liked it that way too <br><br>I am an ugly brunette I want to have a lonely child <br><br>I'll be patient w you thats the way the garden grows and the gardener forgets]]></content><category term="Horse Jumper Of Love" label="Horse Jumper Of Love"/><category term="Ugly Brunette" label="Ugly Brunette"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Self_Defense_Family/Self_Immolation_Family_BBC_Live_Ver/</id><title>Self Defense Family - Self Immolation Family (BBC Live Ver.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:14:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:14:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Self_Defense_Family/Self_Immolation_Family_BBC_Live_Ver/" title="Self Defense Family - Self Immolation Family (BBC Live Ver.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Redhead in the office, blonde at discount store <br>Brunette wife's friend, bald woman from rehab <br>Thin girl from college, bhick girl from marriage <br>Fit girl from dreams, shit girl from here <br><br>Slipped between your sandal and foot <br>Brushed the gums so it exposed the root <br>Got on drugs, got off drugs, got on drugs <br><br>Show by the boss, show by the square <br>Show by the masses, show by the heirs <br>Tune with no balls, tune with no teeth <br>Tune with no bite, tune with no reach <br><br>Slipped between your sandal and foot <br>Brushed the gums so it exposed the root <br>Got on drugs, got off drugs, got on drugs <br>Slipped between your sandal and foot <br>Brushed the gums so it exposed the root <br>Got on drugs, got off drugs, got on drugs <br><br>Green lights from here until Venice <br>Slaughterhouse march down the promenade <br>They told you no so you invited a chemist <br>Joyful dance past the prison bars <br>Green lights from here until Venice <br>Slaughterhouse march down the promenade <br>They told you no so you invited a chemist <br>Joyful dance past the prison bars <br><br>Wanted some girls, I tell you <br>Wanted some drugs, I tell you]]></content><category term="Self Defense Family" label="Self Defense Family"/><category term="Self Immolation Family (BBC Live Ver.)" label="Self Immolation Family (BBC Live Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/La_Nef_Des_Fous_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - La Nef Des Fous (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:14:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:14:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/La_Nef_Des_Fous_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - La Nef Des Fous (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Je dis oui, tu dis non <br>tu dis noir,, je dis blanc <br>sans savoir <br><br>Quand je te dis va t'en, tu restes <br>et si tu pars, moi, je reste <br>C'est pas grave <br>Quand vient le soir, les masques tombent <br>et deux accords, a l'unisson, montent <br>vers la lune <br>qui nous pousse, un jour <br>a grimper au mat de hune <br>de la nef des fous <br>amants malgre tout <br>mais tu t'endors deja <br>te detournes de moi <br>et dans l'ombre <br>la peur d'une trahison <br>peu importe son nom <br>se faufile <br>et tres vite les soupcons <br>delivre moi des sortileges <br>quand vers minuit, un loup hurle en moi <br><br>a le lune <br>qui nous pousse tous <br>a quitter de force <br>les rues tranquilles de l'amour <br>pour monter a bord <br>de la nef des fous <br><br>La nef des fous <br><br>J'ai confondu l'amour <br>amour et devotion <br>C'est ma faute <br>Sur un socle, l'idole <br>touchait la perfection <br>Tout s'ecroule au premier faux pas <br>Un collier rouge <br>autour du cou <br>et sous mes ongles <br>des rubis sombres <br>coulent <br>sous la lune <br>nous pousse dans l'abime <br>plus loin, plus profond <br>laver <br>l'arme de nos crimes <br>la honte sur le front <br>sur la nef des fous <br><br>La nef des fous <br><br>La lune <br>qui nous pousse tous <br>a quitter de force <br>les rues <br>tranquilles de l'amour <br>pour monter a bord <br>de la nef des fous <br><br>La nef des fous <br>Amants malgre tout]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="La Nef Des Fous (Remasterise En 2017)" label="La Nef Des Fous (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Fascination_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Fascination (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:14:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:14:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Fascination_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Fascination (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Une histoire commence, une autre s'acheve <br>Mais les chiens errants pleurent toujours leur laisse <br>Parfois, les eaux du fleuve peuvent devenir claires <br>Si l'amour est aveugle, il connait nos faiblesses <br><br>Elle, la belle, a mis la bete en cage <br>M'a pris au piege en otage <br>Dans le theatre qu'elle appelle son ame, son ame <br><br>Avec elle, la spirale des cercles, l'enfer <br>Les nuits sans sommeil <br>Une ronde infernale dans son sillage m'entraine <br>Une chute precipitee d'hotels en meubles <br><br>Pour elle, j'ai noye au fond d'un verre <br>Ma maigre fierte <br>Pour elle, j'ai noye au fond d'un verre <br>Mon double, mon reflet, mon frere <br><br>Ange ou demon une obsession <br>Ange ou demon une obsession <br>Mi ange, mi demon une obsession <br>A tort, a raison, Fascination <br>Fascination, Fascination, Fascination <br><br>C'est l'enfer sur la Terre <br>Mon enfer sur la Terre <br><br>Un cri de haine, appel a l'aide x3 <br><br>Le long des rives, la ville brille <br>Comme une coulee de givre <br>Un millier d'aiguilles que la nuit herisse <br>Un millier de desirs m'incitent a sortir <br>Elle est partie, partie fini <br><br>Un peu de rouge a levres au bout d'une cigarette douce <br>Deux ou trois petites choses que je garde secretes <br>Mais je vendrais pere et mere pour l'emmener danser <br><br>Elle peut faire de moi ce qu'elle veut <br>Une langue de feu sous la glace <br>Elle fait de moi ce qu'elle veut <br>Quand ses cheveux noirs s'enflamment <br><br>Mi ange, mi demon une obsession <br>A tort, a raison, Fascination <br>Mi ange, mi demon une obsession <br>A tort, a raison, Fascination <br>Fascination, Fascination, Fascination <br><br>Pour une opale sombre <br>Une opale d'ombre <br>L'enfer sur la Terre <br>Mon enfer sur la Terre]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Fascination (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Fascination (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Jeux_De_Lumieres_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Jeux De Lumieres (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:14:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:14:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Jeux_De_Lumieres_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Jeux De Lumieres (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A contre jour tout d'abord <br>les contours de son corps <br>a contrecoeur, semblent eclore <br>aux premieres heures de l'aurore <br><br>Il la voit s'elever, fragile <br>et il la devine jeune ballerine <br>La regarde s'etirer, feline <br>et s'elancer dans le prisme <br>irreel <br>des jeux de lumieres <br>Qui est elle <br>Les yeux du mystere <br><br>Une suite de gestes lents <br>dans l'air chauffe a blanc <br>Une fuite de gestes brefs <br>revele d'autres facettes <br><br>Comme la danse des perles de rosee <br>sur les fils d'une toile d'araignee <br>dessine, l'espace d'un court instant <br>une etoile de mer en argent <br><br>Dans les jeux de lumieres <br>elle se voile <br>Dans les jeux de lumieres <br>se devoile <br>Dans les jeux de lumieres <br>ses entrechats siamois <br>glissent en petits pas sournois <br><br>Elle se derobe <br>puis s'abandonne <br>furtive a ses caresses <br>un sourire sur les levres <br>Elle se derobe <br>une fois encore <br>puis s'evapore <br>ivre d'ether <br>dans les jeux de lumieres <br><br>Une fuite de gestes lents <br>dans l'air chauffe a blanc <br>Une suite de gestes souples <br>dans la fievre du jour <br><br>Regarde comme le ciel est changeant <br>Un arc en ciel de sentiments <br>Et quand il devient menacant <br>regarde comme il effraie l'enfant <br>irreel <br>dans les jeux de lumieres <br>Ou est elle <br>Dans les yeux du mystere <br><br>Il l'a suivie longtemps des yeux <br>esperant quelques pas de deux <br>Dehors le temps etait pluvieux <br>plus vieux au moins d'un siecle ou deux <br><br>Dans les jeux de lumiere <br>elle se voile <br>Dans les jeux de lumieres <br>se devoile <br>Dans les jeux de lumieres <br>ses entrechats siamois <br>glissent en petits pas sournois <br><br>Elle se derobe <br>puis s'abandonne <br>furtive a ses caresses <br>un sourire sur les levres <br>Elle se derobe <br>une fois encore <br>puis s'evapore <br>ivre d'ether <br><br>Elle me monte a la tete <br>dans les jeux de lumieres <br>Elle me monte a la tete <br>a la tete <br>L'ether l'ether <br><br>There's still a light <br>that shines all night <br>There's still a light <br>that shines all night]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Jeux De Lumieres (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Jeux De Lumieres (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Lamour_Aux_Trousses_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - L`amour Aux Trousses (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:14:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:14:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Lamour_Aux_Trousses_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - L`amour Aux Trousses (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Il leve l'ancre <br>Gonflent ses voiles un nouveau depart <br><br>SI tu l'attends <br>il te reviendra <br>Quelqu'un, quelque part, te tend les bras <br><br>Une jeune geisha <br>dans une maison de the <br>a Kyoto <br>sur une natte <br>l'a enivre de sake <br>au son du koto <br><br>Il t'a cherchee <br>cherchee de bras en bras <br>croisee et perdue mille fois deja <br><br>Si tu l'attends <br>il te reviendra <br>Quelqu'un, quelque part, vers toi, tend ses bras <br><br>Dans les vitrines <br>des rues chaudes de Breme <br>ou de Hanovre <br>des mannequins s'animent <br>le temps d'un je vous aime <br>my love <br><br>Si tu attends, il reviendra <br>Si tu l'attends, il reviendra <br>L'amour aux trousses <br>aveugle et sourd <br>enfin <br>L'amour au coeur <br>attend son heure <br>pour te prendre par la main <br><br>Sur chaque lit de passage <br>se precise ton visage <br><br>Dans cette chambre, comme dans un ecrin <br>les tentures blanches ont conserve les plaintes <br>Les traces d'un passe qu'il reste a assembler <br>les rires et les chagrins, les regles d'un jeu a reinventer <br><br>Il a force <br>la porte des cites <br>defendues <br>Il est tombe <br>dans les pieges que Circe <br>lui a tendus <br><br>Si tu attends, il reviendra <br>Si tu l'attends, il reviendra <br>L'amour aux trousses <br>aveugle et sourd <br>avance <br>L'amour au coeur <br>attend son heure <br>si tu lui laisses une petite chance <br><br>Un soir, le ciel s'ouvrira un instant, lumineux <br>un jour perdu, un point s'agrandira, merveilleux <br>un soir, le ciel s'ouvrira a jamais, lumineux <br>un jour nouveau, un homme s'avancera, amoureux]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="L`amour Aux Trousses (Remasterise En 2017)" label="L`amour Aux Trousses (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Dans_Ses_Reves_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Dans Ses Reves (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:14:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:14:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Dans_Ses_Reves_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Dans Ses Reves (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rose, comme la fleur du desert <br>dont rien n'entame la lle de pierre <br>pas meme les vents de sable <br>Ton regard un degrade de gris <br>ou le brouillard de la nuit se dissipe <br>me pose l'etrange question <br>de quelle couleur est la passion <br>La passion <br><br>Blanc, comme la trace dans la craie <br>d'un animal disparu a jamais <br>laisserons nous tant de preuves <br>Sans reponse, quand l'emotion me serre la gorge <br>sans raison, monte la peur de fondre en larmes <br>comme un gosse <br><br>Et j'ai danse, danse, danse face au vent du Nord <br>et j'ai danse, danse seul, dans un monde incolore <br>Si longtemps Jusqu'a sentir sur ma peau <br>lentement <br>longuement <br>j'ai cru sentir sur ma peau <br>le bout de ses doigts <br>Le bout de tes doigts <br><br>Jaune, les eaux d'un fleuve de Chine <br>la peau d'un enfant de faience fine <br>aux amours mortes de rire <br><br>Bleu, or, une vision nouvelle <br>Devant la toile achevee <br>le modele se pose l'etrange question <br> de quelle couleur est la passion <br><br>Et j'ai danse, danse, danse face au vent du Nord <br>et j'ai danse, danse seul, dans un monde incolore <br>Si longtemps Jusqu'a sentir sur ma peau <br>Lentement <br>longuement <br>j'ai cru sentir sur ma peau <br>le bout de ses doigts <br>pleins de tendresse <br>apparaissent puis disparaissent <br>Au gre de ses caresses, je danse <br>danse <br>danse <br>danse et reve <br>dans ses reves <br><br>Comme la lle de pierre <br>de la fleur du desert <br>danse et reve <br>Un degrade de gris <br>dans la nuit se dissipe <br>Danse danse danse <br>dans ses reves <br>Dans ses reves]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Dans Ses Reves (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Dans Ses Reves (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박희정/눈을_들어_밭을_보라/</id><title>박희정 - 눈을 들어 밭을 보라 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:16:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:16:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%ED%9D%AC%EC%A0%95/%EB%88%88%EC%9D%84_%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4_%EB%B0%AD%EC%9D%84_%EB%B3%B4%EB%9D%BC/" title="박희정 - 눈을 들어 밭을 보라 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈을 들어 저기 밭을 보라 <br>익은 곡식 보라 <br>추수하게 되었도다 <br>예배하며 깨어 부르짖어 <br>주님 오실 그날 예비하는 <br>왕의 세대 <br>우리들은 육신으로 사나 <br>육신을 따라서 <br>싸우지는 아니하고 우리들의 <br>싸우는 무기는 모든 것 이기는 <br>하나님의 능력이라 <br>깨어서 기도하리라 <br>나가서 모두 외치리 <br>깨어서 기도하리라 <br>나가서 모두 외치리 <br>눈을 들어 보라 <br>주님 다시 오시리라 <br>오 영광 오 존귀 오 능력 <br>눈을 들어 보라 <br>주님 다시 오시리라 <br>오 영광 오 존귀 오 능력 주께 <br>눈을 들어 저기 밭을 보라 <br>익은 곡식 보라 <br>추수하게 되었도다 <br>예배하며 깨어 부르짖어 <br>주님 오실 그날 예비하는 <br>왕의 세대 <br>우리들은 육신으로 사나 <br>육신을 따라서 <br>싸우지는 아니하고 우리들의 <br>싸우는 무기는 모든 것 이기는 <br>하나님의 능력이라 <br>깨어서 기도하리라 <br>나가서 모두 외치리 <br>깨어서 기도하리라 <br>나가서 모두 외치리 <br>눈을 들어 보라 <br>주님 다시 오시리라 <br>오 영광 오 존귀 오 능력 <br>눈을 들어 보라 <br>주님 다시 오시리라 <br>오 영광 오 존귀 오 능력 주께 <br>기도의 향 올라가네 <br>예배의 향 올라가네 <br>기도의 향 올라가네 <br>예배의 향 올라가네 <br>기도의 향 올라가네 <br>예배의 향 올라가네 <br>기도의 향 올라가네 <br>예배의 향 올라가네 <br>눈을 들어 보라 <br>주님 다시 오시리라 <br>오 영광 오 존귀 오 능력 <br>눈을 들어 보라 <br>주님 다시 오시리라 <br>오 영광 오 존귀 오 능력 <br>눈을 들어 보라 <br>주님 다시 오시리라 <br>오 영광 오 존귀 오 능력 <br>눈을 들어 보라 <br>주님 다시 오시리라 <br>오 영광 오 존귀 오 능력 주께 <br>이때라 이때라 <br>듣는 자는 살아나리라 <br>이때라 이때라 <br>듣는 자는 살아나리라 <br>이때라 이때라 <br>듣는 자는 살아나리라 <br>이때라 이때라 <br>듣는 자는 살아나리라 <br>이때라 이때라 <br>듣는 자는 살아나리라 <br>]]></content><category term="박희정" label="박희정"/><category term="눈을 들어 밭을 보라" label="눈을 들어 밭을 보라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코다_브릿지/Lovely_Day_Feat_일나티_석환/</id><title>코다 브릿지 - Lovely Day (Feat. 일나티, 석환) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:17:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:17:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%8B%A4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/Lovely_Day_Feat_%EC%9D%BC%EB%82%98%ED%8B%B0_%EC%84%9D%ED%99%98/" title="코다 브릿지 - Lovely Day (Feat. 일나티, 석환) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 두고 집으로 넌 돌아간 뒤에 <br>허전해 아쉬움들 뿐 <br>맛있는 입술 생각나 자꾸 맘은 <br>아직도 사소한것 까지도 <br>두근거려 더 조금씩 다가와 oh baby <br>hey girl 시간이 안가 아무것도 <br>손에 잡히지 않아 그 무엇도 <br>오늘 내 관심을 끌 수 있는건 <br>하나 없어 너만이 awesome <br>시간아 가라 어서 <br>tic toc 대는 시침 내가 직접 <br>빠르게 돌리고 널 보러가고 싶어 <br>세상일 굴러가는건 I don't care <br>내 머릿속엔 너만 가득해 <br>음 오늘은 집에 가기 싫어 <br>여기 있고 싶다 둘이 <br>음 오늘은 그냥 같이있고 싶어 <br>오늘은 밤새 같이 얘기 하고싶어 아니 <br>손도 잡고 싶어 아니 입 맞추고 싶어 <br>널 만지고 싶어 <br>오늘 같이 자고 싶어 아니 <br>나를 두고 집으로 넌 돌아간 뒤에 <br>허전해 아쉬움들 뿐 <br>맛있는 입술 생각나 자꾸 맘은 <br>아직도 사소한것 까지도 <br>두근거려 더 조금씩 다가와 oh baby <br>너 일부러 그러는거지 <br>사실 모르는 것도 말이 안되지 <br>난 그냥 오늘밤엔 <br>너와 같이 있고 싶어 <br>색다른 가정법 신이 있다면 <br>너의 통금을 없애달라고 <br>나 빌어볼래 <br>간절한 바람 이뤄지는게 사실이라면 <br>너와 같은 밤 별을 세길 빌어볼게 <br>너무 부드러운 손길 ye <br>쉿 둘만 아는 비밀 um <br>너의 숨소리마져 달콤해 <br>이걸 어떡해 woo baby <br>이건 꿈이라도 좋아 ha <br>깨고 싶지 않아 ha <br>이대로 시간을 stop <br>이대로 모든걸 멈추고 싶어 <br>stop best time lovely day <br>혼자 집으로 돌아가는 길엔 <br>허전해 아쉬움만 더 <br>안고 싶어 가지고 싶어 <br>마음은 아직도 이런 널 가지고 <br>두근거려 난 doo ba baby lovely day <br>]]></content><category term="코다 브릿지" label="코다 브릿지"/><category term="Lovely Day (Feat. 일나티, 석환)" label="Lovely Day (Feat. 일나티, 석환)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코다_브릿지/조금도_아름답지_않아_Album_Mix/</id><title>코다 브릿지 - 조금도 아름답지 않아 (Album Mix) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:17:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:17:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%8B%A4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%EC%A1%B0%EA%B8%88%EB%8F%84_%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84%EB%8B%B5%EC%A7%80_%EC%95%8A%EC%95%84_Album_Mix/" title="코다 브릿지 - 조금도 아름답지 않아 (Album Mix) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어제랑 다른 말투보다 <br>지금 표정이 불안해 <br>니가 심각한 얼굴 질때마다 <br>웃으면서 피할 때 <br>평소처럼 다정한 말로 <br>항상 설래였던 표정으로 <br>우리 이쯤에서 우리 웃으면서 <br>지난 시간은 추억하자 난 <br>조금도 아름답지 않아 <br>왜 너만 그래 아름다운 <br>이별이 이별이 <br>우리 시간을 시간을 <br>하나 둘 지우는데 <br>어떻게 웃어줄 수 있겠니 <br>조금만 더 말하면 <br>울컥 쏟아질 것 같아 <br>왜 나도 괜찮을꺼라 생각해 <br>생각해 <br>두 눈을 감고 뜰때에도 <br>나의 꿈이길 바랬어 <br>어제랑 다른 이 순간에도 <br>난 너밖에 없는데 <br>내 눈물 보여 보여 <br>눈을 보고 보고 <br>넌 어떻게 그런 말을 해 <br>너만 괜찮다고 나도 웃어주면 <br>너는 좀 편하겠지 <br>조금도 아름답지 않아 <br>왜 너만 그래 아름다운 <br>이별이 이별이 <br>우리 시간을 시간을 <br>하나 둘 지우는데 <br>어떻게 웃어줄 수 있겠니 <br>조금만 더 말하면 <br>울컥 쏟아질 것 같아 <br>왜 나도 괜찮을꺼라 생각해 <br>아니라고 아니라고 <br>한번만 더 나를 생각해 <br>이런 내 마음 안다면 <br>너는 또 어땠을까 <br>거리를 걷다가 문득 <br>네 생각에 또 기대 <br>행복했던 시간이 시간이 <br>우리 흔적이 흔적이 <br>계속 눈에 보이는데 <br>하나도 아름답지 않아 <br>왜 지금도 넌 <br>이 길 어딘가 걷고 있을텐데 <br>너와 함께면 행복했을텐데 <br>]]></content><category term="코다 브릿지" label="코다 브릿지"/><category term="조금도 아름답지 않아 (Album Mix)" label="조금도 아름답지 않아 (Album Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코다_브릿지/둘이서_놀자/</id><title>코다 브릿지 - 둘이서 놀자 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:17:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:17:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%8B%A4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%EB%91%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9C_%EB%86%80%EC%9E%90/" title="코다 브릿지 - 둘이서 놀자 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너를 보면은 맘이 불편해 <br>이상하게 너만 보면은 <br>괜히 미안해 <br>baby 나도 니가 보고 싶고 <br>너의 볼도 꼬집고 <br>또 내가 먼저 다가가서 <br>먼저 말해 보고 싶어 <br>단둘이 주말에 어디든지 갈래 <br>운전은 내가 해도 돼 <br>너도 조금 쉬게 <br>너를 위해 준비한 나를 받아줘 <br>하루 종일 둘이서 놀자 <br>그냥 티비만 봐도 너무 좋아 <br>피곤하면 자고 <br>그냥 잠만 자더라도 <br>love you boy I love you baby <br>I wanna be with you oh baby <br>하루 종일 둘이서 놀자 단둘이 <br>피곤하진 않아 좀더 누워있어 <br>알아 요리할 때 좀 내가 <br>많이 섹시하지 woo <br>그렇게 웃을 때마다 <br>행복한걸 느껴 <br>이미 알고 있겠지만 <br>너를 위해 준비한 나를 안아줘 <br>하루 종일 둘이서 놀자 <br>그냥 티비만 봐도 너무 좋아 <br>피곤하면 자고 <br>그냥 잠만 자더라도 <br>love you boy I love you baby <br>I wanna be with you oh baby <br>하루 종일 둘이서 놀자 단둘이 <br>아침에 눈을 떴을 때는 <br>제일 먼저 생각이 나는 걸 <br>눈을 감으면 더 니가 보고 싶어 <br>이걸 어떻게 해 <br>오늘밤 하루 종일 둘이서 놀자 <br>그냥 티비만 봐도 너무 좋아 <br>피곤하면 자고 <br>그냥 잠만 자더라도 <br>love you boy I love you baby <br>I wanna be with you oh baby <br>하루 종일 둘이서 놀자 단둘이 <br>]]></content><category term="코다 브릿지" label="코다 브릿지"/><category term="둘이서 놀자" label="둘이서 놀자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코다_브릿지/Go_Own_Way/</id><title>코다 브릿지 - Go Own Way - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:17:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:17:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%8B%A4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/Go_Own_Way/" title="코다 브릿지 - Go Own Way - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[where I can go someday <br>ain't no other way <br>so listen to my day <br>ain't no other way <br>over again 눈이 떠지질 않아 <br>출근길 버스 안에서 또 하룰 그려 <br>이건 내 잘못이 아닌데 <br>다 내가 했대 <br>내가 제일 만만해 <br>앞에선 한마디도 못해 <br>억지로 웃어야 해 <br>오늘 꾹 참고 <br>어떻게든 견디면 <br>더 좋은 날이 오겠지 <br>내가 하고 싶은 것과 <br>해야 하는 건 너무 많이 달라 <br>내가 할 수 있는 건 <br>이겨내라 하는데 <br>왜 이리 쉽지 않아 <br>where I can go someday <br>there ain't no other way <br>난 할 수 있는데 이 길 끝에 <br>so listen to my day <br>the reason to go own way <br>웃으며 서있는 그날 <br>go own way <br>하루의 반은 회사 안에서 <br>살은 빼야 해 <br>점심엔 고픈 배를 참어 <br>종일 일에 시달리다가도 <br>저녁엔 나만의 <br>작업실에서 노래하며 <br>다시 행복할 텐데 <br>나만의 시간에 <br>새벽 3시반 <br>늦은 잠을 청할 때면 <br>나은 내일이 오겠지 <br>내가 하고 싶은 것과 <br>해야 하는 건 너무 많이 달라 <br>내가 할 수 있는 건 <br>이겨내라 하는데 <br>왜 이리 쉽지 않아 <br>where I can go someday <br>there ain't no other way <br>난 할 수 있는데 이 길 끝에 <br>so listen to my day <br>the reason to go own way <br>웃으며 서있는 그날 <br>go own way <br>니가 뭘 한다고 <br>나를 조금 안다고 <br>그렇게 해서 되겠냐고 <br>말은 쉽게 잘하고 <br>바로 어제도 <br>내가 뭘 했었는지 모르게 <br>흘러가는 하루들 안에서 <br>]]></content><category term="코다 브릿지" label="코다 브릿지"/><category term="Go Own Way" label="Go Own Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코다_브릿지/말해야_하는데/</id><title>코다 브릿지 - 말해야 하는데 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:17:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:17:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%8B%A4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%EB%A7%90%ED%95%B4%EC%95%BC_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94%EB%8D%B0/" title="코다 브릿지 - 말해야 하는데 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 그대 주위를 맴돌아요 <br>멀리서 바라만 보는 게 <br>이제는 힘이 드네요 <br>그댄 왜 몰라 줄까요 <br>나와 다른 곳을 보나요 <br>아님 내 맘 보이지 않아 그런가 봐 <br>난 그댈 보는 것 만으로 <br>가끔씩 그대 짓는 미소 만으로 <br>감사할 뿐이죠 <br>말을 해야 하는데 말하고 싶은데 <br>그대 앞에만 서면 <br>용기가 나질 않네요 <br>한걸음 다가갈수록 <br>그대와 멀어질까 봐 <br>나 오늘도 저 멀리서 <br>그댈 바라만 보네요 <br>늦은 밤 누웠을 때 <br>울리는 벨 소리도 <br>그대 이길 바라는 <br>난 왜이리 바보 같아 <br>난 그댈 보는 것 만으로 <br>가끔씩 그대 짓는 미소 만으로 <br>감사할 뿐이죠 <br>말을 해야 하는데 말하고 싶은데 <br>그대 앞에만 서면 <br>용기가 나질 않네요 <br>한걸음 다가갈수록 <br>그대와 멀어질까 봐 <br>나 오늘도 저 멀리서 <br>그댈 바라만 보네요 <br>수많은 사람 중에서 <br>내 눈엔 그대만 보여요 <br>조금만 더 그대 가까이 하고 싶어 <br>이런 내 맘 보이나요 <br>사랑하는데 <br>정말 그대뿐인데 난 <br>그대와 멀어지면 어떡하죠 난 <br>오늘도 그대 뒤에서 <br>한참을 바라보다가 <br>들리지도 않는 목소리로 <br>그댈 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="코다 브릿지" label="코다 브릿지"/><category term="말해야 하는데" label="말해야 하는데"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코다_브릿지/시간이_빼앗아/</id><title>코다 브릿지 - 시간이 빼앗아 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:17:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:17:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%8B%A4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B9%BC%EC%95%97%EC%95%84/" title="코다 브릿지 - 시간이 빼앗아 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사실은 나 알고 있었어 <br>점점 어렵기만 해 <br>의미 없이 들어주는 얘기들 <br>이렇게 내게 말 했었는지도 <br>설레였던 날들 이미 지나가고 <br>시간이 흐른 듯 네 마음마저 <br>시간이 빼앗아 가져 가려고 <br>우릴 괴롭히나 봐 <br>거울 앞에서 웃고 <br>너에게 할 말을 연습하고 <br>나를 볼 땐 니가 좋아하는 <br>옷을 보며 준비했는데 <br>넌 나를 정리 할 시간에 <br>그땐 난 널 위해 <br>다 말로 설명 안 해도 알잖아 <br>니가 필요해 <br>너무 오랜 시간 함께하다 보니 <br>소중함이 잊혀가 <br>설레였던 날들 이미 지나가고 <br>시간이 흐른 듯 네 마음마저 <br>시간이 빼앗아 가져 가려고 <br>우릴 괴롭히나 봐 <br>거울 앞에서 웃고 <br>너에게 할 말을 연습하고 <br>나를 볼 땐 니가 좋아하는 <br>옷을 보며 준비했는데 <br>넌 나를 정리 할 시간에 <br>그땐 난 널 위해 <br>매일 같은 곳을 보고 <br>잠시만 떨어져도 넌 <br>불안해 또 전화해 보고 싶다고 <br>가끔 귀찮긴 했었는데도 <br>난 그때가 행복했었는데 <br>웃어보려고 웃고 <br>억지로 눈물을 참으려고 <br>재미없는 농담을 하며 <br>관심 없는 너를 돌려보려고 <br>조금만 돌아서 달라고 <br>제발 날 위해 제발 날 위해 <br>]]></content><category term="코다 브릿지" label="코다 브릿지"/><category term="시간이 빼앗아" label="시간이 빼앗아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코다_브릿지/내맘에_놀러와/</id><title>코다 브릿지 - 내맘에 놀러와 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:17:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:17:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%8B%A4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%BF%EC%A7%80/%EB%82%B4%EB%A7%98%EC%97%90_%EB%86%80%EB%9F%AC%EC%99%80/" title="코다 브릿지 - 내맘에 놀러와 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[유난히 오늘은 걷고 싶어져 <br>우리 손잡고 걸었던 그 거리 <br>자주 가던 그 카페 <br>햇살이 내려앉아 너를 비춰줘 <br>눈이 부셔 널 못 보겠어 <br>나만 그런 거니 <br>when i see your face <br>너무 멋져 볼 때마다 설레어 내 맘 <br>and when you smile <br>가슴 터질 거 같이 오늘부터 넌 <br>내 맘에 놀러 와 내 안에 들어와 <br>너를 위해 준비한 내 마음을 느껴 <br>you are my everything fall in love <br>함께 할수록 좋은 사람 <br>I give you my love <br>두근두근해 <br>너를 보고 있을 때 baby <br>어느새 나도 모르게 <br>너의 볼에 입이 닿게 돼 <br>오늘은 단둘이만 있고 싶어져 <br>어디라도 괜찮아 둘만 함께 있는 곳 <br>when i see your face <br>너무 멋져 볼 때마다 설레 오 내 맘 <br>and when you smile <br>가슴 터질 거 같이 오늘부터 넌 <br>내 맘에 놀러 와 내 안에 들어와 <br>너를 위해 준비한 내 마음을 느껴 <br>you are my everything fall in love <br>함께 할수록 좋은 사람 <br>I give you my love <br>잘 모를 거야 <br>널 얼마나 많이 생각하는지 <br>보여주고 싶어 <br>내 안에 널 들이고 싶어 <br>내 옆에서만 지금처럼 웃어줘 <br>너만 있으면 돼 너 하나면 돼 <br>]]></content><category term="코다 브릿지" label="코다 브릿지"/><category term="내맘에 놀러와" label="내맘에 놀러와"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤태규/무정한_사람/</id><title>윤태규 - 무정한 사람 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:17:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:17:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%ED%83%9C%EA%B7%9C/%EB%AC%B4%EC%A0%95%ED%95%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C/" title="윤태규 - 무정한 사람 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑한다고 나만을 사랑한다고 <br>믿어달라는 말만 해놓고 <br>속절없이 기다리는 내맘 아나요 <br>아 당신 무정한 사람 <br>미련 없이 떠날 거라면 <br>그 흔한 정이나 주지말지 <br>줄 듯 말듯 애만 태우다 <br>그렇게 가는 건가요 <br>바보처럼 기다리지는 <br>않을 겁니다 <br>아 당신 무정한사람 <br>오직 나만을 나만을 사랑한다고 <br>믿어달라는 말만 해놓고 <br>속도 없이 울고있는 내맘 아나요 <br>아 당신 무정한 사람 <br>냉정하게 떠날 거라면 <br>그 흔한 정이나 주지말지 <br>줄듯말듯 애만 태우다 <br>그렇게 가는 건가요 <br>바보처럼 기다리지는 <br>않을 겁니다 <br>아 당신 무정한사람 <br>바보처럼 기다리지는 <br>않을 겁니다 <br>아 당신 무정한사람 <br>]]></content><category term="윤태규" label="윤태규"/><category term="무정한 사람" label="무정한 사람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Northern_Ghost/Deathwish/</id><title>Northern Ghost - Deathwish - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:19:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:19:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Northern_Ghost/Deathwish/" title="Northern Ghost - Deathwish - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm covered in scars <br>Deeper than an ocean <br>We bury the truth as a notion <br>But all these faceless bodies <br>Tell me what I need to know <br><br>I walk the halls of regret <br>With no end in sight, it's not over yet <br>We all change when the sun goes down <br><br>It's funny we see things <br>So different in the dark <br>It's funny how life works <br>When everything falls apart <br>Yeah, yeah <br><br>So this is what it's like to die <br>To be on the other side <br>I'm afraid that I won't catch you <br>Is it God Is it me <br>Who's controlling everything <br>Does it matter when I'm begging for a deathwish <br>Deathwish, deathwish <br><br>Pull me under cause I'm not the same <br>And I'm not the way they want me to be <br>Is this the only thing you seem to notice <br>Give me my mind <br>Give me back my mistakes <br><br>So this is what it's like to die <br>To be on the other side <br>I'm afraid that I won't catch you <br>Is it God Is it me <br>Who's controlling everything <br>Does it matter when I'm begging for a deathwish <br>Deathwish, deathwish <br><br>I think I need a priest to exercise what's in my head <br>He took a look at me and told me <br>I'm already dead <br>Hey Hey Hey <br><br>So this is what it's like to die <br>To be on the other side <br>I'm afraid that I won't catch you <br>Is it God Is it me <br>Who's controlling everything <br>Does it matter when I'm begging for a deathwish <br>Deathwish, deathwish <br>So this is what it's like to die <br>To be on the other side <br>I'm afraid that I won't catch you <br>Is it God Is it me <br>Who's controlling everything <br>Does it matter when I'm begging for a deathwish <br>Deathwish, deathwish <br><br>Searching and searching for a deathwish <br>But something inside is telling me I can't quit <br>Drag my body, drag my body <br>Bring me back to life]]></content><category term="Northern Ghost" label="Northern Ghost"/><category term="Deathwish" label="Deathwish"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OneInThe4Rest/Jiu_Jitsu_Feat_Chris_Brown/</id><title>OneInThe4Rest - Jiu Jitsu (Feat. Chris Brown) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:19:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:19:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OneInThe4Rest/Jiu_Jitsu_Feat_Chris_Brown/" title="OneInThe4Rest - Jiu Jitsu (Feat. Chris Brown) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[That juju, oh yeah <br><br>Oh, when the spotlight hits you, oh, nah, nah, nah <br>I need Jiu like Jitsu, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>When the spotlight hits you, oh, nah, nah, nah <br>I need Jiu like Jitsu <br><br>I need Jiu like Jitsu <br>I see you in the club, I miss you <br>Every other time I see you <br>You be in a dress that's see through <br>Girl, you know a nigga been balling <br>And the only shot I miss is you <br>Girl, you know you hear me calling <br>Girl, you know you hear me calling you <br>Girl, won't you say something <br>Got me out here waiting <br>Got me losing all my patience <br>Got me out here about to break something <br>Girl, won't you say something <br>Got me out here waiting <br>Got me losing all my patience <br>Got me out here about to break something <br><br>You know, when the spotlight hits you, oh, nah, nah, nah <br>I need Jiu like Jitsu, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>When the spotlight hits you, oh, nah, nah, nah <br>I need Jiu like Jitsu <br>Oh, nah, nah, nah <br>When the spotlight hits you <br>Oh, nah, nah, nah <br>I need Jiu like Jitsu, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>When the spotlight hits you, oh, nah, nah, nah <br>I need Jiu like Jitsu <br><br>Took them naked pictures, better give me my photo credit <br>Body perfect, but I know you shy <br>Fuck a filter, you don't need an edit <br>Picture perfect for me every time <br>Let the flashes hit you <br>Please girl, don't act different <br>'Cause I'm gonna be right there with you <br>And you know I'm the type to get ignorant <br>Girl, won't you say something <br>If it's too bright, put your shades on <br>Red carpet, yo outfit gone slay 'em <br>Now look at everybody hating <br>Don't even say nothing <br>Don't even sweat it you number one <br>These bitches ain't even runner ups <br>You got me out here about to break something <br><br>You know, when the spotlight hits you, oh, nah, nah, nahspotlight hits you <br>I need Jiu like Jitsu, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah you, you, you <br>When the spotlight hits you, oh, nah, nah, nah get you spotlighted <br>I need Jiu like Jitsu <br>Oh, nah, nah, nah <br>When the spotlight hits you <br>Oh, nah, nah, nah <br>I need Jiu like Jitsu, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>When the spotlight hits you, oh, nah, nah, nah <br>I need Jiu like Jitsu]]></content><category term="OneInThe4Rest" label="OneInThe4Rest"/><category term="Jiu Jitsu (Feat. Chris Brown)" label="Jiu Jitsu (Feat. Chris Brown)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/서온/그네/</id><title>서온 - 그네 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:20:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:20:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%84%9C%EC%98%A8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%84%A4/" title="서온 - 그네 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 나를 밀지 마요 <br>그대 나를 밀지 마요 <br>나는 이미 그네에 올라타 <br>내릴 수 없어요 <br>그대 나를 밀지 마요 <br>그대 나를 밀지 마요 <br>나는 이미 그네에 올라타 <br>내릴 수 없어요 <br>그댄 어차피 나를 보지 못하죠 <br>내 뒷모습으로 그대에게 <br>아무것도 말할 수 없겠죠 <br>그대 나를 밀지 마요 <br>그대 나를 밀지 마요 <br>나는 이미 그네에 올라타 <br>내릴 수 없어요 <br>그댄 어차피 나를 보지 못하죠 <br>내 뒷모습으로 그대에게 <br>아무것도 말할 수 없겠죠 <br>그대 나를 밀지 마요 <br>그대 나를 밀지 마요 <br>내 뒷모습으로 그대에게 <br>아무것도 말할 수 없겠죠 <br>그대 나를 밀지 마요 <br>그대 나를 밀지 마요 <br>내 뒷모습으로 그대에게 <br>아무것도 말할 수 없겠죠 <br>]]></content><category term="서온" label="서온"/><category term="그네" label="그네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/배다해/알아_Inst/</id><title>배다해 - 알아 (Inst.) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:20:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:20:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B0%EB%8B%A4%ED%95%B4/%EC%95%8C%EC%95%84_Inst/" title="배다해 - 알아 (Inst.) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알아 날 잊어버린걸 <br>넌 어찌 그리 쉽게 지우니 <br>알아 돌아 올 수 없는걸 <br>하지만 난 천천히 지울게 <br>알아 눈물이 흐르면 <br>기억이 녹을까 봐서 <br>난 계속 울고 있어 <br>자꾸 울다 보면 <br>니가 모두 녹을까 봐 <br>우리에게 시간은 모두다 <br>잘못 흘러 여기로 왔네요 <br>알겠어요 우리들은 <br>처음부터 잘못된 사랑을 몰랐죠 <br>알아 눈물이 흐르면 <br>기억이 녹을까 봐서 <br>난 계속 울고 있어 <br>자꾸 울다 보면 <br>니가 모두 녹을까 봐 <br>우리에게 시간은 모두다 <br>잘못 흘러 여기로 왔네요 <br>알겠어요 우리들은 <br>처음부터 잘못된 사랑을 <br>우리에게 시간은 모두다 <br>잘못 흘러 여기로 왔네요 <br>알겠어요 우리들은 <br>처음부터 잘못된 사랑을 <br>몰랐죠 <br>]]></content><category term="배다해" label="배다해"/><category term="알아 (Inst.)" label="알아 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/배다해/알아/</id><title>배다해 - 알아 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:20:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:20:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B0%EB%8B%A4%ED%95%B4/%EC%95%8C%EC%95%84/" title="배다해 - 알아 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알아 날 잊어버린걸 <br>넌 어찌 그리 쉽게 지우니 <br>알아 돌아 올 수 없는걸 <br>하지만 난 천천히 지울게 <br>알아 눈물이 흐르면 <br>기억이 녹을까 봐서 <br>난 계속 울고 있어 <br>자꾸 울다 보면 <br>니가 모두 녹을까 봐 <br>우리에게 시간은 모두다 <br>잘못 흘러 여기로 왔네요 <br>알겠어요 우리들은 <br>처음부터 잘못된 사랑을 몰랐죠 <br>알아 눈물이 흐르면 <br>기억이 녹을까 봐서 <br>난 계속 울고 있어 <br>자꾸 울다 보면 <br>니가 모두 녹을까 봐 <br>우리에게 시간은 모두다 <br>잘못 흘러 여기로 왔네요 <br>알겠어요 우리들은 <br>처음부터 잘못된 사랑을 <br>우리에게 시간은 모두다 <br>잘못 흘러 여기로 왔네요 <br>알겠어요 우리들은 <br>처음부터 잘못된 사랑을 <br>몰랐죠 <br>]]></content><category term="배다해" label="배다해"/><category term="알아" label="알아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/멜로우독/건대입구/</id><title>멜로우독 - 건대입구 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:20:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:20:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%EB%8F%85/%EA%B1%B4%EB%8C%80%EC%9E%85%EA%B5%AC/" title="멜로우독 - 건대입구 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔 거리를 걷다가 <br>문득 느껴지는 시선에 <br>두리번거릴 때가 있죠 <br>우리 함께 앉던 자리에 <br>추억이랑 단둘이 남아서 <br>긴 한숨 쉴 때가 있죠 <br>잘 지내니 <br>혹시 너도 나와 거릴 걸었니 <br>난 아직까지 너를 못 잊고 여기 <br>다 잊었니 <br>같이 그려왔던 꿈도 지웠니 <br>난 너에 대한 그리움으로 살아 <br>곁에 있을 때는 몰랐던 <br>작고 여렸었던 네 맘을 <br>난 홀로 그리워하고 <br>네가 내게 준 그 사랑에 <br>무게를 이제서야 알았고 <br>뒤늦은 후회를 하네 <br>잘 지내니 <br>혹시 아직도 나를 원망하니 <br>너 떠난 뒤에 많이 아팠어 난 <br>다 잊었니 <br>내 곁에서 많이 힘들었니 <br>난 너에 대한 그리움으로 살아 <br>같은 시간 같은 공간 다른 모습으로 <br>서로를 지워가겠지 <br>잘 지내니 <br>아픈 상처는 모두 지운 거니 <br>난 아직까지 너를 그리며 살아 <br>넌 잊었니 <br>사랑했을 때 우리의 시간들 <br>서로를 바라봤던 그날을 <br>가끔 거리를 걷다 <br>]]></content><category term="멜로우독" label="멜로우독"/><category term="건대입구" label="건대입구"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/멜로우독/그만_만나요/</id><title>멜로우독 - 그만 만나요 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:20:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:20:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A9%9C%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B0%EB%8F%85/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A7%8C_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94/" title="멜로우독 - 그만 만나요 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊을 만 하면 또 다시 <br>잠든 창가에 그려지고 <br>졸린 두 눈을 감아 보아도 <br>선명한 너의 미소가 <br>벌써 밖은 따스한 봄이 왔죠 <br>그 거리엔 또 꽃이 피겠죠 <br>내 마음엔 언제쯤 봄이 오나요 <br>내게도 따스한 바람은 부는데 <br>자꾸 멀어지려 말아요 <br>내게 상처 주지 말아요 <br>네게도 당신이 필요 한 거죠 <br>한발 다가간 것뿐인데 <br>그저 곁에 있을 뿐인데 <br>내겐 뒷모습만 보여 주네요 <br>벌써 밖은 따스한 봄이 왔죠 <br>당신 만난 그 계절인 거죠 <br>내 마음엔 언제쯤 님이 오나요 <br>코끝에 향기가 또 설레게 하죠 <br>자꾸 멀어지려 말아요 <br>내게 상처 주지 말아요 <br>네게도 당신이 필요한 거죠 <br>한발 다가간 것뿐인데 <br>그저 곁에 있을 뿐인데 <br>내겐 뒷모습만 보여 주네요 <br>라랄라 랄라라 <br>당신을 보고 있으면 <br>라랄라 랄라라 <br>난 그저 웃기만 하죠 <br>라랄라 랄라라 <br>내 맘은 그게 아니라 <br>난 또 다시 거짓말을 하죠 <br>우리 이제 그만 만나요 <br>더 이상은 미련한 거죠 <br>당신을 만날수록 더 아파요 <br>내게 잘 해 주지 말아요 <br>내게 미안해 하지 마요 <br>이제는 내가 뒤돌아 갈게요 <br>이제는 내가 그댈 지울게요 <br>우리 이제 그만 만나요 <br>]]></content><category term="멜로우독" label="멜로우독"/><category term="그만 만나요" label="그만 만나요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/포레스트/All_the_time/</id><title>포레스트 - All the time - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:20:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:20:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8F%AC%EB%A0%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8/All_the_time/" title="포레스트 - All the time - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[la la la la la la la <br>la la la la la la la <br>la la la la la la la la la la <br>la la la la la <br>la la la la la la la <br>la la la la la la la <br>la la la la la la la la la la <br>la la la la la <br>baby all the time <br>you make me shine <br>baby all the time <br>you make me proud <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>baby all the time <br>you make me shine <br>baby all the time <br>you make me proud <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>지금 당장이라도 <br>난 너에게 달려갈게 <br>I'm falling love <br>고개는 falling down <br>시간을 거꾸로 되돌려 봤지 <br>all the time <br>그 동안 내가 떨어지기 전에 <br>또는 멀어지기 전에 <br>넌 시계처럼 내 손목을 꽉 <br>쥐고 놓질 않던 <br>너의 늘 차분한 떨림 <br>그걸 느낄 때면 <br>내 마음은 가벼워 졌지 <br>허나 넌 깨버렸어 <br>내 삶의 따분한 rolling <br>널 데려가고 싶어 <br>생각보다도 더 멀리 <br>지금 내가 널 만나러 <br>나간 거리는 로데오 <br>오늘 내 머리스타일의 <br>컨셉은 5대5 <br>흑과 백인 세상의 <br>너라는 오레오 <br>처럼 달콤하길 <br>바라지 말야 이 노래도 <br>I wish <br>이 세상엔 영원한 것은 없어 <br>everywhere <br>허나 세상에 <br>너만한 건 없어 baby <br>널 만나러 갈 땐 <br>이 모든걸 잊지 않고 <br>널 만나러 갈게 <br>baby all the time <br>you make me shine <br>baby all the time <br>you make me proud <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>baby all the time <br>you make me shine <br>baby all the time <br>you make me proud <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>지금 당장이라도 <br>난 너에게 달려갈게 <br>오늘밤 끝나지 않을 것 같던 <br>하루에 지친 <br>둥근 달 아래 <br>너라는 생각에 별표 치지 <br>물론 그 달 아래서 널 찾고 있어 <br>어디에 있는지 내게 말을 해줘 <br>지금 너의 위치 <br>Baby all the time <br>일루와 my baby <br>오붓한 낭만을 꿈꿔 <br>널 위해 준비한 pan cake <br>You make me shine <br>갚아줄게 난 백배 <br>매일매일 다른 날에 <br>널 위한 내가 될게 <br>우린 보폭을 맞춘 <br>가벼운 걸음걸이 <br>이 거릴 온통 <br>무지개 색으로 물들였지 <br>눈은 번쩍거리고 올려다본 <br>하늘의 해는 저물고 있어 <br>아무런 예고도 없이 <br>이런 밤마다 최선을 다해 <br>널 알고 싶고 <br>이러다 자연스럽게 <br>난 너의 속도 알고 싶어 <br>불어난 행복이 <br>어쩔 땐 좀 불안해도 <br>지금 이런 상상을 <br>할 수 있단 게 기뻐 <br>I wanna go 난 지금 무진장 <br>애타게 너를 찾고 있어 바로 do it now <br>because oh oh oh oh oh <br>oh oh oh oh oh <br>I wanna go 난 지금 무진장 <br>애타게 너를 찾고 있어 바로 do it now <br>왜냐면 넌 내가 고개를 숙인 밤 <br>날 위해 웃어주는 <br>유일한 내 stupid right <br>baby all the time <br>you make me shine <br>baby all the time <br>you make me proud <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>baby all the time <br>you make me shine <br>baby all the time <br>you make me proud <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>지금 당장이라도 <br>난 너에게 달려갈게 <br>baby all the time <br>you make me shine <br>baby all the time <br>you make me proud <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>baby all the time <br>you make me shine <br>baby all the time <br>you make me proud <br>딱 그 지금처럼만 있어 <br>지금 당장이라도 <br>난 너에게 달려갈게 <br>]]></content><category term="포레스트" label="포레스트"/><category term="All the time" label="All the time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이규진/꽃샘추위/</id><title>이규진 - 꽃샘추위 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:20:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:20:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EA%B7%9C%EC%A7%84/%EA%BD%83%EC%83%98%EC%B6%94%EC%9C%84/" title="이규진 - 꽃샘추위 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길 거리를 걷다 보면 <br>주변에 커플만 수둑해 <br>나도 추운 눈 녹이는 <br>햇살처럼 따뜻하고 파 <br>우울해져 <br>사람들은 다 봄을 타는데 <br>왜 나 혼자 겨울인 거야 <br>꽃샘추위가 나를 시리게 만들어 <br>꽃샘추위가 나를 외롭게 만들어 <br>입김을 불어도 따뜻한 차를 마셔도 <br>옆구리는 채워지질 않아 <br>또 니 생각이 나를 슬프게 만들어 <br>또 니 생각이 나를 아프게 만들어 <br>니 사진을 봐도 널 떠올려도 <br>내 맘은 녹아지지 않아 <br>꽃샘추위야 <br>커플 그게 뭐야 <br>혼자도 충분해 <br>쎈척해도 사실 아니지 <br>허전한 기분은 생각보다 <br>쉽게 무뎌지질 않나 봐 <br>쓸쓸해져 <br>사람들은 다 봄을 타는데 <br>왜 나 혼자 겨울인 거야 <br>꽃샘추위가 나를 시리게 만들어 <br>꽃샘추위가 나를 외롭게 만들어 <br>입김을 불어도 따뜻한 차를 마셔도 <br>옆구리는 채워지질 않아 <br>또 니 생각이 나를 슬프게 만들어 <br>또 니 생각이 나를 아프게 만들어 <br>니 사진을 봐도 널 떠올려도 <br>내 맘은 녹아지지 않아 <br>꽃샘추위야 <br>사실 춥지 않아 <br>날씨는 화창한데 <br>나 혼자 춥게 느끼는 거야 <br>너무나 외로워서 <br>너무나 그리워서 <br>맘속이 아리나 봐 <br>꽃샘추위가 나를 시리게 만들어 <br>꽃샘추위가 나를 외롭게 만들어 <br>입김을 불어도 따뜻한 차를 마셔도 <br>옆구리는 채워지지 않아 <br>또 니 생각이 나를 슬프게 만들어 <br>또 니 생각이 나를 아프게 만들어 <br>니 사진을 봐도 널 떠올려도 <br>내 맘은 녹아지질 않아 <br>꽃샘추위야 <br>]]></content><category term="이규진" label="이규진"/><category term="꽃샘추위" label="꽃샘추위"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Strikes_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Strikes (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Strikes_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Strikes (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No noise nor silence <br>but echoes of violence <br><br>Always on the search for any stranger's hand <br>reaching down to me take from the quicksands <br>The mud's too slippery, my fingers couldn't grope <br>I allowed myself to sink by cowardice and sloth <br><br>Because I thought that I was dreaming <br>I found myself crushed in a Schiele's Embrace <br>in security, crucified on its picture frame <br><br>I was shooting so high <br>and diving so low <br>shooting so high <br>diving so low <br><br>Someone came and broke the glass to pieces <br>changed the rythm, set the insect free <br><br>from its stiff attitude into a waving misery <br>something like a slug <br><br>Always on the search for an ultimate hand <br>to put me back in my picture frame <br><br>My life drags on between the light and shade <br>of the electric tones of my TV set <br>I'm dragging on and on between the light and shade <br>I'm never too close to the receding screen <br>but always too far from a new color scheme <br>I'm running on and on wild and wild in an endless line <br><br>I was shooting so high <br>and diving so low <br>shootinf so high <br>diving so low <br>I did it slow <br><br>Put me in my picture frame, leave me in my own embrace <br>put me in my picture frame <br>and leave my own embrace]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Strikes (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Strikes (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Sans_Memoire_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Sans Memoire (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Sans_Memoire_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Sans Memoire (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dans le brouillard des idees vagues <br>sans larme ni un regard <br>Effacee, la plus petite trace d'avant hier, sans un regret <br><br>Au hasard seul, en quete d'un sanctuaire <br>que desormais ses mains s'apaisent <br>Garder les levres closes <br>lorsque s'annonce si proche <br>la metamorphose <br>Les entrepots en ruine a l'est du port, de longs corridors <br>Les couloirs deserts ou se traine l'insecte solitaire <br>Et prier dans le noir <br>pour rester sans memoire <br>Je suis le meme, tu sais <br>Rien n'a vraiment change <br>Toujours le meme, tu sais <br>tout pres, tout pres de tout recommencer <br>Et la craie laisse sur mon imper <br>M pour Meurtre, pour Misere <br>La preuve que la plaie reste ouverte <br>S'asseoir la, ne plus rien faire <br>ne rien dire, juste se taire <br>Au hasard seul en quete d'un sanctuaire <br>le calme d'un moulage mortuaire <br>Garder les levres closes <br>lorsque s'annonce l'aube <br>Je suis le meme, tu sais <br>Rien n'a vraiment change <br>Toujours le meme, tu sais <br>Tout pres, tout pres de tout recommencer <br>Le chant des enfants morts <br>hier un jeu de courtes lames <br>Le chant des enfants morts <br>hier Berkert, Ann Beckmann <br>Le chant des enfants morts <br>hier <br>une priere <br>pour rester sans memoire]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Sans Memoire (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Sans Memoire (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Dont_Fall_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Don`t Fall (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Dont_Fall_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Don`t Fall (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't fall <br>The morning rain removed the stains <br>don't fall <br><br>The morning light chased the rain <br>don't fall <br>in love with <br>in love woth her <br>don't fall <br><br>The halls were filled with hissing ghosts <br>don't fall again <br>right into sweet illusions traps <br>don't fall again <br>in love with past <br>in love with traps <br>I fall <br><br>And the same old vision dressed in the past <br>don't call it <br>It won't be back for a long time <br>don't fall again <br>in love with pictures <br>in love forever <br>I fall <br><br>I hold on to her pretty face <br>there is nothing else to think about <br>I hang on to her pretty arms <br>there is nothing else to do to night <br>To night <br>I fall <br><br>Wake up to the real thing, don't fall asleep <br>Her smell, her taste, they linger on in vain <br><br>Wake up to the real thing, don't fall asleep <br>Someday, someone will call your name again <br><br>I hold on to my idle frights <br>there is nothing else to think about <br>I fall]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Don`t Fall (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Don`t Fall (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Sylvie_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Sylvie (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Sylvie_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Sylvie (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sur un fil en equilibre, et le vide sous ses pieds <br>Il est tombe par erreur dans les bras de celle qui passait par la <br><br>par hasard <br>reunis sous la pluie <br>Par manque d'espoir on se laisse toujours faire <br><br>Sylvie si seulement Sylvie si seulement Sylvie <br>avait fui dans la nuit <br><br>Marc n'a plus la meme allure, il apparait si sur <br>Aucun souffle, aucun remous <br>ne vient rider la surface tranquille <br>du bonheur <br>Il etouffe, trop d'amour <br>Et de nouveau se sentir prisonnier <br><br>Sylvie si seulement Sylvie si seulement Sylvie <br><br>Je sais, mes images sont faibles et mes mots trop naifs <br>Tout juste bon a fredonner les memes rengaines <br> la solitude me pese, la vie a deux m'oppresse <br>Ni tragique, ni comique <br>je ne sais plus, je ne sais rien <br>mais je crois, j'ai besoin de toi <br><br>Sylvie si seulement Sylvie si seulement Sylvie <br>est partie dans la nuit <br><br>Les lames s'emoussent <br>meme le plus bel acier rouille par abandon <br>Et de funambule tres vite on devient somnambule <br>sans y faire attention <br>Alors les heures s'ecoulent, un lent goutte a goutte <br>de longues secondes tombent et l'eclaboussent <br>Les yeux fixes sur la porte refermee <br>Marc est la, tout juste bon sans cesse a repeter <br><br>Sylvie si seulement Sylvie si seulement Sylvie <br>etait restee dans sa vie]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Sylvie (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Sylvie (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Personnalities_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Personnalities (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Personnalities_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Personnalities (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Leave me, love me <br>leave me something <br><br>Something to believe in <br>a word to repeat to the walls <br>that enclosed my world <br>any word <br>Up from the start, I swear <br>I suspected the worst <br>Facts didn't disappoint me <br>I always acted like a whore <br>So now the time has come <br>to pay the price of crimes <br>of never giving anything <br>of always begging on my knees <br>for a <br>personality <br>as bright as yours <br><br>Leave me, love me <br>leave me something <br>Anything you please <br>a word, a curse <br>a sword, a nurse <br>To tell me how to join <br>the creatures of the twilight zone <br><br>So now the time has come <br>to pay the price of crimes <br>but all the bites on my skin <br>were like to play at hide and seek <br>It's a strange game with yourself <br>when you're pulling out your eyes <br>without no suffer and no pain <br>the pressure's got a bit too high <br>for a <br>personality <br>on the border <br>personality personality <br>personelity out of order <br>now fading away <br><br>I'm fed up with screaming <br>now I'm whispering <br>like the chirpings of the birds <br>like the leaves on the trees <br><br>But remember the child <br>lost in the white room <br>No strength left to die <br>No strength left to survive <br><br>You were wrong, you were wrong <br>to try to change him into another personallity <br>oh change <br>oh change me <br>Creatures of the twilight zone <br>Creatures of the twilight zone <br>Creatures of the twilight zone personalities <br>Creatures of the twilight zone PERSONALITIES <br>Personalities <br>Personalities]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Personnalities (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Personnalities (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Surabaya_Johnny_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Surabaya Johnny (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Surabaya_Johnny_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Surabaya Johnny (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was young, I was just sixteen then <br>when you came up from Burma one day <br>And you told me to pack up my suitcase <br><br>and I did, and you took me away <br>I said, Do you work nice and steady <br>or do you go sailing and roving out to sea <br>And you said, I have a job on the railroad <br>and baby, how swell it's all gonna be <br>You said a lot, Johnny It was all lies <br>You sure had me fooled, right from the start <br>I hate you when you laugh at me like that <br>Take that pipe out of your mouth, Johnny <br><br>Surabaya Johnny Is it really the end <br>SurabayaJohnny Will the hurt ever mend <br>Surabaya Johnny Ooh, I burn at your touch <br>You got no heart, Johnny, but oh, I love you so much <br><br>Thought at first you were kind and gentle <br>'til I packed up and went off with you <br>And it lasted two weeks until one day <br>you laughed at me and hit me too <br>You dragged me all over the city <br>up the river and down to the sea <br>Now I look at myself in the mirror <br>and some old woman looks back at me <br>You didn't want love, Johnny, you wanted money <br>I gave you all I had You wanted more <br>Oh, don't look at me that way <br>I'm only trying to talk to you <br>Wipe that grin off your face, Johnny <br>&gt;Surabaya Johnny Is it really the end <br>SurabayaJohnny Will the pain never mend <br>Surabaya Johnny How I burn at your touch <br>You got no heart, Johnny, but oh, I love you so much <br><br>When we met I forgot to ask you <br>why they called you that funny name <br>but in every hotel on the seacoast <br>I found out, and I loved you all the same <br>I'm tired I'm worn out <br>The sea's pounding in my ears <br>And I reach out my arms to hold you <br>You're not here and who even cares <br>You got no heart, Johnny You're just no good <br>You going now Oh, tell me why <br>I love you after all, Johnny, like that very first day <br>Don't laugh at me no more, Johnny <br><br>Surabaya Johnny Is it really the end <br>SurabayaJohnny Will the hurt ever mend <br>Surabaya Johnny Oh, I burn at your touch <br>You got no heart, Johnny, but oh, I love you <br>I love you, I love you so much]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Surabaya Johnny (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Surabaya Johnny (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Jour_Apres_Jour_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Jour Apres Jour (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Jour_Apres_Jour_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Jour Apres Jour (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jour apres jour de verre en verre <br>et puis de bars de nuit en d'autres verres <br><br>Les reves s'evanouissent sans bruit <br>au bout d'un comptoir ivre d'ennui <br>ivre de vin, ne plus se mordre les mains <br><br>Tourne et tourne, a l'envers, a l'endroit <br>dans des draps sans odeur qui restent toujours froids <br>Me detourne, me retourne, a l'etroit, mal a l'aise <br>dans des bras sans chaleur qui restent toujours raides <br><br>Le rythme regulier des vagues <br>ne t'a jamais emmene nulle part <br>Ces maigres filles que tu entraines <br>dans des hotels de bord de mer <br>pour un naufrage en solitaire <br><br>En rage d'en etre encore la <br>toujours au meme endroit <br>Sans attache, mais toujours la <br>ancre au meme endroit du rivage <br>un grain de sable <br><br>Le sable qui coule entre mes mains <br>sur cette plage, j'espere, enfin <br>que la maree vienne et m'emmene plus loin <br><br>Tourne et tourne, a l'endroit, a l'envers <br>dans des bras sans chaleur qui restent toujours raides <br>Me detourne, me retourne, a l'etroit, mal a l'aise <br>dans le flux d'une ecume trop legere <br><br>Et tu enrages d'etre encore <br>toujours au meme endroit de la greve <br>Sans attache mais toujours la <br>ancre au meme endroit Que se leve <br>le vent du large]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Jour Apres Jour (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Jour Apres Jour (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Revanche_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Revanche (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Revanche_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Revanche (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Elle, elle rit pour un rien <br>Des heures, des heures le fou rire l'etreint <br>Les mains offertes aux pluies de sel du desert <br><br>Elle rit SANS FIN NI CESSE dans l'air acide <br>Et pierre a pierre elle releve les ruines <br>Du mur, ce mur que la nuit detruit <br>VIEILLIR, dit elle <br>Ensemble, en silence, sans mystere <br>Faire une victoire de nos defaites <br>Et perdre nos memoires en mer <br>Pleure, pleure pour moi <br>Moi, je meurs en toi <br>Oh leurre, leurre moi <br>Moi, je me rends ou tu vas <br>Tout en toi <br>Elle se retourne <br>Elle traine au pied ma chaine lourde <br>Un jour d'orage, de rage sourde <br>En vrille s'enroulera LA FOUDRE <br>Pleure, pleure pour moi <br>Moi, je meurs en toi <br>Oh leurre oui leurre moi <br>Mais moi, je meurs en toi <br>Les yeux dans les yeux <br>A chaque pas plus vieux <br>A chaque larme, la peur <br>De se perdre PETITE SoeUR <br>Le temps nous manque <br>Le temps nous mange <br>Le temps nous change <br>Petite soeur <br>Le temps d'attendre <br>Le temps d'apprendre <br>Le temps nous manque <br>LA TENDRESSE nous venge <br>Douce, douce revanche Mmmmm]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Revanche (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Revanche (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Le_Blues_Du_Serpent_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Le Blues Du Serpent (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Le_Blues_Du_Serpent_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Le Blues Du Serpent (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Le blues du serpent <br>C'est pas le train du soir <br>C'est pas le serpent noir <br>Qui chantent pour nous entre chien and loup <br>Un vieux fantome est de retour <br>Billy Holliday feule le blues <br><br>La voix nonchalante, lointaine et trainante <br>La voix languissante comme teintee de cendre <br>Une brume d'alcool voile sa gorge <br>Les mots s'arretent au bord des levres <br>Dechirent le cercle de lumiere <br>Et frappent les hommes sans paroles <br><br>C'est pas la plainte du serpent noir <br>C'est pas le train dans le soir <br>Le long desespoir <br><br>Blanc, l'amour trop grand <br>Blanc, l'aveuglement <br>De gardenias en came blanche <br>Noir, les fruits etranges <br>Noir, le bruit des branches <br>Les corps dans les arbres s'en balancent <br>Quand la deprime se met en scene <br>Dans les cabarets de la ville <br>Elle sourit quoiqu'il advienne <br>Sa vie, la vraie, est en coulisse <br><br>C'est pas la plainte du serpent noir <br>C'est pas le train dans le soir <br>Le long desespoir <br>Roule, roule sur les planches <br>Tourne, tourne la chance <br>Et sous les ailes d'un corbeau <br>Dans un hotel tout la haut <br><br>A l'heure ou l'Uptown House eteint <br>La magie d'une robe de satin <br>Elle rentre a l'hotel sans un bruit <br>Et jette un long, long retard a son lit <br><br>C'est pas la plainte du serpent noir <br>C'est pas le train dans le soir <br>Le long desespoir <br>Sur la chaine de sa montre <br>J'ai pose un dollar en or <br>Et je veille sur sa tombe <br><br>Let'Roll Let's Roll <br>I'm just an old graveyard ghost <br>I'm just an old graveyard ghost <br>And THE BLACK SNAKE MOAN]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Le Blues Du Serpent (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Le Blues Du Serpent (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Un_Homme_Marche_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Un Homme Marche (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Un_Homme_Marche_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Un Homme Marche (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Si cette forme au loin est un homme <br>Les temps sont ils revenus <br>De sortir de l'automne <br><br>Et de partir vers l'inconnu <br>Si cette forme la bas est un homme <br>Un fleuve s'eveille en amont <br>Les douze tribus de l'ombre <br><br>Mon pere, ouvre lui la porte <br>Voici l'homme en chemin <br>Ouvre la porte <br>L'OURAL est encore loin <br><br>Voici l'homme <br>L'homme debout, l'homme d'argile <br>Voici l'homme <br>Golem aux pieds fragiles <br>En lui souffle l'esprit Israel <br>En lui coule la tenebre dans la veine <br><br>Mon pere, ouvre lui la porte <br>Voici l'homme en chemin <br>Ouvre la porte <br>L'OURAL est encore loin <br>Voici l'homme de la jihad <br>Voici l'homme de la Sohah <br>Les tours de Babel montent and levent le front <br>Les tribus rebelles vibrent a l'unisson <br>Les tours de Babel montent and levent le front <br>and s'effondrent <br>Les tribus rebelles se lient a l'horizon <br>and s'affrontent <br>Hey Chante moi l'HYMNE A LA JOIE <br>c'est comme un coeur qui bat c'est comme un coeur qui bat <br>mais c'est un homme qui marche <br><br>VOICI L'HOMME <br>Et s'il parle trop fort <br>VOICI L'HOMME <br>S'il couve le bruit des bottes <br>Sous les battements sourds <br>De ce coeur qui s'embrase <br>Cette forme fragile <br><br>Qui avance, timide <br>Pas de doute <br>Lui aussi c'est un homme <br>Et lui si c'est un homme <br>Et lui si c'est un homme <br>SI C'EST UN HOMME <br>C'est un homme]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Un Homme Marche (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Un Homme Marche (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Ligne_De_Fuite_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Ligne De Fuite (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:26:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:26:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Ligne_De_Fuite_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Ligne De Fuite (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lignes de fuites Dechirure Perspectives L'avenir en friche <br><br>Un chasse croise de lignes brisees <br><br>Ouvre la blessure <br>Ad nauseam brule dans l'embrasure <br>Plaisir ou peine, amour and haine s'ils persistent and signent <br>Sous la pluie deteignent et s'adoucissent <br>Sous la pluie s'etreignent and de nouveau s'unissent <br><br>Les souvenirs, hier, tout de suite <br>Retour a l'enfance la ligne de fuite <br><br>Un battement de cils pris sur le vif <br>L'oiseau en plein vol <br>Un instant derobe a la mort <br>Un instant epingle sur un morceau de roche <br><br>Les souvenirs ouverts jour et nuit <br>Retour a l'enfance ma ligne de fuite <br><br>Sur la retine, l'illusion optique persiste and saigne <br>En secret une ligne de fuite, sans limite <br>L'avenir lui s'en fiche]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Ligne De Fuite (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Ligne De Fuite (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Lautre_Rive_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - L`autre Rive (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:27:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:27:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Lautre_Rive_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - L`autre Rive (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sans foi ni loi au pavillon noir <br>Les voisins font feu de tout bois <br>Le rhum coule a flot l'immeuble prend l'eau <br><br>Le salut se cache tout la haut, la haut <br>Je t'ai promis d'atteindre l'autre rive, l'autre etage <br>Je sais plus si je pars, si j'arrive a me suivre a la nage <br>Au fond de la court un vaisseau fantome <br>A l'abordage, matelot hisse and ho <br><br>Au rez de chaussee c'est l'escalade <br>Une raz de maree contre attaque <br>Cloue le sur la porte Fais machine arriere <br>Je prends tout sur moi, ta faute la mienne <br>Je t'ai promis d'atteindre l'autre rive sous le vent, l'autre ville <br>Mon frere de la cote, droit devant l'autre rive nous attend <br><br>A Rennes a l'Ouest <br>Oh rien de neuf sous le soleil <br>Le meme ciel, la meme gare <br>Je connais meme un train qui s'egare <br>Je t'ai promis d'atteindre l'autre rive, l'autre rive c'est ici <br>Je sais plus si je pars, si j'arrive a me suivre a la ligne <br>L'hamecon auquel le poisson mord poisson mort <br>C'est pas mon ame, non C'est ton corps et encore <br><br>Je t'ai promis de faux departs <br>Je t'ai promis de vrais brouillards <br><br>De mauvaises blagues <br>En fausses alarmes <br>Fais ce que tu peux mais reste a flot]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="L`autre Rive (Remasterise En 2017)" label="L`autre Rive (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Quelque_Chose_Noir_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Quelque Chose, Noir (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:27:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:27:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Quelque_Chose_Noir_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Quelque Chose, Noir (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Le general Hiver plonge sa depression <br>Du bout des nerfs, sous une chape de plomb <br>Je me souviens d'un morceau de bleu <br><br>Dans le feu de l'absinthe, une couleur s'est eteinte <br>QUELQUE CHOSE NOIR se traine <br>Dans le silence s'enfonce <br>and se ronge les ongles <br>and me ronge les sangs <br>QUELQUE CHOSE NOIR, je l'aime <br>Comme un trou dans la nuit <br>Comme un trou dans l'oubli <br>and roule au fond d'un puits <br>Mais dehors c'est l'hiver <br>Creve l'arriere saison <br>Un pou ta mort dans une caisse a savon <br>Je me souviens d'un morceau de vert <br>De la douceur de vivre, de l'ivresse du vide <br>QUELQUE CHOSE NOIR se traine <br>Dans le silence s'enfonce <br>and se ronge les ongles <br>and me ronge les sangs <br>QUELQUE CHOSE NOIR, je l'aime <br>Comme un trou dans la nuit <br>Comme un trou dans l'oubli <br>Je l'aime c'est bien ma veine <br>Je reste la <br>Face contre terre <br>Ils ont vendu leur ame <br>Ils ont rendu les armes <br>Je regarde <br>QUELQUE CHOSE NOIR <br>QUELQUE CHOSE NOIR se traine <br>Dans le silence s'enfonce <br>and se ronge les ongles <br>and me ronge les sangs <br>QUELQUE CHOSE NOIR, je l'aime <br>Comme un trou dans la nuit <br>Comme un trou dans l'oubli <br>Roule au fond d'un puits <br>Je reste la <br>Face contre terre <br>Ils ont vendu leur ame <br>Ils ont rendu les armes <br>Je regarde <br>Je reste la <br>Face contre ciel <br>Dans les salles ou se perdent <br>Jusqu'au bruit de mes pas <br>Je me perds <br>Je laisse faire <br>QUELQUE CHOSE NOIR <br>La, quelque part]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Quelque Chose, Noir (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Quelque Chose, Noir (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Je_Taccorde_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Je T`accorde (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:27:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:27:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Je_Taccorde_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Je T`accorde (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Un ciel de lit sans etoile <br>L'abri d'une museliere <br>L'arome d'une fleur male <br><br>Qu'emprisonne une laniere <br>Tout cela and plus encore <br>Tout un monde je t'accorde <br>Si a mon diable, mon ange <br>Tu offres ton corps en echange <br>O Dieu sans remords <br>Le fruit de ma colere <br>Se plante dans la corolle <br>Carnivore ma chair <br>J'ai crie Seigneur <br>Que mon regne arrive <br>L'extase est trop vive <br>Un collier de larmes fines <br>Les perles d'une jeunesse passent <br>Ma charite l'assassine <br>O ma cherie triste et lasse <br>Pour l'amour est mal armee <br>L'amour aime les a cotes <br>A l'heure ou nos coeurs se brisent <br>Sur ton hotel sacrifie <br>Aux Dieux sans remords <br>Le fruit de ma colere <br>Se plante dans la corolle <br>Carnivore, ma chair <br>J'ai crie Seigneur <br>Que mon regne arrive <br>L'extase est trop vive <br>Danse au fil de l'ame <br>Racle la laniere <br>Rampe le long de l'arme <br>Danse a ma lumiere <br>and dans la verite des masques <br>Quand les rythmes se gravent au creux du cuir <br>Je t'abandonnerai mon ARME <br>Au ventre de l'idole, reluis <br>Sur la detente, ensuite appuie <br>Odieux, sans remords, le fruit de ma colere <br>Se plante dans la corolle <br>Carnivore ma chair <br>Alors je crie Seigneur <br>La peine est trop belle <br>L'extase est trop vive OH OH OH OH OH <br>Quand le corps se dehanche <br>Quand le corps se dehanche <br>La MANDRAGORE <br>Elle m'affole Oh m'affole <br>L'ange danse and dehanche son corps sous l'effort <br>L'ange danse and la Mandragore implore <br>L'ange danse and dehanche son corps sous l'effort <br>L'ange danse and la Mandragore implore <br>SEIGNEUR, merci <br>Serviteur servi <br>Philippe Pascal]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Je T`accorde (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Je T`accorde (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Galverran_Remasterise_En_2017/</id><title>Marc Seberg - Galver`ran (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T19:27:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T19:27:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Marc_Seberg/Galverran_Remasterise_En_2017/" title="Marc Seberg - Galver`ran (Remasterise En 2017) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ivre, la mer La mer immense <br>Eventre la pierre and cisele les vents <br><br>De lourds chevaux d'ecumes grondent <br>and roulent en greve les chants de guerre <br>La terre affronte la mer profonde <br>Quand se leveront les vents d'Ouest <br><br>Galver'ran Galv ac'hanon <br><br>La vie est breve, la braise est morte <br>L'Armor appelle, reve and s'endort <br>La braise est morte, morte la langue <br>Comme une eau forte gravee sur la lande <br><br>La terre se brise en sortileges <br>Un arpege de recifs vierges <br>Comme autant de navires les iles <br>derivent en quete d'Amerique <br>Galver'ran Galv ac'hanon <br>Galver'ran Galv ac'hanon <br>Hey <br><br>La vie est breve, la braise est vive <br>Le vent se leve, le vent l'attise <br>La braise est vive, de jour en jour <br>Elle refleurit, la fleur rouge <br><br>Galver'ran Galv ac'hanon Appelle Appelle moi <br>Galver'ran Galv ac'hanon Appelle Appelle moi <br><br>Quand sera noye noye Paris <br>Renaitra, Ys ma ville engloutie <br><br>Galver'ran Galv ac'hanon <br>Galver'ran Galv ac'hanon]]></content><category term="Marc Seberg" label="Marc Seberg"/><category term="Galver`ran (Remasterise En 2017)" label="Galver`ran (Remasterise En 2017)"/></entry></feed>