<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T07:23:31+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양수경/당신은_어디_있나요_2016_Ver/</id><title>양수경 - 당신은 어디 있나요 (2016 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:18:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:18:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%88%98%EA%B2%BD/%EB%8B%B9%EC%8B%A0%EC%9D%80_%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94_%EC%9E%88%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94_2016_Ver/" title="양수경 - 당신은 어디 있나요 (2016 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그래요 말을 해봐요 <br>나는 알고 있어요 <br>어젯밤의 그 맹세가 <br>무엇을 말하는지 <br>그래요 떠나갈게요 <br>당신이 원하신다면 <br>한번가면 그 뿐이에요 <br>이대로 떠나겠어요 <br>아 하 내가 외로울 때는 <br>날 위로해 주던 <br>아 그런 당신은 <br>당신은 어디 있나요 <br>마음대로 왔다가 마음대로 <br>그렇게 그렇게 가시나요 <br>말해 봐요 말해 봐요 <br>사랑이 죄인가요 <br>그래요 말을 해봐요 <br>나는 알고 있어요 <br>어젯밤의 그 맹세가 <br>무엇을 말하는지 <br>그래요 떠나갈게요 <br>당신이 원하신다면 <br>한번가면 그 뿐이에요 <br>이대로 떠나겠어요 <br>아 하 내가 외로울 때는 <br>날 위로해 주던 <br>아 그런 당신은 <br>당신은 어디 있나요 <br>마음대로 왔다가 마음대로 <br>그렇게 그렇게 가시나요 <br>말해 봐요 말해 봐요 <br>사랑이 죄인가요 <br>마음대로 왔다가 마음대로 <br>그렇게 그렇게 가시나요 <br>말해 봐요 말해 봐요 <br>사랑이 죄인가요 <br>]]></content><category term="양수경" label="양수경"/><category term="당신은 어디 있나요 (2016 Ver.)" label="당신은 어디 있나요 (2016 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양수경/그대는_2016_Ver/</id><title>양수경 - 그대는 (2016 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:18:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:18:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%88%98%EA%B2%BD/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EB%8A%94_2016_Ver/" title="양수경 - 그대는 (2016 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소리내어 울어봤지만 <br>그대는 떠났네 <br>소리내어 웃어도 봤지만 <br>그대는 떠났네 <br>가지 말아 가지 말아 가지 말아 <br>하면서 나는 울었네 <br>울지 말아 울지 말아 울지 말아 <br>하면서 그대는 떠났네 <br>그대를 불러봐도 <br>아무런 대답이 없네 <br>그대를 불러봐도 <br>아무런 소용이 없네 <br>소리내어 울어봤지만 <br>그대는 떠났네 <br>소리내어 웃어도 봤지만 <br>그대는 떠났네 <br>가지 말아 가지 말아 가지 말아 <br>하면서 나는 울었네 <br>울지 말아 울지 말아 울지 말아 <br>하면서 그대는 떠났네 <br>그대를 불러봐도 <br>아무런 대답이 없네 <br>그대를 불러봐도 <br>아무런 소용이 없네 <br>그대를 불러봐도 <br>아무런 대답이 없네 <br>그대를 불러봐도 <br>아무런 소용이 없네 <br>]]></content><category term="양수경" label="양수경"/><category term="그대는 (2016 Ver.)" label="그대는 (2016 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양수경/사랑은_차가운_유혹_2016_Ver/</id><title>양수경 - 사랑은 차가운 유혹 (2016 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:18:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:18:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%88%98%EA%B2%BD/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%80_%EC%B0%A8%EA%B0%80%EC%9A%B4_%EC%9C%A0%ED%98%B9_2016_Ver/" title="양수경 - 사랑은 차가운 유혹 (2016 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑은 차가운 유혹 <br>그래도 피할 순 없어 <br>이별은 때늦은 후회 <br>다시는 만날 수 없어 <br>마지막 인사를 하지도 못하고 <br>어깨를 움츠린 채로 <br>고개만 떨구네 <br>힘없이 다가와 내손을 잡을 때 <br>뺨 위로 흐르는 눈물 <br>가슴만 메이네 <br>이 세상 모두를 사랑한 당신이 <br>어이해 나만을 사랑할 수 없나 <br>사랑은 차가운 유혹 <br>그래도 피할 순 없어 <br>이별은 때늦은 후회 <br>다시는 만날 수 없어 <br>언젠가 우연히 마주친다 해도 <br>모르는 사람들처럼 <br>지나쳐 가겠지 <br>이 세상 모두를 사랑한 당신이 <br>어이해 나만을 사랑할 수 없나 <br>사랑은 차가운 유혹 <br>그래도 피할 순 없어 <br>이별은 때늦은 후회 <br>다시는 만날 수 없어 <br>사랑은 차가운 유혹 <br>그래도 피할 순 없어 <br>이별은 때늦은 후회 <br>다시는 만날 수 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="양수경" label="양수경"/><category term="사랑은 차가운 유혹 (2016 Ver.)" label="사랑은 차가운 유혹 (2016 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양수경/이별의_끝은_어디인가요_2016_Ver/</id><title>양수경 - 이별의 끝은 어디인가요 (2016 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:18:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:18:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%88%98%EA%B2%BD/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%98_%EB%81%9D%EC%9D%80_%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94%EC%9D%B8%EA%B0%80%EC%9A%94_2016_Ver/" title="양수경 - 이별의 끝은 어디인가요 (2016 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 돌아왔는지 <br>아무 생각도 나지 않아 <br>예감할 수 없었던 이별이었기에 <br>그 무슨 말을 했는지 <br>그저 눈물만 흐르네요 <br>믿을 수가 없었던 이별이었기에 <br>무슨 이유로 떠나야 했나요 <br>나보다 더 나를 사랑했던 그대가 <br>왜 나를 떠나야 했는지 <br>아직도 눈물이 남아 있었나요 <br>내 모습이 정말 싫어요 <br>또 다른 사랑을 찾아야 하나요 <br>내 이별의 끝은 어디인가요 <br>그 무슨 말을 했는지 <br>그저 눈물만 흐르네요 <br>믿을 수가 없었던 이별이었기에 <br>무슨 이유로 떠나야 했나요 <br>나보다 더 나를 사랑했던 그대가 <br>왜 나를 떠나야 했는지 <br>아직도 눈물이 남아 있었나요 <br>내 모습이 정말 싫어요 <br>또 다른 사랑을 찾아야 하나요 <br>내 이별의 끝은 어디인가요 <br>아직도 눈물이 남아 있었나요 <br>내 모습이 정말 싫어요 <br>또 다른 사랑을 찾아야 하나요 <br>내 이별의 끝은 어디인가요 <br>]]></content><category term="양수경" label="양수경"/><category term="이별의 끝은 어디인가요 (2016 Ver.)" label="이별의 끝은 어디인가요 (2016 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/양수경/바라볼_수_없는_그대_2016_Ver/</id><title>양수경 - 바라볼 수 없는 그대 (2016 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:18:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:18:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%96%91%EC%88%98%EA%B2%BD/%EB%B0%94%EB%9D%BC%EB%B3%BC_%EC%88%98_%EC%97%86%EB%8A%94_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_2016_Ver/" title="양수경 - 바라볼 수 없는 그대 (2016 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 가슴에 기대고 싶은 <br>나의 여린 눈길에 <br>왜 그대는 아픔으로 <br>돌아서고 있나 <br>흐느껴 울면 바라볼까 <br>가만히 그댈 보아도 <br>왜 가까이 불렀어도 <br>그렇게 멀리 떠나나 <br>정말로 나를 사랑하고 있다면 <br>이별이란 있을 수 없어 <br>그리움 속에 기다릴 수 있다면 <br>이렇게 애원하진 않아 <br>그렇게 떠나가는 사람 <br>난 정말 울어 버렸네 <br>그대 가슴에 기대고 싶은 <br>나의 여린 눈길에 <br>왜 그대는 아픔으로 <br>돌아서고 있나 <br>흐느껴 울면 바라볼까 <br>가만히 그댈 보아도 <br>왜 가까이 불렀어도 <br>그렇게 멀리 떠나나 <br>정말로 나를 사랑하고 있다면 <br>이별이란 있을 수 없어 <br>그리움 속에 기다릴 수 있다면 <br>이렇게 애원하진 않아 <br>그렇게 떠나가는 사람 <br>난 정말 울어 버렸네 <br>그렇게 떠나가는 사람 <br>난 정말 울어 버렸네 <br>]]></content><category term="양수경" label="양수경"/><category term="바라볼 수 없는 그대 (2016 Ver.)" label="바라볼 수 없는 그대 (2016 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Cant_Wait_Feat_Hailey_Cramer/</id><title>PEZ - Can`t Wait (Feat. Hailey Cramer) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:20:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:20:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PEZ/Cant_Wait_Feat_Hailey_Cramer/" title="PEZ - Can`t Wait (Feat. Hailey Cramer) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro: Pez] <br>Yeah, it's been a long time coming, huh <br>Ayy <br><br>[Verse 1: Pez] <br>Let me dust off my feet on the welcome mat <br>'Cause I feel like I just been to hell and back <br>I had to tell you that <br>Because there's been a lot of people asking "where's your album at?" <br>I gotta hand those fans love <br>For sticking with me when I didn't have an answer <br>Now I do I think we need to catch up <br>It's been a minute, hope there isn't any bad blood <br>See I really nearly thought about <br>Getting a job and just walking out, but I'm over that <br>'Cause Aunt Mary got buried that very <br>First minute that I wrote a rap and I'm not going back <br>But at least if I can help her right <br>Cause this is all that I know and it's calling me home <br>I spent too long standing at a fork in a road <br>Thinking "what way," but I'm done waiting <br><br>[Hook: Hailey Cramer] <br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer <br>No?mo?ohhh (I can't wait) <br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer, no <br>Can't wait any longer, no <br>No, no, no <br><br>[Verse 2: Pez] <br>Uh, they got us all on a hunt for wealth <br>If it ain't that then it's something else to fill a void <br>So I thought I'd write for the kids and <br>Let 'em know there's more to life than just this shit <br>'Cause they're in need of some truth <br>Somebody's gotta speak to the youth, tell 'em something real <br>And let 'em know the fucking deal <br>While they're trying to find their way through the maze <br>And I know how you're feeling 'cause I feel for ya <br>Just know as long as you hear me that I'm here for ya <br>And I will always keep speaking from my heart <br>All the way from my very first CD to my last <br>Uh, to help you see it's a mirage <br>It's got us all believing that we can't <br>We're living life and when your aim is attained <br>Life shouldn't have to be mundane <br>So, this is for the people out there tired of being stepped on <br>For the rappers out there tired of being slept on <br>Nah, I wasn't always in the upper echelon <br>Yes, I was once down the bottom but I kept on <br>I hear 'em saying "where's Pez gone?" <br>Man, I'm back, I'm picking up right left off <br>'Cause I ended up inside a maze <br>Took a little while to find my way, but now <br><br>[Hook: Hailey Cramer] <br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer <br>No?mo?ohhh (I can't wait) <br>Can't wait any longer <br>Can't wait any longer, no (yeah) <br>Can't wait any longer, no <br>No, no, no]]></content><category term="PEZ" label="PEZ"/><category term="Can`t Wait (Feat. Hailey Cramer)" label="Can`t Wait (Feat. Hailey Cramer)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Couros/Breathe_Again/</id><title>Couros - Breathe A.gain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:27:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:27:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Couros/Breathe_Again/" title="Couros - Breathe A.gain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't you wanna try it? <br>People gonna say what they gonna say <br>They could be desire <br>Think it's a mistake that we gotta make <br>'Cause you're almost messed up as me <br>And go but don't go very deep <br>But honey, you're my life <br>Get us some space I could still escape <br>We both know <br>That we're taking the weight of the world <br>On our own <br>But it won't work, could it hurt to be hurt <br>This ain't love, it ain't freedom <br>We've got someone to lean on <br>This ain't love, it ain't easy when we hurt, <br>All I know is I can breathe a-gain <br>You helped when I need a friend <br>Breathe a-gain <br>The only one I need, the only one I need to <br>Breathe a-gain <br>You helped when I need a friend <br>Breathe a-gain <br>The only one I need, the only one I need <br><br>Did you see it coming? <br>Guess we found [?] on the floor <br>Hitting rock bottom, <br>It's pretty cold to hold something warm <br>'Cause you give me space to pretend <br>That all of my demons are friends <br>Only thing in common <br><br>Is we don't wanna be alone anymore <br>We both know <br>That we're taking the weight of the world <br>On our own <br>But it won't work, could it hurt to be hurt <br>This ain't love, it ain't freedom <br>We've got someone to lean on <br>This ain't love, it ain't easy when we hurt, <br>All I know is I can breathe a-gain <br>You helped when I need a friend <br>Breathe a-gain <br>The only one I need, the only one I need to <br>Breathe a-gain <br>You helped when I need a friend <br>Breathe a-gain <br>The only one I need, the only one I need <br><br>Don't need to be that fantasy [?] <br>Just some company to remedy how hard it can get <br>We won't worry bout our tiny dots <br>So where it's gonna go <br>Spend it with or without, live for an hour <br>Honey, we both know <br>That we're taking the weight of the world <br>On our own <br>But it won't work, could it hurt to be hurt <br>This ain't love, it ain't freedom <br>We've got someone to lean on <br>This ain't love, it ain't easy when we hurt, <br>All I know is I can breathe a-gain <br>You helped when I need a friend <br>Breathe a-gain <br>The only one I need, the only one I need to <br>Breathe a-gain <br>You helped when I need a friend <br>Breathe a-gain <br>The only one I need, the only one I need]]></content><category term="Couros" label="Couros"/><category term="Breathe A.gain" label="Breathe A.gain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Black_Grape/In_The_Name_Of_The_Father_Choppers_Mix/</id><title>Black_Grape - In The Name Of The Father (Choppers Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:30:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:30:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Black_Grape/In_The_Name_Of_The_Father_Choppers_Mix/" title="Black_Grape - In The Name Of The Father (Choppers Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's coming from the side! <br>And it's coming from the back! <br>People! <br>Multitudes of people! <br>Walking up the hills! <br>Go forward! <br><br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>In the name of your father and your holy ghost <br><br>I don't do what you do <br>And you don't do what I do <br>But you should do <br>You <br>Oh, you've got your voodoo <br>But you've got no clue <br>You know me easy bongo poo-poo for me <br><br>Well because I'm no learned <br>Well I get away with murder <br>Going boldly where no man's been before <br><br>Ere we go, ere we go <br>Once ag-ain <br><br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>I have the holy spirit in me! <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>I have the holy spirit in me! <br>Neil Armstrong <br>Astronaut <br>He had balls bigger than King Kong! <br>Fay Wray! <br>First big suit on the moon <br>And he starts to play golf! <br>Hole-in-one! <br><br>[ Psycho raps? ] <br><br>Here we go, 'ere we go <br>Once ag-ain <br><br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>I have the holy spirit in me! <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>I have the holy spirit in me! <br>[ Psycho raps? ] <br><br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>I have the holy spirit in me! <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>I have the holy spirit in me! <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>I have the holy spirit in me! <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>I have the holy spirit in me! <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost <br>In the name of the father and the holy ghost...]]></content><category term="Black Grape" label="Black Grape"/><category term="In The Name Of The Father (Choppers Mix)" label="In The Name Of The Father (Choppers Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/핑거소울/어디든지_갈_수_있어_Feat_애프터나잇_프로젝트_Afternight_Project/</id><title>핑거소울 - 어디든지 갈 수 있어 (Feat. 애프터나잇 프로젝트 (Afternight Project)) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:31:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:31:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%91%EA%B1%B0%EC%86%8C%EC%9A%B8/%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94%EB%93%A0%EC%A7%80_%EA%B0%88_%EC%88%98_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4_Feat_%EC%95%A0%ED%94%84%ED%84%B0%EB%82%98%EC%9E%87_%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9D%ED%8A%B8_Afternight_Project/" title="핑거소울 - 어디든지 갈 수 있어 (Feat. 애프터나잇 프로젝트 (Afternight Project)) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지구의 맨 끝에 있는걸까 <br>나만의 파라다이스 <br>세상의 지도에는 없는 곳 <br>매일밤 꿈꿨어 <br>누구도 달려보지 못한 그 길 <br>그 위를 나는 날 만났어 <br>어디든지 갈 수 있어 난 <br>A brand new day has come <br>다시 꿈을 꾸는거야 난 <br>Let my dreams come true <br>복잡한 생각은 이제 그만 <br>마음을 따라가 <br>아무도 갈 수 없다 말했었지 <br>하지만 지금 난여기에 <br>어디든지 갈 수 있어 난 <br>A brand new day has come <br>다시 꿈을 꾸는거야 난 <br>Let my dreams come true <br>난 행복해 <br>]]></content><category term="핑거소울" label="핑거소울"/><category term="어디든지 갈 수 있어 (Feat. 애프터나잇 프로젝트 (Afternight Project))" label="어디든지 갈 수 있어 (Feat. 애프터나잇 프로젝트 (Afternight Project))"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김홍석/Good_Bye/</id><title>김홍석 - Good Bye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:32:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:32:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%99%8D%EC%84%9D/Good_Bye/" title="김홍석 - Good Bye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밖엔 항상 햇살이 <br>있었는데 몰랐었어 <br>내 뒤엔 항상 니가 <br>있었는데 몰랐었어 <br>그 짧았던 봄날 같았던 너를 <br>이젠 제자리로 돌려 놓으려 해 <br>이젠 굿바이 굿바이 <br>이젠 굿바이 굿바이 오 굿바이 <br>늘 꿈을 꾸는 그대에겐 난 항상 <br>모자랄 수 밖에 없었겠죠 미안해 <br>bye bye <br>눈 감으면 더 잘 <br>볼 수도 있었는데 <br>변하는 건 항상 나였는데 <br>항상 그랬는데 <br>그 짧았던 봄날 같았던 너를 <br>이젠 제자리로 돌려 놓으려 해 <br>이젠 굿바이 굿바이 <br>이젠 굿바이 굿바이 오 굿바이 <br>늘 꿈을 꾸는 그대에겐 난 항상 <br>모자랄 수 밖에 없었겠죠 미안해 <br>bye bye <br>바이 굿바이 <br>]]></content><category term="김홍석" label="김홍석"/><category term="Good Bye" label="Good Bye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김홍석/난_앵무새/</id><title>김홍석 - 난 앵무새 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:32:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:32:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%99%8D%EC%84%9D/%EB%82%9C_%EC%95%B5%EB%AC%B4%EC%83%88/" title="김홍석 - 난 앵무새 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈이 온다는 건 적어도 내겐 <br>사탕발림 같은 것 조금 위험해 <br>헉 하고 눈 한송이가 <br>내 입으로 들어왔다 <br>목젖을 간지르는 그 맛을 보니 <br>눈 같은 내 맘이 <br>너무 부끄러워 지더라 <br>그 흔한 감정이 <br>늘 거짓은 아니었다고 <br>그 많은 눈들이 <br>그대를 향하고 있다고 <br>늘 똑같은 말만 되풀이 하는 <br>되풀이 하는 난 앵무새 <br>목젖을 간지르는 그 맛을 보니 <br>눈 같은 내 맘이 <br>너무 부끄러워 지더라 <br>그 흔한 감정이 <br>늘 거짓은 아니었다고 <br>그 많은 눈들이 <br>그대를 향하고 있다고 <br>늘 똑같은 말만 되풀이 하는 <br>되풀이 하는 난 앵무새 <br>난 앵무새 <br>]]></content><category term="김홍석" label="김홍석"/><category term="난 앵무새" label="난 앵무새"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/폴_송/사랑_뺏기_Feat_골드/</id><title>폴_송 - 사랑 뺏기 (Feat. 골드) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:33:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:33:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8F%B4_%EC%86%A1/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EB%BA%8F%EA%B8%B0_Feat_%EA%B3%A8%EB%93%9C/" title="폴_송 - 사랑 뺏기 (Feat. 골드) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너를 처음 봤을때 <br>난 숨이 멎는줄 알았지 <br>너무 가슴이 커서 <br>니가 내게 왔을때 <br>조금 당황해서 <br>숨이 안쉬어져 <br>도와줘요 <br>mayday mayday <br>니 남친이 모르게 <br>너의 폰은 뒤집어놔 <br>아직은 우리 사이를 <br>알리기엔 조금 일러 <br>너도 잘 모르게 쓸데없이 <br> 욕하는 사람들 <br>이젠 신경 안써 <br>내 사랑은 u u u <br>i got a catch <br>u u u lady <br>니가 바라는건 다해줄께 <br>제발 그 녀석은 좀 빼 <br>심장이 쿵쿵쿵 baby <br>i fall in <br>love with you <br>계속 바라만봐도 좋은걸 <br>이건 나만의 사랑 뺏기야 <br>listen to my words <br>by my side you <br>say u r my u r my <br>lovely baby <br>i just want to make <br>it in side you <br>oh no <br>baby 1 2 3 <br>하나 둘 셋 <br>n step by step <br>들어봐 <br>조심스레 다가올래 <br>내게 들어올래 <br>들킬까 겁이나 <br>서툰 내 마음을 <br>너무 빨리 <br>허락한건 아닌지 <br>이런 내가 가벼워 <br>보인건 아닌건지 <br>정신 못차려 <br>널 보고 있으면 나 <br>baby 1 2 3 <br>니 남친이 모르게 <br>그 놈 속을 뒤집어놔 <br>더 이상 둘의 사이를 <br>신경쓰긴 정말 싫어 <br>너도 잘 모르게 <br>조심스레 넘어온 네 모습 <br>이젠 신경 안써 <br>내 사랑은 u u u <br>i got a catch <br>u u u lady <br>내가 바라는걸 말해줄께 <br>이제 그 녀석과는 끝내 <br>심장이 쿵쿵쿵 baby <br>i fall in love with you <br>계속 바라만봐도 좋을껄 <br>이건 나만의 사랑뺏기야 <br>아무리 생각해도 <br>good thing <br>너와 둘이 이어져가는 <br>something <br>네 사랑이 빨리 지나 <br>make it love i wish <br>make it love <br>내 사랑은 <br>u u u i got a catch <br>u u u lady <br>내가 바라는걸 말해줄께 <br>이제 그 녀석과는 끝내 <br>심장이 쿵쿵쿵 baby <br>i fall in love with you <br>계속 바라만봐도 좋을껄 <br>이건 나만의 사랑뺏기야 <br>with you <br>]]></content><category term="폴 송" label="폴 송"/><category term="사랑 뺏기 (Feat. 골드)" label="사랑 뺏기 (Feat. 골드)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/그린_Green/그대에게_바래요/</id><title>그린_Green - 그대에게 바래요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:33:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:33:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%B0_Green/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%98%EC%9A%94/" title="그린_Green - 그대에게 바래요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아련한 밤공기가 <br>그대를 내게 데려와 <br>서글픈 눈물이 나를 또 흔드네요 <br>오늘은 그대가 나 많이 그리워 <br>그대를 그리다 술 한잔 했어요 <br>지워도 지워지지 않는 그때 우리 <br>함께 있지 않아도 서로 <br>사랑했던 시간을 말하지 않아도 <br>느낄 수가 있었는데 <br>설레는 마음으로 그대와 <br>굳어진 그대 마음 <br>돌릴 수는 없나요 <br>내가 또 그대를 <br>다시 힘들게 하나요 <br>오늘은 그대가 나 많이 그리워 <br>그대를 그리다 술 한잔 했어요 <br>지워도 지워지지 않는 우리 모습 <br>함께 있지 않아도 서로 <br>사랑했던 시간을 말하지 않아도 <br>느낄 수가 있었는데 <br>설레는 마음으로 그대와 <br>그대가 없는 나 이젠 정말 <br>아무렇지가 않아 아픈 만큼 <br>사랑한 거라 믿을래요 <br>그대도 믿어줘요 나처럼 <br>그대도 믿어줘요 나처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="그린 (Green)" label="그린 (Green)"/><category term="그대에게 바래요" label="그대에게 바래요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/영호/내가_못나서_엄재_Ver/</id><title>영호 - 내가 못나서 (엄재 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:33:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:33:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%81%ED%98%B8/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EB%AA%BB%EB%82%98%EC%84%9C_%EC%97%84%EC%9E%AC_Ver/" title="영호 - 내가 못나서 (엄재 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 떠나고 일년 지나면 <br>그냥 그렇게 잊혀질까봐 <br>가지 말라는 말도 못하고 <br>눈물로 너를 떠나보냈다 <br>우리 만남이 길어질 수록 <br>아파하는 널 볼 수 없었다 <br>멀어져가는 우리 사랑이 <br>길어질 수록 상처만 깊었다 <br>내가 못나서 내가 부족해서 <br>그 흔한 꽃 한번 사주지 못 하고 <br>하염없이 날 기다린 너에게 <br>줄 수있는건 이별뿐이라 <br>미안하다고 아프지말라고 <br>많이 울지말고 기다리지마 <br>울고 있는 날 뒤돌아 보지마 <br>돌아서는 널 잡을 수 없다 <br>내가 못나서 <br>우리 이별이 다가올 수록 <br>추억이란게 눈 앞을 가렸다 <br>잊혀져가는 우리 사랑이 <br>가까워 올 수록 더 잡고 싶었다 <br>내가 못나서 내가 부족해서 <br>그 흔한 옷 한벌 사주지 못 하고 <br>하염없이 날 기다린 너에게 <br>줄 수있는건 이별뿐이라 <br>미안하다고 아프지말라고 <br>많이 울지말고 기다리지마 <br>울고 있는 날 뒤돌아 보지마 <br>슬퍼하는 널 잊을수없다 <br>내가 못나서 우우후 <br>내가 못나서 내가 부족해서 <br>비오는 날엔 너를 감싸안고 <br>너의 우산이 되고 싶었고 <br>너 아픈기억도 다 안고 살아갈 <br>넓은 바다가 되고 싶었다 <br>내가 못나서 내가 부족해서 <br>그 흔한 꽃 한번 사주지 못했다 <br>하염없이 날 기다린 너에게 <br>줄 수있는 건 이별 뿐이다 <br>내가 못나서 <br>]]></content><category term="영호" label="영호"/><category term="내가 못나서 (엄재 Ver.)" label="내가 못나서 (엄재 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/영호/내가_못나서_영호_Ver/</id><title>영호 - 내가 못나서 (영호 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:33:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:33:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%81%ED%98%B8/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EB%AA%BB%EB%82%98%EC%84%9C_%EC%98%81%ED%98%B8_Ver/" title="영호 - 내가 못나서 (영호 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 떠나고 일년 지나면 <br>그냥 그렇게 잊혀질까봐 <br>가지 말라는 말도 못하고 <br>눈물로 너를 떠나보냈다 <br>우리 만남이 길어질 수록 <br>아파하는 널 볼 수 없었다 <br>멀어져가는 우리 사랑이 <br>길어질 수록 상처만 깊었다 <br>내가 못나서 내가 부족해서 <br>그 흔한 꽃 한번 사주지 못 하고 <br>하염없이 날 기다린 너에게 <br>줄 수있는건 이별뿐이라 <br>미안하다고 아프지말라고 <br>많이 울지말고 기다리지마 <br>울고 있는 날 뒤돌아 보지마 <br>돌아서는 널 잡을 수 없다 <br>내가 못나서 <br>우리 이별이 다가올 수록 <br>추억이란게 눈 앞을 가렸다 <br>잊혀져가는 우리 사랑이 <br>가까워 올 수록 더 잡고 싶었다 <br>내가 못나서 내가 부족해서 <br>그 흔한 옷 한벌 사주지 못 하고 <br>하염없이 날 기다린 너에게 <br>줄 수있는건 이별뿐이라 <br>미안하다고 아프지말라고 <br>많이 울지말고 기다리지마 <br>울고 있는 날 뒤돌아 보지마 <br>슬퍼하는 널 잊을수없다 <br>내가 못나서 우우후 <br>내가 못나서 내가 부족해서 <br>비오는 날엔 너를 감싸안고 <br>너의 우산이 되고 싶었고 <br>너 아픈기억도 다 안고 살아갈 <br>넓은 바다가 되고 싶었다 <br>내가 못나서 내가 부족해서 <br>그 흔한 꽃 한번 사주지 못했다 <br>하염없이 날 기다린 너에게 <br>줄 수있는 건 이별 뿐이다 <br>내가 못나서 <br>]]></content><category term="영호" label="영호"/><category term="내가 못나서 (영호 Ver.)" label="내가 못나서 (영호 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도플러즈_Dopplerz/Hosoh_Homo_Supra_Omnia_Humanas/</id><title>도플러즈_Dopplerz - Hosoh (Homo Supra Omnia Humanas) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:34:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:34:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%ED%94%8C%EB%9F%AC%EC%A6%88_Dopplerz/Hosoh_Homo_Supra_Omnia_Humanas/" title="도플러즈_Dopplerz - Hosoh (Homo Supra Omnia Humanas) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이대로 가다간 난 <br>진짜로 전설이 돼 <br>좀 늦었지만 다 <br>예비한 길이기에 <br>걍 걸어가도 되지 <br>A living legend is <br>livin' a dream <br>we made a dream team <br>새로운 세계가 <br>건설이 돼 whoo <br>많이 배웠어 <br>다들 하도 많이 <br>가르치려고들 들어서 <br>철 들었어 <br>but 문제라 생각하고 <br>다 풀었어 <br>삶의 어떤 난제도 <br>두려운 적이 <br>없는 나이기에 <br>i just did it like Nike <br>so 나의 길은 <br>온갖 역경과 고초 라는 <br>성공의 요소 들을 <br>갖춰 가고 있는 중 <br>신은 알겠지 <br>내가 진짜로 <br>도달하게될 그 끝을 <br>니들이 겨우 날 <br>따라왔다 생각할 때쯤 <br>내 관심사는 <br>이미 잘 하는 거 <br>걍 막 해도 대충 <br>내 이름 밑에 백 명이 넘는 <br>인재들을 늘어놓을 때 <br>일 대신 이를 내 넥타이 <br>위에다가 고이 <br>아로새겼네 <br>내 나이 서른셋 <br>예뻤던 여자도 <br>이 때쯤엔 못 생겨지네 <br>but i stay hard stay foolish <br>so i'm finally winnin' <br>we're not rappers <br>but we fuckin' better <br>than the rappers <br>we diggin' chapters <br>of the books <br>rather than the swagger <br>we're Dopplerz <br>we gonna make you dope chiga <br>we're not high <br>중독자는 의사 안 되니까 <br>we're not rappers <br>but we fuckin' better <br>than the rappers <br>we diggin' chapters <br>of the books <br>rather than the swagger <br>we're Dopplerz <br>we gonna make <br>you dope chiga <br>we're not high <br>중독자는 의사 안 되니까 <br>날 이제 못 보겠지 <br>삐알콩이 어디 <br>어디기는 난 지금 <br>무대 바로 그 위 <br>i e i ain't ya homie <br>헐디헌 계집애 <br>배알 없을 줄은 몰랐네 <br>너네 stop hovering <br>왜냐면 started to starvin' <br>스타빙의 연예인병 <br>병신들은 빨아제껴 <br>다 뒷담화 <br>나 젖어있다만 <br>말리지 말지어다 <br>빨래 아니지 <br>모르냐 내 <br>배가 빨래판이지 <br>예 내 창작은 <br>빚지고 빚어내는 짓 <br>그래 순수와 동기나 <br>물을거면 가라 가 <br>나는 몸집을 키워 <br>난 괴물이 되어가는 중 <br>누가 그러대 <br>말려서 포기면 <br>애초에 시작도 안 했어 <br>후두에 눌러붙은 <br>타르 가루 <br>박박 긁어내 뱉은 <br>피도 섞인 내 토사물 <br>어디서 들어보건 <br>직접 게워내야 개운해 <br>너 내 토 위에 머리 박아 <br>백형아 빠가야 <br>니도 마 처 박아라 <br>여기는 우릴 악마로 <br>보는 이가 많아 <br>머리 위에 술 붓고 <br>소독해줄게 <br>we're not rappers <br>but we fuckin' better <br>than the rappers <br>we diggin' chapters <br>of the books <br>rather than the swagger <br>we're Dopplerz <br>we gonna make <br>you dope chiga <br>high high <br>중독자는 의사 안 되니까 <br>we're not rappers <br>but we fuckin' better <br>than the rappers <br>we diggin' chapters <br>of the books <br>rather than the swagger <br>we're Dopplerz <br>we gonna make <br>you dope chiga <br>high high <br>중독자는 의사 안 되니까 <br>야 임마 냄새나 <br>보기 싫어 저리 가 <br>야 임마 냄새나 <br>보기 싫어 저리 가 <br>야 이 개새끼야 <br>너 이 쌍놈새끼의 <br>죄목은 대체 무어냐 <br>그럼 백형아 저 죄인과 <br>너의 차이는 대체 무어냐 <br>너네 가면을 내가 찢겠어 <br>당신 애인까지 뺏겠어 <br>you let these motherfuckas <br>judging your sin <br>for god sake <br>몇 빼곤 <br>여기엔 내 편은 없지 <br>백형 편도 없지 <br>이 판은 씨발 <br>형편이 없지 <br>내 말투가 꼽냐 꼽겠지 <br>시간 지나고 <br>내가 뜨고 나면 <br>니 핸드폰에 <br>내 전화번혼 없겠지 <br>the one for the team <br>so the fuck out the gory details <br>hiphop <br>we're not rappers <br>but we fuckin' better <br>than the rappers <br>we diggin' chapters <br>of the books <br>rather than the swagger <br>we're Dopplerz <br>we gonna make <br>you dope chiga <br>we're not high <br>중독자는 의사 안 되니까 <br>we're not rappers <br>but we fuckin' better <br>than the rappers <br>we diggin' chapters <br>of the books <br>rather than the swagger <br>we're Dopplerz <br>we gonna make <br>you dope chiga <br>we're not high <br>중독자는 의사 안 되니까 <br>]]></content><category term="도플러즈 (Dopplerz)" label="도플러즈 (Dopplerz)"/><category term="Hosoh (Homo Supra Omnia Humanas)" label="Hosoh (Homo Supra Omnia Humanas)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스트레이_The_Stray/Dont_worry_baby/</id><title>스트레이_The_Stray - Don`t worry baby - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:37:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:37:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_The_Stray/Dont_worry_baby/" title="스트레이_The_Stray - Don`t worry baby - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[항상 어른스러웠던 <br>너를 봤을 때 <br>그래 나도 기댈 곳이 <br>생겼구나라고 <br>생각했었어 <br>오 그건 내 착각이었어 <br>너는 너무나도 <br>여린 소녀였었지 <br>이젠 내가 네 <br>버팀목이 돼줄게 <br>지금까지 오 <br>Don't worry baby <br>don't worry baby <br>don't worry baby <br>don't worry baby <br>]]></content><category term="스트레이 (The Stray)" label="스트레이 (The Stray)"/><category term="Don`t worry baby" label="Don`t worry baby"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스트레이_The_Stray/기다릴게/</id><title>스트레이_The_Stray - 기다릴게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:37:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:37:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_The_Stray/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A6%B4%EA%B2%8C/" title="스트레이_The_Stray - 기다릴게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[햇빛은 따스한데 <br>내 마음속에서는 <br>비가 내려 <br>네가 떠난 날부터 <br>내 마음속에서는 <br>비가 내려 <br>너의 첫 번째가 <br>아니라도 좋아 <br>그냥 내 옆에만 <br>있어주면 돼 <br>너의 두 번째라도 좋아 <br>내가 아닌 다른 남자를 <br>만나도 난 괜찮아 <br>가지마 널 못 <br>보내는 한마디 <br>날 버리고 가지마 <br>사랑해 널 <br>기다리는 내 맘이 <br>네 마음 기다릴게 여기서 <br>너의 첫 번째가 <br>아니라도 좋아 <br>그냥 내 옆에만 <br>있어주면 돼 <br>너의 두 번째라도 좋아 <br>내가 아닌 다른 남자를 <br>만나도 난 괜찮아 <br>가지마 널 못 <br>보내는 한마디 <br>날 버리고 가지마 <br>사랑해 널 기다리는 내 맘이 <br>네 마음 기다릴게 여기서 <br>너는 잊지 못할 사람이야 <br>내 마음속에 가득히 <br>닿아도 닿지 않는 것처럼 <br>눈 앞에서 자꾸 아른거려 <br>너의 첫 번째가 <br>아니라도 좋아 <br>그냥 내 옆에만 <br>있어주면 돼 <br>너의 두 번째라도 좋아 <br>내가 아닌 다른 남자를 <br>만나도 난 괜찮아 <br>]]></content><category term="스트레이 (The Stray)" label="스트레이 (The Stray)"/><category term="기다릴게" label="기다릴게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스트레이_The_Stray/길_건너편에_네가/</id><title>스트레이_The_Stray - 길 건너편에 네가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:37:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:37:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_The_Stray/%EA%B8%B8_%EA%B1%B4%EB%84%88%ED%8E%B8%EC%97%90_%EB%84%A4%EA%B0%80/" title="스트레이_The_Stray - 길 건너편에 네가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길 건너편엔 <br>네가 날 바라보고 있지 <br>네게 이렇게 말해 <br>그땐 왜 그랬냐고 <br>나를 속였던 날들 <br>거짓에 찬 네 눈빛 <br>그리고 그 남자와 있던 <br>그날 밤의 모든 것 <br>너를 믿었던 <br>내가 너무나 한심해 <br>이젠 내가 널 <br>마음속에서 지우려 해 <br>너 없어도 아무렇지 않아 <br>널 향한 내 마음이 아까워 <br>길 건너편엔 네가 <br>남자를 보고 있지 <br>내게 했던 것처럼 <br>거짓된 얼굴로 또 <br>그 남자를 홀리고 있겠지 <br>나를 속였던 날들 <br>거짓에 찬 네 눈빛 <br>그리고 그 남자와 있던 <br>그날 밤의 모든 것 <br>너를 믿었던 <br>내가 너무나 한심해 <br>이젠 내가 널 <br>마음속에서 지우려 해 <br>너 없어도 아무렇지 않아 <br>널 향한 내 마음이 아까워 <br>넌 처음부터 날 <br>이렇게 만났으니까 <br>생각 없이 만났으니까 <br>아직도 다친 게 <br>난 너무나 아프니까 <br>이제 내 마음에서 나가줘 <br>너 없어도 아무렇지 않아 <br>널 향한 내 마음이 아까워 <br>]]></content><category term="스트레이 (The Stray)" label="스트레이 (The Stray)"/><category term="길 건너편에 네가" label="길 건너편에 네가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스트레이_The_Stray/Lucky_night_Feat_Reddy/</id><title>스트레이_The_Stray - Lucky night (Feat. Reddy) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:37:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:37:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_The_Stray/Lucky_night_Feat_Reddy/" title="스트레이_The_Stray - Lucky night (Feat. Reddy) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 처음 봤던 그 순간 <br>얼굴이 빨갛게 <br>달아 올라올라 <br>오 너무나 떨렸지 <br>너에게 처음 말 걸던 날 <br>내 마음은 몰라 몰라 <br>조마조마 해 <br>네가 무슨 말로 받아칠지 <br>눈을 마주치지 못하겠어 <br>너무 떨려 숨을 못 쉬겠어 <br>간당간당 해 <br>나를 바라보는 너의 눈빛이 <br>가지고 싶다고 말하고 싶어 <br>그냥 좋아한다고 말하고 싶어 <br>Love it love it love it <br>네가 나에게로 오던 <br>그 날 밤은 내게 <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>Love it love it love it <br>네가 나에게로 오던 <br>그 날 밤은 내게 <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>너에게 한 발짝 더 <br>다가갈 때마다 <br>숨이 차올라 올라 <br>오 너는 잘 모르지 <br>너에 대한 나의 떨림이 <br>내 마음을 몰라 몰라 <br>두근두근 해 <br>어떤 얼굴로 날 바라볼지 <br>눈을 마주치지 못하겠어 <br>너무 떨려 숨을 못 쉬겠어 <br>조금은 기대돼 <br>나를 바라보는 너의 눈빛이 <br>가지고 싶다고 말하고 싶어 <br>그냥 사랑한다고 말하고 싶어 <br>Love it love it love it <br>네가 나에게로 오던 <br>그 날 밤은 내게 <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>Love it love it love it <br>네가 나에게로 오던 <br>그 날 밤은 내게 <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>뛰었어 널 보고 <br>심장이 어이없게 <br>그때를 생각하면 <br>지금도 어이없네 <br>농담이고 그땐 몰랐어 <br>어떻게 말해야 될지 <br>정신이 없었어 기억도 않나 <br>내가 한 얘기 <br>서툴렀어 번호를 <br>물어보는 말투가 <br>네 주변에서 한참을 <br>고민했어 그냥 관둘까 <br>차지하겠지 용기 있는 놈이 <br>그놈이 꼭 나여야 <br>겠더라고 혹시 <br>남자친구가 있는 건 아닌지 <br>슬쩍 봤는데 없더라고 <br>네 번째 손가락이 <br>비어있어 가서 물어봤잖아 <br>교포는 아닌지 <br>네 노출의 퍼센티지와 몸매에 <br>처음 반응하더라 내 심장이 <br>그리고 네가 쓰는 향수 <br>또 네 목소리 <br>모든 게 갖고 싶었어 <br>어렵게 입을 띄었어 <br>그래서 지금 내가 <br>네 옆에 있어 <br>Love it love it love it <br>네가 나에게로 오던 <br>그 날 밤은 내게 <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>Love it love it love it <br>네가 나에게로 오던 <br>그 날 밤은 내게 <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>Lucky lucky lucky lucky night <br>]]></content><category term="스트레이 (The Stray)" label="스트레이 (The Stray)"/><category term="Lucky night (Feat. Reddy)" label="Lucky night (Feat. Reddy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스트레이_The_Stray/뭔데/</id><title>스트레이_The_Stray - 뭔데 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:37:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:37:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_The_Stray/%EB%AD%94%EB%8D%B0/" title="스트레이_The_Stray - 뭔데 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뭔데 뭔데 너한테 난 <br>뭔데 뭔데 도대체 왜 <br>이러는 건데 <br>네가 보자던 영화관 앞에서 <br>1시간째 난 기다리고 있잖아 <br>이럴 거면 왜 나한테 호감 줬어 <br>내 마음 헷갈리게 <br>숨 막히니깐 그냥 네가 말 좀 해줘 <br>넌 어장이라고 <br>넌 날 가지고 놀고 있지 <br>수많은 남자 속에서 <br>그냥 난 한 마리일 뿐이고 <br>그런 넌 웃으면서 내게 말하지 <br>네가 너무 마음에 든다고 <br>나는 거기에서 또 허우적거리지 <br>뭔데 뭔데 너에게 난 <br>뭔데 뭔데 왜 이렇게 <br>멀어지는 건데 <br>네가 만나자는 그 날만 <br>늘 밤새 나 혼자 기다리고 있잖아 <br>이럴 거면 왜 나한테 호감 줬어 <br>내 마음 헷갈리게 <br>숨 막히니깐 그냥 네가 말 좀 해줘 <br>넌 어장이라고 <br>넌 날 가지고 놀고 있지 <br>수많은 남자 속에서 <br>그냥 난 한 마리일 뿐이고 <br>그런 넌 웃으면서 내게 말하지 <br>네가 너무 마음에 든다고 <br>나는 거기에서 또 허우적거리지 <br>나도 잘 알고 있어 <br>네가 내게서 느끼는 것들을 <br>알고 있으면서도 왜 그러는 걸까 <br>있잖아 있잖아 그냥 <br>이유는 없는 것 같아 <br>너에게 빠진 거겠지 <br>넌 날 가지고 놀고 있지 <br>수많은 남자 속에서 <br>그냥 난 한 마리일 뿐이고 <br>그런 넌 웃으면서 내게 말하지 <br>네가 너무 마음에 든다고 <br>나는 거기에서 또 허우적거리지 <br>넌 날 가지고 놀고 있지 <br>수많은 남자 속에서 <br>그냥 난 한 마리일 뿐이고 <br>그런 넌 웃으면서 내게 말하지 <br>네가 너무 마음에 든다고 <br>나는 거기에서 또 허우적거리지 <br>]]></content><category term="스트레이 (The Stray)" label="스트레이 (The Stray)"/><category term="뭔데" label="뭔데"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스트레이_The_Stray/내_손을_잡아/</id><title>스트레이_The_Stray - 내 손을 잡아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:37:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:37:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_The_Stray/%EB%82%B4_%EC%86%90%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%A1%EC%95%84/" title="스트레이_The_Stray - 내 손을 잡아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나에게만 보여 <br>힘든 모습이 <br>티 나진 않을까 <br>애써 웃어보이는 너 <br>하지만 내 눈엔 <br>네가 다 보여 <br>오 너 <br>모든 게 낯설게만 <br>느껴질 꺼야 <br>하지만 넌 <br>견딜 수 있을 거야 <br>나와 함께라면 <br>내 손을 잡아 <br>행복을 줄게 <br>내 손을 잡아 <br>이대로 영원히 <br>네 마음이 보여 <br>순수할 줄 알았던 <br>세상에 대한 배신감 <br>오 너 <br>그 모든 짐 풀어 <br>내게 나누어줘 <br>내 손을 잡아 <br>행복을 줄게 <br>내 손을 잡아 <br>이대로 영원히 <br>아무 말 하지 않아도 <br>서로의 눈빛만으로도 <br>나는 널 느낄 수 있어 <br>너와 나 함께 한다는 걸 <br>네 모습 있는 그대로 <br>받아들일 준비돼 있어 <br>너의 모든 걱정 뒤로한 채 <br>나와 함께 한다면 <br>내 손을 잡아 <br>행복을 줄게 <br>내 손을 잡아 <br>이대로 영원히 <br>]]></content><category term="스트레이 (The Stray)" label="스트레이 (The Stray)"/><category term="내 손을 잡아" label="내 손을 잡아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스트레이_The_Stray/PARADISE/</id><title>스트레이_The_Stray - PARADISE - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:37:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:37:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_The_Stray/PARADISE/" title="스트레이_The_Stray - PARADISE - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[PARADISE 내가 네 품 안에 <br>안겨 있을 때 느낄 수 있는 그 감정 <br>바로 그 곳 PARADISE <br>따뜻한 널 바라볼 수만 <br>있는 것만으로도 <br>내겐 너무나도 축복이야 <br>그래 바로 너 PARADISE <br>힘들 때나 지칠 때나 <br>언제나 내 곁에 있어 <br>보잘것없는 날 감싸주는 <br>네가 네가 네가 있어 <br>행복할 때도 기쁠 때도 <br>언제나 내 곁에 있어 <br>예쁜 미소로 날 반겨주는 <br>네가 네가 네가 있어 <br>넌 나의 PARADISE PARADISE <br>love you love you <br>너라는 천국에 갇혀서 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>넌 나의 PARADISE PARADISE <br>love you love you <br>너라는 천국에 갇혀서 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>힘들 때나 지칠 때나 <br>언제나 내 곁에 있어 <br>보잘것없는 날 감싸주는 <br>네가 네가 네가 있어 <br>행복할 때도 기쁠 때도 <br>언제나 내 곁에 있어 <br>예쁜 미소로 날 반겨주는 <br>네가 네가 네가 있어 <br>넌 나의 PARADISE PARADISE <br>love you love you <br>너라는 천국에 갇혀서 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>넌 나의 PARADISE PARADISE <br>love you love you <br>너라는 천국에 갇혀서 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>잊지 않아 네가 준 사랑과 <br>그 따뜻한 감정에 대해서 baby <br>울지 않아 네가 없던 그날처럼 <br>우울함에 빠질 때에도 <br>네가 있어서 네가 있어서 <br>내 옆에 함께 있어서 함께 있어서 <br>나는 더욱더 강해졌어 <br>너의 품 안에 있는 난 <br>넌 나의 PARADISE PARADISE <br>love you love you <br>너라는 천국에 갇혀서 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>넌 나의 PARADISE PARADISE <br>love you love you <br>너라는 천국에 갇혀서 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>시간이 멈췄으면 해 <br>]]></content><category term="스트레이 (The Stray)" label="스트레이 (The Stray)"/><category term="PARADISE" label="PARADISE"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스트레이_The_Stray/bye_bye/</id><title>스트레이_The_Stray - bye bye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:37:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:37:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_The_Stray/bye_bye/" title="스트레이_The_Stray - bye bye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지친 하루의 끝에 네가 서 있을 때 <br>날 위로해주는 <br>너의 따뜻한 목소리 <br>매일 늘어만 가는 나의 투정 섞인 <br>어리광마저 받아주는 <br>너의 큰 그림자 <br>이제야 날 감싸 안아주던 <br>네 모습이 <br>나의 심장을 두드리면 뭘 해 <br>이미 내 곁에 없는 <br>네 뒷모습만 그리워하네 <br>그래 bye bye bye bye bye bye bye <br>너의 기억을 잊어 <br>이제 내 가슴 한켠에 <br>그래 bye bye bye bye bye bye bye <br>그때 추억들만 안고 <br>계속 살아가 이렇게 난 <br>너와 함께한 추억 그 많은 행복들 <br>따스했던 기억은 <br>날 놓아주지 않아 <br>우리 함께 떠났던 수많은 여행들 <br>추억 속에 지쳐가는 <br>내 자신이 싫어 <br>이제야 날 바라봐주던 <br>너의 모습이 <br>나의 심장을 두드리면 뭘 해 <br>이미 내 곁에 없는 <br>네 뒷모습만 그리워하네 <br>그래 bye bye bye bye bye bye bye <br>너의 기억을 잊어 <br>이제 내 가슴 한켠에 <br>그래 bye bye bye bye bye bye bye <br>그때 추억들만 안고 <br>계속 살아가 이렇게 난 <br>우리 다시 돌아갈 수 없을까 <br>너에게 한 걸음씩 <br>다가갈 순 없을까 <br>다시 내게 돌아와 <br>내 손을 붙잡아줘 <br>나와 같은 생각이었으면 <br>그래 bye bye bye bye bye bye bye <br>너의 기억을 잊어 <br>이제 내 가슴 한켠에 <br>그래 bye bye bye bye bye bye bye <br>그때 추억들만 안고 <br>계속 살아가 이렇게 난 <br>]]></content><category term="스트레이 (The Stray)" label="스트레이 (The Stray)"/><category term="bye bye" label="bye bye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스트레이_The_Stray/짙어_Feat_Kriz/</id><title>스트레이_The_Stray - 짙어 (Feat. Kriz) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:37:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:37:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_The_Stray/%EC%A7%99%EC%96%B4_Feat_Kriz/" title="스트레이_The_Stray - 짙어 (Feat. Kriz) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈을 마주쳐도 <br>아무 말 없이 바라보네 <br>너와 나의 감정이 <br>익숙해진 것 같아 것 같아 뭣 같아 <br>입을 맞춰 봐도 <br>너를 껴안아 봐도 쓰다듬어 봐도 <br>너무 편해진 건지 떨리지 않아 <br>넌 내게 너무나 짙어 <br>하지만 영원할 순 없어 <br>우리 사이 너무나 짙어 <br>하지만 위태로워 보여 <br>Don't don't don't you get no <br>지금 이 감정을 <br>Keep keep keep in your mind <br>We cannot go back anymore <br>Don't don't don't you get no <br>이런 감정이 넌 뭔지 <br>Keep keep keep in your mind <br>We cannot go back anymore <br>손을 잡아봐도 oh I don't know <br>우린 아무 느낌 없이 스쳐가네 <br>대체 뭘하고 있는지 oh my baby <br>설렜던 감정이 조금 <br>무뎌진 것 같아 것 같아 뭣 같아 oh <br>분위기를 잡아도 <br>무드 있게 가려 노력해도 <br>너무 가까워 진 건지 <br>between us black and dot 보이지 않아 <br>내 가슴속에 뒤엉켜 <br>까매진 감정들을 <br>흐르는 물에 끝도 없이 풀어 <br>넌 내게 너무나 짙어 <br>하지만 영원할 순 없어 <br>우리 사이 너무나 짙어 <br>하지만 위태로워 보여 <br>Don't don't don't you get no <br>지금 이 감정을 <br>Keep keep keep in your mind <br>We cannot go back anymore <br>Don't don't don't you get no <br>이런 감정이 넌 뭔지 <br>Keep keep keep in your mind <br>We cannot go back anymore <br>특별한 감정이라고 생각했어 <br>지치고 항상 반복되는 일이라도 <br>남들과는 다를 거라고 생각했어 <br>우리만큼 짙지 않을 거라고 <br>넌 내게 너무나 짙어 <br>하지만 영원할 순 없어 <br>우리 사이 너무나 짙어 <br>하지만 위태로워 보여 <br>Don't don't don't you get no <br>지금 이 감정을 <br>Keep keep keep in your mind <br>We cannot go back anymore <br>Don't don't don't you get no <br>이런 감정이 넌 뭔지 <br>Keep keep keep in your mind <br>We cannot go back anymore <br>]]></content><category term="스트레이 (The Stray)" label="스트레이 (The Stray)"/><category term="짙어 (Feat. Kriz)" label="짙어 (Feat. Kriz)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스트레이_The_Stray/Lonely/</id><title>스트레이_The_Stray - Lonely - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:37:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:37:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_The_Stray/Lonely/" title="스트레이_The_Stray - Lonely - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[네가 생각날 때면 <br>그 길을 혼자 걷곤 했어 <br>너와 손을 잡았던 <br>그때 그날들이 떠올라 <br>난 널 보고 싶어 <br>우연히라도 스치고 싶어 <br>너에겐 할 말이 너무 많아 <br>왜 날 떠났는지 <br>말없이 왜 떠났는지 <br>남자는 생겼는지 <br>Lonely Lonely 그때 내가 정말 <br>왜 그랬을까 난 후회가 돼 <br>Lonely Lonely 네 마음속에서 <br>내가 사라지지 않았기를 <br>너의 집 앞에서 난 혼자 <br>서성이고 그랬어 <br>마주칠 수 있을까 헛된 <br>생각들이 떠올라 날 힘들게 해 <br>난 널 보고싶어 <br>우연히라도 스치고 싶어 <br>너에겐 할말이 너무 많아 <br>왜 날 떠났는지 <br>말없이 왜 떠났는지 <br>남자는 생겼는지 <br>Lonely Lonely 그때 내가 정말 <br>왜 그랬을까 난 후회가 돼 <br>Lonely Lonely 네 마음속에서 <br>내가 사라지지 않았기를 <br>나를 지우지 말아줘 <br>나를 계속 간직해줘 <br>지금 내 말이 크나큰 <br>욕심이라는 걸 나도 잘 알고 있어 <br>언젠가 다시 볼 수도 있으니 <br>그때까지 부탁해 <br>Lonely Lonely 그때 내가 정말 <br>왜 그랬을까 난 후회가 돼 <br>Lonely Lonely 네 마음속에서 <br>내가 사라지지 않았기를 <br>Lonely Lonely 그때 내가 정말 <br>왜 그랬을까 난 후회가 돼 <br>Lonely Lonely 네 마음속에서 <br>내가 사라지지 않았기를 <br>]]></content><category term="스트레이 (The Stray)" label="스트레이 (The Stray)"/><category term="Lonely" label="Lonely"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daddy_Yankee/Shaky_Shaky_Remix/</id><title>Daddy_Yankee - Shaky Shaky (Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:38:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:38:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daddy_Yankee/Shaky_Shaky_Remix/" title="Daddy_Yankee - Shaky Shaky (Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tamo en vivo! <br><br>Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky (4x) <br>Como es dame una vueltita otra vez! <br><br>(Nicky Jam) <br><br>El Nicky Jam Daddy Yankee con el shaky solo piensalo <br>vamos pa la disco mami muevelo <br>esta es la musica pa’ guayar mahon tu y yo tu y yo tu y yo <br><br>El Nicky Jam Daddy Yankee con el shaky solo piensalo <br>vamos pa la disco mami muevelo <br>esta es la musica pa’ guayar mahon <br>este es el remix <br><br>Dale al shaky nos fuimo a lo equi <br>ando con pal de amigas la susana y la becky <br>ellas estan pa lo oscuro no le gustan los fequi <br>ya me traje la tequi pa bajarle la sequi <br><br>bien loquita se pone la gatita <br>se puso caliente cuando suena la musica <br>esta noche Yankee yo no corro con etica <br>pero las dejamos si se ponen patetica <br><br>(Daddy) <br><br>Hula Hoop HUla <br>Hula Hoop HUla <br>HUla Hoop HUla <br>Cintura dura dura <br><br>Ella le mete al terremoto <br>forma sendo alboroto <br>con ella gane la lotto <br>me noquea a lo miguel cotto <br>bailando es la presidenta <br>yo por mi te doy el voto <br>saquen to los celulares graben y tirenle fotos al <br><br>(2X) <br>Hula Hoop HUla <br>Hula Hoop HUla <br>HUla Hoop HUla <br>Cintura y nos fuimos con el <br><br><br>Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky (4x) <br>Como es Daddy Yankee Nicky Otra vez <br><br>Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky (4x) <br>Tu la vez como hace lo suyo tu la vez <br><br>(Chencho) <br><br>Lo de ella y lo mio es cosa de pana <br>no hay compromiso por que ella es malvada <br>se nota en su cara que la mente trama <br>Shaky Shaky Shaky hasta por la manana <br><br>(Maldy) <br><br>Por dentro tiene ella la musica <br>y cada video que sube con su movimiento <br>tiene a medio mundo envuelto con una soltura unica <br>reduplica deseos que a muchas llena de celo <br>a otras les causa desvelo <br>facil tu mente desubica <br>Shaky shaky matadora <br>en busca de una encerrona <br>famosita en su instagram buscale frikitona <br>provocadora bailando de forma tentadora <br>que no demora y me pregona la demoledora y terremoto dile chencho!! <br><br>(Chencho) <br><br>tus ojos me hablaron y me lo piden a lo sadico <br>rusticos con ganas de hacer momentos epicos <br>sexo sin palabras con un deseo erratico <br>crearon humedad a ver tu movimiento pelvico <br>labia anti poetica pa no verme antipatico <br>provocando que no entraras ni en miedo ni en panico <br>tu lengua de elastico que pida a grito un satiro <br>que te rompa la ropa y te lo haga pornografico <br><br><br>(Daddy Yankee) <br><br>(2X) <br>Hula Hoop HUla <br>Hula Hoop HUla <br>HUla Hoop HUla <br>Cintura y nos fuimos con el <br><br>Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky (4x) <br>Como es dame una vueltita otra vez <br><br>Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky Shaky (4x) <br>Como es Daddy Yankee Nicky Otra vez]]></content><category term="Daddy Yankee" label="Daddy Yankee"/><category term="Shaky Shaky (Remix)" label="Shaky Shaky (Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전인권/사랑한_후에/</id><title>전인권 - 사랑한 후에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:39:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:39:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EC%9D%B8%EA%B6%8C/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%9C_%ED%9B%84%EC%97%90/" title="전인권 - 사랑한 후에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[긴 하루 지나고 <br>언덕 저 편에 <br>빨간 석양이 <br>물들어 가면 <br>놀던 아이들은 <br>아무 걱정 없이 <br>집으로 하나 둘씩 <br>돌아가는데 <br>나는 왜 여기 서 있나 <br>저 석양은 <br>나를 깨우고 <br>밤이 내 앞에 <br>다시 다가오는데 <br>이젠 잊어야만 하는 <br>내 아픈 기억이 <br>별이 되어 반짝이며 <br>나를 흔드네 <br>저기 철길 위를 <br>달리는 기차의 <br>커다란 울음으로도 <br>달랠 수 없어 <br>나는 왜 여기 <br>서 있나 <br>오늘 밤엔 <br>수많은 별이 <br>기억들이 <br>내 앞에 다시 <br>춤을 추는데 <br>어디서 왔는지 <br>내 머리위로 <br>작은 새 한 마리 <br>날아가네 <br>어느새 밝아온 <br>새벽하늘이 <br>다른 하루를 <br>재촉하는데 <br>종소리는 <br>맑게 퍼지고 <br>저 불빛은 <br>누굴 위한 걸까 <br>새벽이 내 앞에 <br>다시 설레이는데 <br>]]></content><category term="전인권" label="전인권"/><category term="사랑한 후에" label="사랑한 후에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Die_A_Happy_Man_The_Remix_Feat_Tori_Kelly/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Die A Happy Man (The Remix) (Feat. Tori Kelly) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Die_A_Happy_Man_The_Remix_Feat_Tori_Kelly/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Die A Happy Man (The Remix) (Feat. Tori Kelly) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby last night was hands down <br>One of the best nights <br>That I've had no doubt <br>Between the bottle of wine <br>And the look in your eyes and the Marvin Gaye <br>Then we danced in the dark under September stars <br>In the pourin' rain <br><br>And I know that I can't ever tell you enough <br>That all I need in this life is your crazy love <br><br>If I never get to see the Northern lights <br>Or if I never get to see the Eiffel Tower at night <br>Oh if all I got is your hand in my hand <br>Baby I could die a happy man <br>Yeah <br><br>Baby that red dress mmm brings me to my knees <br>Oh but that black dress makes it hard to breathe no, baby <br>You're a saint, you're a goddess, the cutest, the hottest <br>A masterpiece <br>It's too good to be true, nothing better than you <br>In my wildest dreams <br><br>And I know that I can't ever tell you enough <br>That all I need in this life is your crazy love <br><br>If I never get to see the Northern lights <br>Or if I never get to see the Eiffel Tower at night <br>Oh if all I got is your hand in my hand <br>Baby I could die a happy man yeah <br>Oh <br><br>I don't need no vacation, no fancy destination <br>Baby you're my great escape <br>We could stay at home, listen to the radio <br>Or dance around the fireplace <br><br>And if I never get to build my mansion in Georgia <br>Or drive a sports car up the coast of California <br>Well if all I got is your hand in my hand <br>Baby I could die oh a happy man <br><br>Baby I could die a happy man <br>Oh, I could die a happy man <br>Oh <br>You know I could, darling <br>I could die, I could die a happy man <br>I could die, yeah <br>Baby I could die a happy man]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Die A Happy Man (The Remix) (Feat. Tori Kelly)" label="Die A Happy Man (The Remix) (Feat. Tori Kelly)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Playing_With_Fire_Feat_Danielle_Bradbery/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Playing With Fire (Feat. Danielle Bradbery) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Playing_With_Fire_Feat_Danielle_Bradbery/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Playing With Fire (Feat. Danielle Bradbery) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know I should let it go <br>Take a different road <br>When I'm driving home <br>But I don't want to <br>Delete your number from my phone <br>Instead of calling <br>Asking if you're all alone <br>But I don't want to <br><br>Stay away <br>From your side of town <br>But it's too late <br>I'm in your drive right now <br><br>I don't know, why I don't <br>Put it out baby <br>We kiss and the flames <br>Just get higher <br>But yeah I know <br>When I hold onto you baby <br>I'm all tangled up in barbed wire <br>I get burned, I don't learn <br>I'll be back, give it time <br>Yeah, I know it sounds crazy <br>But guess I like playing with fire <br><br>I could find a spot to <br>Go hang out on Friday night <br>Where you are gonna be <br>But I don't want to, no <br>I could let it end <br>Call it quits, call off <br>All this on and off again <br>But I just don't want to <br><br>Yeah that key <br>Is right under the mat <br>Come on in, baby <br>Let's strike that match <br><br>I don't know, why I don't <br>Put it out baby <br>We kiss and the flames <br>Just get higher <br>But yeah I know <br>When I hold onto you baby <br>I'm all tangled up in barbed wire <br>I get burned, I don't learn <br>I'll be back, give it time <br>Yeah, I know it sounds crazy <br>But guess I like playing with fire <br>Playing with fire <br><br>So let's fire it up one more time <br>Fire it up one more time <br>Baby just put your lips on mine <br>Lips on mine <br><br>I don't know, why I don't <br>Put it out baby <br>We kiss and the flames <br>Just get higher <br>We kiss and the flames <br>Just get higher <br>But yeah I know <br>When I hold onto you baby <br>Onto you baby <br>I'm all tangled up in barbed wire <br>All tangled up <br>I'm all tangled up <br>I get burned, I don't learn <br>I'll be back, give it time <br>Give it time <br>Yeah, I know it sounds crazy <br>Sounds crazy <br>But guess I like playing with fire <br>Playing with fire <br>Playing with fire <br>Playing with fire <br><br>Playing with fire, huh]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Playing With Fire (Feat. Danielle Bradbery)" label="Playing With Fire (Feat. Danielle Bradbery)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Background_Music/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Background Music - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Background_Music/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Background Music - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well it's shoulder to shoulder in here tonight <br>Got bottles poppin', floor is rockin', packed in tight <br>It's hot, and it's hazy <br>It's loud, and it's crazy <br>Girl, when you take my hand <br>You don't even understand <br><br>Everything that's going on is just background music <br>And everything except you girl just fades away <br>It's like me and you, are the only two <br>Dancin' 'round this crowded room <br>So, tell me how you do it tell me how do you do it <br>Turning everything into background music <br>Tell me how you do it tell me how do you do it <br>Turning everything <br>Into background music background music <br>Hey hey hey <br><br>Girl it don't matter where we really are <br>Your face outshines the moon, the sun, and stars hey, hey <br>Baby your eyes are like diamonds <br>And your smile's so blindin' <br>I could be front row at the stones <br>And I wouldn't even know they're on <br><br>Everything that's going on is just background music <br>And everything except you girl just fades away <br>It's like me and you, are the only two <br>Dancin' 'round this crowded room <br>So, tell me how you do it tell me how do you do it <br>Turning everything into background music <br>Tell me how you do it tell me how do you do it <br>Turning everything into background music <br>Tell me how you do it tell me how you do it <br>Turning everything into background music <br>Tell me how you do it tell me how you do it <br>Turning everything into background music <br><br>Oh baby girl, you know you got all my attention <br>Ain't even gotta say a word cause baby I miss it <br>Everything that's goin on is just background music background music <br>Everything except you girl just fades away fades away <br>It's like me and you, are the only two <br>Dancin' 'round this crowded room <br><br>Everything that's going on is just background music <br>And everything except you girl just fades away <br>It's like me and you, are the only two <br>Dancin' 'round this crowded room <br>So, tell me how you do it tell me how do you do it <br>Turning everything into background music <br>Tell me how you do it tell me how do you do it <br>Turning everything into background music <br>Tell me how you do it tell me how you do it <br>Turning everything into background music <br>Tell me how you do it tell me how you do it <br>Turning everything into background music]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Background Music" label="Background Music"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/American_Spirit/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - American Spirit - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/American_Spirit/" title="Thomas_Rhett - American Spirit - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ridin' down red dirt, drivin' in a white truck, lookin' at a pretty blue sky <br>Tired eyed kids playin' in a sprinkler, daddy drinkin' cold budlight <br>Talk about a big life in a small town, ain't got a lot <br>But we sure found what we were looking for <br><br>Georgia red lipstick, tied white tanktop, Levi denim blue eyes <br>Bottle rockets blowin' up, hot dogs servin' up, it ain't even fourth of July <br>That's just how it is 'round here and we love it <br>We wouldn't trade it all in for nothin' more <br><br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>It's in the song, baby can't you feel it <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>And if you can't baby, listen to the lyrics <br>It's Friday night freedom, football game <br>It's proud of where you from, it's your last name <br>It's thirteen stripes and fifty stars in the wind <br>So hold up your beer and holler if you hear it <br>That American spirit <br><br>Old red six string, white piece of paper, scribbled down lovin' blue ink <br>Sweet pretty girl, sweet southern melody, sweep her right off of her feet <br>It's a preacher, it's a , it's a ring on a finger and a bible <br>And a on a fixer up house <br><br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>It's in the song, baby can't you feel it <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>And if you can't baby, listen to the lyrics <br>It's Friday night freedom, football game <br>It's proud of where you from, it's your last name <br>It's thirteen stripes and fifty stars in the wind <br>So hold up your beer and holler if you hear it <br>That American spirit <br><br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>It's in the song, baby can't you feel it <br>Oh oh oh oh oh <br>And if you can't baby, listen to the lyrics <br>It's Friday night freedom, football game <br>It's proud of where you from, it's your last name <br>It's thirteen stripes and fifty stars in the wind <br>So hold up your beer and holler if you hear it <br>That American spirit <br><br>Ridin' down red dirt, drivin' in a white truck, lookin' at a pretty blue sky]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="American Spirit" label="American Spirit"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Star_Of_The_Show/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Star Of The Show - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Star_Of_The_Show/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Star Of The Show - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Walking down the street, hand in mine <br>It don't keep them other guys <br>And their wandering eyes from looking at you <br>That's alright and that's okay <br>Who can blame 'em anyway <br>You're so pretty, and you ain't even got a clue <br><br>Cause everywhere we go girl <br>You're the star of the show <br>And everybody's wondering and wanting to know <br>What's your name <br>Who's that girl, with the prettiest smile in the world <br>Oh, what gets me the most is you don't even know <br>That you are, you are, you are <br>The star of the show <br>You're the star of the show, yeah, baby <br><br>Friday night on the town <br>We walk in and you draw a crowd <br>Even the band seems to sing for you <br>Ease on up, order a drink, barkeep says its all on me <br>You look at me and laugh <br>Like you don't know what to do <br>Baby you're so cute <br><br>Cause everywhere we go girl <br>You're the star of the show <br>And everybody's wondering and wanting to know <br>Whats your name <br>Who's that girl, with the prettiest smile in the world <br>Oh, what gets me the most is you don't even know <br>That you are, you are, you are <br>The star of the show, yeah <br>You're the star of the show, baby, yeah yeah <br><br>Even in a ponytail in a pair of jeans you look like a cover <br>Of a magazine, baby you're the only one who doesn't see <br><br>That everywhere we go girl <br>You're the star of the show <br>And everyone's wondering and wanting to know <br>Whats your name <br>Who's that girl with the luckiest guy in the world <br>Oh, what gets me the most is you don't even know <br>That you are, you are, you are <br>You are, you are, you are, baby <br>You are, you are, you are, you are <br>The star of the show <br><br>Don't you know, you're the star of the show, baby]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Star Of The Show" label="Star Of The Show"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Learned_It_From_The_Radio/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Learned It From The Radio - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Learned_It_From_The_Radio/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Learned It From The Radio - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How to be proud of that town ain't nobody heard of <br>Had a big dream, seventeen, some day how to grow up <br>How to make dust fly out on no name road <br>I learned it from the radio <br><br>How to wake up <br>How to work tough <br>How to roll up those sleeves <br>How to throw down <br>How to get loud <br>What to put in that drink <br>To give the stars in the sky a little halo <br>I learned it from the radio <br><br>If it wasn't for the speakers in the door <br>Telling me a truth I hadn't ever heard before <br>I never would have kissed that girl <br>Never would have known what to say <br>I would have never known better <br>I'd have let her get away <br><br>Thank God for 4 wheel drive <br>Thank God for windows down <br>And all the DJs in all those little static towns <br>How to live <br>How to love <br>Everything I need to know <br>I learned it from the radio <br><br>What to say when you think that you've found that girl <br>Who to call when she's gone and she wrecks your world <br>How to get over it yeah how to let her go <br>I learned it from the radio <br>How to see it all from a front porch <br>And how to say it all just using three chords <br>And when to run when you're young <br>When to come back home <br>I learned it from the radio <br><br>If it wasn't for the speakers in the door <br>Telling me a truth I hadn't ever heard before <br>I never would have kissed that girl <br>Never would have known what to say <br>I would have never known better <br>I'd have let her get away <br><br>Thank God for 4 wheel drive <br>Thank God for windows down <br>And all the DJs in all those little static towns <br>How to live <br>How to love <br>Everything I need to know <br>I learned it from the radio <br><br>From the radio <br>I learned it form the radio <br>Back when we use to burn it up, turn it up up up up <br><br>If it wasn't for the speakers in the door <br>Telling me a truth I haven't ever heard before <br>I never would have kissed that girl <br>Never would have known what to say <br>I would have never known better <br>I'd have let her get away <br><br>Thank God for 4 wheel drive <br>Thank God for windows down <br>And all the DJs in all those little static towns <br>How to live <br>How to love <br>Everything I need to know <br>I learned it from the radio <br><br>Mmmm, from the radio <br>I learned it from the radio <br>Back when we use to burn it up <br>Turn it up]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Learned It From The Radio" label="Learned It From The Radio"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/I_Feel_Good_Feat_Lunchmoney_Lewis/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - I Feel Good (Feat. Lunchmoney Lewis) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/I_Feel_Good_Feat_Lunchmoney_Lewis/" title="Thomas_Rhett - I Feel Good (Feat. Lunchmoney Lewis) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ray Bans on that sky is blue <br>Cannonball into the pool <br>Drink in hand goin' act a fool like sha la la <br>Boombox playin' that third eye blind <br>Wife is sippin' that rose wine <br>I just lost all track of time like sha la la <br><br>My truck A C is broken <br>That Georgia breeze is blowin' <br>I'm feelin' easy goin' that's right <br><br>I feel good, today <br>can't nobody bring me down <br>I just got paid, and I think I'm gonna hit the town <br>Yeah my problems can wait til tomorrow <br>cause I feel good today yeah <br>can't nobody bring me down <br>can't nobody bring me <br><br>Uh excuse me can someone bring the beat back <br><br>My team won in overtime <br>I'm three sheets on bud light lime <br>Don't taste good but that's alright now <br>It ain't even Saturday <br>But I'm gonna celebrate <br>So don't you rain on my parade now, no no <br><br>My truck A C is broken <br>That Georgia breeze is blowin' <br>I'm feelin' easy goin' that's right <br><br>I feel good, today <br>can't nobody bring me down <br>I just got paid, and I think I'm gonna hit the town <br>Yeah my problems can wait til tomorrow <br>cause I feel good today yeah <br>can't nobody bring me down <br><br>Lunchmoney Lewis <br>Down I feel good, James Brown <br>turn the lights low turn the music up loud <br>got a good party goin' on back at the house <br>Bunch of big booty girls yeah they come from the south <br>The good vibes when you feelin' it <br>Whoever made potato salad put they foot in it <br>I know we ain't the same yeah we different <br>But we all stay connected like the internet <br><br>I got no motivation <br>Except for recreation <br>Feels like I'm on vacation that's right <br><br>I feel good, today <br>can't nobody bring me down <br>I just got paid, and I think I'm gonna hit the town <br>Yeah my problems can wait til tomorrow <br>cause I feel good today yeah, can't nobody bring me down <br>Can't nobody bring me]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="I Feel Good (Feat. Lunchmoney Lewis)" label="I Feel Good (Feat. Lunchmoney Lewis)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Playing_With_Fire_Feat_Jordin_Sparks/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Playing With Fire (Feat. Jordin Sparks) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Playing_With_Fire_Feat_Jordin_Sparks/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Playing With Fire (Feat. Jordin Sparks) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know I should let it go <br>Take a different road <br>When I'm driving home <br>But I don't want to <br><br>Delete your number from my phone <br>Instead of calling <br>Asking if you're all alone <br>But I don't want to <br><br>Stay away <br>From your side of town <br>But it's too late <br>I'm in your drive right now <br><br>I don't know, why I don't <br>Put it out baby <br>We kiss and the flames <br>Just get higher <br>But yeah I know <br>When I hold onto you baby <br>I'm all tangled up in barbed wire <br>I get burned, I don't learn <br>I'll be back, give it time <br>Yeah, I know it sounds crazy <br>But guess I like playing with fire <br><br>I could find a spot to <br>Go hang out on Friday night <br>Where you are gonna be <br>But I don't want to, no <br><br>Yeah, I could let it end <br>Call it quits, call off <br>All this on and off again <br>But I just don't want to <br><br>Yeah that key <br>Is right under the mat <br>Come on in, baby <br>Let's strike that match <br><br>I don't know, why I don't <br>Put it out baby <br>We kiss and the flames <br>Just get higher <br>But yeah I know <br>When I hold onto you baby <br>I'm all tangled up in barbed wire <br>I get burned, I don't learn <br>I'll be back, give it time <br>Yeah, I know it sounds crazy <br>But guess I like playing with fire <br>Playing with fire <br><br>So let's fire it up one more time <br>Fire it up one more time <br>Baby just put your lips on mine <br>Lips on mine <br><br>I don't know, why I don't <br>Put it out baby <br>We kiss and the flames <br>Just get higher <br>We kiss and the flames <br>Just get higher <br>But yeah I know <br>When I hold onto you baby <br>Onto you baby <br>I'm all tangled up in barbed wire <br>All tangled up <br>I'm all tangled up <br>I get burned, I don't learn <br>I'll be back, give it time <br>Give it time <br>Yeah, I know it sounds crazy <br>Sounds crazy <br>But guess I like playing with fire <br>Playing with fire <br>Playing with fire <br>Playing with fire <br><br>Playing with fire, huh]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Playing With Fire (Feat. Jordin Sparks)" label="Playing With Fire (Feat. Jordin Sparks)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Tangled/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Tangled - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Tangled/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Tangled - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm tangled in your arms <br>And in my head and in my bed again <br>And wreckin' me in pieces on the floor <br>I'm tangled in your smile <br>You drive me wild for just a while <br>I think that I'll keep you from walkin' out that door <br>I, I wanna say <br><br>I want more than what this is <br>My lips are busy kissin' you <br>So I'd just like to stay <br>One more night in paradise <br>It feels so right to me 'cause girl <br><br>I'm tangled up <br>I can't ever get too much <br>I'm tangled up <br>Ah, baby what you do to me <br>I'm tangled up <br>You give me just enough of your love <br>To keep me tangled up <br>And I don't wanna be free <br><br>Girl you got me tangled <br>Girl you got me tangled <br>Girl you got me tangled <br>Up <br>I'm in <br>I'm tangled in your sheets <br>I can't compete your sugar tastes so sweet <br>I want it girl again, and again <br>I, I wanna say <br>I want more than what this is <br>My lips are busy kissin' you <br>So I'd just like to stay <br>One more night in paradise <br>It feels so right to me 'cause girl <br><br>I'm tangled up <br>I can't ever get too much <br>I'm tangled up <br>Ah, baby what you do to me <br>I'm tangled up <br>You give me just enough of your love <br>To keep me tangled up <br>And I don't wanna be free <br><br>Tangled up, oh <br>Tangled up, oh <br>Up <br>So I'd just like to stay <br>One more night in paradise <br>It feels so right to me girl <br>Baby <br><br>I'm tangled up <br>I can't ever get too much <br>I'm tangled up <br>Ah, baby what you do to me <br>I'm tangled up <br>You give me just enough of your love <br>To keep me tangled up <br>And I don't wanna be free <br><br>Tangled up, oh <br>Tangled up, oh <br>Tangled up, oh <br>Girl you got me tangled, girl you got me tangled <br>Tangled up <br>That's right I can't ever get too much <br>I'm tangled up <br>Tangled up <br>That's right I can't ever get too much <br>I'm tangled up]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Tangled" label="Tangled"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/The_Day_You_Stop_Lookin_Back/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - The Day You Stop Lookin` Back - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/The_Day_You_Stop_Lookin_Back/" title="Thomas_Rhett - The Day You Stop Lookin` Back - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stop starin' at the rear view <br>You ain't checkin' your hair <br>That wheel has spun and them lights are out <br>There ain't nothin' for you back there <br>Stop holdin' on so dang tight, 'bout time you let go <br>Well he's a heart breakin', let you down son of a gun <br>But I ain't sayin' nothin' you don't know <br>Well <br><br>The day that you stop lookin' back <br>You're gonna find that the future <br>Sure beats the hell outta the past <br>Now he ain't no good <br>I guess he's good as gone <br>The day you stop lookin' back, girl yeah <br>Is the day you start movin' on, yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>That sun's gonna come up <br>It's gonna feel good <br>And after all the rain and pain you've seen <br>I hope you soak it up like you should <br>Now and then it's gonna stir up <br>But when you hear that old song <br>But don't let it get to ya baby <br>It's only three and a half minutes long <br>Well <br><br>The day that you stop lookin' back <br>You're gonna find that the future <br>Sure beats the hell outta the past <br>Now he ain't no good <br>I guess he's good as gone <br>The day you stop lookin' back, girl yeah <br>Is the day you start movin' on, yeah, yeah, yeah <br><br>Oh, oh oh <br><br>Well now hey girl why you lookin' back like that <br>Don't you wanna trade tears for laughs and love <br>That could be us tonight <br><br>The day that you stop lookin' back <br>You're gonna find that the future <br>Sure beats the hell outta the past <br>Now he ain't no good <br>I guess he's good as gone <br>The day you stop lookin' back, girl yeah <br>Is the day you start movin' on, yeah, yeah, yeah <br>Is the day you start movin' on <br><br>Stop staring at the rear view <br>You ain't checkin' your hair <br>That wheel is spun and them lights are out <br>There ain't nothin' for you back there]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="The Day You Stop Lookin` Back" label="The Day You Stop Lookin` Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Single_Girl/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Single Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Single_Girl/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Single Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Single girl <br>I know you're out there on a run <br>Out on a town baby havin' fun <br>But don't you want someone <br>Single girl <br>How long you wanna be all alone <br>Don't it get lonely baby on your own <br>Like a rolling stone, well I <br><br>I think that I could be the guy <br>Just what you're missin' baby in your life <br>By your side <br>When the nights get cold <br>And I could be there for you to hold <br>Oh baby ain't it gettin' old <br>Livin' in this lonely world <br>When you don't have to be single girl <br><br>Single girl <br>Aw you so pretty baby don't you know <br>You can have anybody that you want <br>So what you waitin' on <br>Tell me girl <br>That smile on your face is it for me <br>'Cause somethin' tells me that you're startin' to see <br>How it could be <br>When I <br><br>I think that I could be the guy <br>Just what you're missin' baby in your life <br>By your side <br>When the nights get cold <br>And I could be there for you to hold <br>Oh baby ain't it gettin' old <br>Livin' in this lonely world <br>When you don't have to be single girl <br><br>Oh single girl <br>Don't wanna rush you girl <br>But I promise you can trust me girl <br>When I tell you, when I tell you <br>That I <br><br>I think that I could be the guy <br>Just what you're missin' baby in your life <br>By your side <br>When the nights get cold <br>And I could be there for you to hold <br>Oh baby ain't it gettin' old <br>Livin' in this lonely world <br>When you don't have to be single girl <br><br>Oh no you don't have to be single girl]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Single Girl" label="Single Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/T-Shirt/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - T-Shirt - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/T-Shirt/" title="Thomas_Rhett - T-Shirt - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Get off of work and we meet down at our spot <br>We had a patio with a view of a parkin' lot <br>It was 2 for 1 and 4 for 2 <br>Had Christmas lights in the middle of June <br>All hung up, like I was on you <br><br>I say Hey, hey, baby do you wanna come over <br>You say No way, then you move in closer <br>Next thing I know you were in my <br><br>T Shirt, right there <br>Your hair, messed up like a Guns N Roses video <br>Oh, oh, so hot <br>Still got it up in my head, you were movin' around in the TV light <br>I ain't ever seen anything like your dress my floor the way you wore my, my T Shirt Yeah <br>You look good in my t shirt, girl <br>Oh yeah <br><br>We were walkin' up the stairs with the neighbors sayin', keep it down <br>But, it's hard to unlock the door when you're makin' out know what I'm sayin' <br>You've been sayin' that we've gotta quit doing this <br>So, why you leanin' in for one more kiss <br>And pretty soon you're sliding off what you've got on <br>And slippin' into my <br><br>T Shirt, right there <br>Your hair, messed up like a Guns N Roses video <br>Oh, oh, so hot <br>Still got it up in my head, you were movin' around in the TV light <br>I ain't ever seen anything like your dress my floor the way you wore my, my T Shirt in my t shirt <br><br>Oh no, baby no, I can't lie <br>Cause you sure look good in my t shirt <br>Oh no, baby no, I can't lie <br>You look g ood on my mind <br><br>I say Hey, hey, baby do you wanna come over <br>You say No way, then you move in closer <br>Next thing I know, you were in my T Shirt <br>Mmm, you look just so dang hot in my t shirt <br><br>I see you spinnin' around in my t shirt <br>Right there <br>Your hair, messed up like a Guns N Roses video <br>Oh, oh, so hot <br><br>In my T Shirt right there <br>Your hair, messed up like a Guns N Roses video <br>Oh, oh, so hot <br>Still got it up in my head, you were movin' around in the TV light <br>I ain't ever seen anything like your dress my floor the way you wore my, my T Shirt <br><br>Nah nah nah nah nah nah nah <br>You look good in my t shirt, baby <br>Yeah, you look so good in my t shirt <br>Yeah baby, you look good in my t shirt <br>Oh yes, you look so good in my t shirt <br>Nah nah nah nah nah nah nah]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="T-Shirt" label="T-Shirt"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Like_Its_The_Last_Time/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Like It`s The Last Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Like_Its_The_Last_Time/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Like It`s The Last Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Throw on your boots and your jeans <br>With the worn out seams <br>And your goin' out shirt <br>Put some shine on your truck <br>Get it all cleaned up <br>Just to kick it in the dirt <br>You put it in drive <br>Start comin' alive <br>You point them high beam lights into Friday night <br>And you swear this life never burns bright as it does right now <br><br>So soak it all up <br>Let it sink in crank it up loud <br>All the way to 10 <br>Raise your cup to the sky <br>Tip 'em back to friends <br>And let your party lights shine <br>On top of the world <br>In the back of the truck <br>Living like the sun <br>Ain't coming back up <br>Yeah buddy tonight <br>We're gonna do it up right <br>Gonna do it up right <br>Like its the last time <br><br>Build you a fire, sing along <br>To a feel good song <br>At the top of your lungs <br>Grab a jar, twist the top <br>Hold your breath, take a shot <br>Feel the fire on your tongue <br>And let it drown your pride and your butterflies <br>Tell the girl you like what you're feelin' tonight <br>And pull her in tight, let the sparks ignite <br>Like the Fourth of July <br><br>So soak it all up, let it sink in <br>Crank it up loud, all the way to 10 <br>Raise your cup to the sky <br>Tip 'em back to friends and let your party lights shine <br>On top of the world in the back of a truck <br>Livin' like the sun ain't comin' back up <br>Yeah, buddy tonight <br>We're gonna do it up right <br>Gonna do it up right <br>Like it's the last time <br><br>You'll ever be together like this <br>Like it's the last time <br>You're ever gonna taste that kiss <br><br>So soak it all up, let it sink in <br>Crank it up loud, all the way to 10 <br>Raise your cup to the sky <br>Tip 'em back to friends and let your party lights shine <br>On top of the world in the back of a truck <br>Livin' like the sun ain't comin' back up <br>Yeah, buddy tonight <br>We're gonna do it up right <br>Gonna do it up right <br><br>Yeah buddy tonight <br>We're gonna do it up right <br>Gonna do it up right <br>Whoah, like it's the last time <br>Yeah like it's the last time]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Like It`s The Last Time" label="Like It`s The Last Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Vacation/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Vacation - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Vacation/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Vacation - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My girl is rocking that Billabong bikini like she's sponsored <br>Asking me if I can rub that Coppertone on her <br>Got a couple bucks but I'm spending them like they pesos <br>Might be Motel Sixing but it feels like Turks and Caicos <br><br>Put a little liquor in my coconut water <br>Party all day like you at your alma mater <br>Put a little liquor in my coconut water <br>Ice has started melting cause it's always getting hotter <br><br>Singing hey, let's party like we on vacation <br>Hey, let's party like we on vacation <br>I got my toes up in the sand <br>Cold one in my hand <br>Toes up in the sand <br>Cold one in my hand <br>Singing hey, let's party like we on vacation <br><br>I got my Solo Cup amplifier, playing all my jams <br>And my Walgreens beach chair working on my tan <br>This like it's Jamaica and I'm sipping on some Red Stripe <br>But I'm in Decatur, baby, crushing on that Busch light <br><br>Hey, let's party like we on vacation <br>Hey, let's party like we on vacation <br>I got, I got, I got <br>Toes up in the sand <br>Cold one in my hand <br>Toes up in the sand <br>Cold one in my hand <br>Singing hey, let's party like we on vacation <br><br>Put a little liquor in my coconut water <br>Party all day like you at your alma mater <br>Put a little liquor in my coconut water <br>Ice has started melting so I'll take another swallow <br><br>Singing hey, let's party like we on vacation <br>Hey, let's party like we on vacation <br>You know I got my toes up in the sand <br>Cold one in my hand <br>Toes up in the sand <br>Cold one in my hand <br>Singing hey, let's party like we on vacation <br><br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh <br>Party like I'm on vacation <br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh <br>Party like I'm on vacation <br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh <br>Party like I'm on vacation <br>Oh oh oh, oh oh oh oh <br>I'm gonna rehydrate, while I dehydrate, you know <br><br>Singing hey, let's party like we on vacation <br>Hey, let's party like we on vacation <br>I got my toes up in the sand <br>Cold one in my hand <br>Toes up in the sand <br>Cold one in my hand <br>Singing hey, let's party like we on vacation <br><br>Sing it to me <br>Hey, let's party like we on vacation <br>Hey, party like we on vacation <br>Yeah dude, just party every time]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Vacation" label="Vacation"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Die_A_Happy_Man/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Die A Happy Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Die_A_Happy_Man/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Die A Happy Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby, last night was hands down <br>One of the best nights <br>That I've had no doubt <br>Between the bottle of wine <br>And the look in your eyes and the Marvin Gaye <br>Then we danced in the dark under September stars in the pourin' rain <br><br>And I know that I can't ever tell you enough <br>That all I need in this life is your crazy love <br><br>If I never get to see the Northern lights <br>Or if I never get to see the Eiffel Tower at night <br>Oh, if all I got is your hand in my hand <br>Baby, I could die a happy man <br><br>Happy man, baby <br>Mmm <br><br>Baby, that red dress brings me to my knees <br>Oh, but that black dress makes it hard to breathe <br>You're a saint, you're a Goddess <br>The cutest, the hottest <br>A masterpiece <br>It's too good to be true <br>Nothing better than you <br>In my wildest dreams <br><br>And I know that I can't ever tell you enough <br>That all I need in this life is your crazy love <br><br>If I never get to see the Northern lights <br>Or if I never get to see the Eiffel Tower at night <br>Oh, if all I got is your hand in my hand <br>Baby, I could die a happy man, yeah <br><br>I don't need no vacation <br>No fancy destination <br>Baby, you're my great escape <br>We could stay at home <br>Listen to the radio <br>Or dance around the fireplace <br><br>And if I never get to build my mansion in Georgia <br>Or drive a sports car up the coast of California <br>Oh, if all I got is your hand in my hand <br>Baby, I could die a happy man <br><br>Baby, I could die a happy man <br>Oh, I could die a happy man <br>You know I could girl <br>I could die, I could die a happy man]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Die A Happy Man" label="Die A Happy Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/South_Side/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - South Side - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/South_Side/" title="Thomas_Rhett - South Side - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Please commence shaking your south side <br><br>Thomas on that beat <br>Yeah <br>Ah ha Feels good <br><br>Ain't no place, it ain't going on <br>It's going around like a vagabond <br>It gets in your bones like you caught the flu nah there ain't no cure <br>You just gotta move, when you feel the groove <br><br>Now people on the left, shake your south side <br>People on the right, shake your south side <br>Every single girl, shake your south side <br>All around the world, shake your south side <br><br>Like Memphis, Tennessee, got in bed with CDB <br>And had a baby and when the baby cried <br>It made this sound, ain't no lie it was funkified <br><br>People on the left, shake your south side <br>People on the right, shake your south side <br>Every single girl, shake your south side <br>All around the world, shake your south side <br><br>Oh Yeah <br>Feels good don't it <br>Let me break it down <br><br>Shake it like a salt, shake it like a pepper, shake it like champagne number one record <br>Shake it 'til you just can't shake it no more <br>Shake that thing all the way to the floor <br><br>People on the left, shake your south side <br>People on the right, shake your south side <br><br>People on the left, shake your south side <br>People on the right, shake your south side <br>Every single girl, shake your south side <br>All around the world, shake your south side]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="South Side" label="South Side"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Crash_And_Burn/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Crash And Burn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Crash_And_Burn/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Crash And Burn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So I guess it's over baby <br>Deja vu again <br>Who'd have thought that time don't stop <br>And somehow girl, the world keeps spinning <br>I guess I've turned myself into a solitary man <br>Ain't like I'm the only one <br>That's in the shoes that I am <br><br>Do you hear that <br>I'm right back <br>At the sound of lonely calling <br>Do you hear that <br>It's where I'm at <br>It's the sound of teardrops falling down, down <br>A slamming door and a lesson learned <br>I let another lover crash and burn <br><br>I know that it might sound jaded <br>And I have to say <br>I think love is overrated <br>But I don't like throwing it away <br><br>I know you could probably tell me <br>Right where I went wrong <br>Some guys can't have all the luck <br>If others don't sing sad songs <br><br>Do you hear that <br>I'm right back <br>At the sound of lonely calling <br>Do you hear that <br>It's where I'm at <br>It's the sound of teardrops falling down, down <br>A slamming door and a lesson learned <br>I let another lover crash and burn <br><br>That's right <br>Another lover <br>Another lover crash and burn <br>Ooooh yeah <br><br>Do you hear that <br>I'm right back <br>At the sound of lonely calling <br>Do you hear that <br>It's where I'm at <br>It's the sound of teardrops falling down, down <br>A slamming door and a lesson learned <br>I let another lover crash and burn <br>Yeah, I let another lover crash and burn <br><br>Mhhhmm <br><br>Mhhhmm]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Crash And Burn" label="Crash And Burn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Anthem/</id><title>Thomas_Rhett - Anthem - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:40:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:40:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Thomas_Rhett/Anthem/" title="Thomas_Rhett - Anthem - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is the beat that puts the fire in your feet <br>Gives you the license to be a little crazy <br>This is the groove that gives you swagger to move <br>And gets you talkin' real smooth to a lady <br>This is the hook that gets you givin' the look <br>That gets you gettin' the number in your pocket <br>This is the part where the bass gonna start <br>And even last call can't stop it <br><br>All night Anthem <br>Ain't never gonna leave your head <br>All night anthem <br>Ain't nobody goin' to bed <br>'Til the drinks go down <br>And the sun comes up <br>The rhythm's gonna hold you for ransom <br>It's an all night anthem <br><br>And this is the verse where you don't know the words <br>And you don't give a dang 'cause it feels good <br>Put a whole generation in heavy rotation <br>Play it over and over and it's still good <br>This is the sound of a bigger little town <br>Just throwin' it down to where the floor is <br>You startin' to feel that momentum build <br>So bring it on back to the chorus <br><br>All night Anthem <br>Ain't never gonna leave your head <br>All night anthem <br>Ain't nobody goin' to bed <br>'Til the drinks go down <br>And the sun comes up <br>The rhythm's gonna hold you for ransom <br>It's an all night anthem <br><br>This ain't about who's got money <br>And it ain't about what kind of car you drive <br>This ain't about where you came from <br>And it ain't about how you're gettin' home tonight <br>This ain't about who's got money <br>And it ain't about what kind of car you drive <br>This ain't about where you came from <br>It's about livin' while you're alive <br><br>All night Anthem <br>Ain't never gonna leave your head <br>All night anthem <br>Ain't nobody goin' to bed <br>'Til the drinks go down <br>And the sun comes up <br>The rhythm's gonna hold you for ransom <br>It's an all night anthem <br><br>It's an all night anthem yeah, yeah <br>It's an all night anthem, baby <br>All night anthem <br>All night anthem]]></content><category term="Thomas Rhett" label="Thomas Rhett"/><category term="Anthem" label="Anthem"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Teleport/</id><title>Bambus - Teleport - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:43:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:43:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Teleport/" title="Bambus - Teleport - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo <br>Druck auf'm Kopf, aber im Endeffekt noch da <br>Nach Holland gefahrn', aber im Endeffekt noch da <br>Nach Hause gekommen, aber im Endeffekt noch dort <br>Joa, brauche es nach wie vor <br>Frei wie ein Teleport, auf dem Court <br>Hebe ab und werf nen' Korb <br>21 Points, keeping short <br>Null Ferrari und keinen Porsche <br>Fahr mit Polo, fahr auch nach Vorne <br>Esse Doner und kaue Torte <br>Flieg wie Mowen und flieg wie Korken <br>Ich leg dir auf, letzter Gang <br>Aber geh nicht drauf, stehe druber <br>Geh in den Wald, wie fruher <br>Atme die Luft ein, zahle die Blatter und Steine <br>Spitze die Stocke und bastel mir Speere fur Feinde <br><br>(4x) <br>Bitte bleib an meiner Seite <br><br>Druck auf'm Kopf, aber im Endeffekt noch da <br>Nach Holland gefahrn', aber im Endeffekt noch da <br>Nach Hause gekommen, aber im Endeffekt noch dort <br>Brauche es nach wie vor <br>Frei wie ein Teleport <br><br>So frei <br>Frei wie ein .. Nein, nein <br>Frei, so frei <br>Frei, frei, frei <br><br>Druck auf'm Kopf, aber im Endeffekt noch da <br>Nach Holland gefahrn', aber im Endeffekt noch da <br>Nach Hause gekommen, aber im Endeffekt noch dort <br>Brauche es nach wie vor <br>Frei wie ein Teleport]]></content><category term="Bambus" label="Bambus"/><category term="Teleport" label="Teleport"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Mental_Vision/</id><title>Bambus - Mental Vision - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:43:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:43:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Mental_Vision/" title="Bambus - Mental Vision - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Hook: Bambus] <br><br>Yo <br>Es nimmt Form an, Haruno, B-A-M <br>Wir sind der Vorwand fur <br>Was, was? <br>Wir sind der Vorwand fur <br>Was, was? <br>Wir sind der Vorwand fur.. <br><br>[Part: Bambus] <br><br>Dies und das, Ihn und Sie <br>Erlebe nicht viel, aber mach Musik <br>Ich mach Musik, und was geschieht? <br>Leute lacheln mich an und sagen "Das klappt nie." <br>Doch es lauft gut <br>Ich bin Halbblut-Prinz, verzauber den Sinn damit wie es klingt <br>Alles ist gut, digga, ich habs drin <br>Freestyle-Rap Radio als Kind gerappt, digga <br>Ich bin back, digga, ich bin echt <br>Nicht in der Lage zu sagen wie schlecht ich war <br>Doch habs getan jetzt grad <br>Ub doch mal n' Jahr, denk nach <br>Ubung macht den Meister, wenn du willst <br>Du wirst alter und traurig, denn du hast jahrelang gechillt <br>...Jahre <br><br>[Bridge: Bambus] <br>Jahrelang, "B-A-M macht weak shit" <br>Haruno die Beat-Hits <br>Ich schreib nur wenn das Weed spricht (sheesh) <br>Das sind so Phrasen, die die Meisten schreiben <br>Doch bei mir hort man von Weitem schon die Flugel spreizen <br><br>[Hook: Bambus] <br><br>[Bridge: Bambus]]]></content><category term="Bambus" label="Bambus"/><category term="Mental Vision" label="Mental Vision"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Johan_Cruyff/</id><title>Bambus - Johan Cruyff - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:43:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:43:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Johan_Cruyff/" title="Bambus - Johan Cruyff - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Hook: Bambus] <br><br>Rest in Peace <br>Johann Cruyff (Kick it) <br>Istanbul, Brussel, Paris, Snape <br>Bald auch Deutschland (Auf jeden) <br>Toronto Major (Rob Ford), Rest in Pu$$y <br>B-A-M-Haruno-Mucke wird in Himmels Luft spieln' <br><br>[1. Part: Bambus] <br><br>Yo <br>Wahlt weiter die Angst, Ich reise umher <br>Gedanken umkreisen sogar das Gewehr <br>Silkroad, Darknet, is' nich so schwer <br>Nur bisschen lesen, verschlusseln und Proxy <br>Ich rappe offbeat, du bist so in <br>Du hast so Rastas und Linsen drin <br>Ich bin unfassbar und frei wie Wind <br>Ich fall nie hin <br>Ich schreib mit Sinn, weil wir so sind <br>Kapitalistisch erzogen als Kind aber Drogen sind schlimm <br>Grune Drogen auch (was?) <br>Lugner raus <br>Raus <br><br>[Hook: Bambus] (2x) <br><br>[Outro: Bambus] <br><br>Cruyff, Brussel, Paris, Deutschland <br>Major, Pu$$y <br>Haruno-Mucke wird in ..]]></content><category term="Bambus" label="Bambus"/><category term="Johan Cruyff" label="Johan Cruyff"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Wechselhaft/</id><title>Bambus - Wechselhaft - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:43:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:43:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Wechselhaft/" title="Bambus - Wechselhaft - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Hook: Bambus] <br><br>Ey <br>B-A-M, ich hab Bars (hey) <br>B-A-M, ich hab Gras (hey) <br>B-A-M, ich hab Spaß (ne) <br>B-A-M, ich bin da und geh <br>Wechselhaft so wie A B C <br>Warte erst und dann fahr ich eh <br>Supermarkt am Bahnhof, steh <br>Mitten auf der Fahrbahn, bae <br>Alles gut, ich bin auch zu spat <br>Sprit ist leer, doch mein Motor dreht <br>Berg hinab, das Dach aufgesagt <br>Boxen laut, Cabrio-Feeling ist was die Fotze braucht <br>Und ich brauch Sie, nein ich hab kein Geld <br>Ich hab nur Musik, baby <br><br>[Bridge: Bambus] <br><br>Baby <br>Ich hab es drauf <br>Denk ich auch, aber ich gebe auf <br>Lebe mein Leben, lauf weiter weg in deinen Traum <br>Ich bin immer auf der Suche nach n' bisschen Raum <br><br>Und dann seh ich wieder dich <br>Ich gebe keinen Fick, ich gebe keinen Fick <br>Und morgen geb' ich dann auch keinen Fick, bitch <br>Ich bin immer auf der Suche nach n' bisschen Licht <br><br>[Part: Bambus] <br><br>Siebenkommaacht, HSB <br>B-A-M, ich hab die Scheiße schon gesehn' <br>Ihr rappt halt weiter wie mit 10, so larifari <br>Fazit: Ihr seid Nazis <br>Musikalisch demente Spastis <br>Wir hingegen fantastisch, alles andere ist Plastik <br>Ali As'se, hasse alle deutschen Rapper außer ein Paar <br>Guck' mich nicht so an als hatt' ich irgendwas Schlimmes gesagt, Ist doch wahr <br>Willst du up to date sein Falk-Schacht, hor mein Part <br>Heut' noch anonym und morgen im Passat <br>Normal, na klar, ja... <br><br>[Hook: Bambus]]]></content><category term="Bambus" label="Bambus"/><category term="Wechselhaft" label="Wechselhaft"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Schneewei/</id><title>Bambus - Schneewei$$ - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:43:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:43:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Schneewei/" title="Bambus - Schneewei$$ - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Part: Bambus] <br><br>Portemonnaie gefullt mit Ott <br>Beweg mich ruhig, neben dem Cop <br>Ich geh gleich Hops, sagt mir mein Kopf <br>Ich hoff' es lauft wie sonst so oft <br>Ich schein so soft, schein zu lieb <br>Die Augen schneeweiß, doch was er riecht... <br><br>[Hook: Bambus] (2x) <br><br>Ich riech da ist irgendwas falsch <br>Ich hab was ubersehn, er war mir zu kalt <br>Irgendetwas am Benehmen, war zu bequem <br>Doch lies es gestatten, tief in ihm drin sind die Ratten <br>Sie fressen und irgendwann werden Sie's schaffen <br>Sie wachsen, Sie wachsen <br><br>[Bridge: Bambus] <br><br>Sie wachsen <br>Sie wachsen, Sie wachsen <br>Sie wachsen, Sie wachsen, Sie wachsen <br><br>[Part: Bambus] <br><br>Portemonnaie gefullt mit Ott <br>Beweg mich ruhig, neben dem Cop <br>Ich geh gleich Hops, sagt mir mein Kopf <br>Ich hoff' es lauft wie sonst so oft <br>Ich schein so soft, schein zu lieb <br>Die Augen schneeweiß, doch was er riecht's... shit]]></content><category term="Bambus" label="Bambus"/><category term="Schneewei$$" label="Schneewei$$"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Sense8/</id><title>Bambus - Sense8 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:43:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:43:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Sense8/" title="Bambus - Sense8 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Part: Bambus] <br><br>Yo <br>B-A-M, sense8 Mist <br>Ich weiß wie's ist, immernoch leicht im Blick <br>Ey, eigentlich ist Alles frisch <br>Doch alles wird vermischt mit Nichts <br>Wenn man immer anders tickt, immer anders strickt <br>Nicht mehr spricht <br>Nie mehr wieder auf der Stelle stehn', Fehler zahln' <br>Guck halt zu, Alles hier ist Pay2View <br>Mach nich' mit, mach nen' Shoot <br>Irgendjemand wirds schon tun <br>Doch jeder denkt so nun, also was willst du versuchen? <br>Sie verfluchen? Ich weiß nicht <br>Nein, nein, ich weiß nicht <br>B-A-M produziert weiter fließig <br>Haruno Beat, Beichte, verteidigt <br>Keeper, punkte Rocket Liga <br>Im echten Leben nen' Cheater <br>B-A-M unbesiegbar <br>Redest du von Musik Kram, du beim Thema Shishan? <br>Ey mies man <br>Du hast mies Plan, und ich bin mies am Arsch <br>Denn ich bin viel zu straff <br>Yo <br><br>[Bridge: Bambus] <br><br>Ey (Ok) <br>Shoutouts to .. (alle Leute) <br>BVB '09 (Nein, nein), Tim Motherfuck (Ok) <br>(Was noch digga, was noch? Noch irgendwas?) <br>Ey.. <br>(Ok korrekt) <br><br>[Outro: Bambus] <br><br>HSB <br>B-A-M, sense8 Mist <br>Ich weiß wie's ist, immernoch leicht im Blick <br>Ey, eigentlich ist Alles frisch <br>Doch alles wird vermischt mit Nichts <br>Wenn man immer anders tickt, immer anders strickt <br>Nicht mehr spricht <br><br>(Nie mehr.. nie mehr digga, nie mehr, nie mehr, nie)]]></content><category term="Bambus" label="Bambus"/><category term="Sense8" label="Sense8"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Dito/</id><title>Bambus - Dito - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:43:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:43:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Dito/" title="Bambus - Dito - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Hook: Bambus] <br><br>Die Sonne scheint, yep, Ich auch <br>Alles gut digga, ich gebe nicht auf <br>Im Winter wars leise <br>Jetzt bin ich drauf, und schraub <br>Weiter an Zeichen, die ich verbau und brauch, yo <br><br>[1. Part: Bambus] <br><br>B-A-M, ich bleib halt wie ich bin <br>Wechselhaft so wie'n Ditto, digga <br>Du bleibst wie'n Kind <br>Irgendwo ist da der Sinn, doch so wie Sido werd' ich nie <br>Musiziere nur was ich lieb, egal ob es dir grad nicht liegt <br>Ich habs entschieden, ich mach des <br>Lugen, ja, des mach ich auch <br>Aber is' ok, du haltst es aus <br>Du gehst ja pumpen, willst mich schlagen <br>Aber du haltst mich nicht unten <br>Niemals lass ich mich verarschen von so Hunden <br>Paar Jahre warten und ihr seid meine Kunden (Pahh) <br><br>[Hook: Bambus] <br><br>Die Sonne scheint, yep, Ich auch <br>Alles gut digga, ich gebe nicht auf <br>Im Wnter wars leise <br>Jetzt bin ich drauf, und schraub <br>Weiter an Zeichen, die ich verbau und brauch, yo <br><br>[2. Part: Bambus] <br><br>B-A-M, ich tappe weiter Karten <br>Rap in Kamen, keiner hat hier was zu sagen <br>Nur so Standardphrasen, Hamburg-Connecte <br>Um was zu starten musst ich machen <br>Dis' kein Disrespect ihr Lappen, sorry <br>Ich mach bisschen Faxen <br>Hobbies muss man sich erschaffen <br>Sonst versaut man im Haus <br>Ich bin immer sehr gut drauf, hab ich Ruhe auf der Couch <br>Guck ich filme an nem' Netz, gehn die Augen wieder auf <br>Paar Tage spater wieder schlecht, yau yau <br><br>[Bridge: Bambus] <br><br>Die Sonne scheint, yep, ich auch <br>Alles gut digga, ich geb nicht auf <br>Im Winter wars leise, jetzt bin ich drauf <br>Und schraub, und schraub, yau]]></content><category term="Bambus" label="Bambus"/><category term="Dito" label="Dito"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Revo/</id><title>Bambus - Revo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:44:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:44:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bambus/Revo/" title="Bambus - Revo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[1. Part: Bambus] <br><br>Viel Scheiß gesehn', ich bleib liegen <br>Keine Zeit mehr fur Leute, die Miesen schieben <br>Aufgestiegen nach 7 Titeln <br>Octo war so eher easy, Liebe <br>Lieber nicht auf der Suche nach Gluck vertiefen (Nein) <br>Eher so machen und machen und siegen <br>Bin weiter am triefen vor Ideen <br>Alles gut, Ich hab Sonne nie gesehn, nein (Nein) <br>Ich bin weiter geheim, B-A-M, Haruno <br>Alles ist Eins, Ihr auch, wir steigen hinauf, wohin? <br>Generation Pimpshit <br>20 Jahre lang mach ich schon mit <br>20 Jahre lang bin ich gefickt <br>Mal gucken wie's weiter so ist, wie's weiter so ist <br><br>[Bridge: Bambus] <br><br>Revoluzzer am Mic, yes, yes, yes <br>Ihr macht weiterhin Tests, yo <br>Revoluzzer am Mic, yes, yes, yes <br>Ihr macht weiterhin Tests, yo <br><br>[Hook: Bambus] (2x) <br><br>Viel Scheiß gesehn, ich bleib liegen im -Fliegendem Mode <br>Siebenen auf meim' Achter, alles ist machbar <br>Wir biegens hin, Geld ist nicht wichtig <br>Wir haben Stimmen, wir haben Zeit, yo <br>Wir haben Mics, yo, wir haben die Grafik von DICE <br>All das Odd der Polizei, yo <br><br>[Outro: Bambus] <br><br>Revolzzer am Mic, yes, yes, yes <br>Ihr macht weiterhin Tests, yo <br>Revoluzzer am Mic, yes, yes, yes <br>Ihr macht weiterhin Tests, yo]]></content><category term="Bambus" label="Bambus"/><category term="Revo" label="Revo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hex__Tonic/사의_찬가/</id><title>Hex__Tonic - 사의 찬가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:44:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:44:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hex__Tonic/%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%98_%EC%B0%AC%EA%B0%80/" title="Hex__Tonic - 사의 찬가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하나도 없고 둘도 없는 <br>나는 let it go <br>시기와 질투와 분노와 <br>무감각 속에서 <br>깨달음을 찾는 나는 <br>졸라 멍청이고 <br>돌아갈 수 없는 <br>1차로에 서있는 나 <br>깊은 심해에 빠져 <br>허우적 대고 있는 <br>나를 발견해도 <br>떠오를 수 없어 버둥대 <br>웃고 있는 너와 <br>울고 있는 나는 <br>과연 다른 삶을 <br>살고 있는 걸까 <br>발 끝에 느껴지는 <br>싸늘한 시퍼런 날들은 <br>살아가기에도 내 목을 <br>베기에도 날카로워 <br>비껴나간 니 눈빛이란 <br>화살은 어느새 <br>커다란 반원을 그려 <br>내 등뒤를 하염없이 노리네 <br>끝이 보이지 않는 <br>광야를 달리는 나란 존재는 <br>쓸쓸한 세상 어디로 <br>무엇을 찾으러 가는가 <br>스러져가는 생명과 <br>탄생으로 말미암아 <br>빛을 보는 존재들은 <br>그 가치가 달라야만 하는가 <br>빛과 어둠 <br>삶과 죽음 <br>그 사이에서 헤매이는 <br>너와 나는 누구일까 <br>빛과 어둠 <br>삶과 죽음 <br>그 사이에서 헤매이는 <br>너와 나는 누구일까 <br>한번은 생각해 봤을거야 <br>지금 내가 살고 있는 <br>이 곳이 지옥은 아닐까 <br>어떤 씨발놈들은 <br>천국 처럼 살고 <br>어떤 놈은 네발로 <br>시궁창 버러지 처럼 기고 <br>한방을 꿈꾸는 이들에게 <br>망상이라 비웃고 <br>때리고 넘어뜨려 <br>올라 올 생각일랑 말아 <br>봐라 니가 올라오는 사다리는 <br>내 발로 차라고 있는거야 <br>빛과 어둠 <br>삶과 죽음 <br>그 사이에서 헤매이는 <br>너와 나는 누구일까 <br>빛과 어둠 <br>삶과 죽음 <br>그 사이에서 헤매이는 <br>너와 나는 누구일까 <br>빛과 어둠 <br>삶과 죽음 <br>그 사이에서 헤매이는 <br>너와 나는 누구일까 <br>]]></content><category term="Hex &amp; Tonic" label="Hex &amp; Tonic"/><category term="사의 찬가" label="사의 찬가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김태윤/바라만_봐도/</id><title>김태윤 - 바라만 봐도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:44:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:44:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%83%9C%EC%9C%A4/%EB%B0%94%EB%9D%BC%EB%A7%8C_%EB%B4%90%EB%8F%84/" title="김태윤 - 바라만 봐도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바라만 봐도 나는 너무 행복해 <br>바라만 봐도 세상 다 가진것 같아 <br>그런 너는 어디로 갔는지 <br>찾을수 없어 <br>아무리 둘러보아도 찾을수 없어 <br>바라만 봐도 나는 너무 즐거워 <br>하지만 지금 이제 너는 없는걸 <br>그런 너는 어디로 갔는지 <br>찾을수 없어 <br>아무리 둘러보아도 찾을수 없어 <br>바라만 봐도 나는 너무 즐거워 <br>하지만 지금 이제 너는 없는걸 <br>]]></content><category term="김태윤" label="김태윤"/><category term="바라만 봐도" label="바라만 봐도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/셀프어쿠스틱/삼겹살송/</id><title>셀프어쿠스틱 - 삼겹살송 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:45:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:45:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%85%80%ED%94%84%EC%96%B4%EC%BF%A0%EC%8A%A4%ED%8B%B1/%EC%82%BC%EA%B2%B9%EC%82%B4%EC%86%A1/" title="셀프어쿠스틱 - 삼겹살송 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[삼 삼삼 삼겹살 삼겹살 먹고 싶다 <br>아침부터 먹고 싶다 <br>어제 먹었는데 또 먹고 싶다 <br>노릇노릇 익어가는 <br>도톰한 살코기 <br>한 점 집어 쌈장에 콕 찍어 먹고파 <br>내 배가 삼겹살이 <br>오겹살이 된다 해도 참을 수 없어 <br>그리고 잊으면 안돼 <br>고마워 돼지야 꿀 <br>]]></content><category term="셀프어쿠스틱" label="셀프어쿠스틱"/><category term="삼겹살송" label="삼겹살송"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최이슬/Tictoc/</id><title>최이슬 - Tictoc - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:45:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:45:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%AC/Tictoc/" title="최이슬 - Tictoc - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[발가락 사이 <br>들어오는 모래가 <br>그대의 발을 <br>움직이게 하나요 <br>TICTOC <br>음악에 맞춰서 <br>탁탁 발을 맞추고 <br>랄라 콧노래 부르며 <br>춤을 춰요 <br>그대 걱정 하지마요 <br>우린 행복할거야 <br>그저 이 바람에 취해 춤을 <br>발가락 사이 <br>들어오는 모래가 <br>그대의 발을 <br>움직이게 하나요 <br>바람에 그저 <br>등을 떠밀려서 <br>우린 그냥 춤을 춰요 <br>우린 그냥 춤을 춰요 <br>TICTOC <br>그대에게 취해 <br>랄라 난 춤을춰요 <br>그대 놓치지 말아요 <br>지금 이 순간 <br>그대 부끄러워 마요 <br>우린 함께하잖아 <br>그저 서로에게 취해 춤을 <br>발가락 사이 <br>들어오는 모래가 <br>그대의 발을 <br>움직이게 하나요 <br>바람에 그저 <br>등을 떠밀려서 <br>우린 그냥 춤을 춰요 <br>우린 그냥 춤을 춰요 <br>]]></content><category term="최이슬" label="최이슬"/><category term="Tictoc" label="Tictoc"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달/붉은_구두/</id><title>달 - 붉은 구두 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:46:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:46:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC/%EB%B6%89%EC%9D%80_%EA%B5%AC%EB%91%90/" title="달 - 붉은 구두 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[검붉은 구두를 신고 <br>바람이 부는 <br>하늘 계단 올라가나 <br>그댈 기다릴까 <br>아니면 니가 먼저와 <br>안아주나 예전처럼 <br>두근두근 댄다 <br>눈가엔 눈물이 추억이 <br>흐르고 있는 건지 <br>자꾸만 따듯해지네 <br>붉은 구두에 떨어진 <br>와인향기의 계단 <br>검붉은 구두를 신고 <br>불빛이 없는 <br>안개 속에 혼자 서있는 <br>그대 나를 기다리네 <br>자정까지 소식이 없는데도 <br>기다리네 오늘따라 <br>달빛도 하나 없고 <br>조그만 카페에 <br>들어가지도 못하고 다가올 <br>그대의 모습만 <br>생각하네 두근 <br>뚜벅 뚜벅 걷네 <br>먼곳에서 볼까 <br>새벽바람이 분다 <br>붉은 구두를 신고 <br>하늘 계단에 올라 <br>붉은 구두를 신고 <br>안개 속에서 찾네 너를 <br>]]></content><category term="달" label="달"/><category term="붉은 구두" label="붉은 구두"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신철/섬강_아가씨/</id><title>신철 - 섬강 아가씨 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:46:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:46:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%B2%A0/%EC%84%AC%EA%B0%95_%EC%95%84%EA%B0%80%EC%94%A8/" title="신철 - 섬강 아가씨 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잔잔한 섬강물결 <br>흘러흘러 어디로 가나 <br>진달래 피고 뻑국새 울면 <br>다시오마 약속한님 <br>어이해 안오시나 <br>이내가슴 멍이 들어요 <br>오늘도 보고파서 <br>애태우는 섬강 아가씨 <br>잔잔한 물결 따라 <br>떠나가는 나룻배 하나 <br>복사꽃 피고 소쩍새 울면 <br>돌아오마 약속한님 <br>어이해 안오시나 <br>이내가슴 멍이 들어요 <br>오늘도 보고파서 <br>애태우는 섬강 아가씨 <br>어이해 안오시나 <br>이내가슴 멍이 들어요 <br>오늘도 보고파서 <br>애태우는 섬강 아가씨 <br>섬강 아가씨 <br>]]></content><category term="신철" label="신철"/><category term="섬강 아가씨" label="섬강 아가씨"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장뮤직프로젝트/속마음_Vocal_최동찬/</id><title>장뮤직프로젝트 - 속마음 (Vocal 최동찬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:46:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:46:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EB%AE%A4%EC%A7%81%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9D%ED%8A%B8/%EC%86%8D%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C_Vocal_%EC%B5%9C%EB%8F%99%EC%B0%AC/" title="장뮤직프로젝트 - 속마음 (Vocal 최동찬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무에게도 못했던 <br>내 이야기를 들어 주겠니 <br>혼자서만 아파했던 <br>내 얘기를 말야 <br>끝없는 방황과 <br>슬픔 앞에도 <br>날 지킬수 있던건 <br>더 크게 노래 할 수 있는 <br>이거 하나 때문에 <br>곁에는 아무도 없어도 <br>내몸이다 부서져 <br>간다 해도 <br>난 두렵지 않아 <br>행복하니까 <br>그거면 되니까 <br>모두가 내꿈을 <br>말려도 포기 않고 <br>꼭 이뤄내 갈거야 <br>많은건 바라지 않아 <br>난 괜찮아 이거면 되니까 <br>내 꿈이니까 <br>힘들고 지치고 <br>외로웠었던 <br>삶의 이유를 준건 <br>모든걸 버려도 <br>바꿀수 없는 <br>그건 노래야 <br>곁에는 아무도 없어도 <br>내몸이다 부서져 <br>간다 해도 <br>난 두렵지않아 <br>행복하니까 <br>그거면 되니까 <br>모두가 내꿈을 <br>말려도 포기 않고 <br>꼭 이뤄내갈거야 <br>많은건 바라지 않아 <br>난 괜찮아 이거면 되니까 <br>내 꿈이니까 <br>누구보다 아픈 시련들을 <br>참고 견뎌왔어 <br>세상에 내 노랠 <br>들려줄때까지 <br>간절한 맘을 담아서 <br>곁에는 아무도 없어도 <br>내몸이다 부서져 간다 해도 <br>난 두렵지 않아 <br>행복하니까 <br>그거면 되니까 <br>모두가 내꿈을 말려도 <br>포기않고 꼭 <br>이뤄내 갈거야 <br>많은건 바라지 않아 <br>난 괜찮아 이거면 되니까 <br>내 꿈이니까 <br>내 꿈이니까 <br>]]></content><category term="장뮤직프로젝트" label="장뮤직프로젝트"/><category term="속마음 (Vocal 최동찬)" label="속마음 (Vocal 최동찬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임상목/길치/</id><title>임상목 - 길치 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:46:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:46:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%83%81%EB%AA%A9/%EA%B8%B8%EC%B9%98/" title="임상목 - 길치 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길을 걸어 가다 우연히 널 만나 <br>요즘 뭐하냐고 먼저 말을 건네 <br>그냥 똑같지 뭐 <br>별 일 없이 지낸다는 너의 말 <br>오랜 친굴 만나 길을 걸어 가다 <br>요즘 뭐하냐고 내게 말을 건네 <br>그냥 똑같지 뭐 <br>매일같이 지낸다고 <br>매일 걷던 길인데 <br>이상하게 보여 왜 <br>이 길이 난 맞는지 <br>이 길을 왜 걷는지 또 생각을 해 <br>어제와 같은 곳에서 <br>이상하게 보여 왜 <br>매일 걷는 길인데 <br>이 길이 난 맞는지 <br>이 길을 왜 걷는지 자꾸 생각을 해 <br>어제와 같은 길 <br>저기 보이는 저 별을 따라 <br>올려다 보는 내 눈엔 <br>구름에 가려 이 밤에 가려 <br>어둡게만 보이는 게 <br>나만 그런 것 같아 <br>여기 서있는 이 시간 따라 <br>매일같이 걷는 나는 <br>어디로 이대로 가는 게 <br>다른 사람들도 그러겠지 <br>누군가의 그 길도 나와 똑같겠지 <br>매일 걷던 길인데 <br>이상하게 보여 왜 <br>이 길이 난 맞는지 <br>이 길을 왜 걷는지 또 생각을 해 <br>어제와 같은 곳에서 <br>이상하게 보여 왜 <br>매일 걷는 길인데 <br>이 길이 난 맞는지 <br>이 길을 왜 걷는지 자꾸 생각을 해 <br>어제와 같은 길 <br>]]></content><category term="임상목" label="임상목"/><category term="길치" label="길치"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/그루비_레인/Mad_Stalker/</id><title>그루비_레인 - Mad Stalker - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:46:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:46:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A3%A8%EB%B9%84_%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Mad_Stalker/" title="그루비_레인 - Mad Stalker - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[딱히 관심 없는 눈빛 <br>사뿐사뿐 도도하게 <br>걷는 하이힐 소리 <br>찰랑이는 머릿결 사이로 <br>풍기는 도도한 <br>너의 향기가 끌려 <br>In the silence silence space <br>In the silence silence night <br>니 걸음 끝에 <br>내 발걸음이 <br>시간이 지날 수록 <br>점점 멀어지고 있어 <br>누구 보다 눈에 띄는 Style <br>미끈하게 빠져있는 <br>니 Stocking <br>검정색 치마 <br>검정색 하이힐 <br>조금은 시크하게 <br>삐뚤어진 니입술 <br>Do you wanna feel me <br>can i get your mind <br>사실 니가 조금 <br>부담 스러워 <br>Do you wanna feel me <br>can i get your mind <br>Red lip apple hip <br>똘망한 눈빛 <br>그 꿀피부가 <br>날 죽인 흉기 <br>그래 굳이 끼 <br>안부려도 돼 <br>Just move it <br>난 이미 느끼고 있어 <br>너의 모든거 <br>내 얼굴이 <br>왜 빨개지는거야 <br>I love it <br>니 도도한 걸음마저도 <br>좀 더 널 알고 싶어서 <br>마냥 너의 뒤를 걸어가 <br>좋은 예감이 들어 <br>In the silence silence space <br>In the silence silence night <br>니 걸음 끝에 내 발걸음이 <br>시간이 지날 수록 <br>점점 멀어지고 있어 <br>누구 보다 눈에 띄는 Style <br>미끈하게 빠져있는 <br>니 Stocking <br>검정색 치마 <br>검정색 하이힐 <br>조금은 시크하게 <br>삐뚤어진 니입술 <br>DO you wanna feel me <br>can i get your mind <br>사실 니가 <br>조금 부담스러워 <br>DO you wanna feel me <br>can i get your mind <br>꽉 낀 Skinny jeans <br>입지 않아도 <br>티가 나는 몸매 <br>어딜가든 보여 눈에 <br>모든 기집애들의 <br>질투에 과민반응 안해 <br>You that's cool lady <br>어쩜 이 모습에 <br>나는 과감히 끌린듯 <br>니 맘을 살 수 있다면 <br>됐을거야 무일푼 <br>더 몰입을 해 이건 <br>숨겨둔 내 의미야 <br>이미 알고 있다면 <br>You Just follow me <br>and be my love yeah uh <br>]]></content><category term="그루비 레인" label="그루비 레인"/><category term="Mad Stalker" label="Mad Stalker"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/배하은/예수_소망/</id><title>배하은 - 예수 소망 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:48:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:48:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B0%ED%95%98%EC%9D%80/%EC%98%88%EC%88%98_%EC%86%8C%EB%A7%9D/" title="배하은 - 예수 소망 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그런 날들이 있었어 <br>한참을 걸었었나봐 <br>누군가 툭 내 어깨를 스치면 <br>눈물이 주저앉을 것 같았지 <br>세상의 어떤 소망도 <br>내 두 눈엔 보이지 않았고 <br>두 손에 움켜쥐고 있던 <br>희망들 모두 <br>새벽녘 사라지는 별빛 같았지 <br>그 때 나를 찾아오신 분 <br>사랑으로 알게 하신 분 <br>세상의 보이는 소망 소망 아님을 <br>사랑으로 알게 하신 분 <br>예수 소망 예수 소망 <br>사랑의 주 내 갈 길 인도하시니 <br>예수 소망 예수 소망 <br>내 삶의 전부되었네 <br>세상의 어떤 소망도 <br>내 두 눈엔 보이지 않았고 <br>두 손에 움켜쥐고 있던 <br>희망들 모두 <br>새벽녘 사라지는 별빛 같았지 <br>그 때 나를 찾아오신 분 <br>사랑으로 알게 하신 분 <br>세상의 보이는 소망 소망 아님을 <br>사랑으로 알게 하신 분 <br>예수 소망 예수 소망 <br>사랑의 주 내 갈 길 인도하시니 <br>예수 소망 예수 소망 <br>내 삶의 전부되었네 <br>예수 소망 예수 소망 <br>사랑의 주 내 갈 길 인도하시니 <br>예수 소망 예수 소망 <br>내 삶의 전부되었네 <br>내 삶의 전부되었네 <br>내 삶의 전부되었네 <br>]]></content><category term="배하은" label="배하은"/><category term="예수 소망" label="예수 소망"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이뱃/Dirty_Miss_Afraid/</id><title>제이뱃 - Dirty Miss Afraid - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:49:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:49:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EB%B1%83/Dirty_Miss_Afraid/" title="제이뱃 - Dirty Miss Afraid - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어쩌다 이렇게 됐을까 <br>왜 넌 내옆에 없을까 <br>우린 남부럽지 않게 <br>아니 그보다 더 훨씬 사랑했어 <br>아침에 일어나 눈을떠 <br>현관을 열고 출근길에 나서 <br>아무렇지 않아 보여 <br>너 생각 벌써 몇번은 했어 <br>밉다가도 보고싶어 <br>우릴 응원하던 내친구마저 <br>그딴년 얘긴 꺼내지도 말래 <br>이렇게 서글플때 날 달래 줘야지 <br>정신 확차리게 <br>넌 등돌렸어 나에게 <br>4년이란 시간이 무색하게 <br>날버리고 그놈에게 <br>가서 상처만 쌓인채 <br>다시 내앞에 섰을때 <br>아무말도 못했네 <br>다시 널 만날수 없기에 <br>이젠 다른만남 다른 사랑 <br>아니 다른 사람 만나기가 두려워 <br>너가 그리운 내가 두려워 <br>넌 내친구 말대로 더러워 <br>근데 그리워 이런 내가 두려워 <br>넌 내친구 말대로 더러워 <br>근데 그리워 이런 내가 두려워 <br>내친구 말대로 더러워 <br>근데 그리워 이런 내가 두려워 <br>내친구 말대로 더러워 <br>근데 그리워 이런 내가 두려워 <br>내 과거에게 미안해 <br>지금 널 보고싶은게 <br>예전나를 부정하는건데 <br>불을끄고 깜깜한방에 <br>나혼자 고립된 채 지난날을 <br>끊임없이 그리네 좋았던날 <br>너와 갔던 식당부터 여행지까지 <br>소환해 널 사랑한 날 <br>폰을켜 <br>너의 톡 대화명과 사진을 봐 <br>어느덧 일상이 돼버렸어 <br>이런 나 참 찌질해 그래 난 찌질해 <br>누구에겐 좋은형오빠 <br>좀 놀줄 아는 보이 <br>너앞에만 서면 작아지는데 <br>넌 내친구 말대로 더러워 <br>근데 그리워 이런 내가 두려워 <br>넌 내친구 말대로 더러워 <br>근데 그리워 이런 내가 두려워 <br>모기때문인지 일찍깼어 <br>불면증은 아냐 <br>깨고나서 잠또올수있어 <br>근데 그전에 일단 담배 <br>물고 밖으로나가 어 벌써 춥네 <br>딱 요시기때 너 만났지 <br>그래 기억나 <br>계절을 핑계삼아 너 잠깐 그려봐 <br>오늘따라 참좋아 달이 <br>멍한 눈매로 자꾸만 발이 <br>어딘갈 향하고 싶어 <br>너있던 자리 한번더 <br>시작하고싶어 딱 거기 <br>검게 물들어버린 <br>하얗고 파랗던 하늘 <br>숨은 턱 막히고 <br>시도때도 없이 찾어 너를 <br>시간은 이쯤이면 <br>충분히 흘렀어 널잊기에 <br>이젠 내가 필요없단걸 다알기에 <br>그러면서도 널 못잊네 <br>이런 내모습 모순 <br>넌 내친구 말대로 더러워 <br>근데 그리워 이런 내가 두려워 <br>넌 내친구 말대로 더러워 <br>근데 그리워 이런 내가 두려워 <br>넌 내친구 말대로 더러워 <br>근데 그리워 이런 내가 두려워 <br>넌 내친구 말대로 더러워 <br>근데 그리워 이런 내가 두려워 <br>]]></content><category term="제이뱃" label="제이뱃"/><category term="Dirty Miss Afraid" label="Dirty Miss Afraid"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sushi__Kobe/Flexer/</id><title>Sushi__Kobe - Flexer - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:51:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:51:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sushi__Kobe/Flexer/" title="Sushi__Kobe - Flexer - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ja jeg vil bare flexe <br>e du e du e du <br>kan eg bare flexeeee <br><br>kan eg bare flexeee <br>la meg bare flexeeee <br>la meg bare flex-e <br>eg har en ting jeg vil si <br>eg har hundre tusen <br>eg gidsje bar gi deg <br>ble du kald for rimet? <br>Eg gir deg en søyle frityrstekt <br>milepæl for den fitten din <br>Du blir dusjet fra haken til klitten din <br>Du kan skryte til dine venner <br>Og ga da Kobe <br>Forandrer virkeligheten, tankesett og drømmen din <br>Eg har tusen lekser eg flexar pa <br>Dritar i karakter <br>Sa lenge eg star <br>Totusen puppar <br>Totusen lar <br>Eg har tusen lekser eg flexar pa <br>Eg har tusen flaskar eg drikkar fra <br>eg har tusen matcher pa tindar og <br>eg har tusenlapp <br>eg har tusenlapp <br>eg har tusenlapp <br>Eg har tusen klubbar <br>Eg eiar bare strippar <br>Du kjennar meg sikkart <br>sa mange som ikkje vet om han e rik eller blakk <br>Nar du ser meg gli rundt i candy lakk og fuckings mammut fuck <br>Gullgruve diamantspade <br>Eg begravar tyve diamantspadar <br>Eg eiar bare diamantspadar <br>Kan noen fylle hullet no? <br>Ute a plukkar kjøtt igjen <br>Eg har fire gullkjeder og en bunke spenn <br>Bitch vi trengar ikkje holde hendar <br>Bitch inviter en av dine venner <br>Eg har alt du trengar <br>Eg har fine tennar <br>Har lommene fulle av rap pengar <br>Forlater meg og du vet du vet <br>du sier følg etter meg og du vet du vet <br>Flexaaaaar <br>PA MINE EXAR <br>Flexaaaaar <br>PA MINE EXAR <br>Flexaaaaar <br>PA MIN PA MIN HEI <br>HEI <br>Flexar flexar flexar <br>Flexaaaaaar <br>PA MINE EXAR <br>Flexaaaar <br>FLEXAR PA MINE EXAR <br>Flexaaaaar <br>PA-PA MINE EXAR <br>Flexaaaaar <br>FLEXER <br><br>Pappa ville presse meg <br>til a vær muslim <br>Gikk pa koranskole <br>og eg fikk det til <br>Sjpillte cello <br>Sang Opera <br>Det ekke rart <br>at jeg <br>dopet meg <br>Det ekke rart <br>at jeg vinnaaaaar <br>no har jeg blitt smart <br>no har jeg lært <br>min mor e gammel <br>min mor hon vil stresse meg <br>hun siar <br>jeg ma slutte a være $ushi mane <br>Fokk alle andre <br>Bare la meg sveve <br>Tjommi tjenar pengar jeg har gjeld opp til ørene <br>Tro meg <br>nar jeg sier <br>Dette livet som jeg lever <br>det var skapt for en spillar <br>Bankar fitten som Rihanna <br>Har en hore pa mitt fang <br>Eg tipper min Miranda <br>Hakke spist pa to dagar jeg er sa blakk <br>Sendte pengar til min far, kall meg en polakk <br>Flexaaaaar <br>PA MINE EXAR <br>Flexaaaaar <br>PA MINE EXAR <br>Flexaaaaar <br>PA MIN PA IN HEI <br>HEI <br>Flexar flexar flexar <br>Flexaaaaaar <br>PA MINE EXAR <br>Flexaaaar <br>FLEXAR PA MINE EXAR <br>Flexaaaaar <br>PA-PA MINE EXAR <br>Flexaaaaar <br>FLEXER]]></content><category term="Sushi &amp; Kobe" label="Sushi &amp; Kobe"/><category term="Flexer" label="Flexer"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN/New_Dawn/</id><title>헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN - New Dawn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:52:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:52:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_%ED%98%BC_HAZY_HORN/New_Dawn/" title="헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN - New Dawn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일렁이는 길가 아래 <br>그려졌던 눈동자는 <br>움츠린 어깨 너머 <br>소중히 쥔 누군가는 옅어져가 <br>걷히는 안개 속에 <br>드러났던 옅은 이는 <br>옅어진 그림자는 <br>다시 마주할 너의 기억인지 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이지 혼 (HAZY HORN)" label="헤이지 혼 (HAZY HORN)"/><category term="New Dawn" label="New Dawn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN/Nuclear_Beach/</id><title>헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN - Nuclear Beach - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:52:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:52:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_%ED%98%BC_HAZY_HORN/Nuclear_Beach/" title="헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN - Nuclear Beach - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Through the gravity <br>we step on the edge <br>silence in the crowd <br>we riding our wave <br>We alive <br>we alive <br>we alive and drive <br>We alive <br>we alive <br>we alive and drive <br>We alive <br>we alive <br>we alive and drive <br>We alive <br>we alive <br>we alive <br>Day and break that's <br>where we came from <br>people are running around <br>back on our side one evaporation <br>we see the new born star's rising <br>Somewhere nowhere to go <br>something nothing to show <br>kill the gravity alone <br>new born star is rising alone <br>]]></content><category term="헤이지 혼 (HAZY HORN)" label="헤이지 혼 (HAZY HORN)"/><category term="Nuclear Beach" label="Nuclear Beach"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN/Cant_Take_It_Anymore/</id><title>헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN - Can`t Take It Anymore - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:52:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:52:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_%ED%98%BC_HAZY_HORN/Cant_Take_It_Anymore/" title="헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN - Can`t Take It Anymore - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When she’s lights are growing <br>When she’s wings are falling <br>She is <br>She is <br>She walks out from her cave <br>Burning ash is rising <br>She is <br>She is <br>No way to return again <br>to be a fire <br>No way to return again <br>to be a liar <br>No way to become again <br>to be a liar <br>No way to become again <br>to be a sister <br>She’ve been out from her way <br>reaching out to her name <br>She can’t take it anymore <br>can’t take it anymore <br>When her eyes are dying <br>Waterfall is rising <br>She is <br>She is <br>She fills sorrow with her <br>Plastic words that she touched <br>She is <br>She is <br>No way to return again <br>to be a fire <br>No way to return again <br>to be a liar <br>No way to become again <br>to be a liar <br>No way to become again <br>to be a sister <br>She’ve been out from her way <br>reaching out to her name <br>She can’t take it anymore <br>can’t take it anymore <br>can’t take it anymore <br>can’t take it anymore <br>can’t take it anymore <br>can’t take it anymore <br>can’t take it anymore <br>can’t take it anymore <br>]]></content><category term="헤이지 혼 (HAZY HORN)" label="헤이지 혼 (HAZY HORN)"/><category term="Can`t Take It Anymore" label="Can`t Take It Anymore"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN/Twilight/</id><title>헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN - Twilight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:52:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:52:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%80_%ED%98%BC_HAZY_HORN/Twilight/" title="헤이지_혼_HAZY_HORN - Twilight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Living in the twilight <br>like we all did <br>I want the roses are <br>blooms in my place <br>When my lungs are <br>filler without the haze <br>Every moves of yours <br>turns to the light <br>Who wants my mind <br>Who wants be mine <br>When the floor is rising <br>the rain’s won’t fall <br>Lying on my dream <br>watching my fall <br>Burning sword got <br>the shadow <br>build up my fear <br>Below the wings <br>I’m waiting relies <br>and chain <br>Who wants my mind <br>Who wants be mine <br>]]></content><category term="헤이지 혼 (HAZY HORN)" label="헤이지 혼 (HAZY HORN)"/><category term="Twilight" label="Twilight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slumber_Line_슬럼버라인/Hedgehog/</id><title>Slumber_Line_슬럼버라인 - Hedgehog - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:52:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:52:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slumber_Line_%EC%8A%AC%EB%9F%BC%EB%B2%84%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B8/Hedgehog/" title="Slumber_Line_슬럼버라인 - Hedgehog - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 모습 없는 두 눈에 <br>건네어 보는 미소 <br>수줍은 손을 내밀다 <br>이내 주머니 속에 <br>나의 마음은 아지랑이지 <br>바라만보는 사람들에게 <br>다가가보고 뒷걸음치며 <br>나에게 맞는 벽을 만드네 <br>곧게도 자란 가시는 <br>내 몸을 감싸 주네 <br>날 이선 너의 가시는 <br>내 몸을 찔러 오네 <br>나의 마음은 아지랑이지 <br>바라만보는 사람들에게 <br>다가가보고 뒷걸음치며 <br>나에게 맞는 벽을 만드네 <br>검게도 변해버렸다 검게도 게도 <br>]]></content><category term="Slumber Line (슬럼버라인)" label="Slumber Line (슬럼버라인)"/><category term="Hedgehog" label="Hedgehog"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slumber_Line_슬럼버라인/Sailor/</id><title>Slumber_Line_슬럼버라인 - Sailor - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:52:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:52:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Slumber_Line_%EC%8A%AC%EB%9F%BC%EB%B2%84%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B8/Sailor/" title="Slumber_Line_슬럼버라인 - Sailor - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비틀 비틀 춤을 추듯이 <br>흔들흔들 노를 져가네 <br>찡그리며 앞을 바라봐 <br>고갤 돌려 뒤를 돌아봐 <br>아무 것도 알 수 없음이 <br>내게 어떤 의미 였는지 <br>내가 쥐고 있다 생각한 <br>이것 들은 어떤 의민지 <br>가득 채워 보려 했음에 <br>내린 닻을 올릴 수 없네 <br>힘들 다한 허무 함들이 <br>노를 계속 젓게 해주네 <br>아무 것도 알 수 없음이 <br>내게 어떤 의미 였는지 <br>내가 쥐고 있다 생각한 <br>이것 들은 어떤 의민지 <br>쥐고 있던 주먹 사이로 <br>흩날리는 모래알들은 <br>울상 짓는 그의 눈앞에 <br>원을 돌며 사라 져가네 <br>]]></content><category term="Slumber Line (슬럼버라인)" label="Slumber Line (슬럼버라인)"/><category term="Sailor" label="Sailor"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시기펩_Siggie_Feb/Wake_Up_Good_Night_Feat_hyeuk/</id><title>시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Wake Up Good Night (Feat. hye.uk) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:52:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:52:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B8%B0%ED%8E%A9_Siggie_Feb/Wake_Up_Good_Night_Feat_hyeuk/" title="시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Wake Up Good Night (Feat. hye.uk) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Wake Up <br>좋은 꿈속에서 <br>매일 아침 깨서 <br>매일 좋은 아침을 맞을 <br>수는 없지 never <br>우린 때론 악몽에게 <br>때론 설잠에게 <br>좋은 아침을 뺏겨 <br>계속해서 반복 되네 <br>good morning coffee <br>한 잔 이면 <br>good morning coffee <br>한 잔 이면 <br>good morning coffee <br>한 잔 이면 <br>오늘도 역시 좋은 밤이 <br>올 것 같군요 <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>Good night <br>내 곁에 있어줘 forever <br>내 하루의 마무리는 언제나 <br>good 그렇게 기억해줘 <br>아침은 어땠고 점심은 어땠고 <br>baby it doesn't matter <br>우리가 만드는 거지 <br>좋은 밤은 항상 우리 옆에서 <br>good morning coffee <br>한 잔 이면 <br>good morning coffee <br>한 잔 이면 <br>good morning coffee <br>한 잔 이면 <br>오늘도 역시 좋은 밤이 <br>올 것 같군요 <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>봄 여름 가을 겨울 <br>점점 흐려지네 uh <br>겨울 따뜻한 캔 커피 <br>여름 물론 치맥 uh <br>애인과의 밤샘 통화 <br>좋은 밤을 지새웠어 <br>오늘 술도 안 했는데 <br>벌써 우린 취했어 <br>봄 여름 가을 겨울 <br>점점 흐려지네 uh <br>겨울 따뜻한 캔 커피 <br>여름 물론 치맥 uh <br>애인과의 밤샘 통화 <br>좋은 밤을 지새웠어 <br>오늘 술도 안 했는데 <br>벌써 우린 취했어 <br>good morning coffee <br>한 잔 이면 <br>good morning coffee <br>한 잔 이면 <br>good morning coffee <br>한 잔 이면 <br>오늘도 역시 좋은 밤이 <br>올 것 같군요 <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>Wake Up Wake Up baby Good Night <br>]]></content><category term="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)" label="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)"/><category term="Wake Up Good Night (Feat. hye.uk)" label="Wake Up Good Night (Feat. hye.uk)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시기펩_Siggie_Feb/Dance_With_U/</id><title>시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Dance With U - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:52:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:52:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B8%B0%ED%8E%A9_Siggie_Feb/Dance_With_U/" title="시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Dance With U - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘이 지나면 <br>딱 하나 확실한 건 <br>우린 한 발자국 더욱 더 <br>나아가 있을 거야 <br>우울한 시간도 <br>때론 날 찾아오겠지 <br>뭐 어쩌겠어 다 달아나도록 <br>I sing a song everytime <br>I sing a song everywhere <br>가끔은 여자친구가 <br>내 이런 점을 창피해해도 <br>난 이걸 멈출 수 없어 <br>내 음악이 이 길에 <br>울려 퍼질 때 까지 <br>따라서 불러 볼 때 까지 <br>춤춰 볼 때 까지 <br>I wanna Dance With U <br>아무 것도 필요 없어 <br>필요 없어 지금 <br>I wanna Dance With U <br>아무 것도 필요 없어 <br>필요 없어 yeah <br>내일은 또 어떤 멋진 <br>하루와 없던 <br>새롭고 즐거운 경험이 <br>반겨줄까 과연 <br>슬럼프가 날 덮쳐 때론 <br>빛을 못 보겠지 <br>뭐 어쩌겠어 다 날아가도록 <br>I sing a song everytime <br>I sing a song everywhere <br>가끔은 여자친구가 <br>내 이런 점을 창피해해도 <br>난 이걸 멈출 수 없어 <br>내 음악이 이 길에 <br>울려 퍼질 때 까지 <br>따라서 불러 볼 때 까지 <br>춤춰 볼 때 까지 <br>I wanna Dance With U <br>아무 것도 필요 없어 <br>필요 없어 지금 <br>I wanna Dance With U <br>아무 것도 필요 없어 <br>필요 없어 yeah <br>누가 쳐다보든 말든 <br>I don't give a F about it <br>더 중요하지 시선보단 <br>내 이 순간이 <br>우린 너무 서로 견제해 <br>그럼 하고 싶은 거는 <br>언제 해 <br>이미 허비 아니 이미 <br>소비한 시간이 많으니까 <br>난 이제 더 이상 시간은 <br>안 버릴 거야 <br>너희가 남 탓하면서 <br>불만만 많을 때 <br>우린 그냥 전부 <br>달아날 때 까지 <br>I sing a song everytime <br>I sing a song everywhere <br>가끔은 여자친구가 <br>내 이런 점을 창피해해도 <br>난 이걸 멈출 수 없어 <br>내 음악이 이 길에 <br>울려 퍼질 때 까지 <br>따라서 불러 볼 때 까지 <br>춤춰 볼 때 까지 <br>I wanna Dance With U <br>아무 것도 필요 없어 <br>필요 없어 지금 <br>I wanna Dance With U <br>아무 것도 필요 없어 <br>필요 없어 yeah <br>]]></content><category term="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)" label="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)"/><category term="Dance With U" label="Dance With U"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시기펩_Siggie_Feb/딸기_생크림_케익/</id><title>시기펩_Siggie_Feb - 딸기 생크림 케익 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:52:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:52:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B8%B0%ED%8E%A9_Siggie_Feb/%EB%94%B8%EA%B8%B0_%EC%83%9D%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%BC_%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B5/" title="시기펩_Siggie_Feb - 딸기 생크림 케익 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랜만에 홍대입구역에 <br>올 때마다 점심은 아비꼬 <br>네가 좋아해서 기분 좋네 <br>잘 먹어서 예뻐 <br>하나도 안 남기고 <br>배부르게 먹고 <br>이 기분 좋은 vibe <br>유지시키기는 <br>왜 이리 어려울까 <br>그래서 나는 집에서 <br>홍대 좋은 카페를 <br>세 시간 동안 검색했어 <br>어젯밤에 <br>나는 어젯밤에 미리 정해놨지 <br>오늘 딸기 생크림 케익 <br>케익 먹을 거야 반드시 <br>피오니로 널 데려가는 길 <br>오늘 미친 듯이 <br>네가 너무 예뻐 왜 <br>날씨가 좋아서 피분 우윳빛 <br>두꺼운 입술은 더욱 새빨개 <br>새하얀 얼굴 위 <br>새빨간 입술이 달콤해서 <br>딸기 생크림 케익 <br>먹는 기분이야 <br>Oh Oh 그런 기분이야 <br>Oh OH 그런 기분이야 <br>딸기 생크림 Babe <br>딸기 생크림 Babe <br>딸기 생크림 Babe <br>너무 달콤해서 <br>딸기 생크림 케익 <br>먹는 기분이야 <br>Oh 장사 잘 되나봐 <br>5분정도 웨이팅 하고 앉았고 <br>바로 아메리카노 아이스 <br>두잔 and 딸기 <br>생크림 조각 케익 <br>계산 카드로 할게요 <br>기다리래 요 앞에서 넵 <br>생각보다 빨리 나왔고 <br>한 입 하기 전에 사진부터 <br>빨리 한 장 Woah <br>아이스 아메는 그저 <br>그렇고 빨리 포크 들어 <br>사이좋게 한 입 하자고 <br>오 맛있어 어때 <br>나는 좋은데 너의 반응이 <br>난 더 중요해 <br>나는 궁예같이 너의 <br>마음을 읽어보려 했어 <br>부질없네 Ay <br>너의 미소 때문에 <br>나는 확신했지 <br>오늘 딸기 생크림 <br>케익케익 선택 탁월했지 <br>너의 행복감에 찬 <br>얼굴을 봤어 <br>초승달 눈웃음의 <br>너는 애기 같지 <br>기분이 좋아서 피부는 생크림 <br>도톰한 입술은 마치 생딸기 <br>새하얀 얼굴 위 <br>새빨간 입술이 달콤해서 <br>딸기 생크림 케익 <br>먹는 기분이야 <br>Oh Oh 그런 기분이야 <br>Oh OH 그런 기분이야 <br>딸기 생크림 Babe <br>딸기 생크림 Babe <br>딸기 생크림 Babe <br>너무 달콤해서 <br>딸기 생크림 케익 <br>먹는 기분이야 <br>상큼 고소 달콤 awesome <br>상큼 고소 달콤 awesome <br>상큼 고소 달콤 awesome <br>상큼 고소 달콤 awesome <br>상큼 고소 달콤 awesome <br>상큼 고소 달콤 awesome <br>상큼 고소 달콤 awesome <br>너무 달콤해서 <br>딸기 생크림 케익 <br>먹는 기분이야 <br>]]></content><category term="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)" label="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)"/><category term="딸기 생크림 케익" label="딸기 생크림 케익"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시기펩_Siggie_Feb/가깝게/</id><title>시기펩_Siggie_Feb - 가깝게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:53:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:53:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B8%B0%ED%8E%A9_Siggie_Feb/%EA%B0%80%EA%B9%9D%EA%B2%8C/" title="시기펩_Siggie_Feb - 가깝게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[수줍게 눈 맞춘 순간 <br>난 알아버렸어 <br>너도 나와 같은 미래를 <br>상상했다는 걸 <br>상상했다는 걸 <br>두 번째 눈 맞춘 순간 <br>난 알아버렸어 <br>이건 아마 이전과는 <br>많이 다를 거란 걸 <br>많이 다를 거란 걸 <br>지금 필요한 건 너의 <br>내숭과 내 자신감이지 <br>이건 너와 내 밀고 당기기 <br>오늘 뭔가 진짜 <br>이뤄질 것 같은 밤이지 <br>이게 내 설레발은 아니길 <br>알다시피 난 잠깐 <br>힙합도 내려놨어 <br>넌 그 벽을 내려 <br>놓는 게 답 <br>택배보다 기다려지는 <br>너의 대답 <br>눈웃음으로 때우지 <br>말고 말을 해봐 <br>좀 더 가깝게 <br>내게 다가오네 <br>어서와 나의 그늘 안으로 <br>내가 막아줄게 <br>너의 자외선을 오늘부터 <br>지금 당장 막아줄거야 <br>내가 전부 <br>어서와 나의 그늘 안으로 <br>내가 막아줄게 <br>이번엔 조금 천천히 <br>하고 싶었는데 <br>참을 수가 없었지 <br>널 가만히 볼 땐 온 <br>우주가 멈춰있지 <br>너의 두 눈으로 <br>내 시선이 꽂혔지 <br>네가 걱정하는 게 뭔지 <br>네가 싫증난 게 뭔지 <br>내가 다 생각해뒀으니 <br>넌 그냥 즐겨 해돋이를 <br>Oh yeah 그런 걱정들은 해롭지 <br>끝이 언제가 되든지 <br>난 준비 되었지 <br>난 이미 날 멈출 수 없어 <br>그래서 만들어야만했어 <br>이 love song <br>내 주위 여자들 <br>신경 쓸 필요 없어 <br>지금 네 감정을 <br>숨길 필요 없어 <br>날 둘러싸고 있는 편견을 <br>다 깨부시고 싶어 <br>알이 부화할 때처럼 <br>다시 날 태어나게 해줘 오늘 <br>그런 눈웃음으로 <br>때우지 말고 어서 <br>좀 더 가깝게 <br>내게 다가오네 <br>어서와 나의 그늘 안으로 <br>내가 막아줄게 <br>너의 자외선을 오늘부터 <br>지금 당장 막아줄거야 <br>내가 전부 <br>어서와 나의 그늘 안으로 <br>내가 막아줄게 <br>아직 감이 안와 <br>너의 날 향한 마음이 <br>어서 확답을 줘 babe <br>아직 감이 안와 <br>너의 날 향한 마음이 <br>어서 확답을 줘 babe <br>아직 감이 안와 <br>너의 날 향한 마음이 <br>어서 확답을 줘 babe <br>아직 감이 안와 <br>너의 날 향한 마음이 <br>어서 확답을 줘 <br>]]></content><category term="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)" label="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)"/><category term="가깝게" label="가깝게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시기펩_Siggie_Feb/추월차선/</id><title>시기펩_Siggie_Feb - 추월차선 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:53:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:53:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B8%B0%ED%8E%A9_Siggie_Feb/%EC%B6%94%EC%9B%94%EC%B0%A8%EC%84%A0/" title="시기펩_Siggie_Feb - 추월차선 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>절대 좌회전은 아니 ey <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>절대 좌회전은 아니 ey <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>절대 좌회전은 아니 ey <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>Siggie Max on the fast lane <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 키고 <br>머리 박아 박아 비켜 비켜 <br>평생 아마 아마추어들 Fuck <br>우린 프로처럼 벌어 억 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 끄고 <br>존나 밟아 밟아 비켜 비켜 <br>Beemer Benz <br>Bentley Lamborghini처럼 <br>쌩쌩 이 도로 위를 <br>우린 없어 망할 일이 <br>네 음악은 사라지지 <br>따라와봐 자빠지지 <br>조심할 건 가랑이지 <br>우린 맨날 장난치지 <br>fuck the fake friend homie <br>너흰 서로 똥까시 짓 <br>fuck the fake fam homie <br>우린 엔진부터 간지까지 <br>급이 다르지 아직까지 <br>밟아봐 더 세게 빨리 <br>우리 느낌 지금 존나 난리나지 <br>경쟁자들을 살인하지 <br>못 멈추지 왕의 자리까지 <br>siggie feb 할 말이 많지 <br>나머지 fluxury 마찬가지 <br>절대 좌회전은 아니 ey <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>독일 아우토반 위에 <br>Siggie Max on the fast lane <br>앞 유리가 단숨에 <br>깨질 듯이 밟아 세게 <br>앞 유리가 단숨에 <br>깨질 듯이 밟아 세게 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>절대 좌회전은 아니 ey <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>절대 좌회전은 아니 ey <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>절대 좌회전은 아니 ey <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>Siggie Max on the fast lane <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>내 동료들은 <br>전부 내 친구들 <br>BadMax 처음본지가 <br>이제 거의 15년 <br>우린 이름걸고 해 yeah <br>우린 이름걸고 해 yeah <br>무한동력 엔진 때매 필요 없어 <br>기름 연료 yeah yeah <br>바빠 바빠 밟아 밟아 <br>우리가 왜 밟는지 <br>저번에 낸 CLS에 <br>4분 꽉 담았지 <br>학교 수위 아저씨 <br>낙엽 쓸어 담듯이 <br>신사임당 paper <br>더블백에 터질 듯이 가득히 <br>가사 쓸 때는 caffeine에 <br>취해서 머리 팽 <br>끊을 수가 없는 커피 damn <br>데려가 날 zero to hunnit 백 <br>어떤 track에서든 <br>아 발라드랩 track은 별로 <br>오버워치 대 서든2의 <br>갭 물론 넌 서든 <br>왼쪽으로 달리지만 <br>우리 항상 right <br>우주에서 chillin <br>너는 지구 빵상 aight <br>우리 결과는 언제나 <br>전부 상상한 대로 나오지 <br>근데 너희 결과는 참담하지 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>왼쪽 깜빡 깜빡이를 켜 <br>절대 좌회전은 아니 ey <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>절대 좌회전은 아니 ey <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>절대 좌회전은 아니 ey <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>Siggie Max on the fast lane <br>우린 지금 추월차선에 <br>]]></content><category term="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)" label="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)"/><category term="추월차선" label="추월차선"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시기펩_Siggie_Feb/Flying_Feat_Tu_Neon/</id><title>시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Flying (Feat. Tu Neon) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:53:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:53:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B8%B0%ED%8E%A9_Siggie_Feb/Flying_Feat_Tu_Neon/" title="시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Flying (Feat. Tu Neon) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날개 없이 하늘을 <br>날고 싶어 왜냐면 <br>새 옷을 찢긴 싫으니까 <br>머나먼 데 날아가기 전에 <br>지금의 이야기를 <br>할 거야 하고 싶으니까 <br>불행한 나에 대해 <br>나쁜 사람에 대해 <br>말할 필요 없지 <br>앞으로만 가야 돼 <br>하지만 만약에 이런 말이 <br>내 꿈을 죽이는 건 <br>그만 봐야 돼 <br>사람의 욕심은 <br>끝이 없다는 걸 <br>다들 배웠잖아 <br>소환사의 협곡에서 <br>예전에 나도 백금 <br>테두리 한번 달아보려 <br>퇴근 후 부리나케 접속했었지 <br>다시 래퍼가 <br>되려고 했을 때 <br>많은 용기를 <br>필요로 했었네 <br>지금 예술가가 <br>난 되려해 <br>그래 내가 <br>온전하게 되려 해 <br>소년 점프처럼 <br>우린 우정 노력 승리 <br>모두 얻어 mo fucka <br>없었던 용기 땜에 <br>뭔가 해내기 전에 <br>겁부터 먹고 버렸어 <br>나는 사랑하고 싶어 <br>여자뿐이 아니고 모든 걸 <br>내가 싫어했던 <br>사람까지 포함해서 <br>어른은 됐지만 <br>성인은 아닌가봐 <br>아직 잘 모르겠어 <br>그래 뭘 알겠어 <br>길을 모르겠음 <br>오르겠어 그냥 <br>남자새끼가 왜 <br>말로만 떠드냐 <br>간보지 말고 <br>존나게 퍼부어 <br>용기가 없다면 <br>목소린 넣어둬 <br>날개 없이 하늘을 날고 싶어 <br>왜냐면 새 옷을 찢긴 싫으니까 <br>카페라떼 한잔이면 <br>이미 충분하게 <br>날 수 있는 기분이야 <br>I feel like feel like <br>하늘 위 날 수 <br>있을 것만 같은 <br>기분이야 이야 woo <br>마치 에픽하이처럼 <br>we fly we fly too <br>마치 에픽하이처럼 <br>we fly we fly too <br>I feel like feel like <br>하늘 위 날 수 <br>있을 것만 같은 <br>기분이야 이야 woo <br>마치 에픽하이처럼 <br>we fly we fly too <br>마치 에픽하이처럼 <br>we fly we fly too <br>날개 없이 <br>하늘을 날고 싶어 <br>골텐딩을 해보고 싶으니까 <br>아니 프리드로우 라인에서 <br>비트윈더레그 덩크를 <br>찍을 시간 <br>Half Neon half amazing <br>내 성이 Carter이기라도 한 듯 <br>미들네임이 Lamar거나 <br>적어도 애칭이 <br>Vince기라도 한 듯 <br>Neon Light's Flashing <br>like it's '06 <br>그 아무도 나의 승리 따윈 <br>기대조차 안하고 있어도 <br>홈 어드밴티지 없는 게임 <br>그거지 내 뚜껑을 여는 게 <br>그래 뚜껑 열려 <br>냄비 날아가면 <br>나는 피하지 <br>않을 거야 비프도 <br>Mo'fuggas Yeah <br>I'm counting these <br>Pistons Mo'fuggas <br>철공소 골목 옆 예술가 <br>like I'm in Detroit Mo'fuggas <br>Those rims seem like Donuts <br>when I'm on my lightworks <br>이 높이에서부터 <br>입 맞추거나 <br>베어물거나 할거야 <br>날개 없이 하늘을 날고 싶어 <br>골텐딩 얘기는 반은 핑계고 <br>Your Airness <br>소리를 듣고 싶어 <br>Your Brightness 까지도 괜찮아 <br>Like I'm Black Cat Jordan <br>아홉심장 속 심방과 <br>심실의 개수 <br>그래서 이 가슴 속에는 <br>언제나 36 Chambers <br>I feel like feel like <br>하늘 위 날 수 <br>있을 것만 같은 <br>기분이야 이야 woo <br>마치 에픽하이처럼 <br>we fly we fly too <br>마치 에픽하이처럼 <br>we fly we fly too <br>I feel like feel like <br>하늘 위 날 수 <br>있을 것만 같은 <br>기분이야 이야 woo <br>마치 에픽하이처럼 <br>we fly we fly too <br>마치 에픽하이처럼 <br>we fly we fly too <br>]]></content><category term="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)" label="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)"/><category term="Flying (Feat. Tu Neon)" label="Flying (Feat. Tu Neon)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시기펩_Siggie_Feb/Flying_Interlude/</id><title>시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Flying Interlude - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:53:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:53:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B8%B0%ED%8E%A9_Siggie_Feb/Flying_Interlude/" title="시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Flying Interlude - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날개 없이 사람이 <br>날아다닐 수 있을까 높은 하늘 위 <br>구름보다 높은 곳엔 태양과 달뿐 <br>올라가는 건 헛고생 <br>여긴 하루 종일 전쟁 <br>절대 알려주지 않는 선생 <br>그렇다면 날개 없이 사람이 <br>날 수 있을지도 몰라 높은 하늘 위 <br>난 남들 말을 멍청하게 믿고서 <br>용기를 잃을 일 따위 <br>소년만화 주인공처럼 없어 <br>동료들이 옆에 있잖니 <br>Fluxury waves 우리 인생의 끝 <br>전설에 대입하지 <br>성적은 A plus 따위 <br>비유가 머리에 안 떠오를 때 까지 <br>좆같은 가사 똑같은 가사 <br>랩을 하기 위한 가사 좆까길 바라 <br>what the fuck is goin' on <br>what the fuck is goin' on <br>꿈을 버린 놈은 음악 좀 하지 마라 <br>Fluxury Waves 이런 병신 새끼들 <br>귀신처럼 쌩까지 <br>멍청한 래퍼들 사기꾼들이 <br>모두 없어질 때까지 <br>난 날아가고 싶어 <br>여긴 너무 좆같아 <br>사람들이 똑같아서 <br>부정적인 사람들의 얘기는 <br>듣기도 보고 싶지도 않았어 <br>컨텐츠보다 중요해진 프로모 <br>좆도 필요 없어진 가치 <br>난 날아가지 Oh Yeah <br>내가 원하는 예술에 <br>닿을 때까지 Oh Yeah <br>Oh Yeah Oh Yeah <br>내가 원하는 예술에 <br>닿을 때까지 Oh Yeah <br>]]></content><category term="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)" label="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)"/><category term="Flying Interlude" label="Flying Interlude"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시기펩_Siggie_Feb/Maiden_Voyage/</id><title>시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Maiden Voyage - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:53:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:53:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B8%B0%ED%8E%A9_Siggie_Feb/Maiden_Voyage/" title="시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Maiden Voyage - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[요즘 공기 중에는 <br>미세먼지가 너무 많아 <br>숨쉬기 좀 힘들어 <br>나를 가로막는 문제들 뒤로 <br>이제 우리 꿈 보따리 봉인 풀어 <br>어떤 친구들은 공무원이 됐고 <br>자동차 딜러가 됐단 소식을 들어 <br>나는 아직 스물같이 놀고 <br>스물같이 말하면서 <br>스물 같은 랩노래를 불러 아직도 <br>우린 꿈을 꾸고 있어 아직도 <br>고등학생 때 꿨던 꿈을 가지고 <br>여기까지 왔고 갈 때까지 또 <br>랩 동아리부터 예술가까지 <br>의여고부터 world tour까지 <br>겁쟁이들은 난 용납하지 않네 <br>용납하지 않네 <br>어제 뭐였던 오늘은 <br>어떤 모습이고 <br>내일 내가 뭘 하든 <br>오늘 지금의 Siggie Feb과 <br>똑같은 놈은 없어 <br>Live for today 놈은 없어 <br>Live for today 놈은 없어 <br>Live for today <br>Baby Wassup 오늘이 우리 무대야 <br>Rock하는 아는 동생은 <br>HipHop하는 내가 부럽대 <br>한국 Rock판은 지금 거의 죽었대 <br>백수나 다름없지 우린 추석 때 <br>비교하면 우린 패자가 돼 <br>우리와 추락해 저 바닥에 <br>오늘의 다짐 또 새까맣게 <br>잊기 전에 손을 꽉 잡아 man <br>어떤 친구는 스피닝 강사가 됐어 <br>다른 친구는 <br>타코야끼 장사 잘돼서 <br>가게 앞에 손님들이 줄을 서 <br>유명해 의정부에서 <br>스무 살 땐 내가 다시 <br>래퍼가 될 줄 몰랐듯이 <br>내일 뭐가 될지 몰라 <br>이젠 잘나가는 <br>프로게이머가 됐어 <br>같이 Fluxury 만들었던 진효가 <br>어제 뭐였던 오늘은 <br>어떤 모습이고 <br>내일 내가 뭘 하든 <br>오늘 지금의 Siggie Feb과 <br>똑같은 놈은 없어 <br>Live for today 놈은 없어 <br>Live for today 놈은 없어 <br>Live for today <br>Baby Wassup 오늘이 우리 무대야 <br>첫 항해를 하는 거야 <br>같은 배를 타는 너와 <br>첫 항해를 하는 거야 <br>다른 배를 타는 넌 어떠니 <br>첫 항해를 하는 거야 <br>같은 배를 타는 너와 <br>첫 항해를 하는 거야 <br>다른 배를 타는 넌 어떠니 <br>첫 항해를 하는 거야 <br>같은 배를 타는 너와 <br>첫 항해를 하는 거야 <br>다른 배를 타는 넌 어떠니 <br>첫 항해를 하는 거야 <br>같은 배를 타는 너와 <br>첫 항해를 하는 거야 <br>다른 배를 타는 넌 어떠니 <br>어제 뭐였던 오늘은 <br>어떤 모습이고 <br>내일 내가 뭘 하든 <br>오늘 지금의 Siggie Feb과 <br>똑같은 놈은 없어 <br>Live for today 놈은 없어 <br>Live for today 놈은 없어 <br>Live for today <br>Baby Wassup 오늘이 우리 무대야 <br>]]></content><category term="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)" label="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)"/><category term="Maiden Voyage" label="Maiden Voyage"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시기펩_Siggie_Feb/Oh_Yeah/</id><title>시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Oh Yeah - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:53:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:53:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B8%B0%ED%8E%A9_Siggie_Feb/Oh_Yeah/" title="시기펩_Siggie_Feb - Oh Yeah - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나도 참 많이 변했지 <br>곤조만 세우는 게 <br>멋이라고 생각한 게 거의 어제 <br>예술에서 색안경은 중죄 <br>염따 앨범이 내 편견을 부쉈네 <br>미국처럼 하고 싶었거든 <br>미국처럼 <br>빈지노처럼 하고 싶었거든 <br>미로처럼 빠져 나오기 어려웠어 <br>난 지금처럼 친구 서너 명과 <br>기분 좋은 음악 할래 feel good <br>엉터리들 멍청이들 멈춰 <br>나는 두려울 게 하나도 없어 <br>Fluxury는 벌써 기름 끼얹어 <br>버벌진트 벤틀리에서 <br>몰래 훔쳐서 <br>온전히 예술가로 살기 위해 <br>나는 돈 벌어야 돼 랩해서만 <br>지금 너희가 노동력을 <br>뺏어가지만 <br>내 느낌은 못 뺏어가지 Oh Yeah <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Oh Yeah Alright 이건 <br>우리들의 Maiden Voyage <br>Oh Yeah Alright 이건 <br>우리들의 Maiden Voyage <br>요즘 산책 할 시간 <br>빼기도 빡빡해서 <br>이 앨범에서 산책은 <br>빼기로 답했어 <br>아침에 일어나서 밖에서 밥 먹고 <br>체육관에서 바벨 들어 <br>샤워 후에 작업해 우린 존나 바빠 <br>이젠 I ain't no fuckin' 말라깽 <br>노래를 하든 또 <br>랩을 하든 카페에서 <br>노랫말 쓰든 그런 삶에 가깝게 yo <br>얼마 전에 마이크 샀어 100만원 <br>너희에게 좀 더 <br>좋은 랩 들려주고파서 <br>너흰 그냥 가서 퍼뜨려줘 Siggie Feb <br>BadMax K$ dollar sign 잊지 말고 uh <br>미소지기 Siggie 이제 <br>미소 지키지 내 가족 <br>지기 싫어서 음악 했던 <br>시기는 지났어 <br>yo 이제는 나에게서 <br>아무것도 못 뺏어가 <br>자신 있음 뺏어봐 bish Oh Yeah <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Oh Yeah Alright 이건 <br>우리들의 Maiden Voyage <br>Oh Yeah Alright 이건 <br>우리들의 Maiden Voyage <br>월 백이면 월 천 누워 떡 <br>월 백이면 월 천 누워 떡 <br>월 백이면 월 천 누워 떡 <br>월 백이면 월 천 누워 떡 <br>월 백이면 월 백이면 <br>저기까지 금방 가 <br>눈 깜빡 하는 순간 아 <br>눈 깜빡 하는 순간 아 하면 도착하지 <br>Fluxury 모두 다 같이 Oh Yeah <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Siggie Feb은 알바를 해도 <br>아니지 돈의 노예 <br>Oh Yeah Alright 이건 <br>우리들의 Maiden Voyage <br>Oh Yeah Alright 이건 <br>우리들의 Maiden Voyage <br>]]></content><category term="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)" label="시기펩 (Siggie Feb)"/><category term="Oh Yeah" label="Oh Yeah"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/킨타나/그대의/</id><title>킨타나 - 그대의 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:53:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:53:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%A8%ED%83%80%EB%82%98/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%9D%98/" title="킨타나 - 그대의 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[솔직한 내 마음 <br>지금 말할게요 <br>쑥스런 고백을 <br>들어봐주세요 <br>당신을 너무나 <br>사랑하고 있죠 <br>하지만 불안한 맘도 <br>난 있어요 <br>아직은 우리 둘 <br>완전하지 않죠 <br>서로가 모르는 <br>부분도 있죠 <br>아픔도 실수도 <br>모두 사랑해요 <br>온전하게 이해해주길 <br>바래요 <br>그대의 옷향기로도 <br>너무나 가슴이 따듯해져요 <br>그대의 웃는 얼굴이 <br>세상을 다 가진 것만 같아요 <br>그대가 볼 만질 때면 <br>귀여운 소녀가 된 것만 같죠 <br>그대의 미소가 <br>너무 좋죠 <br>전화기 넘어서 <br>들리는 목소리 <br>어두운 새벽을 <br>가득히 채우죠 <br>많은 걸 바라고 <br>있지는 않아요 <br>그저 어깨 기대게만 <br>해주세요 <br>그대의 옷향기로도 <br>너무나 가슴이 따듯해져요 <br>그대의 웃는 얼굴이 <br>세상을 다 가진 것만 같아요 <br>그대가 볼 만질 때면 <br>귀여운 소녀가 된 것만 같죠 <br>그대의 oh <br>향기가 oh <br>그대의 미소가 <br>너무 좋죠 <br>]]></content><category term="킨타나" label="킨타나"/><category term="그대의" label="그대의"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/킨타나/밤_속삭임/</id><title>킨타나 - 밤 속삭임 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:53:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:53:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%82%A8%ED%83%80%EB%82%98/%EB%B0%A4_%EC%86%8D%EC%82%AD%EC%9E%84/" title="킨타나 - 밤 속삭임 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[영원히 빛날 듯한 <br>별빛은 은은하게 <br>나의 매일 밤을 지켜주네 <br>내 맘은 온통 촛불처럼 <br>타들어만 가고 있어 <br>언제쯤 그댄 <br>내게 돌아올까 <br>낯익은 목소리만 들어도 <br>뒤돌아 보는데 <br>그댈 기다리네 <br>난 더 이상 기다릴 수 없어 <br>난 더 이상 안돼 <br>그댄 꿈속에만 살아요 <br>꿈속에선 나의 <br>매일 밤을 함께하네 <br>영원히 그와 별빛처럼 <br>서로 비춰주고 싶어 <br>언제쯤 그댄 <br>내게 돌아올까 <br>낯익은 목소리만 들어도 <br>뒤돌아 보는데 <br>그댈 기다리네 <br>난 더 이상 기다릴 수 없어 <br>난 더 이상 안돼 <br>이럴 수는 없어 <br>멀어지는 널 <br>상상하지도 못한 나인데 <br>모든게 흩어진 조각인 채로 <br>오 난 한 조각씩 모아 <br>너를 기다려 <br>언제쯤 그댄 내게 돌아올까 <br>낯익은 목소리만 들어도 <br>뒤돌아 보는데 <br>그댈 기다리네 <br>난 더 이상 기다릴 수 없어 <br>난 더 이상 안돼 <br>난 더 이상 안돼 <br>]]></content><category term="킨타나" label="킨타나"/><category term="밤 속삭임" label="밤 속삭임"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유리Yuri/Work_It_Out_Inst/</id><title>유리Yuri - Work It Out (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:53:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:53:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EB%A6%ACYuri/Work_It_Out_Inst/" title="유리Yuri - Work It Out (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girls Baby I Wanna Wanna <br>Girls Baby I Wanna Wanna <br>니 눈빛이 Special해 <br>왠지 남달라 보여 니가 <br>너만의 탄탄한 <br>Muscle Brown Skin <br>내 눈을 뗄 수가 없잖아 <br>Take Take Me <br>널 보는 나의 눈은 Stop <br>Take Me <br>모든 게 너에게로 Stop <br>Take Me <br>궁금해져 궁금해져 <br>난 지금 니 생각에 <br>Thinkin' About <br>U So Cool Like That <br>U Look So Hot Like That <br>U Look So Chill Like That <br>U Look So Fine Like That <br>난 Lucky Lucky 해 <br>맘이 두근 두근대 <br>너를 노크 노크해 <br>눈치채지 못하게 <br>Work It <br>내게 내게 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>몸이 가는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>나에게만 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>니가 원하는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>Ha You Work It <br>Ha Work It <br>I'm Crushed On You <br>너에게 풍기는 느낌이 <br>아주 달콤해 <br>Please Take Me <br>전부 알고 싶어 너란 사람이 <br>너의 말투와 몸짓이 <br>조금씩 커지는 호기심 <br>난 너에겐 버릴래 자존심 <br>한 번 더 봐도 어쩜 넌 <br>Awesome <br>다시 봐도 너는 Perfect <br>너는 왜 자꾸 <br>My Heart Attack <br>드디어 넌 내게 <br>Eye Contact <br>나 같은 스타일은 너는 어때 <br>Take Take Me <br>날 보는 너의 눈은 Stop <br>Take Me <br>모든 게 나에게로 Stop <br>Take Me <br>궁금할 걸 궁금할 걸 <br>나라는 여자가 <br>What's Thinkin' About <br>내게 내게 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>몸이 가는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>나에게만 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>니가 원하는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>조금만 더 자연스럽게 <br>나에게만 비밀스럽게 <br>좀 더 다가와 <br>긴 말은 필요 없어 <br>달콤한 혀끝에서 <br>너만을 찾고 있어 <br>내게 내게 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>몸이 가는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>나에게만 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>니가 원하는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>Ha You Work It <br>Ha Work It <br>]]></content><category term="유리(Yuri)" label="유리(Yuri)"/><category term="Work It Out (Inst.)" label="Work It Out (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/유리Yuri/Work_It_Out/</id><title>유리Yuri - Work It Out - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:53:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:53:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A0%EB%A6%ACYuri/Work_It_Out/" title="유리Yuri - Work It Out - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Girls Baby I Wanna Wanna <br>Girls Baby I Wanna Wanna <br>니 눈빛이 Special해 <br>왠지 남달라 보여 니가 <br>너만의 탄탄한 <br>Muscle Brown Skin <br>내 눈을 뗄 수가 없잖아 <br>Take Take Me <br>널 보는 나의 눈은 Stop <br>Take Me <br>모든 게 너에게로 Stop <br>Take Me <br>궁금해져 궁금해져 <br>난 지금 니 생각에 <br>Thinkin' About <br>U So Cool Like That <br>U Look So Hot Like That <br>U Look So Chill Like That <br>U Look So Fine Like That <br>난 Lucky Lucky 해 <br>맘이 두근 두근대 <br>너를 노크 노크해 <br>눈치채지 못하게 <br>Work It <br>내게 내게 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>몸이 가는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>나에게만 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>니가 원하는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>Ha You Work It <br>Ha Work It <br>I'm Crushed On You <br>너에게 풍기는 느낌이 <br>아주 달콤해 <br>Please Take Me <br>전부 알고 싶어 너란 사람이 <br>너의 말투와 몸짓이 <br>조금씩 커지는 호기심 <br>난 너에겐 버릴래 자존심 <br>한 번 더 봐도 어쩜 넌 <br>Awesome <br>다시 봐도 너는 Perfect <br>너는 왜 자꾸 <br>My Heart Attack <br>드디어 넌 내게 <br>Eye Contact <br>나 같은 스타일은 너는 어때 <br>Take Take Me <br>날 보는 너의 눈은 Stop <br>Take Me <br>모든 게 나에게로 Stop <br>Take Me <br>궁금할 걸 궁금할 걸 <br>나라는 여자가 <br>What's Thinkin' About <br>내게 내게 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>몸이 가는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>나에게만 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>니가 원하는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>조금만 더 자연스럽게 <br>나에게만 비밀스럽게 <br>좀 더 다가와 <br>긴 말은 필요 없어 <br>달콤한 혀끝에서 <br>너만을 찾고 있어 <br>내게 내게 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>몸이 가는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>나에게만 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>니가 원하는 대로 <br>Work It Out <br>Baby Work It Work It Work It Out <br>Ha You Work It <br>Ha Work It <br>]]></content><category term="유리(Yuri)" label="유리(Yuri)"/><category term="Work It Out" label="Work It Out"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데이브니어_Dave_Near/지금_넌_어디로/</id><title>데이브니어_Dave_Near - 지금 넌 어디로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:54:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:54:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%8C%EB%8B%88%EC%96%B4_Dave_Near/%EC%A7%80%EA%B8%88_%EB%84%8C_%EC%96%B4%EB%94%94%EB%A1%9C/" title="데이브니어_Dave_Near - 지금 넌 어디로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 아무말 없는거니 <br>이제 내곁을 떠나려고 하니 <br>너무나 아름답던 <br>우리의 사랑 지우려고 하니 <br>왜 너 가려고 하니 <br>아무 말도 없이 그렇게 <br>왜 한마디도 없이 <br>고개 숙인 채로 그렇게 <br>사랑의 시간이 흐르고 흘러 <br>너를 보내게 될 줄은 몰랐어 <br>끝도 없는 사랑을 <br>우린 꿈꾸었는데 <br>지금 넌 어디로 <br>지금 넌 어디로 가는거니 <br>왜 너 가려고 하니 <br>아무 말도 없이 그렇게 <br>왜 한마디도 없이 <br>고개 숙인 채로 그렇게 <br>사랑의 시간이 이렇게 흘러 <br>너를 보내게 될 줄은 몰랐어 <br>끝도 없는 사랑을 <br>우린 꿈꾸었는데 <br>지금 넌 어디로 지금 넌 어디로 <br>사랑의 시간이 이렇게 흘러 <br>너를 보내게 될 줄은 몰랐어 <br>끝도 없는 사랑을 <br>우린 꿈꾸었는데 <br>지금 넌 어디로 <br>지금 넌 어디로 가는거니 <br>]]></content><category term="데이브니어 (Dave Near)" label="데이브니어 (Dave Near)"/><category term="지금 넌 어디로" label="지금 넌 어디로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/길미/시간에_너를_잠군다_Inst/</id><title>길미 - 시간에 너를 잠군다 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:54:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:54:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%B8%EB%AF%B8/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%97%90_%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9E%A0%EA%B5%B0%EB%8B%A4_Inst/" title="길미 - 시간에 너를 잠군다 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부서질것만 같아서 내 마음을 <br>더 굳게 잠그려 했어 <br>만지지 말라고 난 약해서 <br>너로 인해 사라진다고 제발 <br>아무 일 없듯이 지나가 <br>시간아 지나가 제발 <br>시간에 너를 잠군다 <br>널 놓칠까 봐 <br>눈물에 너를 잠군다 <br>사랑을 두고 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>기억이 너를 삼키면 <br>돌아오겠니 <br>차가워지는 바람에 베여버린 <br>가슴에 아파하는 날 <br>바라만보는 너 변해버린 <br>네 눈빛이 달라졌다고 제발 <br>아무 일 없듯이 지나가 <br>시간아 지나가 제발 <br>시간에 너를 잠군다 <br>널 놓칠까 봐 <br>눈물에 너를 잠군다 <br>사랑을 두고 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>기억이 너를 삼키면 <br>돌아오겠니 제발 <br>한 순간의 꿈을 꾸듯 지나가 <br>시간아 제발 <br>사랑에 너를 잠군다 <br>널 놓칠까 봐 <br>사랑에 너를 숨긴다 <br>정말 끝일까 봐 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>기억이 너를 삼키면 <br>돌아오겠니 <br>]]></content><category term="길미" label="길미"/><category term="시간에 너를 잠군다 (Inst.)" label="시간에 너를 잠군다 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/길미/시간에_너를_잠군다/</id><title>길미 - 시간에 너를 잠군다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:54:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:54:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%B8%EB%AF%B8/%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84%EC%97%90_%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9E%A0%EA%B5%B0%EB%8B%A4/" title="길미 - 시간에 너를 잠군다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[부서질것만 같아서 내 마음을 <br>더 굳게 잠그려 했어 <br>만지지 말라고 난 약해서 <br>너로 인해 사라진다고 제발 <br>아무 일 없듯이 지나가 <br>시간아 지나가 제발 <br>시간에 너를 잠군다 <br>널 놓칠까 봐 <br>눈물에 너를 잠군다 <br>사랑을 두고 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>기억이 너를 삼키면 <br>돌아오겠니 <br>차가워지는 바람에 베여버린 <br>가슴에 아파하는 날 <br>바라만보는 너 변해버린 <br>네 눈빛이 달라졌다고 제발 <br>아무 일 없듯이 지나가 <br>시간아 지나가 제발 <br>시간에 너를 잠군다 <br>널 놓칠까 봐 <br>눈물에 너를 잠군다 <br>사랑을 두고 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>기억이 너를 삼키면 <br>돌아오겠니 제발 <br>한 순간의 꿈을 꾸듯 지나가 <br>시간아 제발 <br>사랑에 너를 잠군다 <br>널 놓칠까 봐 <br>사랑에 너를 숨긴다 <br>정말 끝일까 봐 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>가지마 가지마 <br>기억이 너를 삼키면 <br>돌아오겠니 <br>]]></content><category term="길미" label="길미"/><category term="시간에 너를 잠군다" label="시간에 너를 잠군다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/구추_Goochu/Nobody_Knows/</id><title>구추_Goochu - Nobody Knows - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:55:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:55:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B5%AC%EC%B6%94_Goochu/Nobody_Knows/" title="구추_Goochu - Nobody Knows - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너 미안하단 말로 <br>나를 밀어내려 하지마 <br>더이상 아무말도 <br>내겐 필요없잖아 <br>이미 초라해져 버린 <br>내가 너무 미워져 <br>나를 앞에두고 <br>네가 떠나가잖아 <br>내 곁에는 없어 <br>I don't wanna let you go <br>내 모든건 다 너였잖아 <br>집착이 되어버린 지금 내맘 <br>Nobody knows <br>사랑했던 모든 기억들은 <br>Let you know <br>네 모든걸 다 <br>Give it to me <br>집착이 되어버린 지금 내맘 <br>Nobody knows <br>너 사랑이란 말로 <br>나를 밀어내려 하지마 <br>멀어져가는 널 <br>붙잡을수가 없잖아 <br>이미 초라해져 버린 <br>내가 너무 미워져 <br>나를 앞에두고 <br>네가 떠나가잖아 <br>내 곁에는 없어 <br>I don't wanna let you go <br>내 모든건 다 너였잖아 <br>집착이 되어버린 지금 내맘 <br>Nobody knows <br>사랑했던 모든 기억들은 <br>Let you know <br>네 모든걸 다 <br>Give it to me <br>집착이 되어버린 지금 내맘 <br>Nobody knows <br>Nobody knows It but me <br>언제나 너를 향한 마음을 <br>너만을 사랑했던나 <br>기억해줘 날 언제까지나 <br>영원히 널 사랑할께 <br>내 곁에는 없어 <br>I don't wanna let you go <br>이별따윈 없어 <br>I just want to be with you <br>내 모든건 다 너였잖아 <br>집착이 되어버린 지금 내맘 <br>Nobody knows <br>사랑했던 모든 기억들은 <br>Let you know <br>네 모든걸 다 <br>Give it to me <br>집착이 되어버린 지금 내맘 <br>Nobody knows <br>Nobody knows <br>]]></content><category term="구추 (Goochu)" label="구추 (Goochu)"/><category term="Nobody Knows" label="Nobody Knows"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The49ers/In_Love_With_Two_Women/</id><title>The49ers - In Love With Two Women - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:55:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:55:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The49ers/In_Love_With_Two_Women/" title="The49ers - In Love With Two Women - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jas Mace <br><br>I know the musicians in the house are going to feel us on this one <br>You know how it is, sometimes you can’t tell them…you know… <br>I don’t want you to come to the show <br>Cause I don’t really have time to be entertaining people <br>When I’m trying to handle business <br>It goes like this <br><br>Jas Mace <br><br>When we first met you knew I had another Love, Love <br>You knew I was involved with another girl <br>But still you wanted in so I made you my friend <br>With the understanding that she takes presidence <br>At every event and any situation <br>Obligations pulling me away but be patient <br>Cause I’ll be back <br>As sure as the sun rises the next day I’ll be thinking of a way, way <br>That I can spend time with ya <br>Even when I’m out with her at night I’m still thinking of your picture <br>Yeah it might seem kind of selfish <br>I want you both in my life and I can’t help it, help it <br>I understand it’s frustrating <br>But time is a luxury I really can’t engage in <br>Or allocate when she occupies my life <br>But that’s how it is when you make music your wife <br><br>Hook <br><br>I can’t escape this life that I’m living <br>I’m in the mix I’m in love with two women <br>And I don’t know, which one to chose <br>But I don’t want to let none of them go, go <br>I can’t escape this life that I’m living <br>I’m in the mix I’m in love with two women <br>And I don’t know, which one to chose <br>But I don’t want to let none of them go, go <br><br>Marchitect <br><br>When we met I was married, yeah I was spoken for <br>I tied the knot with my music and what I’m working towards <br>And all I need in this life of sin <br>Is my MPC aka my girlfriend <br>Until my world ends, I’m all up in the whirlwind <br>I’m all up in the music biz like George Gershwin <br>Music is my baby girl, I ain’t trying to save the world <br>Don’t make me have to chose you’re going to lose and act crazy girl <br>And succumb to the jealousy <br>And want to see me start to fall off like leprosy <br>Hennessey, that’s just a temporary remedy <br>But your there to whisper in my ear until the end of me <br>I gotta say you’re always get in the way <br>Of every single new girl and have them jetting away <br>But that’s okay because I know you’re still loyal <br>And you know I’m still down you got me whipped something royal like oh <br><br>Hook <br><br>I can’t escape this life that I’m living <br>I’m in the mix I’m in love with two women <br>And I don’t know, which one to chose <br>But I don’t want to let none of them go, go <br>I can’t escape this life that I’m living <br>I’m in the mix I’m in love with two women <br>And I don’t know, which one to chose <br>But I don’t want to let none of them go, go]]></content><category term="The49ers" label="The49ers"/><category term="In Love With Two Women" label="In Love With Two Women"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/열둘/보이나요_Feat_김원종/</id><title>열둘 - 보이나요 (Feat. 김원종) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:56:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:56:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B4%EB%91%98/%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EC%9B%90%EC%A2%85/" title="열둘 - 보이나요 (Feat. 김원종) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[보이나요 그댈 향한 내 마음이 <br>들리나요 뛰는 내 심장 소리가 <br>다가오는 순간이 <br>나 조금은 무섭고 떨려도 <br>지금 만큼은 나 용기 내어 볼게요 <br>보이나요 그댈 향한 내 마음이 <br>들리나요 커지는 심장 소리가 <br>다는 아니더라도 <br>나 이것만은 약속할게요 <br>내가 옆에서 그대 손 잡아 줄게요 <br>보이지는 않아도 알 수 있죠 <br>우리가 함께할 수 있단 걸 <br>안아줘요 나 느낄 수 있게 <br>그대 울지 말아요 괜찮아요 <br>그 눈물 내가 닦아줄게요 <br>나 알아요 그대 사랑해요 <br>힘든 일이 있다면 <br>나는 말할 수 없어 <br>나에게 말해줘요 <br>그대 내게 기댈 수 있게 <br>기댈 수 있게 <br>그대 울지 말아요 날 보지 말아요 <br>나를 바라봐줘요 <br>약속해요 놓지 않을게요 <br>보이지는 않아도 알 수 있죠 <br>우리가 함께 할 수 있단 걸 <br>안아줘요 나 느낄 수 있게 <br>그대 울지 말아요 괜찮아요 <br>그 눈물 내가 닦아줄게요 <br>나 알아요 그대 사랑해요 <br>]]></content><category term="열둘" label="열둘"/><category term="보이나요 (Feat. 김원종)" label="보이나요 (Feat. 김원종)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/열둘/널_보면_울까봐/</id><title>열둘 - 널 보면 울까봐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:56:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:56:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B4%EB%91%98/%EB%84%90_%EB%B3%B4%EB%A9%B4_%EC%9A%B8%EA%B9%8C%EB%B4%90/" title="열둘 - 널 보면 울까봐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 많이 지났어 우리 헤어진 지도 <br>함께 하던 공간도 <br>같이 썼던 물건도 <br>이젠 아무렇지 않아 <br>어쩌다 생각나는 우리 추억도 <br>이제 전처럼 아프지 않은데 <br>가지고 있던 사진들을 <br>지우는 일은 <br>왜 아직도 못하겠는지 <br>널 보면 울까봐 다시 힘들까봐 <br>애써 참았던 내 맘이 널 찾을까봐 <br>혹시나 너도 같은 마음일까봐 <br>나는 아직도 널 못 지워 <br>어쩌다 들려오는 너의 얘기도 <br>이제 전만큼 아프지 않은데 <br>가지고 있던 사진들을 <br>지우는 일은 <br>왜 아직도 못하겠는지 <br>널 보면 울까봐 다시 힘들까봐 <br>애써 참았던 내 맘이 널 찾을까봐 <br>혹시나 너도 같은 마음일까봐 <br>나는 아직도 나는 아직도 너를 <br>널 보면 울까봐 다시 힘들까봐 <br>애써 참았던 내 맘이 널 찾을까봐 <br>혹시나 너도 같은 마음일까봐 <br>나는 아직도 널 못 지워 <br>사실 아직도 많이 울어 <br>]]></content><category term="열둘" label="열둘"/><category term="널 보면 울까봐" label="널 보면 울까봐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/열둘/고백/</id><title>열둘 - 고백 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:57:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:57:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%B4%EB%91%98/%EA%B3%A0%EB%B0%B1/" title="열둘 - 고백 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[널 닮은 곰인형 속에 <br>내 맘 전해볼까 <br>그래도 이건 아닌데 <br>왜 널 좋아하니 <br>늦은 밤 걸려온 전화 <br>니가 아니기를 <br>아니 사실 너였으면 <br>내 맘이 먼저 달려가 <br>나 화난 건 아닌데 <br>자꾸 투정 부리고 <br>혹시라도 밀어낼까봐 <br>눈치도 한 번 봐주고 <br>가을바람 불어오는 소리에 <br>난 너로 물들고 <br>함께 걸었던 그 자리 그 위로 <br>사랑이 내린다 <br>너의 시선 가는 곳에 <br>매일 내가 있고 <br>눈동자 속에는 항상 <br>내가 담겼으면 <br>친구 사이로 남기에 <br>넌 너무 멋있고 <br>같이 하는 시간들이 <br>난 자꾸만 힘들어져 <br>나 화난 건 아닌데 <br>자꾸 투정 부리고 <br>혹시라도 밀어낼까봐 <br>눈치도 한 번 봐주고 <br>가을바람 불어오는 소리에 <br>난 너로 물들고 <br>함께 걸었던 그 자리 그 위로 <br>사랑이 내린다 <br>가을바람 불어오는 소리에 <br>난 너로 물들고 <br>함께 걸었던 그 자리 그 위로 <br>사랑이 내린다 <br>가을바람 불어오는 소리에 <br>난 너로 물들고 <br>함께 걸었던 그 자리 그 위로 <br>추억이 쌓인다 <br>]]></content><category term="열둘" label="열둘"/><category term="고백" label="고백"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/손승연/미아/</id><title>손승연 - 미아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:58:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:58:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%90%EC%8A%B9%EC%97%B0/%EB%AF%B8%EC%95%84/" title="손승연 - 미아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[또 다시 그 길을 만났어 <br>한참을 걸어도 걸어도 <br>익숙한 거리 추억 투성이 <br>미로 위의 내 산책 <br>벗어나려 접어든 길에 <br>기억이 없어서 좋지만 <br>조금도 못 가 눈앞에 닿는 <br>너의 손이 이끌었던 그 때 그 자리 <br>길을 잃어버린 나 <br>가도 가도 끝없는 <br>날 부르는 목소리 날 향해 뛰던 <br>너의 모습이 살아오는 듯 <br>돌아가야 하는 나 <br>쉬운 길은 없어서 <br>돌고 돌아가는 길 <br>그 추억 다 피해 이제 다 와가는 듯 <br>나의 집 저 멀리 보여서 <br>발걸음 재촉하려 하다 <br>너무 많았던 추억뿐인 곳 <br>날 항상 바래다주던 이 길뿐인데 <br>우두커니 한참 바라보다가 <br>어느새 길 한 가득 니 모습들 워 <br>그 속을 지나려 그 속을 지나려 <br>내딛는 한걸음 <br>천천히 두 눈을 감고서 <br>길은 어디에 <br>가도 가도 끝없는 끝없는 <br>날 부르는 목소리 날 향해 뛰던 <br>너의 모습이 살아오는 듯 <br>돌아가야 하는 나 <br>쉬운 길은 없어서 <br>돌고 돌아가는 길 <br>그 추억 다 피해 이제 도착한 듯해 <br>이젠 <br>]]></content><category term="손승연" label="손승연"/><category term="미아" label="미아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한동근/1994년_어느_늦은_밤/</id><title>한동근 - 1994년 어느 늦은 밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:58:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:58:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EB%8F%99%EA%B7%BC/1994%EB%85%84_%EC%96%B4%EB%8A%90_%EB%8A%A6%EC%9D%80_%EB%B0%A4/" title="한동근 - 1994년 어느 늦은 밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 밤 그대에게 <br>말로 할 수가 없어서 <br>이런 마음을 종이 위에 <br>글로 쓴 걸 용서해 <br>한참을 그대에게 <br>겁이 날 만큼 미쳤었지 <br>그런 내 모습 <br>이제는 후회할지 몰라 <br>하지만 그대여 다른 건 다 잊어도 <br>이것만은 기억했으면 좋겠어 <br>내가 그대를 얼만큼 <br>사랑하고 있는지를 <br>사랑하는지를 <br>외로이 텅빈 방에 <br>나만 홀로 남았을 때 <br>그제야 나는 그대 없음을 <br>알게 될지 몰라 <br>하지만 그대여 다른 건 다 잊어도 <br>이것만은 기억했으면 좋겠어 <br>내가 그대를 얼만큼 <br>사랑하고 있는지를 <br>사랑하는지를 <br>그대여 나의 그대여 <br>다른 건 다 잊어도 <br>이것만은 기억했으면 좋겠어 <br>내가 그대를 얼만큼 <br>사랑하고 있는지를 <br>사랑하는지를 <br>사랑하는지를 <br>그대 이제는 안녕 <br>]]></content><category term="한동근" label="한동근"/><category term="1994년 어느 늦은 밤" label="1994년 어느 늦은 밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rough/팅가팅가_Feat_RP-T/</id><title>Rough - 팅가팅가 (Feat. RP-T) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T00:59:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T00:59:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rough/%ED%8C%85%EA%B0%80%ED%8C%85%EA%B0%80_Feat_RP-T/" title="Rough - 팅가팅가 (Feat. RP-T) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[팅가팅가팅가팅 <br>팅가팅가팅가팅 <br>팅가팅가팅가팅 <br>팅가팅가팅가팅 <br>머슥거린 아가씨 <br>거릴 걷는 아가씨 <br>언제나 눈길 주고 <br>고갤 돌릴 아가씨 <br>썬글라스 아저씨 <br>근육질 스키니 <br>언제나 눈길 주고 <br>훑어 대는 아저씨 <br>Love hate of Pain <br>지독한 레이스 <br>맘속에서 벌어지는 <br>소리없는 War fair <br>넌 구름 잡힐 듯 <br>잡히지 않네 im the moon <br>니가 빛날 때면 <br>난 가려지네 <br>뭐가 문제야 <br>뭘 잘못했지 <br>그래 너도 문제야 <br>너도 똑같애 <br>매일매일 Trouble <br>and Trouble Bubble 처럼 <br>부풀어 like 근거 <br>없는 소문 shit <br>you ru ra ru hit it <br>you ru ra ru hit it <br>맘을 열어봐 <br>you ru ra ru scale <br>on you ru ra ru scale on <br>용길내서 봐봐 <br>무엇인가 느껴질 껄 <br>팅가팅가 군상 <br>벗어 던져 너를 <br>우물쭈물 대는 널 <br>되풀이 되기만 하는 <br>오해와 오해 또 <br>건조하게 되뇌이는 <br>Sorry i'm sorry <br>so tired 이젠 지쳤어 <br>그래 내생각도 <br>그래 우린 미쳤어 <br>Don't touch me <br>don't screw me up <br>맘에도 없는 말로 <br>상처를 줬어 <br>붉게 물든 <br>니 입술은 익숙하면서 <br>검게 멍든 <br>니 맘 속을 못 알아 줘서 <br>우연히 비춰지는 <br>가식 속에 갇힌 나야 <br>적잖이 놀랍잖고 <br>부끄럽지 않아 <br>누구나 한번쯤은 <br>가져보는 사랑 <br>이제는 즐길런다 <br>가식 속의 나를 <br>you ru ra ru hit it <br>you ru ra ru hit it <br>맘을 열어봐 <br>you ru ra ru scale on <br>you ru ra ru scale on <br>용길내서 봐봐 <br>무엇인가 느껴질 껄 <br>팅가팅가 군상 <br>벗어 던져 너를 <br>우물쭈물 대는 널 <br>you ru ra ru hit it <br>you ru ra ru hit it <br>내게 말해봐 <br>you ru ra ru scale on <br>you ru ra ru scale on <br>고민하지마 봐 <br>무엇인가 느껴질 껄 <br>팅가팅가 군상 <br>답안지를 들고 <br>떨고 있는 너를 봐 <br>]]></content><category term="Rough" label="Rough"/><category term="팅가팅가 (Feat. RP-T)" label="팅가팅가 (Feat. RP-T)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Voxxclub/Geiles_Himmelblau_Live_Aus_Neu-Ulm___2016/</id><title>Voxxclub - Geiles Himmelblau (Live Aus Neu-Ulm / 2016) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T01:00:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T01:00:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Voxxclub/Geiles_Himmelblau_Live_Aus_Neu-Ulm___2016/" title="Voxxclub - Geiles Himmelblau (Live Aus Neu-Ulm / 2016) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Geiles Himmelblau, alles wie im Traum <br>unser Sonnentisch hier ist gedeckt <br>Geiles Himmelblau, fabelhafte Frau'n <br>alles lauft perfekt <br>Leis verdrangt der Tag das Morgengrau <br>die Sonne scheint voll selbstvertraun <br>die Zeichen stehn auf 30 Grad <br>Laut! Zieht es die Menschen in die Stadt <br>Sie trinken sich am Leben satt <br>und alle feiern diesen Tag! <br>Rasesmildesheis, es ist gut wenn jeder weiß <br>dass die Seele eine Atempause braucht <br>alle machen Hitzefrei und alle sind dabei <br>Nichtstun ist das Motto das uns zeigt: <br>Geiles Himmelblau, alles wie im Traum <br>unser Sonnentisch hier ist gedeckt <br>Geiles Himmelblau, fabelhafte Frau'n <br>alles lauft perfekt <br>Alles lauft perfekt <br>Bald regiert der Mond den Horizont <br>Doch dieser Tag hat sich gelohnt <br>Und ist noch lange nicht vorbei <br>In die Straßen ruft uns der Abendsonnenduft <br>Dass das Herz nen Salto schlagt vor Lebenslust <br>Wenn die Menge Wolka tanzt staut sich die Energie <br>Und der Suden ist so nah wie nie <br>Geiles Himmelblau, alles wie im Traum <br>unser Sonnentisch hier ist gedeckt <br>Geiles Himmelblau, fabelhafte Frau'n <br>Alles lauft perfekt <br>Alles lauft perfekt <br>Geiles Himmelblau, alles wie im Traum <br>unser Sonnentisch hier ist gedeckt <br>Geiles Himmelblau, fabelhafte Frau'n <br>alles lauft perfekt <br>Geiles Himmelblau, in die Sonne schau'n <br>Keine nasse Trane ist versteckt <br>Geiles Himmelblau, alle sollen glaub'n <br>alles lauft perfekt]]></content><category term="Voxxclub" label="Voxxclub"/><category term="Geiles Himmelblau (Live Aus Neu-Ulm / 2016)" label="Geiles Himmelblau (Live Aus Neu-Ulm / 2016)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ASOJUNE/Youth/</id><title>ASOJUNE - Youth - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T07:23:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T07:23:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ASOJUNE/Youth/" title="ASOJUNE - Youth - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매뉴얼은 없어 <br>나의 인생에 <br>돌아서도 결국 <br>혼자 나아가야 해 <br>답답한 현실에 나는 <br>답이 될 수 있을까 <br>멀어진 꿈들은 <br>꽤나 익숙해졌어 <br>아 모든 것이 쉽지 않아 <br>크고 작은 상처들로 <br>어려움은 남아있어 <br>아 매번 잘할 수는 없어 <br>청춘이라 힘든 걸까 <br>별이 사라지는 이 밤 <br>아무래도 나는 <br>이해가 안 돼 <br>서로 다른 것을 <br>틀리다고 하는 게 <br>조금씩은 나도 <br>알 수 있을까 <br>먼저 다가서면 <br>멀어지는 관계를 <br>답답한 현실에 나는 <br>답이 될 수 있을까 <br>나는 너무나도 두려워 <br>아 모든 것이 쉽지 않아 <br>크고 작은 상처들로 <br>어려움은 남아있어 <br>아 매번 잘할 수는 없어 <br>청춘은 왜 힘든 걸까 <br>별이 사라지는 이 밤 <br>있잖아 미래는 어떨까 <br>조금 더 빛날 수 있을까 <br>아 모든 것이 쉽지 않아 <br>크고 작은 상처들로 <br>아 매번 잘할 수는 없어 <br>청춘이라 힘든 걸까 <br>별이 사라져 <br>아 모든 것이 쉽지 않아 <br>크고 작은 상처들로 <br>어려움은 남아있어 <br>아 매번 잘할 수는 없어 <br>청춘은 왜 힘든 걸까 <br>겁이 많은 이 밤 <br>많은 이 밤 <br>]]></content><category term="ASOJUNE" label="ASOJUNE"/><category term="Youth" label="Youth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ASOJUNE/Monday/</id><title>ASOJUNE - Monday - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T07:23:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T07:23:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/ASOJUNE/Monday/" title="ASOJUNE - Monday - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[안녕 선데이 <br>괴로운 밤이야 <br>어서 너를 잡을 <br>방법을 알려줘 <br>키스로는 위로 <br>따윈 되지 않아 <br>그냥 금요일이 <br>내일이면은 안될까 <br>하지만 우린 <br>시간 앞에 평등해 <br>괜찮아 다시 <br>팡파레가 울리면 그때 <br>부스스한 머릴 빗고서 <br>우리 다시 함께 노래해 <br>이봐 너의 <br>시선은 사양할게 <br>반짝이는 너의 모습은 <br>그저 그걸로도 충분해 <br>다시 시작이야 <br>월요일 아침 <br>일어났어 <br>오늘도 지각이야 <br>쉽지 않아 대문 밖을 <br>나서는 순간도 <br>월요일도 잘할 <br>수는 없을까 <br>그냥 금요일이 <br>내일이면은 좋겠다 <br>하지만 우린 <br>시간 앞에 평등해 <br>괜찮아 다시 <br>팡파레가 울리면 그때 <br>부스스한 머릴 빗고서 <br>우리 다시 함께 노래해 <br>이봐 너의 <br>시선은 사양할게 <br>반짝이는 너의 모습은 <br>그저 그걸로도 충분해 <br>다시 시작이야 <br>월요일 아침 <br>부스스한 머릴 빗고서 <br>우리 다시 함께 노래해 <br>이봐 너의 <br>시선은 <br>반짝이는 너의 모습은 <br>그저 그걸로도 충분해 <br>다시 시작이야 <br>월요일 <br>부스스한 머릴 빗고서 <br>우리 다시 함께 노래해 <br>이봐 너의 <br>시선은 사양할게 <br>반짝이는 너의 모습은 <br>그저 그걸로도 충분해 <br>다시 시작이야 <br>월요일 아침 <br>그래도 내일이 <br>금요일이었으면 <br>그래도 내일이 <br>금요일이었으면 <br>]]></content><category term="ASOJUNE" label="ASOJUNE"/><category term="Monday" label="Monday"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이민용/나를_잊지_말아요/</id><title>이민용 - 나를 잊지 말아요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T07:23:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T07:23:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%BC%EC%9A%A9/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9E%8A%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="이민용 - 나를 잊지 말아요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기억하나요 <br>우리가 함께 했었던 <br>그많은 날들의 그댄 <br>참 따뜻했었죠 <br>이젠 차가워진 입술로 <br>나를 울리고 있죠 <br>더이상 날 아프게 <br>하진 말아요 <br>내맘을 적시는 <br>그대의 두 눈을 <br>이제는 더 이상 <br>볼 수는 없겠죠 <br>더는 묻진 않을게요 <br>그댈 아는 나니까 <br>나를 잊진 말아요 그대 <br>외롭진 않나요 <br>우리함께한 날들이 <br>혹시 그대를 <br>힘들게 하지는 않나요 <br>흩어져버린 추억속에 <br>남겨진 그대와나 <br>나를 두고서 <br>떠나지 말아요 <br>내맘을 적시는 <br>그대의 두 눈을 <br>이제는 더이상 <br>볼 수는 없겠죠 <br>더는 묻진 않을게요 <br>그댈 아는 나니까 <br>나를 잊진 말아요 그대 <br>우리 행복했었던 <br>너무 사랑했었던 <br>그땐 소중한걸 <br>내맘을 적시는 <br>그대의 두 눈은 <br>이제는 더이상 <br>볼 수는 없겠죠 <br>더는 묻진 않을게요 <br>그댈 아는 나니까 <br>나를 잊진 말아요 그대 <br>제발 잊지 말아요 그대 <br>]]></content><category term="이민용" label="이민용"/><category term="나를 잊지 말아요" label="나를 잊지 말아요"/></entry></feed>