<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:34:37+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤도현/Sparks_Fly/</id><title>윤도현 - Sparks Fly - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:34:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:34:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EB%8F%84%ED%98%84/Sparks_Fly/" title="윤도현 - Sparks Fly - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어두워진 밤하늘에 별 하나 <br>나를 비추는 너일 거야 <br>유난히도 따스하던 너처럼 <br>더욱 밝게 빛나 안아주듯이 <br>난 아침이 오기 전 <br>이 순간을 기다려 <br>길을 잃은 내 맘에 Sparks fly <br>날 깨워주는 밤 <br>저 수많은 별들 속에서 <br>빛나 너만 <br>Sparks fly <br>I feel sparks fly <br>나지막이 불러보던 노래가 <br>우릴 이어주는 나침반 같아 <br>셀 수 없이 많은 시간 지나도 <br>어디서든 너를 찾을 수 있어 <br>날 감싸는 바람결 <br>널 향해서 떠나봐 <br>길을 잃은 내 맘에 Sparks fly <br>날 깨워주는 밤 <br>저 수많은 별들 속에서 <br>빛나 너만 <br>Sparks fly <br>I feel sparks fly <br>Woo woo woo woo <br>사라지지 않기를 <br>Woo woo woo woo <br>사라지지 않기를 <br>길을 잃은 내 맘에 Sparks fly <br>날 깨워주는 밤 <br>저 수많은 별들 속에서 <br>빛나 너만 Sparks fly <br>길을 잃은 내 맘에 Sparks fly <br>날 깨워주는 밤 <br>저 수많은 별들 속에서 <br>빛나 너만 Sparks fly <br>I feel sparks fly <br>Sparks fly <br>I feel sparks fly <br>Woo woo woo woo woo woo woo <br>woo woo woo woo woo <br>Woo woo woo <br>Woo woo woo woo woo woo woo <br>woo woo woo woo woo <br>Woo woo woo <br>Woo woo woo <br>]]></content><category term="윤도현" label="윤도현"/><category term="Sparks Fly" label="Sparks Fly"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_C/가까워질수록/</id><title>Roy C. - 가까워질수록 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:35:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:35:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_C/%EA%B0%80%EA%B9%8C%EC%9B%8C%EC%A7%88%EC%88%98%EB%A1%9D/" title="Roy C. - 가까워질수록 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[달력이 넘어갈수록 <br>가까워지는 끝 <br>아름다운 이별이었다 <br>자신 있게 말할 수 있길 <br>떠난 자리 아무것도 <br>남지 않게 <br>뜨거웠던 만큼 그리움 <br>아쉬움이 남겠지 <br>그조차 사라질 때까지 <br>태우리 <br>떠난 자리 아무것도 <br>남지 않게 <br>그저 있는 힘 다할 뿐 <br>미소 지을 수 있을 만큼 <br>끝마침 표 찍은 뒤 떠나 <br>보내도 보내도 보내도 보내도 <br>아무리 길어도 결국 <br>닿게 되는 끄트머리 <br>이루어질 수 없는 걸 <br>알면서도 <br>영원하길 바라는 것은 <br>그저 욕심만으론 <br>설명할 수 없는 미련 <br>이상의 감정들 <br>억지로 끌고 간다면 <br>어떻게든 끌고 가겠지 <br>하지만 알아 결국엔 <br>변한다고 <br>언젠가 변해버린 <br>널 본다면 <br>감히 말할 수 있을까 <br>원하던 거였다고 <br>꿈의 바다 잠수하기 <br>직전엔 꽤 많아 보였던 <br>산소통의 개수 다시 <br>세어보니 몇 개 안 남았지 <br>그래 알아 설령 지금 <br>몇 배 남아있어도 <br>언젠가 떠오를 때가 <br>온다는 거 말야 <br>그렇기에 더 많은 것을 <br>최후의 결말을 볼 <br>그때 오기 전 <br>이뤄가는 것뿐 <br>떠난 후 섣부른 타협이라 <br>생각 않기 위해서 <br>지금이 과거가 되어감에 <br>미화되어 진대도 <br>그저 있는 힘 다할 뿐 <br>미소 지을 수 있을 만큼 <br>끝마침 표 찍은 뒤 떠나 <br>보내도 보내도 보내도 보내도 <br>추해지기 전에 박수칠 때 <br>떠나란 말은 사실 <br>타의로 칠해진 그림 <br>지금까지 길을 막아왔지 <br>방해라고 수용할 <br>생각이 없던 전과 달리 <br>그들의 방식으로 그림을 <br>칠하고 있던 건 나 자신 <br>마음만 초심 그대로 <br>그게 현실의 날 그대로 <br>붙잡아 둘 수 없다는 <br>것을 알고 있기에 <br>마지막 잎새 떨어지길 <br>기다리는 모습이 될 순 없네 <br>언젠가 다 떨어질 <br>시계 속의 모래 <br>줄여 결말까지 가는 속도 <br>허나 무작정 늦춰선 <br>그저 산소호흡기를 <br>붙이는 것뿐 <br>그건 안 하니만 못 해 <br>늘인 만큼 굵게 붙이는 살 <br>기적조차 더는 끝을 <br>미루지 못할 때까지 <br>시간을 되돌릴 필요 없을 <br>정도로 다 쏟아 부으면 <br>그 후 겸허히 받아드리리 <br>작별의 운명 <br>다 타고 남은 재까지 모아 <br>불어오는 바람에 실어 보내 <br>아무것도 남지 않게 <br>그저 있는 힘 다할 뿐 <br>미소 지을 수 있을 만큼 <br>끝마침 표 찍은 뒤 떠나 <br>보내도 보내도 보내도 보내도 <br>]]></content><category term="Roy C." label="Roy C."/><category term="가까워질수록" label="가까워질수록"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_C/SOME/</id><title>Roy C. - SOME - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:35:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:35:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_C/SOME/" title="Roy C. - SOME - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[해가 낯 가리는 시간에 봐 <br>풀 가동 에어컨도 휴가 낼 차례 <br>어디서 볼래 그때 그 탐앤탐스 <br>비쌌지 걍 동네 카페 가자 <br>가을 입구서 부는 바람 <br>느낌이 좋아 <br>아직 덥지만 덕분에 <br>네 옷차림이 좋아 <br>힐끗힐끗 하다 마주친 눈 <br>저질이라는 널 보며 그저 싱긋 <br>끓기엔 모자란 99 <br>물 말하는 거 아냐 지금 우리 둘 <br>달달한 느낌은 맞지만 <br>약간 약간 약간 모자라 some <br>아슬아슬해 넌 안 그래 <br>넘을 수 있을 것 같아 난 그래 <br>달달한 느낌은 맞지만 <br>진하기엔 모자란 some <br>맨날 마시던 거 넌 그냥 앉아있어 <br>네가 주문하면 <br>둘 다 항상 치약 맛인걸 <br>하도 먹다 보니 이젠 버릇이 돼서 <br>잘 시키지만 오늘은 못 마시기로 <br>못 마시는 척하는 날 쳐다보면서 <br>우스워 죽겠다는 <br>그 모습 귀여워서 <br>아무리 마셔도 이해 못 하겠다고 <br>새빨간 거짓말 <br>입술 닿은 빨대를 잡어 <br>아깝냐 <br>웃음 참고 정색 넌 멘붕 어떡하지 <br>우물쭈물 대는 게 <br>집사를 잃은 고양이 <br>혹은 혼나기 직전의 강아지 <br>독점하고 싶어 그러려면 <br>우리 관계 아마 지금은 썸 <br>더 더 가까워져야 돼 <br>무슨 말인지 알지 <br>하트 남발하는 <br>일상이 당연한 사이 <br>끓기엔 모자란 99 <br>물 말하는 거 아냐 지금 우리 둘 <br>달달한 느낌은 맞지만 <br>약간 약간 약간 모자라 some <br>아슬아슬해 넌 안 그래 <br>넘을 수 있을 것 같아 난 그래 <br>달달한 느낌은 맞지만 <br>진하기엔 모자란 some <br>바래다주는 길 <br>몇 번씩 부를까 말까 고민해 <br>스쳐 지나가는 <br>손을 잡고 싶어 몇 번씩 <br>썸 썸 썸에서 조금 더 <br>썸 썸 썸에서 조금 더 <br>싫지 않다면 좁혀 볼까 <br>둘 사이 거리 <br>끓기엔 모자란 99 <br>물 말하는 거 아냐 지금 우리 둘 <br>달달한 느낌은 맞지만 <br>약간 약간 약간 모자라 some <br>아슬아슬해 넌 안 그래 <br>넘을 수 있을 것 같아 난 그래 <br>달달한 느낌은 맞지만 <br>진하기엔 모자란 some <br>S O M E <br>이렇다저렇다 말 못하겠고 <br>S O M E <br>너도 싫지 않아 보이는데 뭐 <br>S O M E <br>조금도 금인 듯 귀한 우리 <br>S O M E <br>조급해지는 중 언제까지 우린 <br>]]></content><category term="Roy C." label="Roy C."/><category term="SOME" label="SOME"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_C/주말혼자/</id><title>Roy C. - 주말혼자 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:35:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:35:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_C/%EC%A3%BC%EB%A7%90%ED%98%BC%EC%9E%90/" title="Roy C. - 주말혼자 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[날씨 참 좋은 주말 <br>직전의 불금 <br>이미 들뜬 친구들 <br>소리 없는 흥분 <br>밤이 점점 가까워질수록 <br>선명한 눈빛 <br>돌아오는 월요일 <br>죽기 전의 버킷리스트 <br>한국 사람 특징 <br>넓은 오지랖 <br>괜히 다가와서 너는 <br>주말에 뭐 하시나 <br>걍 쉰다니까 <br>뭐하고 쉬는데 <br>꼭 뭘 해야 한다면 <br>그게 쉬는 건가 싶은데 <br>두시 반쯤 감긴 <br>눈 비비며 <br>주말용 삼선을 <br>발에 걸치고 <br>찐따인듯 혼밥 <br>입에 들이밀어 <br>부른 배 잡고 누우면 <br>뉘엿뉘엿 해 질 녘 <br>Oh sorry mom <br>이번 주도 집 한번 <br>못 가는 못난 <br>아들을 용서해요 <br>위험한 일 <br>하지마라고 해서 <br>이불 밖을 못 <br>나가는 중이에요 <br>금 퇼 순식간에 <br>지나가 버리네 <br>거창하게 뭔가 <br>할 시간이 어디에 <br>몸 편하게 맘 편하게 <br>보내는 주말 워 오 워 오 <br>금 퇼 순식간에 <br>지나가 버리네 <br>거창하게 뭔가 <br>할 시간이 어디에 <br>몸 편하게 맘 편하게 <br>보내는 주말 워 오 워 오 <br>츄리닝 늘어진 반팔티 <br>양손 한가득 팝콘 콤보 <br>영화관 입장 <br>의자 앉자마자 <br>연체동물마냥 늘어져서 <br>광고 시청 <br>빨간 날은 그저 <br>눈치만 신경 쓰지 않아도 <br>피로 풀린다구 <br>금요일 저녁부터 <br>무음이 된 전화기 <br>사실 부재중 전화도 <br>싫어서 꺼놨지 <br>거창한 것 특별한 것 없는 <br>주말이지만서도 그게 좋아 <br>오랜 타지 생활 후 <br>간만에 들른 집 <br>엄마의 집밥처럼 <br>찾을 수 있는 내 <br>마음속의 평화 <br>Oh sorry mom <br>이번 주도 집 한번 <br>못 가는 못난 <br>아들을 용서해요 <br>위험한 일 <br>하지마라고 해서 <br>이불 밖을 못 <br>나가는 중이에요 <br>금 퇼 순식간에 <br>지나가 버리네 <br>거창하게 뭔가 <br>할 시간이 어디에 <br>몸 편하게 맘 편하게 <br>보내는 주말 워 오 워 오 <br>금 퇼 순식간에 <br>지나가 버리네 <br>거창하게 뭔가 <br>할 시간이 어디에 <br>몸 편하게 맘 편하게 <br>보내는 주말 워 오 워 오 <br>]]></content><category term="Roy C." label="Roy C."/><category term="주말혼자" label="주말혼자"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_C/RAP/</id><title>Roy C. - RAP - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:35:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:35:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Roy_C/RAP/" title="Roy C. - RAP - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일상일 뿐인 숨쉬기에 <br>소리 한가지를 더해 <br>소리 섞인 공기는 <br>이제 더는 숨이 <br>아닌 노래 <br>점화의 밤 <br>별과의 만남 <br>아폴로 달의 <br>발자국 남기듯 <br>역사 위 이름 남기는 <br>지금은 아직 이른 <br>동트기 전 아침 <br>새벽 사이 채운 종이만이 <br>지난 밤을 헛되이 <br>보내지 않음의 증거 <br>세상은 증거 <br>불충분이라 말하겠지 <br>흘린 땀 대신 <br>결과만을 보기에 <br>우리네 삶은 <br>매미와 하루살이 <br>부질없다 말하는 것 <br>그걸 위해 전부 <br>걸어버리고 잃어버리고 <br>놓쳐버리며 <br>후회 따윈 없는 삶을 <br>사는가는 가능한 꿈 <br>맞는가를 찾는 <br>매일 답은 <br>없는 물음을 부르면서 <br>박자를 두드리며 춤춰 <br>아직도 먼지 <br>가까운지조차도 <br>알 수 없고 <br>옳은지 그른지 뒤늦게 올 <br>비효율적인 방법으로 <br>삶을 토해 <br>삼킨 시간에 나를 더 해 <br>달뜬 어깨 <br>경배하는 예술 건배 <br>아침이 올 때까지 시를 써 <br>버린 종이들 위 구긴 흔적 <br>All night 동이 트면 <br>그제사 감는 두 눈이 증거 <br>악무는 이와 움직이는 혀 <br>음악 사이에 목소리를 섞어 <br>만들어 귀들로 <br>이야기를 싣는 것 <br>아침이 올 때까지 시를 써 <br>버린 종이들 위 구긴 흔적 <br>All night 동이 트면 <br>그제사 감는 두 눈이 증거 <br>악무는 이와 움직이는 혀 <br>음악 사이에 목소리를 섞어 <br>만들어 귀들로 <br>이야기를 싣는 것 <br>쌍기역 우 미음 <br>꿈 그건 단지 <br>쌍기역 우 니은 <br>꾼다고 다 닿지 않아 <br>단어를 쌓아 <br>하늘에 닿기 위해 <br>만들고 있는 <br>시의 바벨탑 <br>같은 언어건 다른 언어건 <br>같은 길을 가는 이는 많아 <br>책상에 앉아 영감이 <br>번뜩일 때까지 <br>무언가를 만들기 위해 <br>머리만 굴려 가는 쳇바퀴 <br>무에서 유 우에서 주 <br>담고 다듬어 선물해 <br>검은 형상 <br>역사 위에 순간을 <br>박제해 입혀 불변을 <br>아무리 거세게 타올라도 <br>영원할 수 없다는 걸 알어 <br>그렇기에 모든 걸 쏟아 <br>더 몇만 배의 <br>시간이 대가더라도 <br>여전히 난 목소리 <br>안 빛나는 문장을 <br>품고 싶은 아이 <br>더 높이 가고 파 <br>이름 적힌 <br>자서전이 끝날 때까지 <br>Ey hold up man check it out <br>I have a something <br>to say right now <br>Imma let you finish <br>My name is Roy C. <br>and I'm back <br>with this man right here <br>Shout out to Sniper Sound <br>TDM crew <br>and my mu-fuckin' <br>Home Sweet Home <br>Just hope you brace for us <br>Let's show you <br>how we do it <br>Just watch <br>광부의 곡괭이 대신 <br>펜이 내 손에 <br>화가의 붓 대신 <br>역시 펜이 내 손에 <br>채굴하고 표현해 <br>다이아몬드 and Parallel world <br>영원히 눈 감을 때 까지 계속 <br>눈 감을 때 까지 계속 <br>눈 감을 때 까지 계속 <br>눈 감을 때 까지 계속 <br>영원히 눈 감을 때까지 계속 <br>]]></content><category term="Roy C." label="Roy C."/><category term="RAP" label="RAP"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이보람_씨야/엎질러진_물처럼/</id><title>이보람 (씨야) - 엎질러진 물처럼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:35:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:35:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B3%B4%EB%9E%8C_%EC%94%A8%EC%95%BC/%EC%97%8E%EC%A7%88%EB%9F%AC%EC%A7%84_%EB%AC%BC%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC/" title="이보람 (씨야) - 엎질러진 물처럼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[엎질러진 물 <br><br>처럼가슴에 니가 들어온다 <br>슬픈 내 사랑은 이렇게 시작된다 <br>내 눈물을 보이지 않으려 해도 <br>나 돌아서 울먹이는건 말야 <br>널 보면 아파 가슴안에 상처 같아 <br>내 맘이 아파 니가 밀어낼때마다 <br>이미 엎질러진 물처럼 <br>내 사랑은 또 주워 담을수 없어 <br>오 니가 곁에 있어도 난 아파 <br>나를 바라보지 않아 <br>사랑해줘 나를 <br>니 앞에 있는 한여잘 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>천천히 와 <br>오늘밤 니가 찾아온다 <br>슬픈 내 사랑은 이렇게 시작된다 <br>내 눈물을 보이지 않으려 해도 <br>나 돌아서 울먹이는건 말야 <br>널 보면 아파 가슴안에 상처 같아 <br>내 맘이 아파 니가 밀어낼때마다 <br>이미 엎질러진 물처럼 <br>내 사랑은 또 주워 담을수 없어 <br>오 니가 곁에 있어도 난 아파 <br>나를 바라보지 않아 <br>사랑해줘 나를 <br>니 앞에 있는 한여잘 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>나의 마음 그대로 여기 있으니 <br>너만 나에게 와주면 돼 <br>너 때문에 아파 <br>너를 사랑한게 죄야 <br>그래도 차마 너를 잊기에 난 아파 <br>괜찮아 괜찮아 괜찮아 <br>천천히 와 <br>]]></content><category term="이보람 (씨야)" label="이보람 (씨야)"/><category term="엎질러진 물처럼" label="엎질러진 물처럼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/앤츠_Ants/긍정백수/</id><title>앤츠 (Ants) - 긍정백수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:39:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:39:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%A4%EC%B8%A0_Ants/%EA%B8%8D%EC%A0%95%EB%B0%B1%EC%88%98/" title="앤츠 (Ants) - 긍정백수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈을 뜬 건 12신데 <br>30분 째 침대 속에 <br>귀찮아서 아침밥은 <br>안 먹기로 해 <br>휴대폰 속 번호는 많고 <br>연락할 사람은 없고 <br>내 인생만 되돌아봤지 <br>나만 빼고 다 잘 사는 것 같애 <br>나만 빼고 다 즐거운 것 같애 <br>뭔가 기분은 좀 그렇지만 괜찮아 <br>나도 잘 될 거야 <br>될 거야 잘 될 거야 <br>나도 남들처럼 <br>살 거야 잘 살 거야 <br>나도 잘 될 거야 <br>될 거야 잘 될 거야 <br>엄마 보채지 마 <br>나 지금 인생 계획하는 거야 <br>나만 빼고 다 행복한 것 같애 <br>나만 빼고 다 살만한 것 같애 <br>왠지 기분은 씁쓸하지만 괜찮아 <br>나도 잘 될 거야 <br>될 거야 잘 될 거야 <br>나도 남들처럼 <br>살 거야 잘 살 거야 <br>나도 잘 될 거야 <br>될 거야 잘 될 거야 <br>엄마 기다려봐 <br>나도 다 생각하고 있는 거야 <br>찬란은 아니더라도 <br>평범은 당연한 건 줄 알았지 <br>떠밀려 된 어른에 <br>또 밀려드는 걱정까지 <br>그래도 괜찮아 난 <br>나도 잘 될 거야 <br>될 거야 잘 될 거야 <br>나도 남들처럼 <br>살 거야 잘 살 거야 <br>나도 잘 될 거야 <br>될 거야 잘 될 거야 <br>나도 잘 될 거야 <br>될 거야 잘 될 거야 <br>나도 남들처럼 <br>살 거야 잘 살 거야 <br>나도 잘 될 거야 <br>될 거야 잘 될 거야 <br>엄마 보채지 마 <br>나 지금 인생 계획하는 거야 <br>나도 잘 살 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="앤츠 (Ants)" label="앤츠 (Ants)"/><category term="긍정백수" label="긍정백수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/앤츠_Ants/딱_10분만/</id><title>앤츠 (Ants) - 딱 10분만 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:39:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:39:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%A4%EC%B8%A0_Ants/%EB%94%B1_10%EB%B6%84%EB%A7%8C/" title="앤츠 (Ants) - 딱 10분만 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나란히 함께 걷고 있는 밤 <br>무슨 일 있냐 물어보는 너 <br>사실 오늘 좀 힘들었어 <br>별건 아니고 <br>손잡는 것도 좋은데 나는 <br>지금만큼은 그것보다는 <br>너에게 위로 받고 싶어 baby <br>잠깐만 내 옆에 앉아 있어줘 <br>딱 10분만 네 어깨 빌려줘 <br>아님 5분만 나를 꼭 안아줘 <br>그냥 아무 말 하지 말고 <br>날 포근히 감싸줘 <br>딱 10분만 네 어깨 빌려줘 <br>아님 5분만 나를 <br>꼭 끌어안아줘 <br>에너지 드링크 <br>다 필요 없어 네 품이면 돼 <br>난 너면 돼 <br>어둠이 짙은 고요한 거리 <br>걱정스레 날 바라보는 너 <br>좀 센치한 날인 것 같애 <br>별건 아니고 <br>다정한 말도 좋은데 나는 <br>오늘만큼은 그것보다는 <br>너에게 위로 받고 싶어 baby <br>잠깐만 내 옆에 앉아 있어줘 <br>딱 10분만 네 어깨 빌려줘 <br>아님 5분만 나를 꼭 안아줘 <br>그냥 아무 말 하지 말고 <br>날 포근히 감싸줘 <br>딱 10분만 네 어깨 빌려줘 <br>아님 5분만 나를 꼭 끌어안아줘 <br>에너지 드링크 <br>다 필요 없어 네 품이면 돼 <br>깜깜한 내 밤에 <br>넌 마법처럼 별을 그려줘 <br>내 맘을 녹여줘 <br>좀 더 다가와 줄래 <br>딱 10분만 네 어깨 빌려줘 <br>아님 5분만 5분만 안아줘 <br>아무 말 하지 말고 <br>날 포근히 감싸줘 <br>딱 10분만 네 어깨 빌려줘 <br>아님 5분만 나를 꼭 끌어안아줘 <br>에너지 드링크 <br>다 필요 없어 네 품이면 돼 <br>난 너면 돼 <br>oh 난 너면 돼 <br>oh 난 너면 돼 <br>]]></content><category term="앤츠 (Ants)" label="앤츠 (Ants)"/><category term="딱 10분만" label="딱 10분만"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/밀라노/좋은_말할_때_와/</id><title>밀라노 - 좋은 말할 때 와 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:39:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:39:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%80%EB%9D%BC%EB%85%B8/%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80_%EB%A7%90%ED%95%A0_%EB%95%8C_%EC%99%80/" title="밀라노 - 좋은 말할 때 와 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한입에 딱 들어가게 생긴 너의 <br>그 입술이 내겐 젤리 같은걸 <br>사과향기 오렌지 맛 청포도 색도 <br>맛있는 말랑말랑한 젤리 말이야 <br>그건 가끔은 내게 위험해 <br>아작하고 씹고 싶은 그런 충동 <br>매일 몇 번씩 참는지 몰라 <br>가끔씩 나에게 느껴지는 무서움 <br>그것 때문인지는 몰라도 <br>넌 내가 얼마나 너를 사랑하는지 <br>모를 거야 알면 알수록 더욱 <br>무서울 테니까 그래서 니가 나를 <br>못 잊는 거야 그러니까 돌아와줘 <br>기다리는 중이니까 <br>오래 기다리는 건 질색해 알잖아 <br>내 성격 급한 거 <br>you know that <br>하루면 많이 기다린 거야 괜찮아 <br>이해해 무섭게 안 그럴게 <br>그러니까 좋은 말 할 때 와 <br>넌 내가 얼마나 너를 사랑하는지 <br>모를 거야 알면 알수록 더욱 <br>무서울 테니까 그래서 니가 나를 <br>못 잊는 거야 그러니까 돌아와줘 <br>기다리는 중이니까 <br>]]></content><category term="밀라노" label="밀라노"/><category term="좋은 말할 때 와" label="좋은 말할 때 와"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alma/Requiem/</id><title>Alma - Requiem - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:43:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:43:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alma/Requiem/" title="Alma - Requiem - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love dies, love is born <br>Centuries pass and disappear <br>What you believe to be death <br>It's a season and nothing more <br><br>One day tired of this wandering <br>You will go away, whatever <br>Because the world will still turn <br>Even when we won't turn anymore <br><br>Kiss me, tell me that you love me <br>Make me smile in the middle of a requiem <br>Kiss me, tell me that you love me <br>Make me dance until time takes back from us <br><br>What it gave to us <br>A year, two years, a hundred years of happiness <br>Then life picks you like a flower <br>Make me laugh I need it <br>While waiting for the time <br><br>A year, two years, a hundred years together <br>And then one day we're all alone <br>We cry but we still survive <br>It's the beauty of a requiem <br><br>The sparks become flames <br>The little girls become women <br>What you believe to be death <br>It's an inferno and nothing more <br><br>Our rips, our declines <br>They're thought to be important <br>But tomorrow the day will be reborn <br>Like if we have not lived <br><br>Kiss me, tell me that you love me <br>Make me smile in the middle of a requiem <br>Kiss me, tell me that you love me <br>Make me dance until time takes back from us <br><br>What it gave to us <br>A year, two years, a hundred years of happiness <br>Then life picks you like a flower <br>Make me laugh I need it <br>While waiting for the time <br><br>A year, two years, a hundred years together <br>And then one day we're all alone <br>We cry but we still survive <br>It's the beauty of a requiem <br><br>Love is born, love dies <br>Tonight I'm finally not afraid <br>I know that I will love you again <br>When the world doesn't turn anymore <br><br>Love is born, love dies <br>Tonight I'm finally not afraid <br>I know that I will still love you <br>When the world won't turn anymore <br><br>Kiss me, tell me that you love me <br>Make me smile in the middle of a requiem <br>Kiss me, tell me that you love me <br>Make me dance until time takes back from us <br><br>What it gave to us <br>What it gave to us <br>What it gave to us <br>What it gave to us <br>What it gave to us]]></content><category term="Alma" label="Alma"/><category term="Requiem" label="Requiem"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/안갑성/연_緣_안갑성_Ver/</id><title>안갑성 - 연 (緣) (안갑성 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:43:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:43:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%88%EA%B0%91%EC%84%B1/%EC%97%B0_%E7%B7%A3_%EC%95%88%EA%B0%91%EC%84%B1_Ver/" title="안갑성 - 연 (緣) (안갑성 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시리게 푸르른 <br>그대 고운 날개 <br>내 맘 가까이 <br>날아오지 않네 <br>이슬된 서러움에 실어 <br>나를 데려가주오 <br>닿을 듯한 <br>그대의 품으로 <br>여리게 남은 듯 <br>그대 고운 향기 <br>내 맘 가까이 <br>돌아오지 않네 <br>그대의 내가 멀지 않아 <br>나를 사랑해주오 <br>기억 속의 나라면 <br>아 영원한 그리움 <br>나 차가운 눈물에 지워도 <br>기다리네 기나긴 내 사랑 <br>미련을 버리고 <br>편히 잠들라 <br>그 무엇도 남지 않을 듯 <br>꼭 나를 기억해주오 <br>숨결까지 <br>눈물까지 <br>내 모든 것 그대에게로 <br>]]></content><category term="안갑성" label="안갑성"/><category term="연 (緣) (안갑성 Ver.)" label="연 (緣) (안갑성 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Topic/Break_My_Habits/</id><title>Topic - Break My Habits - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:44:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:44:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Topic/Break_My_Habits/" title="Topic - Break My Habits - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is not like me, I don't get that deep <br>I'm usually puttin' all my walls up in between <br>I cannot fight this 'cause you make me weak <br>My heart is pumpin' like it's following the beat <br><br>You have got me feelin' like I'm trippin' <br>Seen a lot of shit, but you're the real thing <br>Nothing like a lovin' that I've witnessed <br>When you're with me <br><br>So just feel my touch and let it <br>Make you feel alright <br>And I might just break my habits <br>And stay with you tonight <br>I'll break my habits <br>I'll break my habits <br>And stay with you tonight <br><br>I'll break my habits <br><br>Always thought I've been fine on my own <br>Now I'm relying on your love to get it on <br><br>You have got me feelin' like I'm trippin' <br>Seen a lot of shit, but you're the real thing <br>Nothing like a lovin' that I've witnessed <br>When you're with me <br><br>So just feel my touch and let it <br>Make you feel alright <br>And I might just break my habits <br>And stay with you tonight <br><br>I'll break my habits <br>I'll break my habits <br>I'll break my habits <br><br>All that I need is a quick fix from you, baby <br>Don't wanna leave 'cause I give something new so I'll <br><br>I'll break my habits <br>I'll break my habits]]></content><category term="Topic" label="Topic"/><category term="Break My Habits" label="Break My Habits"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wednesday_Campanella/一休さん___Ikkyuusan_잇큐우상/</id><title>Wednesday Campanella - 一休さん / Ikkyuusan (잇큐우상) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:45:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:45:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Wednesday_Campanella/%E4%B8%80%E4%BC%91%E3%81%95%E3%82%93___Ikkyuusan_%EC%9E%87%ED%81%90%EC%9A%B0%EC%83%81/" title="Wednesday Campanella - 一休さん / Ikkyuusan (잇큐우상) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소우사 아이츠가 잇큐 <br>이츠데모 민나오 와라와세루 <br>소우사 아이츠가 잇큐 <br>톤치오 키카세테 오쿠레 <br>잇큐상 아리가토 상큐 <br>잇큐상 오츠카레상 <br>잇큐상 아리가토 상큐 <br>잇큐상 <br>야츠니 죠우시키나도 츠지나이 <br>스데니 돈치노 센스가 케타치가이 <br>이츠모 핫토 굿토시테 <br>킷-캇토 쿠이 <br>오테라노 벳도데 have a 잇큐 <br>「코노 바시와타루 베카라즈」 토카 <br>타테 후다요마즈니 츄-오톳파시테 <br>왕간쇼노 호우모 오테아게요우데 <br>레인보-브릿지 후우사데키마셍 <br>톤치 키카시테 톤치 키카시테 <br>톤치키사와기사 <br>톤치 키카시테 톤치 키카시테 <br>톤치 키카시테 Cool <br>하나시노 나가레와 다이타이 와캇타 <br>히토마즈 오치츠이테코우 <br>헤타나 캉가에와 야스무니 니타리사 <br>키미와 홋시테루 have a 잇큐 <br>소우사 아이츠가 잇큐 <br>이츠데모 민나오 와라와세루 <br>소우사 아이츠가 잇큐 <br>톤치오 키카세테 오쿠레 <br>잇큐상 아리가토 상큐 <br>잇큐상 오츠카레상 <br>잇큐상 아리가토 상큐 <br>잇큐상 히토야스미시테 이코우 <br>야츠니 죠우시키나도 츠지나이 <br>스데니 톤치노 센스가 케타치가이 <br>이츠모 핫토 굿토시테 <br>킷캇토 쿠이 <br>오테라노 벳토데 have a 잇큐 <br>뵤부노 토라 오쿄-데 쇼우칸 <br>오토노사마타치와 아비쿄우칸 <br>아이츠가 소노 우치 오토나니 낫타라 <br>팡쿠나 하카이소우니 나리소우 <br>톤치 키카시테 톤치 키카시테 <br>톤치키사와기사 <br>톤치 키카시테 톤치 키카시테 <br>톤치 키카시테 Cool <br>모쿠교 키자무 쥬로쿠 비-토니 <br>코조-상타치모 YMCA <br>혼키오 다스노와 아시타카라사 <br>키미와 홋시테루 have a 잇큐 <br>소우사 아이츠가 잇큐 <br>이츠데모 민나오 와라와세루 <br>소우사 아이츠가 잇큐 <br>톤치오 키카세테 오쿠레 <br>토라토라토라 토라토라토라 <br>토라타이지니 <br>테라테라테라 테라테라테라 <br>테라카라 키타 <br>잇큐상 아리가토 상큐 <br>잇큐상 오츠카레상 <br>잇큐상 아리가토 상큐 <br>잇큐상 히토야스미시테 이코우 <br>잇큐상 아리가토 상큐- <br>잇큐상 오츠카레상 <br>잇큐상 아리가토 상큐-]]></content><category term="Wednesday Campanella" label="Wednesday Campanella"/><category term="一休さん / Ikkyuusan (잇큐우상)" label="一休さん / Ikkyuusan (잇큐우상)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/We_Are/</id><title>Daya - We Are - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:45:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:45:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/We_Are/" title="Daya - We Are - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stay out late night, running red lights <br>That's the air we like to breathe <br>Breaking your ties, crossing your lines <br>Leaping over boundaries <br>There's never been a mold that you could fit us in <br>Doing what we're born to do is not a sin <br><br>'Cause we are gonna be, we are gonna be who we are <br>We don't really care, we don't really care what you want <br>Never put a we, never put a we in the box <br>Gotta let it go 'cause I'm telling you we won't stop <br><br>Because we are, we are, we are, we are <br>We are the young, we are the world <br>You know who we are <br>We are, we are, we are, we are <br>We are the young, we are the world <br>You know who we are <br>We might be reckless, but we're gonna do just what we do 'cause we are, we are, we are, we are <br>We are the young, we are the world <br>You know who we are <br><br>You know who we are <br>You know who we are <br><br>Make our own rules, sticking like fools <br>Ready to call the police <br>We can skip school 'cause we're too cool <br>To be told we can't be free <br>You can go ahead and try to knock us out <br>Ain't no keeping us from doing what we love <br>'Cause we love it too much <br><br>We are gonna be, we are gonna be who we are <br>Gotta let it go 'cause I'm telling you we won't stop, won't stop <br><br>Because we are, we are, we are, we are <br>We are the young, we are the world <br>You know who we are <br>We are, we are, we are, we are <br>We are the young, we are the world <br>You know who we are <br>We might be reckless, but we're gonna do just what we do 'cause we are, we are, we are, we are <br>We are the young, we are the world <br>You know who we are <br><br>You know who we are <br>You know who we are <br><br>We don't hear what you're saying <br>Being us is okay and <br>We don't hear what you're saying <br>Being us is okay and <br><br>We might be reckless, but we're gonna do just what we do 'cause we are, we are, we are, we are <br>We are the young, we are the world <br>You know who we are <br><br>You know who we are <br>You know who we are <br>You know who we are <br>You know who we are <br>We are, you know who we are <br>]]></content><category term="Daya" label="Daya"/><category term="We Are" label="We Are"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Got_The_Feeling/</id><title>Daya - Got The Feeling - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:45:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:45:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Got_The_Feeling/" title="Daya - Got The Feeling - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stuck between the wrong and the right thing <br>Can't make up my mind, it's got a mind of its own <br>Felt a spark, but there was no lightning <br>Could've walked away, but still I'm coming back for more <br><br>Oh, I'm loving your butterfly kisses <br>But it's like something is missing <br>Gonna save quitting your for another day <br><br>I got the feeling that it's not gonna work out <br>I got the feeling that you're not my type <br>Maybe the reason all this shit keeps on happening <br>Happening 'cause I like the feeling <br>No, it's not for life, but it's alright right now <br>Right now, I got the feeling right now <br>It's alright right now <br><br>Stuck between the green and the red light <br>Can't make up my mind, should I stop or should I go? <br>Find it hard to leave after midnight <br>Using the excuse that it's too late to walk me home <br><br>Oh, I'm loving your summertime kisses <br>But it's like something is missing <br>Gonna save quitting your for another day <br><br>I got the feeling that it's not gonna work out <br>I got the feeling that you're not my type <br>Maybe the reason all this shit keeps on happening <br>Happening 'cause I like the feeling <br>No, it's not for life, but it's alright right now <br>Right now, I got the feeling it's alright right now <br>It's alright right now <br><br>I got the feeling, got the feeling <br>I got the feeling, got the feeling <br>I got the feeling, got the feeling, whoa oh <br>Oh, I'm loving your butterfly kisses <br>But it's like something is missing <br>Gonna save quitting your for another day <br><br>I got the feeling that it's not gonna work out <br>I got the feeling that you're not my type <br>Maybe the reason all this shit keeps on happening <br>Happening 'cause I like the feeling <br>No, it's not for life, but it's alright right now <br>Right now, I got the feeling right now <br>Maybe the reason all this shit keeps on happening <br>Happening 'cause I like the feeling <br>No, it's not for life, but it's alright right now]]></content><category term="Daya" label="Daya"/><category term="Got The Feeling" label="Got The Feeling"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Words/</id><title>Daya - Words - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:45:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:45:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Words/" title="Daya - Words - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sorry boy even I'm that loud <br>Doesn't mean I'm out <br>but a word could ruin it <br>Sorry boy gotta slow it down <br>Better shut your mouth <br>do the talking with your lips <br>I'm right on the edge <br>And I know how to swim <br>but I'm not jumping in <br>Not scared to get wet <br>But if we dip our feet <br>I know we'll go too deep <br>Don't want a good heart to break <br>When we're touching <br>those three little words feel <br>too easy to say <br>But but I'm not ready <br>We don't have to say love <br>'cause the words only get in the way <br>In the way oh way oh way oh <br>In the way oh way oh way oh <br>In the way in the way <br>oh way oh way oh <br>We don't have to say love <br>'cause the words only get in the way <br>The words only get in the way <br>The words only get in the way <br>Like you lots I just had a thought <br>We could make it fun <br>doesn't have to have a name <br>Everyone puts the pressure on <br>But we're not everyone <br>so we don't have to do the same <br>I'm right on the edge <br>And I know how to swim <br>but I'm not jumping in <br>Not scared to get wet <br>But if we dip our feet <br>I know we'll go too deep <br>Don't want a good heart to break <br>When we're touching <br>those three little words feel <br>too easy to say <br>But but I'm not ready <br>We don't have to say love <br>'cause the words only get in the way <br>In the way oh way oh way oh <br>In the way oh way oh way oh <br>In the way in the way <br>oh way oh way oh <br>We don't have to say love <br>'cause the words only get in the way <br>The words only get in the way <br>The words only get in the way <br>Don't want a good heart to break <br>Oh no <br>When we're touching <br>those three little words <br>feel too easy to say <br>But but I'm not ready <br>We don't have to say love <br>'cause the words only get in the way <br>In the way oh way oh way oh <br>In the way <br>In the way oh way oh way oh <br>Only get in the way <br>In the way in the way <br>oh way oh way oh <br>Only get in the way <br>We don't have to say love <br>'cause the words only get in the way <br>The words only get in the way <br>Get in the way <br>The words only get in the way <br>]]></content><category term="Daya" label="Daya"/><category term="Words" label="Words"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Talk/</id><title>Daya - Talk - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:45:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:45:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Talk/" title="Daya - Talk - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm not that plain and simple, I'm in another lane <br>I'm like a Shirley Temple, the cherry on the cake <br>Just a throwback kid from the nineties <br>I start my ABCs with the YZ <br>I paint with different colors and never in the lines <br>There isn't any other, I am the prototype <br>Tick tock, waste time with your rumors <br>But I'm so ice cold, good humor <br><br>They say I'm outta my mind <br>Standing on the outside <br>It's cooler, it's fresher <br>I like it here <br><br>They all gonna say what they wanna say anyway <br>Might as well give 'em something <br>Might as well give 'em something to talk about <br>I don't really care if they wanna stare, look at me <br>Might as well give 'em something <br>Might as well give 'em something to talk about <br><br>(Give 'em something, a little something, ah, a little) <br>Something to talk about <br>(Give 'em something, a little something, ah, a little) <br>Something to talk about <br><br>I don't believe in Yeezus, I like 'em Kanye West <br>I'm rocking dirty sneakers with my designer dress <br>Would do a grade A steak with my pomme frite <br>I wake you up, Starbucks, sleep on me <br><br>They say I'm outta my mind <br>Standing on the outside <br>It's cooler, it's fresher <br>I like it here <br><br>They all gonna say what they wanna say anyway <br>Might as well give 'em something <br>Might as well give 'em something to talk about <br>I don't really care if they wanna stare, look at me <br>Might as well give 'em something <br>Might as well give 'em something to talk about <br><br>(Give 'em something, a little something, ah, a little) <br>Something to talk about <br>(Give 'em something, a little something, ah, a little) <br>Something to talk about <br><br>No, you don't know what <br>What you talking 'bout <br>No, you don't know me <br>So just shut your mouth <br>No, you don't know what <br>What you talking 'bout <br>No, you don't know me <br>So just shut your... <br><br>They all gonna say what they wanna say anyway <br>Might as well give 'em something <br>Might as well give 'em something to talk about <br>I don't really care if they wanna stare, look at me <br>Might as well give 'em something <br>Might as well give 'em something to talk about <br><br>(Give 'em something, a little something, ah, a little) <br>Something to talk about <br>(Give 'em something, a little something, ah, a little) <br>Something to talk about]]></content><category term="Daya" label="Daya"/><category term="Talk" label="Talk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Cool/</id><title>Daya - Cool - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:46:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:46:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Cool/" title="Daya - Cool - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I still feel your kisses in the morning <br>Even though you're not around <br>Maybe I should take it as a warning <br>That my secret's finally... out <br><br>And you know that I know that you know just how I feel <br>And I know that you know that I know this thing's for real <br>We lay low but it never feels boring <br>Cause my heart is racing for you <br><br>Let's just sit back and cruise, cruise, cruise <br>That's all I wanna do, do, do <br>I know you want it too, too, too <br>It's perfect, 'cause there's never any pressure, baby <br>You know how to keep it cool <br><br>Funny how you get me so excited <br>When we're doin' nothing at all <br>Simple as a movie at the drive-in <br>Or a good long distance... call <br><br>But you know that I know that you know just how I feel <br>And I know that you know that I know this thing's for real <br>Let's speed off right into the horizon <br>Or just close our eyes and fall <br><br>Let's just sit back and cruise, cruise, cruise <br>That's all I wanna do, do, do <br>I know you want it too, too, too <br>It's perfect, 'cause there's never any pressure, baby <br>You know how to keep it cool <br><br>(Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na) Keep it cool <br>(Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na) Me and you <br>(Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na) Keep it cool <br>(Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na) Me and you <br><br>Let's just sit back and cruise, cruise, cruise <br>That's all I wanna do, do, do <br>I know you want it too, too, too <br>It's perfect, 'cause there's never any pressure, baby <br>You know how to keep it cool <br><br>(Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na) Keep it cool <br>(Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na) Me and you <br>(Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na) Keep it cool <br>(Na-na-na-na-na-na-na-na) Me and you]]></content><category term="Daya" label="Daya"/><category term="Cool" label="Cool"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Love_Of_My_Life/</id><title>Daya - Love Of My Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:46:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:46:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Love_Of_My_Life/" title="Daya - Love Of My Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You got the touch, you got the magic <br>Making me blush, you keep me coming back for more <br>Gave you too much, I'll let you have it <br>It's gonna suck, this is a thing I can't ignore <br><br>You won't mistake me <br>But you never take me all the way <br>All the way (no, no, no) <br>And now I'd hate to break your heart <br>But I don't wanna waste <br>Anymore time on you <br><br>I could like you 'til the day that I die <br>But I'm looking for the love of my life <br>I could like you 'til the day that I die <br>But I'm looking for the love of my life <br><br>Baby don't beg or buy me flowers <br>You cannot stay cause it would only make it worse <br>You want a chick that's on your lips for hours <br>So I walk away, but I don't wanna see you hurt <br><br>You understood me <br>But you never took me all the way <br>All the way (no, no, no) <br>And now I'd hate to break your heart <br>But I don't wanna waste <br>Anymore time on you <br><br>I could like you 'til the day that I die <br>But I'm looking for the love of my life <br>I could like you 'til the day that I die <br>But I'm looking for the love of my life <br><br>I really like you, but you're not that right for me <br>I rather wait all my life to find the one <br>I really like you, but it's just not meant to be <br>Oh, I'm so sorry, I am, oh yeah <br><br>I could like you 'til the day that I die <br>But I'm looking for the love of my life <br>I could like you 'til the day that I die <br>But I'm looking for the love of my life <br>]]></content><category term="Daya" label="Daya"/><category term="Love Of My Life" label="Love Of My Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/ICYMI/</id><title>Daya - I.C.Y.M.I. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:46:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:46:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/ICYMI/" title="Daya - I.C.Y.M.I. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why you? Why you gotta be so uncool? <br>I told you, I didn't want us to continue <br><br>But it's like it went in your ear <br>And came out on the other side <br>I guess you didn't wanna hear <br>But now it's time for you to get it right <br><br>In case you missed it or just don't get it <br>I'm all the way over you, over you <br>In case you missed it, you need to let it go <br>And find, baby, find something better to do <br>Then calling all night, 'cause I won't call back <br>No I don't like, you know I don't like that <br>In case you missed it, let me repeat it <br>I'm all the way over you, over you <br><br>Easy, I tried to make it easy <br>To leave me, but I guess you don't believe me <br><br>Running, telling all your friends <br>We're going on another date <br>Something's missing in your head <br>And now it's time for you to get it straight <br><br>In case you missed it or just don't get it <br>I'm all the way over you, over you <br>In case you missed it, you need to let it go <br>And find, baby, find something better to do <br>Then calling all night, 'cause I won't call back <br>No I don't like, you know I don't like that <br>In case you missed it, let me repeat it <br>I'm all the way over you, over you <br><br>I don't wanna kiss, I don't wanna talk <br>Boy in case you missed it, I don't miss you at all <br>So don't send me a text, don't give me a call <br>Boy in case you missed it, I don't miss you at all <br>I don't wanna kiss, I don't wanna talk <br>Boy in case you missed it, I don't miss you at all <br>So don't send me a text, don't give me a call <br>Boy in case you missed it, I don't miss you at all <br><br>In case you missed it or just don't get it <br>I'm all the way over you, over you <br>In case you missed it, you need to let it go <br>And find, baby, find something better to do <br>Then calling all night, 'cause I won't call back <br>No I don't like, you know I don't like that <br>In case you missed it, let me repeat it <br>I'm all the way over you, over you <br><br>Just in case, you missed it <br>I'm all the way over you, over you <br>Just in case, you missed it <br>I'm all the way over you, over you, over you <br>I'm all the way over you, over you, over you <br>]]></content><category term="Daya" label="Daya"/><category term="I.C.Y.M.I." label="I.C.Y.M.I."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Dare/</id><title>Daya - Dare - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:46:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:46:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daya/Dare/" title="Daya - Dare - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dare me to reach a little higher <br>You can dare me to step <br>over the edge <br>I dare you to dare me <br>to go play with fire <br>I'm gonna do everything <br>that you never did <br>I'll leave my footprints <br>on the water <br>Bet on the dark horse until <br>I'm a millionaire <br>And you can all sit back <br>and say that I'm a loser <br>But I don't worry <br>'cause the truth is in the dare <br>So go on dare me to lose <br>dare me to move <br>Dare me to run <br>And you can dare me <br>to prove something to you <br>Is that what you want <br>I dare you to <br>I dare you to <br>I dare you to <br>I dare I dare I dare <br>I dare you to <br>There was a time I was afraid of <br>The dark and monsters <br>livin' underneath my bed <br>And then I said <br>Enough is enough <br>simply because <br>The only monsters were <br>the voices in my head <br>So go on dare me to lose <br>dare me to move <br>Dare me to run <br>And you can dare me <br>to prove something to you <br>Is that what you want <br>I dare you to <br>I dare you to <br>I dare you to <br>I dare I dare I dare I dare you to <br>Do it all do it all do it al <br>l 'cause I wanna <br>Do it all do it all do it all <br>'cause I'm gonna do everything <br>Do it all do it all do it all <br>'cause I wanna <br>Do it all do it all do it all <br>'cause I'm gonna do everything <br>So go on dare me to lose <br>dare me to move <br>Dare me to run <br>And you can dare me <br>to prove something to you <br>Is that what you want <br>I dare you to <br>I dare I dare I dare I dare you to <br>I dare you to <br>I dare you I I dare you <br>I dare you <br>I dare I dare I dare I dare you <br>I dare you <br>I dare you <br>I dare I dare I dare I dare you to <br>]]></content><category term="Daya" label="Daya"/><category term="Dare" label="Dare"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Run_The_Jewels/Call_Ticketron/</id><title>Run The Jewels - Call Ticketron - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:47:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:47:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Run_The_Jewels/Call_Ticketron/" title="Run The Jewels - Call Ticketron - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Live, Li-li-li-li- <br>Live from the Garden <br><br>Run The Jewels live at the Garden <br>Lickin' off shots and we aim for the darkness <br>Make it get hot for a target <br>Kids cook s'mores off the crotch of our targets <br>Kumbaya bitch <br>Bucker up lil' trooper <br>You can't get past me, I'm stuck in the future <br>The shit ain't all it's cracked up to be <br>The hover craft's cool but the air's so putrid <br><br>You can tell by the stench in the air <br>Blood's on the ground, opportunity is here <br>I'm lookin' into space like, "Is anybody there <br>And if aliens are here, please tell me how near <br>Do you come in peace or should everybody fear <br>I'll wait your reply with a blunt and a beer." <br>I be the high guy with the belly and the beard <br>Smoke signal ET, ATLiens here <br><br>Beggin' your pardon, Run the Jewels live at the garden <br>Li-li-li-li-li-live from the garden <br>Li-li-live from the garden <br>Li-li-li-li-li-live from the garden <br>Run the Jewels live at the garden <br>Run the Jewels Live from the garden <br>Ru-ru-run the Jewels Live from the garden <br>Li-li-li-li-li-live from the- <br><br>Beggin' your pardon, Run the Jewels live at the garden <br>Last two pirates alive are still yargin (yargin) <br>My girl got my heart, it's a bargain <br>Lick from her lips to the crease in her garter <br>Her ass my religion, her love's why I'm livin' <br>I smoke farm to face by the field full, partner <br>Life's a shitnado, the smoke my umbrella <br>The boy's back turnin' his slacks to all yella (Prick) <br>It's a daily lick, I slit throats with a grin that reek of pure shit <br>Travel by backflip, eat from the river, the panther heart taught to talk by smart chicks <br>Sip pure venom and skipped away grinnin' <br>I put that on mom, she ain't raise a Vic <br>Lil' fucknuts, sit <br>I piss on your wit, dismiss your whole shit <br><br>Live from the stage of the garden <br>We be the realest of the killers of the fuck shit squadron <br>Movin' through the streets and we lootin,' robbin' <br>Mobbin,' marchin', carrying a carbine <br>Hello everybody, this is now bank robbery <br>Jesse James gang, we'll walk you through the process <br>You don't wanna be a hero, do not let that thought process <br>We will put a bullet where your thoughts get processed <br>Get that fuck shit straight like a perm or a process <br>'cause for real the money money ain't the mother fuckin' object <br>We just like excitement, gun fights, indictments <br>High speed chase through Manhattan in the night winds <br>Ooh, its the thrill of the kill <br>Watching Kill Bill on a pill as I grip steerin' wheel <br>Cops coulda' had the boy jammed I fear <br>But like Eddie Kane I made it I'm here <br><br>Beggin' your pardon, Run the Jewels live at the garden <br>Li-li-li-li-li-live from the garden <br>Li-li-live from the garden <br>Li-li-li-li-li-live from the garden <br>Run the Jewels live at the garden <br>Run the Jewels Live from the garden <br>Ru-ru-run the Jewels Live from the garden <br>Li-li-li-li-li-live from the- <br><br>I'm the sama lama doo ma lama danger dick'll do your mama <br>Skeeter with the peeter, never eat her, tell her see ya later <br>Holla 'bout tomorrow, baby, I ain't got to holler (Vroom, vroom) <br>My Impala pop a pussy, pop a collar <br>Pop a pill then chill, no Bill, no Cosby <br>Not a raper or a taker, bonafide heartbreaker <br>Hit her once, hit her twice, then tell her see ya later <br>Got head, watch Vice at her home in Decatur <br><br>Full clip, I'm a little bit sick, come equipped <br>Look at what I did for the grit, got it lit, what a cinch <br>Brought 'em just a little pinch of the truth, and they flip <br>Now they hanging from my shit, lil’ bit <br>It’s the Mensch, the myth <br>I do push-ups nude on the edge of cliffs <br>The jewels come quick, all gold and bricked <br>Click, click, boxer cutter spit <br>Brother, what a trip <br><br>Beggin' your pardon, Run the Jewels live at the garden <br>Li-li-li-li-li-live from the garden <br>Li-li-live from the garden <br>Li-li-li-li-li-live from the garden <br>Run the Jewels live at the garden <br>Run the Jewels Live from the garden <br>Ru-ru-run the Jewels Live from the garden <br>Li-li-li-li-li-live from the- <br><br>Tickets are on sale now at the Garden box office <br>And all Ticketron locations, or charge by phone]]></content><category term="Run The Jewels" label="Run The Jewels"/><category term="Call Ticketron" label="Call Ticketron"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Run_The_Jewels/Legend_Has_It/</id><title>Run The Jewels - Legend Has It - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:47:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:47:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Run_The_Jewels/Legend_Has_It/" title="Run The Jewels - Legend Has It - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1: Killer Mike] <br>Hear what I say, we are the business today <br>Fuck shit is finished today (what) <br>RT &amp; J, we the new PB &amp; J <br>We dropped a classic today (what) <br>We did a tablet of acid today <br>Lit joints with the matches and ashes away <br>SKRRRT! We dash away <br>Donner and Dixon, the pistol is wrapped on the way <br><br>[Verse 2: El-P] <br>Doctors of death <br>Curing our patients of breath <br>We are the pain you can trust <br>Crooked at work <br>Cookin' up curses and slurs <br>Smokin' my brain into mush <br>I became famous for flamin' you fucks <br>Maimin' my way through the brush <br>There is no training or taming of me and my bruh <br>Look like a man, but I'm animal raw <br><br>[Verse 3: Killer Mike] <br>We are the murderous pair <br>That went to jail and we murdered the murderers there <br>Then went to Hell and discovered the devil <br>Delivered some hurt and despair <br>Used to have powder to push <br>Now I smoke pounds of the kush <br>Holy, I'm burnin' a bush <br>Now I give a fuck about none of this shit <br>Jewel runner over and out of this bitch <br><br>[Hook] <br>Woo! <br>Woo! <br>Step into the spotlight, woo! <br>Woo! <br><br>[Verse 4: El-P] <br>Copping of uppers and downers get done <br>I'm in a rush to be numb <br>Droppin' a thousand ain't much <br>Come from the clouds <br>On a missile to turn this whole town into dust <br>Don't make a sound, baby, hush <br>I am the living swipe right on the mic, I'm a slut <br>I don't know how to not spit like a lout <br>I'll spill a pound of my kids on your couch <br><br>[Verse 5: Killer Mike] <br>Half of a mongrel and mythical team <br>Villainous treacherous things <br>Legend says El is a spawn out of Hell <br>The myth is my mama's a murderous queen <br>Your life can end like in Godfather 1 <br>You get the gun as I christen my son <br>If I die today and it's Hell I should pay <br>Tell the Lord Mikey said, "Fuck, it was fun" <br><br>[Verse 6: El-P] <br>Every new record's my dick in a box <br>We get a doozy, the mula's a lock <br>You're getting used to me doing no wrong <br>I don't play chicken, you prick, I'm a fox <br>You wanna kick it, I'll give you the rocks <br>You kiss the wood chipper blade if you balk <br>I'm fuckin' magic, in fact I'm a warlock of talk <br>I got a unicorn horn for a (stop) <br><br>[Hook] <br>Woo! <br>Woo! <br>Step into the spotlight, woo! <br>Woo! <br><br>[Interlude] <br>And the crowd goes RTJ! <br>And the crowd goes RTJ! <br>And the crowd goes RTJ! <br>And the crowd goes RTJ! <br>RTJ! <br>RTJ! <br>RTJ! <br>RTJ! <br><br>[Verse 7: Killer Mike] <br>Mike Pentangeli won't snitch <br>I'll rent a room at the Ritz <br>I'll sip a fifth of the whisk <br>I'll smoke a dub in the tub <br>Then I will split both my wrists <br><br>[Verse 8: El-P] <br>I'll pull a sword on you simps <br>Just with a flick of the wrist <br>Get your neck giving up mist <br>Me and Mike skip away whistlin' and grin <br>Every day's golden when you only win <br><br>[Verse 9: Killer Mike &amp; El-P] <br>Bullyin' bastards and beatin' on beats <br>Sounds like a day at the beach, preach <br>I keep it middle school, step on your feet <br>Before you can speak, blow to the teeth <br><br>[Verse 10: El-P] <br>We move among the ones you think are meek <br>You think I'm lion, you right, see my teeth <br>Don't be a bore when I'm roaring vamoose <br>Hunting's no fun when your prey doesn't move <br>I'll put a gun to a bunny like choose <br>Say somethin' funny or bunny go boom <br>You got a bevy of shit you could groove <br>We'd like to thank you for choosing our crew <br><br>[Verse 11: Killer Mike] <br>And that's from the crew you can trust <br>Warranty plus for fuckin' shit up <br>We are the no-gooders, do-gooders <br>Known to the dancers and dealers and doers of dust]]></content><category term="Run The Jewels" label="Run The Jewels"/><category term="Legend Has It" label="Legend Has It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Train/Lottery/</id><title>Train - Lottery - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:47:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:47:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Train/Lottery/" title="Train - Lottery - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want you to know that the love <br>I have for you right now is deep <br>And real, and right, and it will be <br>After tonight <br><br>Here comes the winning number <br>Thunder clapping in the summer skies <br>'Till confetti comes down <br>Here comes a kiss, y'all <br>Wish y'all'd <br>Open up that Cristal <br>Baby, cause we're moving uptown <br><br>Every time you're here with me <br>It's like I won the lottery <br>As rich as I could wish to be <br>It's like I won the lottery <br><br>I want you to know that the love <br>I have for you right now is deep <br>And real, and right, and it will be <br>After tonight <br><br>Here comes the winning number <br>Thunder clapping in the summer skies <br>Till confetti comes down <br>Here comes a kiss, y'all <br>Wish y'all'd <br>Open up that Cristal <br>Baby, cause we're moving uptown <br><br>We got the golden ticket <br>Kick it, hammock and a picket fence <br>And a pool underground <br>Take you on a LV spend spree <br>Open up that Dom P <br>Baby, cause we're Beverly Bound <br><br>Every time you're here with me <br>It's like I won the lottery <br>As rich as I could wish to be <br>It's like I won the lottery <br><br>Every time you're here with me <br>It's like I won the lottery <br>As rich as I could wish to be <br>It's like I won the lottery]]></content><category term="Train" label="Train"/><category term="Lottery" label="Lottery"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Train/The_News/</id><title>Train - The News - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:47:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:47:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Train/The_News/" title="Train - The News - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just in case I don't make it home <br>Just in case I don't make it home <br>Are you seeing this <br>Was it your breath or kiss <br>Upon my neck like this <br>Just like you took my dying wish <br>Now I'm all covered in <br>red from your lips <br>Tweaking from seeking <br>the way to your hips <br>Schizo from your finger tips <br>Can't seem to stop this twitch <br>Are you tuning in <br>The crowd is hollering <br>Jump jump jump jump again <br>Camera crew is wearing thin <br>They wanna see me <br>explode upon emoticon <br>Oh don't you see <br>the road I'm on <br>I'm real bad can't quit <br>Baby are you seeing this <br>Baby turn on the news <br>They're talking about me <br>like I'm going crazy <br>Baby turn on the news <br>Press record when I say it <br>Just in case I don't make it home <br>Are you following <br>Local 5 or CNN <br>They asked me <br>for my next of kin <br>Oh I'm a wreck-ening <br>They think that <br>they should lock me in <br>A rubber room and then <br>make sure I don't hurt myself <br>Or someone else or <br>even worse a nurse <br>Are you getting me <br>They think that I'm crazy <br>But baby this cold <br>straight white jacket <br>Don't even phase me <br>Oh I was playing them <br>tried to give me lithium <br>Didn't know that <br>I could swim home again <br>Come on baby let me in <br>Baby turn on the news <br>They're talking about me <br>like I'm going crazy <br>Baby turn on the news <br>Press record when I say it <br>Just in case I don't make it home <br>Just in case I don't make it home <br>Just in case I don't make it home <br>Flashing lights are blinding <br>all my sights <br>Don't know if I'll make it <br>through the night <br>When you see me on your screen <br>Then you'll know just what I mean <br>when I'm saying <br>Home <br>Baby turn on the news <br>They're talking about me <br>like I'm going crazy <br>Baby turn on the news <br>Press record when I say it <br>Just in case I don't make it home <br>Just in case I don't make it home <br>Just in case I don't make it home <br>]]></content><category term="Train" label="Train"/><category term="The News" label="The News"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Syd/All_About_Me/</id><title>Syd - All About Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:47:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:47:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Syd/All_About_Me/" title="Syd - All About Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I be more than a god <br>in my dreams <br>it's wishful thinking <br>I sleep more than I need to <br>I drink more on the weekend <br>I eat all meat but fish <br>I keep my niggas with me <br>I see sharks in the water <br>I fiend for marijuana <br>I pray for all my homies <br>I'm lyin' at least I try <br>I say that she's my only but <br>got you on my mind <br>Today I'm only human <br>but know that when I die <br>My grave gone be my music <br>my soul is living through it baby <br>Take care of the family <br>that you came with <br>We made it this <br>far and it's amazing <br>People drowning all around me <br>So I keep my squad around me <br>Keep it in the family <br>that you came with <br>Keep enemies close <br>you know the basics <br>People crowded all around me <br>I guess it's all about me <br>We gettin' checks in the mail <br>I don't know if you could tell <br>Stackin' this bread on the shelf <br>stackin' my bread on the shelf <br>I see you mad at yourself <br>I see them mad at themselves <br>I hear ‘em crying for help <br>I hear ‘em crying for help <br>Don't be mad if I switch up <br>my good taste got me this much <br>Too sweet for your taste buds <br>I seen you sleepin' hoe wake up <br>They ain't know what sauce was <br>till we served it offa that tonka <br>Drizzled all on your lobster <br>put shame to your roster <br>Me broke girl dream on <br>my team on <br>my weed strong <br>Need more of what we on <br>my league always D1 <br>We ball all season <br>Kobe's on my feet bruh <br>Pay attention to me bruh <br>pay me my fee bruh <br>You seek answers to <br>questions ‘bout me <br>it's in my music <br>You preach bout <br>revolution and dreams <br>I really do this <br>I lead by my example <br>I see fame as a nuisance <br>I don't take it for granted <br>but god dammit <br>Sometimes I can't stand it <br>Take care of the family <br>that you came with <br>We made it this <br>far and it's amazing <br>People drowning all around me <br>So I keep my squad around me <br>Keep it in the family <br>that you came with <br>Keep enemies close <br>you know the basics <br>People crowded all around me <br>I guess it's all about me <br>]]></content><category term="Syd" label="Syd"/><category term="All About Me" label="All About Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Train/Play_That_Song/</id><title>Train - Play That Song - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:47:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:47:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Train/Play_That_Song/" title="Train - Play That Song - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Play that song <br>The one that makes me <br>go all night long <br>The one that makes me <br>think of you <br>That's all you gotta do <br>Hey Mister DJ <br>when you gonna spin it <br>My baby's favorite record <br>She been waiting for a minute <br>She invited all her friends <br>And I'm buying all the rounds <br>And they're all dolled up <br>DJ please don't let me down <br>When you gonna play <br>that song now <br>When you gonna earn <br>that pay <br>When you gonna play <br>that song <br>And make my day <br>She said <br>Play that song <br>The one that makes me <br>go all night long <br>The one that makes me <br>think of you <br>That's all you gotta do <br>Hey <br>Play that song <br>The one that makes me <br>stay out til dawn <br>The one that makes me go ooh <br>That's all you gotta do <br>Hey Mister Guitar <br>When you gonna strum it <br>My girl just heard this song <br>And you should play it <br>cause she loves it <br>Can you get me off the hook <br>Get them fingers picking now <br>I'll throw some money in your cup <br>Mister please don't let me down <br>When you gonna play <br>that song now <br>Why you gotta hesitate <br>When you gonna play <br>that song <br>And make my day <br>She said <br>Play that song <br>The one that makes me <br>go all night long <br>The one that makes me <br>think of you <br>That's all you gotta do <br>Hey <br>Play that song <br>The one that makes me <br>stay out til dawn <br>The one that makes me go ooh <br>That's all you gotta do <br>Oh wait till you see my baby <br>Moo oo oove moo oo oove <br>Moo oo oove <br>Oh wait till you see my baby <br>Moo oo oove moo oo oove <br>Moo oo oove <br>Oh come on now <br>Play that song <br>The one that makes her <br>go all night long <br>The one that makes her <br>think of me <br>That's all you gotta do <br>Hey <br>Play that song <br>The one that makes her <br>stay out til dawn <br>The one that makes her go ooh <br>That's all you gotta do <br>That's all you gotta do <br>That's all you gotta do <br>That's all you gotta do <br>]]></content><category term="Train" label="Train"/><category term="Play That Song" label="Play That Song"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Khalid/Saved/</id><title>Khalid - Saved - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:48:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:48:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Khalid/Saved/" title="Khalid - Saved - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1 2 3 4 <br>The hard part always seems <br>to last forever <br>Sometimes I forget <br>that we aren't together <br>Deep down in my heart <br>I hope you're doing alright <br>But from time to time <br>I often think of <br>why you aren't mine <br>But I'll keep your number saved <br>Cause I hope one day <br>you'll get the sense to call me <br>I'm hoping that you'll say <br>You're missing me the way <br>I'm missing you <br>So i'll keep your number saved <br>Cause i hope one day <br>I'll get the pride to call you <br>To tell you that no one else <br>Is gonna hold you down <br>the way that I do <br>Now I can't say <br>I'll be alright without you <br>And i can't say <br>that i haven't tried to <br>But all your stuff is gone <br>I erased all the pictures <br>from my phone <br>Of me and you <br>Heres what i'll do <br>I'll keep your number saved <br>Cause I hope one day <br>you'll get the sense to call me <br>I'm hoping that you'll say <br>You're missing me the way <br>I'm missing you <br>So i'll keep your number saved <br>Cause i hope one day <br>I'll get the pride to call you <br>To tell you that no one else <br>Is gonna hold you down <br>the way that I do <br>I hope you think of <br>all the times we shared <br>I hope you'll finally realize <br>I was the only one who cared <br>It's crazy how this love <br>thing seems unfair <br>You won't find a love <br>like mine anywhere <br>But I'll keep your number saved <br>Cause I hope one day <br>you'll get the sense to call me <br>I'm hoping that you'll say <br>You're missing me the way <br>I'm missing you <br>So i'll keep your number saved <br>Cause i hope one day <br>I'll get the pride to call you <br>To tell you that no one else <br>Is gonna hold you down <br>the way that I do <br>So I'll keep your number saved <br>Cause I hope one day <br>you'll get the sense to call me <br>hoping that you'll say <br>You're missing me the way <br>I'm missing you <br>keep your number saved <br>Cause i hope one day <br>I'll get the pride to call you <br>To tell you that <br>]]></content><category term="Khalid" label="Khalid"/><category term="Saved" label="Saved"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강_다니엘/나의_몰약_주머니/</id><title>강 다니엘 - 나의 몰약 주머니 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:48:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:48:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95_%EB%8B%A4%EB%8B%88%EC%97%98/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EB%AA%B0%EC%95%BD_%EC%A3%BC%EB%A8%B8%EB%8B%88/" title="강 다니엘 - 나의 몰약 주머니 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 몰약 주머니 <br>내 가슴속에 늘 <br>품기 원하네 <br>내 사랑하는 자 <br>나의 사랑하는 이를 <br>내 사랑하는 자는 <br>나의 것 나는 <br>그의 것입니다 <br>나는 그의 것 <br>그의 소원은 내 위에 <br>내 안에 함께 하사 <br>날 오라시네 <br>겨울 지나고 <br>꽃 피었다고 <br>나의 사랑 나오라시네 <br>너의 모습이 보고 싶다고 <br>나의 몰약 주머니 <br>내 가슴속에 늘 <br>품기 원하네 <br>내 사랑하는 자 <br>나의 사랑하는 이를 <br>내 사랑하는 자는 <br>나의 것 나는 <br>그의 것입니다 <br>나는 그의 것 <br>그의 소원은 내 위에 <br>내 안에 함께 하사 <br>날 오라시네 <br>겨울 지나고 <br>꽃 피었다고 <br>나의 사랑 나오라시네 <br>너의 모습이 보고 싶다고 <br>나의 사랑 <br>너의 눈빛 만으로도 <br>너무 어지럽다고 <br>너의 사랑 <br>포도주보다 훨씬 더 <br>좋고 향기롭다고 <br>훨씬 더 좋고 향기롭다고 <br>너의 모습이 보고 싶다고 <br>]]></content><category term="강 다니엘" label="강 다니엘"/><category term="나의 몰약 주머니" label="나의 몰약 주머니"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TOM/리칭_Feat_Trigga/</id><title>TOM - 리칭 (Feat. Trigga) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:48:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:48:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TOM/%EB%A6%AC%EC%B9%AD_Feat_Trigga/" title="TOM - 리칭 (Feat. Trigga) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이건 두 여자에 대한 노랜 아냐 <br>침이 말라버린 여자 얘기 ye <br>Oh Ye <br>이게 뭐냐면 매일 밤 편집하는 <br>감독의 비애 Uh Ya <br>모두 끝나면 떠날 거야 <br>나를 찾지를 말어 O EH <br>다 뿔은 라면 두 젓가락 <br>다시 봐야 돼 화면 <br>HO HO 웃지를 말어 <br>반복된 화면 절대 그치질 않어 <br>다그치는 거지 뭐 <br>끄지라는 말은 아냐 <br>트집을 잡을 라니 <br>스트레스를 받어 <br>Ay 혼돈이야 혼또 혼돈이야 <br>여자 1이고 2이고 똔또니야 <br>내 일이 곧 삶이고 똔또니야 <br>아 ho 잠이 오다 또 팔팔해 <br>Ay Ay 담이 온다 내 팔자에 <br>아이 아이 아이 <br>댓글 달어 내 담벼락에 <br>두 여자 Anthem <br>Trigga &amp; Tom <br>Shout out Gonekim 72초 <br>이건 두 여자에 대한 노랜 아냐 <br>두통이 심했던 여자 얘기 ye <br>Oh Ye <br>이게 뭐냐면 편집하기 싫은 <br>감독의 비애 Uh Ya <br>모두 끝나면 떠날 거야 <br>그래 나 잡아봐라 <br>LULULULULULU <br>다 뿔은 라면 지겹다구 <br>다시 봐야 돼 화면 <br>HA HA 웃지를 말어 <br>반복된 화면 절대 끝나질 않어 <br>나긋한 톤으로다가 <br>끄지라는 말은 아냐 <br>트집을 안 잡아두 <br>스트레스를 받어 <br>Ay 혼돈이야 혼또 혼돈이야 <br>여자 12고 3자고 똔또니야 <br>내일이고 모레고 똔또니야 <br>아 ho 잠이 온다 안 팔팔해 <br>Ay Ay 주름진다 내 팔자에 <br>아이 아이 아이 <br>댓글 달지마 내 담벼락에 <br>두 여자 Anthem <br>Trigga &amp; Tom <br>Shout out Gonekim 72초 <br>]]></content><category term="TOM" label="TOM"/><category term="리칭 (Feat. Trigga)" label="리칭 (Feat. Trigga)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TOM/숨_Feat_김민하/</id><title>TOM - 숨 (Feat. 김민하) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:48:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:48:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/TOM/%EC%88%A8_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EB%AF%BC%ED%95%98/" title="TOM - 숨 (Feat. 김민하) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사각사각 간질거리는 <br>시계 초침 소릴 멍한 눈으로 <br>흐린 창 밖으로 떠버린 해가 <br>한 발짝씩 걸어가고 있어 <br>하나 둘 사라지지 <br>않았던 척 또 알았던 적 <br>기억도 없는 척 <br>사각사각 <br>나에게만 들리는 <br>똑같은 그 목소리 <br>깜박깜박 아른거리는 <br>식어버린 이름을 말하려 하네 늘 <br>가슴 짓누르고 멈춘 시간은 <br>한 발짝도 움직이질 않아 <br>땀에 젖어 음 <br>몽롱하게 스며드는 <br>아침의 그림자만이 <br>아직 살아있는 거라고 <br>늘 말하려 하지만 <br>눈을 떠도 나에게는 보이지 않아 <br>숨 막히는 꿈속에서 <br>꺼내주지 마 날 <br>차디차게 내 끝은 짙어져만 가고 <br>아무도 오지 않을 텅 빈 방에서 <br>깨어나지 않을 거야 휘청거리는 <br>기억들이 우리를 비웃는 날에는 <br>알아볼 수도 없는 그의 입술이 <br>영원히 넌 모를 거라 <br>말하려 하네 늘 <br>]]></content><category term="TOM" label="TOM"/><category term="숨 (Feat. 김민하)" label="숨 (Feat. 김민하)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/9991/12월의_어느날에/</id><title>9991 - 12월의 어느날에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:49:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:49:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/9991/12%EC%9B%94%EC%9D%98_%EC%96%B4%EB%8A%90%EB%82%A0%EC%97%90/" title="9991 - 12월의 어느날에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈이 무거워져 <br>따끔거리는 게 <br>며칠째 불면증 <br>언제쯤 편하게 <br>잘 수 있는지 <br>너 떠나고 일주일하고 <br>두 시간째 <br>11월의 어느 마지막 밤에 <br>잠 못 이루다가 <br>니가 놔두고 간 잠옷이 <br>눈에 띄게 보이더니 <br>갑자기 내 눈에 <br>눈물이 허락 없이 <br>길 잃은 아이처럼 <br>방황하던 내 맘으로 <br>어느새 <br>니가 들어와 <br>밥을 먹는 것도 아니 <br>어떤 것도 귀찮아졌어 <br>언제쯤 편하게 쉴 수 있는지 <br>너 떠나고 한달 이나 지나 <br>삼 일째 되어가던 날 <br>12월의 어느 마지막 밤에 <br>잠 못 이루다가 <br>니가 놔두고 간 <br>잠옷이 눈에 띄게 <br>보이더니 갑자기 내 눈에 <br>눈물이 허락 없이 길 잃은 <br>아이처럼 방황하던 <br>내 맘으로 어느새 <br>니가 들어와 <br>]]></content><category term="9991" label="9991"/><category term="12월의 어느날에" label="12월의 어느날에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/진안/하얀_신부/</id><title>진안 - 하얀 신부 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:50:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:50:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%84%EC%95%88/%ED%95%98%EC%96%80_%EC%8B%A0%EB%B6%80/" title="진안 - 하얀 신부 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하얗게 내리는 눈이 <br>나를 더 설레게 <br>두근거리게 <br>오 너는 얼마나 <br>달라졌을까 <br>전화 속 목소리 <br>그때 그대로 <br>차가운 기억들은 <br>시간에 녹아 들었어 <br>손 닿으면 사라지는 <br>이 눈꽃처럼 <br>한 겨울 둘이 손을 잡고 <br>걸었던 눈길 <br>또 다시 함께 걷게 된다면 <br>소복하게 쌓인 그리움 <br>네 미소에 모두 <br>녹아 없어질 때 <br>하얀 신부가 돼 줘 <br>하얗게 웃어주는 너 <br>나를 눈 못 떼게 <br>두근거리게 <br>오 너도 나처럼 <br>기다렸을까 <br>기억 속 그 모습 <br>아직 그대로 <br>따뜻한 추억들은 <br>마음에 녹아 들었어 <br>눈 내리던 어느 날의 <br>네 숨결처럼 <br>한 겨울 둘이 마주 앉아 <br>속삭이던 곳 <br>또 다시 함께 가게 된다면 <br>소복하게 쌓여 갈 사랑 <br>널 만나면 꼭 하고 <br>싶었던 얘기 <br>다신 놓지 않을게 <br>한 겨울 둘이 손을 잡고 <br>걸었던 날들 <br>또 다시 우리 함께 한다면 <br>소복하게 쌓인 그리움 <br>네 미소에 모두 <br>녹아 없어질 때 <br>하얀 신부가 돼 줘 <br>]]></content><category term="진안" label="진안"/><category term="하얀 신부" label="하얀 신부"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하록/숭그리당당_숭당당/</id><title>하록 - 숭그리당당 숭당당 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:50:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:50:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EB%A1%9D/%EC%88%AD%EA%B7%B8%EB%A6%AC%EB%8B%B9%EB%8B%B9_%EC%88%AD%EB%8B%B9%EB%8B%B9/" title="하록 - 숭그리당당 숭당당 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑의 주문을 왼다 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>오직 너 뿐이야 <br>이제것 살아 온날동안 <br>한번도 잊은 적 없었다 <br>그녀가 내맘 두드린다 <br>꿍꿍거린다 <br>얼굴은 새침 하면서도 <br>마음은 몹시 고운가봐 <br>생각은 아직 설레는데 <br>두손은 벌써 그댈잡네요 <br>당신이 바란다면 내가갈게 <br>당신이 원한다면 내가줄게 <br>저 하늘 별이라도 따다줄게 <br>사랑의 주문을 왼다 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>사랑이 내게 온다 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>오직 너 뿐이야 <br>사랑의 주문을 왼다 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>오직 너 뿐이야 <br>세월이 가서 변한데도 <br>나오직 그대 만 바란다 <br>그녀가 내게 다가온다 <br>심쿵거린다 <br>몸매는 섹시 하면서도 <br>마음은 몹시 여린가봐 <br>세월이 가도 변함없이 <br>내맘은 당신 향해있네요 <br>당신이 바란다면 내가갈게 <br>당신이 원한다면 내가줄게 <br>저 하늘 별이라도 따다줄게 <br>사랑의 주문을 왼다 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>사랑이 내게 온다 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>숭그리당당 숭당당 <br>오직 너 뿐이야 <br>오직 너 뿐이야 <br>오직 너 뿐이야 <br>]]></content><category term="하록" label="하록"/><category term="숭그리당당 숭당당" label="숭그리당당 숭당당"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OIJ/Back_To_The_Start_Feat_Gia_Koka/</id><title>OIJ - Back To The Start (Feat. Gia Koka) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:50:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:50:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/OIJ/Back_To_The_Start_Feat_Gia_Koka/" title="OIJ - Back To The Start (Feat. Gia Koka) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't wait <br>For love I'm always running late <br>Used to your heartbeat <br>It's getting in the way <br>Why my name <br>Ain't there a better girl out there <br>I feel the air <br>You're getting in the way <br>Yeah, wasted a night kiss <br>Cause nothing feels like this <br>And I wanna know, tell me you know, what it is <br><br>We have ran a million miles <br>Followed it to where we are <br>Let's go too far <br>Let's go too far <br>Can't go back to the start <br>Only if the stars align <br>They will show me where you are <br>Let's go too far <br>Let's go too far <br>Can't go back to the start, start <br>Can't go back to the start, start <br><br>It's a game <br>But I'm not the one who plays <br>Can't feel your heartbeat <br>Cause it is still the same <br>Yeah, wasted your one wish <br>Cause nothing feels like this <br>I wanna know, tell me you know, what it is <br><br>We have ran a million miles <br>Followed it to where we are <br>Let's go too far <br>Let's go too far <br>Can't go back to the start <br>Only if the stars align <br>They will show me where you are <br>Let's go too far <br>Let's go too far <br>Can't go back to the start, start <br><br>Can't go back to the <br>Can't go back to the start, start <br>Can't go back to the <br>Can't go back to the start <br><br>Only if the stars align <br>They will show me where you are <br>Let's go too far <br>Let's go too far <br>Can't go back to the start, start <br>Can't go back to the <br>Can't go back to the start, start <br>We have ran a million miles <br>Followed it to where we are <br>Let's go too far <br>Let's go too far <br>Can't go back to the start, start]]></content><category term="OIJ" label="OIJ"/><category term="Back To The Start (Feat. Gia Koka)" label="Back To The Start (Feat. Gia Koka)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MC5/Ramblin_Rose/</id><title>MC5 - Ramblin` Rose - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:50:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:50:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/MC5/Ramblin_Rose/" title="MC5 - Ramblin` Rose - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love is like a Ramblin' Rose <br>The more you feed it <br>The more it grows <br>Ramblin'Rose, Ramblin'Rose <br>Come on home <br><br>Ramblin' Rose <br>Is such a ball <br>Diamond rings <br>And a Cadillac car <br>Ramblin' Rose, Ramblin' Rose <br>Come on home <br><br>Ramblin' Rose <br>Ramblin' around <br>Ramblin' Rose <br>I'm gonna put you down <br>Ramblin' Rose, Ramblin' Rose <br>Come on home <br><br>Love is like a Ramblin' Rose <br>The more you feed it <br>The more it grows <br>Ramblin' Rose, Ramblin' Rose <br>Come on home <br><br>I need a Ramblin' Rose <br>Ramblin' Rose]]></content><category term="MC5" label="MC5"/><category term="Ramblin` Rose" label="Ramblin` Rose"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/Loose/</id><title>The Stooges - Loose - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:50:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:50:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/Loose/" title="The Stooges - Loose - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now look out <br><br>I took a record of pretty music <br>I went down and baby you can tell <br>I took a record of pretty music <br>Now I'm putting it to you straight from hell <br><br>I'll stick it deep inside <br>I'll stick it deep inside <br>Cause I'm loose <br><br>I feel fine to be dancin', baby <br>I feel fine, I'm a shakin' leaf <br>I feel fine to be dancin', baby <br>Cause it's love, yeah I do believe <br><br>I'll stick it deep inside <br>I'll stick it deep inside <br>Cause I'm loose <br><br>And I'll stick it deep inside <br>And I'll stick it hey <br>Well I'm loose, well I'm loose <br>Well I'm loose]]></content><category term="The Stooges" label="The Stooges"/><category term="Loose" label="Loose"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/Down_On_The_Street/</id><title>The Stooges - Down On The Street - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:50:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:50:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/Down_On_The_Street/" title="The Stooges - Down On The Street - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Huh <br>Down on the street <br>Where the faces shine <br>Floatin' around I'm <br>A real low mind <br>See a pretty thing ain't no wall <br>See a pretty thing ain't no wall <br>No wall <br>No wall <br>No wall <br>Uuh <br>Yeah deep in the night <br>I'm lost in love <br>Yeah deep in the night <br>I'm lost in love <br>A thousand lights <br>Look at you <br>A thousand lights <br>Look at you <br>I'm lost, I'm lost, I'm lost yeah <br>Huh <br>Faces shine real low mind <br>Real low mind <br>I'm a real low mind <br>Real low mi]]></content><category term="The Stooges" label="The Stooges"/><category term="Down On The Street" label="Down On The Street"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/Little_Doll_Remastered/</id><title>The Stooges - Little Doll (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:50:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:50:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/Little_Doll_Remastered/" title="The Stooges - Little Doll (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Little doll I can't forget <br>smoking on a cigarette <br>In my life a real queen <br>prettiest thing I ever seen <br>Uh huh <br>You're the one who makes me sing <br>Bring happiness and everything <br>you're the only real one <br>A real way to have some fun <br>Uh huh <br>But I don't know you little doll <br>I don't know you little doll <br>Come on shake <br>Come on shake <br>Come on shake you little doll <br>Shake you little doll <br>Come on shake <br>come on shake <br>Shake you little doll]]></content><category term="The Stooges" label="The Stooges"/><category term="Little Doll (Remastered)" label="Little Doll (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/1969_Remastered/</id><title>The Stooges - 1969 (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/1969_Remastered/" title="The Stooges - 1969 (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well it's 1969 OK all across the USA <br>It's another year for me and you <br>Another year with nothing to do <br>Last year I was 21 I didn't have a lot of fun <br>And now I'm gonna be 22 I say oh my and a boo hoo <br>It's 1969 OK all across the USA <br>It's another year for me and you <br>Another year with nothing to do <br>Another year with nothing to do <br>It's 1969 <br>1969 1969 1969 1969 baby <br>And it's 1969 bayyyyyyybee <br>Baby <br>Baby <br>Baby]]></content><category term="The Stooges" label="The Stooges"/><category term="1969 (Remastered)" label="1969 (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/I_Wanna_Be_Your_Dog_Remastered/</id><title>The Stooges - I Wanna Be Your Dog (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/I_Wanna_Be_Your_Dog_Remastered/" title="The Stooges - I Wanna Be Your Dog (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[So messed up I want you here <br>In my room I want you here <br>Now we're gonna be Face to face <br>And I'll lay right down In my favorite place <br>And now I wanna be your dog <br>Now I wanna be your dog <br>Now I wanna be your dog <br>Well c'mon <br>Now I'm ready to close my eyes <br>And now I'm ready to close my mind <br>And now I'm ready to feel your hand <br>And lose my heart on the burning sands <br>And now I wanna be your dog <br>And now I wenna be your dog <br>Now I wanna be your dog <br>Well c'mon]]></content><category term="The Stooges" label="The Stooges"/><category term="I Wanna Be Your Dog (Remastered)" label="I Wanna Be Your Dog (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/No_Fun_Remastered/</id><title>The Stooges - No Fun (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Stooges/No_Fun_Remastered/" title="The Stooges - No Fun (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No fun my babe <br>No fun <br>No fun my babe <br>No fun <br>No fun to hang around <br>Feelin' that same old way <br>No fun to hang around <br>Freaked out for another day <br>No fun my babe <br>No fun <br>No fun my babe <br>No fun <br>No fun to be alone <br>Walking by myself <br>No fun to be alone <br>In love with nobody else <br>Well maybe go out, maybe stay home <br>Maybe call Mom on the telephone <br>Well c'mon, well c'mon <br>C'mon c'mon <br>Now Ron, I say Ron <br>C'mon and lemme hear you tell em <br>Lemme hear you tell em <br>Now I feel <br>I say lemme hear you <br>Tell em how I feel, yeah, my man <br>No fun to be alone <br>It's no fun to be alone <br>Hang on <br>Don't you lemme go <br>It's no fun to alone <br>To be alone]]></content><category term="The Stooges" label="The Stooges"/><category term="No Fun (Remastered)" label="No Fun (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lisa_May/Young_Love/</id><title>Lisa May - Young Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lisa_May/Young_Love/" title="Lisa May - Young Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eey young love <br>We can ride it to the sun <br>You know don't you know that <br>When the galaxies collide <br>They run as one <br>Like the stars <br>Like the stars <br>Crush and burn and the world goes wild <br>I'll give you my all <br>I'll be around <br>Tonight <br><br>See, it's breaking thru my soul <br>And I can't cope <br>Late night minds <br>Make everything feel wrong <br>And I can't escape from you <br>No, I can't escape from you <br><br>See, it's breaking thru my bones <br>And my heart floats <br>Late night minds <br>Spins us out of control <br>And I can't escape from you <br>No, I can't escape <br>From you <br><br>We can love till the moon runs out of light You know don't you know that We can love till it shakes you up And let you touch the sky Look at the endless space Tells a story Of this old man lost in his glory And they know we'll runaway It sets us free tonight <br><br>See, it's breaking thru my soul <br>And I can't cope <br>Late night minds <br>Make everything feel wrong <br>And I can't escape from you <br>No, I can't escape from you <br><br>See, it's breaking thru my bones <br>And my heart floats <br>Late night minds <br>Spins us out of control <br>And I can't escape from you <br>No, I can't escape <br>From you]]></content><category term="Lisa May" label="Lisa May"/><category term="Young Love" label="Young Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maor_Levi/No_Sleep_Feat_Mariah_Mcmanus_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Maor Levi - No Sleep (Feat. Mariah Mcmanus) (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Maor_Levi/No_Sleep_Feat_Mariah_Mcmanus_Radio_Edit/" title="Maor Levi - No Sleep (Feat. Mariah Mcmanus) (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't stop we're on overload <br>No sleep until tomorrow <br>And tonight got to let it go <br>You and I, you and I <br>Don't stop we're on overload <br>No sleep until tomorrow <br>And tonight got to let it go <br>You and I, you and I <br>I won't stop <br>I won't stop <br>I won't stop <br>I'm on overload <br>I won't stop <br>Won't stop <br>We're not letting go <br>Don't stop we're on overload <br>No sleep until tomorrow <br>And tonight got to let it go <br>You and I, you and I <br>Don't stop we're on overload <br>No sleep until tomorrow <br>And tonight got to let it go <br>You and I, you and I <br>I won't stop <br>I won't stop <br>I won't stop <br>I'm on overload <br>I won't stop <br>I won't stop <br>I won't stop <br>I'm on overload <br>I won't stop <br>We're not letting go <br>Don't stop we're on overload <br>No sleep until tomorrow <br>And tonight got to let it go <br>You and I, you and I]]></content><category term="Maor Levi" label="Maor Levi"/><category term="No Sleep (Feat. Mariah Mcmanus) (Radio Edit)" label="No Sleep (Feat. Mariah Mcmanus) (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lisa_May/Broken_Kites/</id><title>Lisa May - Broken Kites - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lisa_May/Broken_Kites/" title="Lisa May - Broken Kites - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sky don't fall, the way he's holding me now <br>I'll take you for a ride he said, he said <br>Let's go get high, let's go get wasted <br>To your madnesses To my madnesses <br><br>As you touch my body, I have no regrets <br>Don't ever let me go, don't ever let me go he said <br>As you touch my body, I am found again <br>Don't ever let me go, don't ever let me go, as my heart goes on and on like <br><br>As my heart goes on and on like <br>As my heart goes on and on like <br>As my heart goes on and on like <br>As my heart goes on and on like <br><br>Unbreakable, undeniably assured <br>You VIBE with my heart like nobody else <br>Escape and run <br>To the places that we've never known <br><br>As you touch my body, I have no regrets <br>Don't ever let me go, don't ever let me go he said <br>As you touch my body, I am found again <br>Don't ever let me go, don't ever let me go, as my heart goes on and on like <br><br>As my heart goes on and on like <br>As my heart goes on and on like <br>As my heart goes on and on like <br>As my heart goes on and on like <br><br>As you touch my body, I have no regrets <br>Don't ever let me go, don't ever let me go he said <br>We need you and I, ain't nobody else <br>Flying broken kites, as my heart goes on and on like <br><br>We need you and I, ain't nobody else <br>Flying broken kites, as my heart goes on and on like <br>We need you and I, ain't nobody else <br>Flying broken kites, crystal magic no regrets <br>We need you and I, ain't nobody else <br>Flying broken kites as my heart goes on and on like <br>As my heart goes on and on like <br>As my heart goes on and on like <br>As my heart goes on and on like <br>As my heart goes on and on like]]></content><category term="Lisa May" label="Lisa May"/><category term="Broken Kites" label="Broken Kites"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Test_Me/</id><title>The XX - Test Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Test_Me/" title="The XX - Test Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I DON’T KNOW WHERE I WENT WRONG <br>TELL ME SHOULD I SEE SOMEONE <br>CEILINGS FALLING DOWN ON ME <br>YOU LOOK BUT YOU NEVER SEE <br>JUST TAKE IT OUT ON ME <br>IT’S EASIER THAN SAYING WHAT YOU MEAN <br>TEST ME <br>SEE IF I BREAK <br>TELL ME THIS TIME YOU’VE CHANGED <br>I’LL TAKE IT OUT ON YOU <br>IT’S EASIER THAN TALKING IT THROUGH <br>TEST ME <br>SEE IF I STAY <br>HOW COULD I WALK THE OTHER WAY]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="Test Me" label="Test Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/I_Dare_You/</id><title>The XX - I Dare You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/I_Dare_You/" title="The XX - I Dare You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1: Oliver Sim] <br><br>I'm in love with it <br><br>Intoxicated <br><br>I'm in rapture <br><br>From the inside I can feel that you want to <br><br>Wake up high on it <br><br>Feel it suspending <br><br>I'm enamoured <br><br>Way up in the sky I can see that you want to <br><br><br><br>[Pre-Chorus: Romy Madley Croft] <br><br>I've been a romantic for so long <br><br>All I've ever heard are love songs <br><br><br><br>[Chorus: Oliver Sim &amp; Romy Madley Croft] <br><br>Singing oh-oh-oh <br><br>Go on, I dare you <br><br>Oh-oh-oh <br><br>I dare you <br><br><br><br>[Verse 2: Romy Madley Croft &amp; Oliver Sim] <br><br>I get chills <br><br>Heart's rate multiplies <br><br>I'm on a different kind of high <br><br>A rush of blood is not enough <br><br>I need my feelings set on fire <br><br>Now I'm deep in it, infatuated <br><br>Strong attraction <br><br>Side by side, and I know that you want to <br><br><br><br>[Pre-Chorus: Romy Madley Croft] <br><br>I've been a romantic for so long <br><br>All I've ever heard are love songs <br><br><br><br>[Chorus: Oliver Sim &amp; Romy Madley Croft] <br><br>Singing oh-oh-oh <br><br>Go on, I dare you <br><br>Oh-oh-oh <br><br>I dare you <br><br><br><br>[Bridge: Romy Madley Croft &amp; together] <br><br>I can hear it now like I heard it then <br><br>I can hear it now like I heard it then <br><br>I can hear it now like I heard it then <br><br>I can hear it now like I heard it then <br><br><br><br>[Chorus: Oliver Sim &amp; Romy Madley Croft] <br><br>Singing oh-oh-oh <br><br>Go on, I dare you <br><br>Oh-oh-oh <br><br>I dare you <br><br>Oh-oh-oh <br><br>Go on, I dare you <br><br>Oh-oh-oh <br><br>I dare you]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="I Dare You" label="I Dare You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/On_Hold/</id><title>The XX - On Hold - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/On_Hold/" title="The XX - On Hold - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't blame you <br>We got carried away <br>I can't hold on <br>To an empty space <br>Now you've found a <br>new star to orbit <br>It could be love <br>I think you're too <br>soon to call us old <br>When and where <br>did we go cold <br>I thought I had <br>you on hold <br>And every time <br>I let you leave <br>I always saw you <br>coming back to me <br>When and where <br>did we go cold <br>I thought I had <br>you on hold <br>Where does it stop <br>where does it stop <br>Where do you dare me to <br>You've got the body <br>you've got the body <br>Dare me to <br>dare me to <br>Where does it stop <br>where does it stop <br>Where do you dare me to <br>You've got the body <br>you've got the body <br>I thought I had you on hold <br>You've got the body <br>you've got the body <br>Where does it stop <br>where does it stop <br>Where do you dare me to <br>You've got the body <br>you've got the body <br>Dare me to <br>dare me to <br>Where does it stop <br>where does it stop <br>Where do you dare me to <br>You've got the body <br>you've got the body <br>Dare me to <br>dare me to <br>My young heart <br>chose to believe <br>We were destined <br>Young hearts <br>All need love <br>Call it a lesson <br>The stars and the charts <br>And the cards make sense <br>Only when we want them to <br>When I lie awake <br>staring in to space <br>I see a different view <br>Now you've found a <br>new star to orbit <br>It could be love <br>I think you're too <br>soon to call us old <br>When and where <br>did we go cold <br>I thought I had <br>you on hold <br>And every time <br>I let you leave <br>I always saw you <br>coming back to me <br>When and where <br>did we go cold <br>I thought I had <br>you on hold <br>I thought I had <br>you on hold <br>I thought I had <br>you on hold <br>Where does it stop <br>where does it stop <br>Where do you dare me to <br>You've got the body <br>you've got the body <br>Dare me to <br>dare me to <br>Where does it stop <br>where does it stop <br>Where do you dare me to <br>You've got the body <br>you've got the body <br>You've got the body <br>you've got the body <br>Where does it stop <br>where does it stop <br>Where do you dare me to <br>You've got the body <br>you've got the body <br>Dare me to <br>dare me to <br>Where does it stop <br>where does it stop <br>Where do you dare me to <br>You've got the body <br>you've got the body <br>Dare me to <br>dare me to <br>And every time <br>I let you leave <br>I always saw you <br>coming back to me <br>When and where <br>did we go cold <br>I thought I had <br>you on hold <br>I thought I had <br>you on hold <br>I thought I had <br>you on hold <br>]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="On Hold" label="On Hold"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Brave_For_You/</id><title>The XX - Brave For You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Brave_For_You/" title="The XX - Brave For You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I’M IN LOVE WITH IT <br>INTOXICATED <br>I’M IN RAPTURE <br>FROM THE INSIDE I CAN FEEL THAT YOU WANT TO <br>WAY UP HIGH ON IT <br>FEELING SUSPENDED <br>IM ENAMOURED <br>WAY UP IN THE SKY I CAN SEE THAT YOU WANT TO <br>I’VE BEEN A ROMANTIC FOR SO LONG <br>ALL I’VE EVER HEARD ARE LOVE SONGS <br>SINGING <br>OH OH OH GO ON I DARE YOU <br>OH OH OH I DARE YOU <br>I GET CHILLS <br>HEARTS RATE MULTIPLIES <br>I’M ON A DIFFERENT KIND OF HIGH <br>A RUSH OF BLOOD <br>IS NOT ENOUGH <br>I NEED MY FEELINGS SET ON FIRE <br>NOW I’M IN DEEP IN IT <br>INFATUATED <br>STRONG ATTRACTION <br>SIDE BY SIDE AND I KNOW THAT YOU WANT TO <br>I’VE BEEN A ROMANTIC FOR SO LONG <br>ALL I’VE EVER HEARD ARE LOVE SONGS <br>SINGING <br>OH OH OH GO ON I DARE YOU <br>OH OH OH I DARE YOU <br>I CAN HEAR IT NOW LIKE I HEARD IT THEN <br>I CAN HEAR IT NOW LIKE I HEARD IT THEN <br>I CAN HEAR IT NOW LIKE I HEARD IT THEN <br>I CAN HEAR IT NOW LIKE I HEARD IT THEN <br>SINGING <br>OH OH OH GO ON I DARE YOU <br>OH OH OH I DARE YOU <br>OH OH OH GO ON I DARE YOU <br>OH OH OH I DARE YOU]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="Brave For You" label="Brave For You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Replica/</id><title>The XX - Replica - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Replica/" title="The XX - Replica - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[SAME RIGHT <br>SAME WRONG <br>ONLY DIFFERENCE IS THAT I’M THE ONE <br>SECOND TIME AROUND <br>FEELS LIKE THE SONG’S ALREADY BEEN SUNG <br>MIRRORING SITUATIONS <br>ACCURATE IMITATION <br>DO I WATCH AND REPEAT <br>AND AS IF I TRIED TO <br>I’VE TURNED OUT JUST LIKE YOU <br>DO WE WATCH AND REPEAT <br>THEY ALL SAY <br>I WILL BECOME A REPLICA <br>YOUR MISTAKES <br>WERE ONLY CHEMICAL <br>TWENTY FIVE AND YOU’RE JUST LIKE ME <br>IS IT IN OUR NATURE TO BE STUCK ON REPEAT <br>ANOTHER ENCORE TO AN AFTER SHOW <br>DO I CHASE THE NIGHT OR DOES THE NIGHT CHASE ME <br>MIRRORING SITUATIONS <br>ACCURATE IMITATION <br>DO I WATCH AND REPEAT <br>AND AS IF I TRIED TO <br>I’VE TURNED OUT JUST LIKE YOU <br>DO WE WATCH AND REPEAT <br>THEY ALL SAY <br>I WILL BECOME A REPLICA <br>YOUR MISTAKES <br>WERE ONLY CHEMICAL <br>DO I CHASE THE NIGHT OR DOES THE NIGHT CHASE ME <br>DO I CHASE THE NIGHT OR DOES THE NIGHT CHASE ME <br>THEY ALL SAY <br>I’LL BECOME A REPLICA <br>YOUR MISTAKES <br>WERE ONLY CHEMICAL]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="Replica" label="Replica"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Performance/</id><title>The XX - Performance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Performance/" title="The XX - Performance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[IF I SCREAM AT THE TOP OF MY LUNGS <br>WILL YOU HEAR WHAT I DON’T SAY <br>IF I DANCE LIKE I’M ON A STAGE <br>WILL YOU SEE <br>I SEEM OUT OF PLACE <br>IF I PUT ON A DISGUISE <br>WILL YOU THINK EVERYTHING’S ALRIGHT <br>IF I LEAVE BEFORE THE END <br>WILL YOU FORGET THAT I WAS THERE <br>WHEN YOU SAW ME LEAVING <br>DID YOU THINK I HAD A PLACE TO GO <br>SINCE YOU STOPPED BELIEVING <br>I’VE HAD TO PUT ON MY OWN SHOW <br>I’LL PUT ON A PERFORMANCE <br>I’LL PUT ON A SHOW <br>IT IS A PERFORMANCE <br>I DO IT ALL SO <br>YOU WON’T SEE ME HURTING <br>WHEN MY HEART IT BREAKS <br>I’LL PUT ON A PERFORMANCE <br>I’LL PUT ON A BRAVE FACE <br>EVEN WHEN I WAS HIDING <br>YOU COULD ALWAYS FIND ME <br>NOW YOU’VE STOPPED LOOKING FOR ME <br>BUT I’M STILL PLAYING HIDE AND SEEK <br>I WANT YOU TO NOTICE <br>BUT YOU JUST DON’T SEE <br>THE SHOW IS WASTED ON YOU <br>SO I PERFORM FOR ME <br>WHEN YOU SAW ME LEAVING <br>DID YOU THINK I HAD A PLACE TO GO <br>SINCE YOU STOPPED BELIEVING <br>I’VE HAD TO PUT ON MY OWN SHOW <br>I’LL PUT ON A PERFORMANCE <br>I’LL PUT ON A SHOW <br>IT IS A PERFORMANCE <br>I DO IT ALL SO <br>YOU WON’T SEE ME HURTING <br>WHEN MY HEART IT BREAKS <br>I’LL PUT ON A PERFORMANCE <br>I’LL PUT ON A BRAVE FACE]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="Performance" label="Performance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/A_Violent_Noise/</id><title>The XX - A Violent Noise - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/A_Violent_Noise/" title="The XX - A Violent Noise - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If I'm beating every hand away <br><br>No one stays <br><br>I've got so cautious <br><br>And now I trip on every move I make <br><br>Let one play <br><br>To be that careless <br><br><br><br>With every kiss from a friend <br><br>With everything I pretend not to feel <br><br>Am I too high? Am I too proud? <br><br>Is the music too loud... for me to hear? <br><br><br><br>Now I go out <br><br>But every beat is a violent noise <br><br>Dries my eye <br><br>With every beat comes a violent noise <br><br>The melody sung <br><br>And I don't know the voice <br><br>Now I go out <br><br>But every beat is a violent noise <br><br><br><br>You've been staying out late <br><br>Trying your best to escape <br><br>I hope you find what you're looking for <br><br>Let a moment take place <br><br>Without running away <br><br>I hope you silence the noise <br><br><br><br>How could eyes this wide <br><br>Lose sight of a world outside? <br><br>I've looked away, cowardice <br><br>With every kiss from a friend <br><br>With everything I pretend not to feel <br><br>Am I too high? Am I too proud? <br><br>Is the music too loud... for me to hear? <br><br><br><br>Now I go out <br><br>But every beat is a violent noise <br><br>Dries my eye <br><br>With every beat comes a violent noise <br><br>The melody sung <br><br>And I don't know the voice <br><br>Now I go out <br><br>But every beat is a violent noise]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="A Violent Noise" label="A Violent Noise"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Lips/</id><title>The XX - Lips - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Lips/" title="The XX - Lips - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Intro: Trio Mediaeval] <br><br>Just your love <br><br>Just your shadow <br><br>Just your voice <br><br>And my soul <br><br>Just your love <br><br>Just your shadow <br><br>Just your voice <br><br>And my soul <br><br>Just your lips <br><br><br><br>[Verse 1: Romy Madley Croft] <br><br>My name on your lips <br><br>Your air in my lungs <br><br>Drowned in oxygen <br><br>Now you've set the scene <br><br>High on intimacy <br><br>Drawing me above <br><br><br><br>[Pre-Chorus: Romy Madley Croft] <br><br>Ooh, ooh <br><br>I don’t wanna know the way down <br><br>Ooh, ooh <br><br>I don’t wanna know the way down <br><br><br><br>[Chorus: Romy Madley Croft + Oliver Sim + Trio Mediaeval] <br><br>Just your love <br><br>I just want it all <br><br>Just your shadow <br><br>Just your voice <br><br>I just want it all <br><br>And my soul <br><br>In my head, in my veins <br><br>In the way you give and take <br><br>In the weight that you weigh <br><br>On my body, on my brain <br><br><br><br>[Verse 2: Oliver Sim] <br><br>Chemistry is rare in a two, three？time affair <br><br>There's no guarantees <br><br>Working through the seasons, pressed up against the ceiling <br><br>Pushing down on me <br><br><br><br>[Pre-Chorus: Oliver Sim] <br><br>Ooh, ooh <br><br>I don't wanna know the way down <br><br>Ooh, ooh <br><br>I don't wanna know the way down <br><br><br><br>[Chorus: Romy Madley Croft + Oliver Sim + Trio Mediaeval] <br><br>Just your love <br><br>I just want it all <br><br>Just your shadow <br><br>Just your voice <br><br>I just want it all <br><br>And my soul <br><br>In my head, in my veins <br><br>In the way you give and take <br><br>In the weight that you weigh <br><br>On my body, on my brain <br><br><br><br>[Outro: Trio Mediaeval + Oliver Sim] <br><br>Just your neck <br><br>Just your eyes <br><br>Just your desire <br><br>Just your love and my soul <br><br>Just your love <br><br>Just your shadow <br><br>Just your voice <br><br>And my soul <br><br>Just your love <br><br>Just your shadow <br><br>Just your voice <br><br>And my soul <br><br>I don't wanna know the way down]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="Lips" label="Lips"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Say_Something_Loving/</id><title>The XX - Say Something Loving - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Say_Something_Loving/" title="The XX - Say Something Loving - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[SAY SOMETHING LOVING <br>I JUST DON’T REMEMBER <br>THE THRILL OF AFFECTION <br>I JUST DON’T REMEMBER <br>SAY SOMETHING LOVING <br>I NEED A REMINDER <br>THE FEELING’S ESCAPED ME <br>I WENT LOOKING FOR IT <br>COULD HAVE BEEN ANYONE’S KISS <br>THROWING MY ARMS AT NO ONE <br>WHEN I GAVE UP I FOUND LOVE <br>THE THOUGHT FLOWS THROUGH MY MIND <br>AND IT’S GROWING ALL THE TIME <br>I DO MYSELF A DISSERVICE <br>TO FEEL THIS WEAK <br>TO BE THIS NERVOUS <br>YOU SAY SOMETHING LOVING <br>IT’S SO OVERWHELMING <br>THE THRILL OF AFFECTION <br>FEELS SO UNFAMILIAR <br>YOU SAY SOMETHING LOVING <br>WITHOUT HESITATION <br>IT HITS ME HITS ME <br>IT FEELS SO UNFAMILIAR <br>YOUR TOUCH STAYS ON MY SKIN <br>I FEEL IT START SINKING IN <br>HERE COME MY INSECURITIES <br>I ALMOST EXPECT YOU TO LEAVE <br>WERE YOU REALLY LOOKING FOR ME <br>TRY YOUR BEST TO REASSURE ME <br>I WAS IMPATIENT TO MEET YOU <br>AM I TOO NEEDY <br>AM I TOO EAGER <br>I DON’T KNOW <br>I DON’T KNOW <br>I DON’T KNOW <br>I DON’T KNOW <br>WHAT THIS IS BUT IT DOESN’T FEEL WRONG <br>DID YOU HEAR ME SAY IT <br>SAY IT <br>DID YOU HEAR ME SAY <br>I SAY SOMETHING LOVING <br>I CAN’T HOLD IT INSIDE <br>THE THRILL OF AFFECTION <br>IS ONLY GETTING STRONGER <br>I SAY SOMETHING LOVING <br>ALL MY HESITATIONS ARE FADING FADING <br>I FEEL IT TAKING OVER <br>DON’T LET IT SLIP AWAY <br>DON’T LET IT SLIP AWAY]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="Say Something Loving" label="Say Something Loving"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Dangerous/</id><title>The XX - Dangerous - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:51:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:51:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_XX/Dangerous/" title="The XX - Dangerous - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Verse 1: Oliver Sim] <br><br>They say we're in danger <br><br>But I disagree <br><br>If proven wrong, shame on me <br><br>But you've had faith in me <br><br>So I won't shy away <br><br>Should it all fall down <br><br>You'll have been my favourite mistake <br><br><br><br>[Chorus: Romy Madley Croft + Oliver Sim] <br><br>They say <br><br>You are dangerous, but I don't care <br><br>I'm going to pretend that I'm not scared <br><br>If this only ends in tears <br><br>Then I won't say goodbye <br><br>'Cause I couldn't care less <br><br>If they call us reckless <br><br>Until they are breathless <br><br>They must be blind <br><br><br><br>[Verse 2: Romy Madley Croft] <br><br>There are voices ringing over <br><br>They keep saying, "Danger, danger" <br><br>I can't make them take you under <br><br>Makes no difference <br><br>No one can take this away <br><br>Should it all fall down, I'll treasure each day <br><br><br><br>[Chorus: Romy Madley Croft + Oliver Sim] <br><br>They say <br><br>You are dangerous, but I don't care <br><br>I'm going to pretend that I'm not scared <br><br>If this only ends in tears <br><br>Then I won't say goodbye <br><br>'Cause I couldn't… <br><br>'Cause I couldn't care less <br><br>If they call us reckless <br><br>Until they are breathless <br><br>They must be blind <br><br><br><br>[Bridge: Romy Madley Croft + Oliver Sim] <br><br>Let them say there are warning signs <br><br>They must be blind <br><br>They must be blind <br><br>They say <br><br><br><br>[Outro: Oliver Sim] <br><br>If this only ends in tears <br><br>Then I won't say goodbye]]></content><category term="The XX" label="The XX"/><category term="Dangerous" label="Dangerous"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Black_Coast/Feel_Something_Feat_Remmi/</id><title>Black Coast - Feel Something (Feat. Remmi) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:53:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:53:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Black_Coast/Feel_Something_Feat_Remmi/" title="Black Coast - Feel Something (Feat. Remmi) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Chest bones fall and rising like a million times <br>A million mornings waking to you in this light <br>Ahhh <br>And everything lies asleep in these streets <br>But the sun's rising <br>And it can redeem you and me <br>Don't you wanna feel something <br><br>And oh I miss loving you <br>But I need to live my own truth <br>I wanna feel it all brand new <br>I found a little something from Miss Angelou <br><br>This path is difficult we travel on <br>Knowing when it's time to move along <br>No we can't stay in the same place <br>Where the light fades away a little every day <br>Take the good and hold it near to you <br>And let go of all that burdens you <br>No we can't stay in the same place <br>Yeah it's brand new, but oh it's gonna be okay <br><br>Desert air <br>The hot despair of summertime <br>Dreams that kept you warm through all those winter nights <br>Ahhh <br>And everything is moving <br>But the dust settles on you and me <br>Lose control to this LA heat <br>Don't you wanna feel something <br><br>And oh I miss loving you <br>But I need to live my own truth <br>I wanna feel it all brand new <br>I found a little something from Miss Angelou <br><br>This path is difficult we travel on <br>Knowing when it's time to move along <br>No we can't stay in the same place <br>Where the light fades away a little every day <br>Take the good and hold it near to you <br>And let go of all that burdens you <br>No we can't stay in the same place <br>Yeah it's brand new, but oh it's gonna be okay]]></content><category term="Black Coast" label="Black Coast"/><category term="Feel Something (Feat. Remmi)" label="Feel Something (Feat. Remmi)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/잇상/닫힌_마음의_편지/</id><title>잇상 - 닫힌 마음의 편지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:53:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:53:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%87%EC%83%81/%EB%8B%AB%ED%9E%8C_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%98_%ED%8E%B8%EC%A7%80/" title="잇상 - 닫힌 마음의 편지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[말하려 해도 이미 굳어버린 나 <br>안으려 해도 이미 식어버린 마음 <br>너에게 기대 울고 싶은 내 맘과는 <br>다른 모습 <br>숨기려 해도 이미 넘쳐버린 나 <br>안기려 해도 타 들어가버린 마음 <br>너에게 안겨 울고 싶은 내 맘과는 <br>다른 표정 <br>스며드는 그리움을 <br>웃어 넘긴 만큼 <br>쓸 말이 많은 거죠 <br>밀려오는 외로움을 <br>쓸어 넘긴 만큼 <br>날 웃게 해줄 편지 <br>멀어져 가는 날 웃게 해줄 편지 <br>]]></content><category term="잇상" label="잇상"/><category term="닫힌 마음의 편지" label="닫힌 마음의 편지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leanne__Naara/New_York_And_Back/</id><title>Leanne &amp; Naara - New York And Back - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:54:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:54:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Leanne__Naara/New_York_And_Back/" title="Leanne &amp; Naara - New York And Back - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do you see the moon <br>How bright it shines for you <br>Leaving tiny bits of silver across the horizon <br>And look at the stars <br>Sweeping in to the dark <br>Oh darling, I must say <br>It's a beautiful night <br><br>And we'll always have a city <br>That never ever sleeps <br>We'll always have <br>The warm breeze <br>The one and only place <br>Where dreams do come true <br>No matter how far I go <br>I know <br>I'll always have you <br>So I, I guess <br>I just want you to know <br>That I will always love you <br><br>To New York and back <br>I'll always love you <br>To New York and back <br><br>There's just something about the way <br>That you see the world <br>How it subtly translates into <br>Every little thing that you do <br>Your smile <br>Your walk <br>Even the smallest of talks <br>I thank the universe <br>For leading me to you <br><br>And we'll have a city <br>That never ever sleeps <br>And we'll always have <br>The warm breeze <br>The one and only place <br>Where dreams do come true <br>No matter how far I go <br>I know <br>I'll always have you <br>So I, I guess <br>I just want you to know <br>That I will always love you <br><br>To New York and back <br>I'll always love you <br>To New York and back <br>To New York and back]]></content><category term="Leanne &amp; Naara" label="Leanne &amp; Naara"/><category term="New York And Back" label="New York And Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/As_Lions/White_Flags/</id><title>As Lions - White Flags - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:54:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:54:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/As_Lions/White_Flags/" title="As Lions - White Flags - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Turn the lights out <br>Follow me to the edge now <br>Take your dreams and shut the world away <br>All you need is faith <br><br>No right time <br>To do or die, no difference <br>Step outside <br>Raise your voice and say <br>Sieze this day, the world is ours to take <br><br>White flags over the mountains <br>Lost out on good advice <br>Don't give up on what you know <br>It's worth the price <br>Can you ever forget that nothing stays the same <br>White flags over the mountains <br>They will fade away <br><br>As we look up <br>Are we that close? <br>Will you reach out <br>Or let it go? <br>This road is what you choose <br>One you win or lose <br><br>Let it out <br>And set it free <br>And on this day, your history <br>Is plain for all to see <br>Make your mark, take your destiny <br><br>White flags over the mountains <br>Lost out on good advice <br>Don't give up on what you know <br>It's worth the price <br>Can you ever forget that nothing stays the same <br>White flags over the mountains <br>They will fade away <br><br>I've exhausted my solutions, seen my patience turn to rage <br>The only thing to keep us strong is faith <br><br>White flags over the mountains <br>Lost out on good advice <br>Don't give up on what you know <br>It's worth the price <br>Can you ever forget that nothing stays the same <br>White flags over the mountains <br>They will fade away <br><br>Because the only thing to keep us strong <br>The only thing to keep us strong <br>Is faith]]></content><category term="As Lions" label="As Lions"/><category term="White Flags" label="White Flags"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bbs/Rewind_Feat_Kean_Cipriano/</id><title>Bbs - Rewind (Feat. Kean Cipriano) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:54:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:54:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bbs/Rewind_Feat_Kean_Cipriano/" title="Bbs - Rewind (Feat. Kean Cipriano) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Summer, sunset <br>We are lost before the sunrise <br>Won't you regret <br>If you choose not to be mine <br><br>I wanna be with you <br>I wanna bleed with you <br>I wanna stay with you <br><br>Hey <br>This is what you want <br>This is all I need <br>This doesn't seem so hopeless <br>You're the air I breathe <br>I wanna be with you <br>You wanna bleed with me <br>I wanna stay with you <br><br>Rewind, regram <br>Pictures of you stayed in my mind <br>You choose to smile <br>Did you see the stars in my eyes <br><br>I wanna be with you <br>I wanna bleed with you <br>I wanna stay with you <br><br>Hey <br>This is what you want <br>This is all I need <br>This doesn't seem so hopeless <br>You're the air I breathe <br>I wanna be with you <br>You wanna bleed with me <br>I wanna stay with you <br><br>Hey <br>This is what I want <br>This is what we need <br>This feeling is not helpless <br>I'll let you take the lead <br>I wanna be with you <br>You wanna bleed with me <br>I wanna stay with you <br><br>I wanna be with you <br>I wanna bleed with you <br>I wanna stay with you <br>I wanna be with you <br>I wanna be with you <br>I wanna be with you]]></content><category term="Bbs" label="Bbs"/><category term="Rewind (Feat. Kean Cipriano)" label="Rewind (Feat. Kean Cipriano)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/반하나/가슴아_그만해/</id><title>반하나 - 가슴아 그만해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:55:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:55:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%98%ED%95%98%EB%82%98/%EA%B0%80%EC%8A%B4%EC%95%84_%EA%B7%B8%EB%A7%8C%ED%95%B4/" title="반하나 - 가슴아 그만해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하늘이 붉어지다 <br>이내 어두워진다 <br>내 눈물엔 별빛이 드리운다 <br>소리 내어 널 <br>부를 용기조차 없었기에 <br>고작 이렇게 <br>눈물만 또 떨구네 <br>하필 너야 <br>다른 사랑 있는데 <br>이러면 더 나만 아플걸 아는데 <br>왜 내 맘은 자꾸 <br>고개 돌려도 널 향해 <br>제발 웃지마 <br>내 맘 돌릴 수 있게 <br>가슴아 제발 그만해 <br>나 미칠 것 같아 <br>멋대로 뛰는데 왜 <br>그는 이미 다른 사랑에 <br>웃는데 난 <br>그 미소에 가슴 뛰는지 <br>바보같이 난 <br>하필 너야 <br>다른 사랑 있는데 <br>이러면 더 나만 아플걸 아는데 <br>왜 내 맘은 자꾸 <br>고개 돌려도 널 향해 <br>제발 웃지마 <br>내 맘 돌릴 수 있게 <br>가슴아 제발 그만해 <br>나 미칠 것 같아 <br>멋대로 뛰는데 왜 <br>그는 이미 다른 사랑에 <br>웃는데 난 <br>그 미소에 가슴 뛰는지 <br>바보같이 난 <br>이별조차 허락될 수 없는 사랑에 <br>다가갈 수도 물러설 수도 없었어 <br>이렇게 나 아픈데 <br>여전히 가슴이 뛰는 나 <br>내 맘 내가 어쩌지 못해 <br>가슴아 제발 그만해 <br>나 미칠 것 같아 <br>멋대로 뛰는데 왜 <br>그는 이미 다른 사랑에 <br>웃는데 난 <br>그 미소에 가슴 뛰는지 <br>가슴아 제발 그만해 <br>나 미칠 것 같아 <br>멋대로 뛰는데 왜 <br>그는 이미 다른 사랑에 <br>웃는데 난 <br>그 미소에 가슴 뛰는지 <br>바보같이 난 <br>]]></content><category term="반하나" label="반하나"/><category term="가슴아 그만해" label="가슴아 그만해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아웃오브캠퍼스/기억/</id><title>아웃오브캠퍼스 - 기억 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:55:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:55:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EC%9B%83%EC%98%A4%EB%B8%8C%EC%BA%A0%ED%8D%BC%EC%8A%A4/%EA%B8%B0%EC%96%B5/" title="아웃오브캠퍼스 - 기억 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈부신 햇살과 나리는 비에도 <br>우리는 모여서 <br>이야기를 만들었지 <br>아무도 모르게 흐르는 시간에 <br>우리는 모여서 <br>이야기를 만들었지 <br>커져간 오해와 줄어든 대화에 <br>서로를 미워한 시간도 있지만 <br>미워한 시간과 조그만 대화에 <br>서로를 이해한 시간도 있었지 <br>눈부신 햇살과 나리는 빗물도 <br>함께 할 수 없는 <br>현실을 만나게 됐지 <br>아무도 모르게 흘러온 시간에 <br>함께 할 수 없는 <br>현실을 만나게 됐지 <br>눈처럼 쌓여간 함께한 시간도 <br>뜨거운 현실에 녹은 듯하지만 <br>눈처럼 쌓여간 우리의 기억은 <br>뜨거운 현실 속 날 위로하겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="아웃오브캠퍼스" label="아웃오브캠퍼스"/><category term="기억" label="기억"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cosmos_Midnight/History/</id><title>Cosmo`s Midnight - History - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:55:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:55:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Cosmos_Midnight/History/" title="Cosmo`s Midnight - History - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[From another life <br>I thought of you I can't deny <br>But the minute that I realized <br>That you were means to an end <br>And I wasn't gonna pretend <br>Then you ran and reappeared <br>You're no longer just a souvenir <br>Taking all the words I wanna hear <br>Your hands wandering in the cab <br>And now you can't take it back <br>'Cause we got too much history <br>And all you wanna do is fuck with me <br>But we got too much history <br>Too wake up in my bed <br>With you lying next to me <br>With you lying next to me oh oh <br>With you lying next to me me <br>'Cause we got too much history <br>With you lying next to me <br>With you lying next to me oh oh <br>With you lying next to me me <br>'Cause we got too much history <br>Your every wish is my command <br>With the Gin and tonic in your hand <br>Only words that me <br>and you can understand <br>But then when nobody knows <br>We're already in the cab home <br>'Cause we got too much history <br>And all you wanna do is fuck with me <br>But we got too much history <br>Too wake up in my bed <br>With you lying next to me <br>With you lying next to me oh oh <br>With you lying next to me me <br>'Cause we got too much history <br>With you lying next to me <br>With you lying next to me oh oh <br>With you lying next to me me <br>'Cause we got too much history <br>With you lying next to me <br>With you lying next to me oh oh <br>With you lying next to me me <br>'Cause we got too much history <br>We got to much <br>History oh <br>We got to much <br>History yeah <br>]]></content><category term="Cosmo`s Midnight" label="Cosmo`s Midnight"/><category term="History" label="History"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로큰_발렌타인/Run_Vocal_by_Byun_Sunghwan/</id><title>브로큰 발렌타인 - Run (Vocal by Byun Sunghwan) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:55:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:55:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%ED%81%B0_%EB%B0%9C%EB%A0%8C%ED%83%80%EC%9D%B8/Run_Vocal_by_Byun_Sunghwan/" title="브로큰 발렌타인 - Run (Vocal by Byun Sunghwan) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[차라리 그땐 편했어 <br>처음부터 그랬다고 <br>그게 바로 나라고 <br>하지만 견딜 수 없었어 <br>내 속의 나의 늪에서 <br>허우적거릴 뿐 <br>Run away out of here <br>Ride the wind ride the flow <br>Run away out of here <br>Ride the wind ride the flow <br>차라리 그땐 편했어 <br>처음부터 그냥 그렇게 <br>날 위로했지 <br>하지만 견딜 수 없었어 <br>기억조차 희미한 <br>무언가를 기다려 <br>Run away out of here <br>Ride the wind ride the flow <br>Run away out of here <br>Ride the wind ride the flow <br>Run away out of here <br>Ride the wind ride the flow <br>Run away out of here <br>Ride the wind ride the flow <br>Run away run away <br>난 나를 태워 가겠어 <br>Run away run away <br>잊혀진 나의 꿈으로 <br>]]></content><category term="브로큰 발렌타인" label="브로큰 발렌타인"/><category term="Run (Vocal by Byun Sunghwan)" label="Run (Vocal by Byun Sunghwan)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로큰_발렌타인/無題_noname_part_2_Feat_허균_of_Hash/</id><title>브로큰 발렌타인 - 無題 (noname part 2.) (Feat. 허균 of Hash) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:55:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:55:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%ED%81%B0_%EB%B0%9C%EB%A0%8C%ED%83%80%EC%9D%B8/%E7%84%A1%E9%A1%8C_noname_part_2_Feat_%ED%97%88%EA%B7%A0_of_Hash/" title="브로큰 발렌타인 - 無題 (noname part 2.) (Feat. 허균 of Hash) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[항상 돌아오는 길은 <br>같은 길인데 <br>익숙하지 못한 괴로움들 <br>처음엔 아득했던 <br>그 뒤엔 분노가 <br>이제는 슬픔만이 남았네 <br>흐린 이 세상 위에 <br>흐린 이 시간 속에 <br>나조차도 모르게 <br>당연했던 모든 게 <br>너무나도 당연하게 <br>사라져버렸네 <br>믿어버리기엔 <br>난 너무 겁이 많았고 <br>믿지 않기에는 <br>지켜야 할 것들이 있었네 <br>흐린 이 세상 위에 <br>흐린 이 시간 속에 <br>내가 이대로일게 <br>알지 못한 채 서 있을게 <br>항상 이런 나일게 <br>같은 아픔 안에 있을게 <br>뭐가 그렇게도 <br>많이 참기 힘든지 <br>더 이상 참기 힘든 <br>너의 옷깃을 잡네 <br>우리는 어느샌가 <br>우리도 모르게 <br>알 수 없는 이곳으로 <br>빠져버린 걸까 <br>흐린 이 세상 위에 <br>흐린 이 시간 속에 <br>내가 이대로일게 <br>알지 못한 채 서 있을게 <br>항상 이런 나일게 <br>같은 아픔 안에 있을게 <br>내가 이대로일게 <br>알지 못한 나인 채로 <br>이 자리에 서 있을게 <br>항상 이런 나일게 <br>같은 아픔 안에서도 <br>여전히 나 아파할게 <br>내가 이대로일게 <br>내가 나이도록 허락된 <br>그 시간이 지난다 해도 <br>항상 이런 나일게 <br>오 나에겐 너에게 그렇게 <br>지금도 이대로일게 <br>이대로일게 <br>]]></content><category term="브로큰 발렌타인" label="브로큰 발렌타인"/><category term="無題 (noname part 2.) (Feat. 허균 of Hash)" label="無題 (noname part 2.) (Feat. 허균 of Hash)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브로큰_발렌타인/Justice_For_Them_Feat_노대건_of_Bursters/</id><title>브로큰 발렌타인 - Justice For Them (Feat. 노대건 of Bursters) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:55:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:55:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A1%9C%ED%81%B0_%EB%B0%9C%EB%A0%8C%ED%83%80%EC%9D%B8/Justice_For_Them_Feat_%EB%85%B8%EB%8C%80%EA%B1%B4_of_Bursters/" title="브로큰 발렌타인 - Justice For Them (Feat. 노대건 of Bursters) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You buried everyone <br>and you say I'm just victim' <br>너의 어제는 오늘 <br>너에게 용서를 얻었나 <br>Imitation Convenient tears <br>네 손에 가득한 <br>냄새를 지워내려 <br>이상도 선도 지웠나 <br>Fake tears <br>You dancing on the grave <br>This is justice for them <br>To be yourself <br>you create the enemy <br>This is justice for them <br>One day you will be suffocated <br>by your mask <br>비춰진 갈기 <br>내려놓지는 못하는 <br>너의 거울은 지금 <br>뭘로 덮여 있는가 <br>죄책감은 이미 잘라 <br>씹어 삼켰는가 <br>결여됨을 진화라 믿는가 <br>Fake tears <br>You dancing on the grave <br>This is justice for them <br>To be yourself <br>you create the enemy <br>This is justice for them <br>One day you will be suffocated <br>by your mask <br>기워진 시련 <br>재단된 품격 <br>너의 자화상 속의 <br>벼려낸 미소 <br>손댈 수 없는 <br>깃발에 가려 <br>오늘도 너는 너의 <br>모든 죄를 쉽게 사한다 <br>This is justice for them <br>To be yourself <br>you create the enemy <br>This is justice for them <br>One day you will be suffocated <br>by your mask <br>]]></content><category term="브로큰 발렌타인" label="브로큰 발렌타인"/><category term="Justice For Them (Feat. 노대건 of Bursters)" label="Justice For Them (Feat. 노대건 of Bursters)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/rimi/오래오래/</id><title>rimi - 오래오래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:56:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:56:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/rimi/%EC%98%A4%EB%9E%98%EC%98%A4%EB%9E%98/" title="rimi - 오래오래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 살고파 난 <br>오래도록 음악을 하고파 난 <br>올해 안에 성공을 하고파 <br>헌금을 많이 거둬 <br>성당을 쌓고파 난 <br>지긋지긋하지 가난은 <br>화가나 화가 나 난 <br>못 이룬 내 자신에 <br>올해 안에 난 필히 정상에 닿고파 <br>난 상위 언제나 난 상위 <br>남의 밑에선 만족을 못 느끼니 <br>여성상위 여성상위 라고 하지 <br>나는 대부분의 남자애들 위니 <br>내 자신이 내 자신을 <br>바른 길로 이끌지니 <br>내 자신이 내 소원을 듣고 <br>이뤄주는 지니 <br>먼 길을 가기 위해 <br>죽은 몸을 일으키지 <br>다신 죽지 않으리 라며 <br>큰 기지개를 켜지 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>요리 요리하기 싫어 <br>요리하기 싫어 <br>나는 매일같이 <br>빨래하고 청소하기 싫어 <br>되도 않는 형편에 결혼하고 <br>애를 낳아서 그 애도 <br>거지같이 기르기는 싫어 <br>거지 같은 음식을 입에 달고 살다 <br>사오십 대쯤에 암에 걸려 <br>일찍 죽기 싫어 <br>그래 그래 무엇 하나 무엇 하나 <br>못 이루기엔 나는 대단하고 <br>나의 삶은 길어 <br>나는 대단하고 나의 삶은 길어 <br>나는 대단하고 나의 삶은 길어 <br>나는 대단하고 나의 삶은 길어 <br>나는 대단하고 나의 삶은 <br>너무나도 길어 <br>이루리라 이루리라 <br>오늘을 바꾸리라 <br>오늘을 바꿈으로 <br>미래를 바꾸리라 <br>미래를 바꿈으로 <br>과거까지 바꾸리라 <br>바꾸네 난 바꾸네 <br>우주가 나서 도우리라 <br>역사를 바꾸리라 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 <br>오래 오래 오래 오래 오래 <br>]]></content><category term="rimi" label="rimi"/><category term="오래오래" label="오래오래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/찰리의_라디오/방화범/</id><title>찰리의 라디오 - 방화범 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:56:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:56:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%9D%98_%EB%9D%BC%EB%94%94%EC%98%A4/%EB%B0%A9%ED%99%94%EB%B2%94/" title="찰리의 라디오 - 방화범 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[여보세요 거기 119죠 <br>네 <br>누가 제 마음에 불을 질렀어요 <br>네 <br>누가 제 마음에 불을 질렀다구요 <br>장난 하지 마세요 <br>장난 아니에요 <br>니가 뭔데 맘에 불쑥 들어와 <br>내 몸 따위 다 줄게 무료봉사 <br>최신 폰에 번호 좀 남겨줄래 <br>지금부터 널 위한 <br>morning caller <br>오늘 밤엔 조금 더 취해도 돼 <br>책임 따윈 내가 다 질 테니까 <br>심장에 불을 낸 치명적 방화범 <br>불 난 집 부채질 해줄래 더더더 <br>나 뜨거뜨거 눈을 뜰 때마다 <br>낯 뜨거뜨거 방화범이야 <br>나 뜨거뜨거 불을 끌 때마다 <br>낯 뜨거뜨거 방화범이야 <br>방화범이야 <br>니가 뭔데 맘에 불쑥 들어와 <br>내 몸 따위 다 줄게 기부천사 <br>뭐 먹을래 뭐든지 사다 줄게 <br>내 지갑은 널 위한 푸드코트 <br>연금복권 기대 할 필요 없어 <br>내가 바로 일등복권이니까 <br>나 뜨거뜨거 눈을 뜰 때마다 <br>낯 뜨거뜨거 방화범이야 <br>나 뜨거뜨거 불을 끌 때마다 <br>낯 뜨거뜨거 방화범이야 <br>요리조리 놀이하고 <br>하고 싶은 불 붙는 노래 <br>나 뜨거뜨거 눈을 뜰 때마다 <br>낯 뜨거뜨거 방화범이야 <br>나 뜨거뜨거 불을 끌 때마다 <br>낯 뜨거뜨거 방화범이야 <br>나 뜨거뜨거 눈을 뜰 때마다 <br>낯 뜨거뜨거 방화범이야 <br>나 뜨거뜨거 불을 끌 때마다 <br>낯 뜨거뜨거 <br>요리 조리 놀이 <br>노래 놀자 요리조리 <br>요리 조리 놀이 <br>노래 놀자 요리조리 <br>방화범이야 <br>여보세요 거기 119죠 <br>아까 신고한 거 <br>취소하려고 하는데요 <br>제 마음에 불 낸 <br>그 여자를 잡았거든요 <br>]]></content><category term="찰리의 라디오" label="찰리의 라디오"/><category term="방화범" label="방화범"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Little_Jimmy_Scott/Day_By_Day/</id><title>Little Jimmy Scott - Day By Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:57:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:57:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Little_Jimmy_Scott/Day_By_Day/" title="Little Jimmy Scott - Day By Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Day by day I'm falling more in love with you <br>And day by day my love seems to grow <br>There isn't any end to my devotion <br>It's deeper dear by far than any ocean <br><br>I find that day by day you're making all my dreams come true <br>So come what may I want you to know <br>I'm yours alone and I'm in love to stay <br>As we go through the years day by day]]></content><category term="Little Jimmy Scott" label="Little Jimmy Scott"/><category term="Day By Day" label="Day By Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rev_James_Cleveland/I_Will_Wear_A_Crown/</id><title>Rev. James Cleveland - I Will Wear A Crown - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:57:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:57:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rev_James_Cleveland/I_Will_Wear_A_Crown/" title="Rev. James Cleveland - I Will Wear A Crown - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Watch ye therefore <br>You know not the day <br>When the Lord shall <br>Call your soul away <br>If you're Fighting <br>Striving for the right <br>Ye shall wear a robe and crown <br><br>I'm shall wear a crown 2x <br>When that trumpet sounds 2x <br>Oh, I shall wear a crown <br>I shall wear a crown <br>I shall wear a golden crown <br>Soon as my feet strike Zion <br>Gonna lay down my heavy burden <br>Put on my robe in glory <br>Shout and tell my story <br>Move over hills and mountains <br>Unto the chrystal fountain <br>All of God's sons and daughters <br>Will be drinking that ole' healing waters <br>I'm gonna move on up a little higher 4x <br>We shall wear a golden and crown]]></content><category term="Rev. James Cleveland" label="Rev. James Cleveland"/><category term="I Will Wear A Crown" label="I Will Wear A Crown"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rev_James_Cleveland/Peace_Be_Still/</id><title>Rev. James Cleveland - Peace Be Still - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:57:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:57:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rev_James_Cleveland/Peace_Be_Still/" title="Rev. James Cleveland - Peace Be Still - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Master, the tempest is raging <br>The billows are tossing high <br>The sky is o'er shadowed with blackness <br>No shelter or help is nigh <br><br>Carest Thou not that we perish <br>How canst Thou lie asleep <br>When each moment so madly is threatening <br>A grave in the angry deep <br><br>The winds and the waves shall obey my will, peace be still <br>Whether the wrath of the storm tossed sea <br>Or demons or men or whatever it be <br>No water can swallow the ship where lies <br><br>The Master of ocean and earth and skies <br>They shall sweetly obey my will <br>Peace be still, peace be still <br>They all shall sweetly obey my will, peace, peace be still <br><br>Master, with anguish of spirit <br>I bow in my grief today <br>The depths of my sad heart are troubled <br>Oh, waken and save, I pray <br><br>Torrents of sin and of anguish <br>Sweep o'er my sinking soul <br>And I perish, I perish, dear Master <br>Oh, hasten and take control <br><br>The winds and the waves shall obey my will, peace be still <br>Whether the wrath of the storm tossed sea <br>Or demons or men or whatever it be <br>No water can swallow the ship where lies <br><br>The Master of ocean and earth and skies <br>They shall sweetly obey my will <br>Peace be still, peace be still <br>They all shall sweetly obey my will, peace, peace be still <br><br>Master, the terror is over <br>The elements sweetly rest <br>Earth's sun in the calm lake is mirrored <br>And heaven's within my breast <br><br>Linger, o blessed Redeemer <br>Leave me alone no more <br>And with joy I shall make the blest harbor <br>And rest on the blissful shore <br><br>The winds and the waves shall obey my will, peace be still <br>Whether the wrath of the storm tossed sea <br>Or demons or men or whatever it be <br>No water can swallow the ship where lies <br><br>The Master of ocean and earth and skies <br>They shall sweetly obey my will <br>Peace be still, peace be still <br>They all shall sweetly obey my will, peace, peace be still]]></content><category term="Rev. James Cleveland" label="Rev. James Cleveland"/><category term="Peace Be Still" label="Peace Be Still"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dinah_Washington/You_Dont_Know_What_Love_Is/</id><title>Dinah Washington - You Don`t Know What Love Is - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:57:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:57:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dinah_Washington/You_Dont_Know_What_Love_Is/" title="Dinah Washington - You Don`t Know What Love Is - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You don't know what love is until you've learned the meaning of the Blues <br>Until you've loved a love you had to lose <br>You don't know what love is <br><br>You don't know how lips burn until you've kissed and had to pay the cost <br>Until you've flipped your heart and you have lost <br>You don't know what love is <br><br>Do you know how a lost heart fears the thought of reminiscing <br>And lips that taste of tears lose their taste for kissing <br><br>You don't know how hearts ache for love that cannot live yet never dies <br>Until you've faced each dawn with sleepless eyes <br>You don't know what love is <br>You don't know what love is]]></content><category term="Dinah Washington" label="Dinah Washington"/><category term="You Don`t Know What Love Is" label="You Don`t Know What Love Is"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/창희/공연이_끝나고_Vocal_왕창엽/</id><title>창희 - 공연이 끝나고 (Vocal 왕창엽) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:57:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:57:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%BD%ED%9D%AC/%EA%B3%B5%EC%97%B0%EC%9D%B4_%EB%81%9D%EB%82%98%EA%B3%A0_Vocal_%EC%99%95%EC%B0%BD%EC%97%BD/" title="창희 - 공연이 끝나고 (Vocal 왕창엽) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[공연이 끝나고 <br>수고 했어 한마디 <br>괜스레 내 입가에 <br>미소 짓게 하네 <br>니가 해준 말들 <br>아무 의미 없겠지만 <br>난 하나하나 되새기며 <br>밤 지새웠지 <br>어쩌다 너와 함께 <br>그 밤길을 걸었을 때 <br>좋아한다고 하고 <br>싶었는데 <br>난 항상 너에게 <br>잘해주고 싶었는데 <br>그게 너를 불편하게 <br>할 준 몰랐어 <br>이제 모든 관심을 접고 <br>뒷모습만 보는 게 <br>난 두려웠을 뿐이야 <br>공연이 끝나고 <br>모두 모인 술자리 <br>넌 그 남자애 옆에 <br>앉아 웃고 떠들었지 <br>난 멀리서 앉아 <br>그 모습만 바라보다 <br>어느새 나도 모르게 <br>눈물 훔쳤었지 <br>술에 취해 용기 내 <br>다가가고 싶었었지만 <br>아무 말 못하고 <br>내 여름은 갔지 <br>난 항상 너에게 <br>잘해주고 싶었는데 <br>그게 너를 불편하게 <br>할 준 몰랐어 <br>이제 모든 관심을 접고 <br>뒷모습만 보는 게 <br>난 두려웠을 뿐인데 <br>넌 이제 나보다 <br>멋진 사람 만나겠지 <br>너만 행복하면 <br>난 괜찮을 것 같아 <br>너를 잡았던 손을 놓고 <br>니 갈 길 가는 게 <br>아마 널 위한 일 일거야 <br>난 두려웠을 뿐이야 <br>]]></content><category term="창희" label="창희"/><category term="공연이 끝나고 (Vocal 왕창엽)" label="공연이 끝나고 (Vocal 왕창엽)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/창희/다가갈_거야_Vocal_김혜민/</id><title>창희 - 다가갈 거야 (Vocal 김혜민) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:57:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:57:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%BD%ED%9D%AC/%EB%8B%A4%EA%B0%80%EA%B0%88_%EA%B1%B0%EC%95%BC_Vocal_%EA%B9%80%ED%98%9C%EB%AF%BC/" title="창희 - 다가갈 거야 (Vocal 김혜민) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 그 애에게 <br>문자 한통이 왔죠 <br>그댄 날 항상 <br>설레게 하죠 <br>밤새 내 맘에 <br>가득 채워진 말들 <br>난 잠이 들 수가 없었죠 <br>혹시 너도 나와 <br>같이 고민했을까 <br>너도 나와 <br>같은 마음일까 <br>고르고 골라 <br>용기 냈던 한마디 <br>우리 내일 만날까 <br>한 걸음 두 걸음 <br>너와 맞춘 발걸음 <br>이렇게 너와 <br>나를 맞춰갈 거야 <br>그래 한발 두발 <br>빛나는 너에게 <br>수줍은 나는 <br>조심스레 다가갈 거야 <br>밤새워 그렸던 <br>오늘이 드디어 왔죠 <br>그대 생각에 <br>웃음이 나죠 <br>가장 아끼는 <br>옷을 꺼내두고서 <br>난 잠이 들 수가 없었죠 <br>혹시 너도 나와 <br>같이 고민했을까 <br>너도 나와 <br>같은 마음일까 <br>매일 밤 너는 <br>내 꿈속에 나타나 <br>나의 손을 잡았지 <br>한 걸음 두 걸음 <br>너와 맞춘 발걸음 <br>이렇게 너와 <br>나를 맞춰갈 거야 <br>그래 한발 두발 <br>빛나는 너에게 <br>수줍은 나는 <br>조심스레 다가갈 거야 <br>한 걸음 두 걸음 <br>너와 맞춘 발걸음 <br>이렇게 너와 <br>나를 맞춰갈 거야 <br>그래 나의 맘속에 <br>간직했던 말들 <br>이제 용기 내 <br>너에게 다 말해줄 거야 <br>용기 내 <br>너에게로 다가갈 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="창희" label="창희"/><category term="다가갈 거야 (Vocal 김혜민)" label="다가갈 거야 (Vocal 김혜민)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Inez/Listen_To_Your_Heart/</id><title>Inez - Listen To Your Heart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:58:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:58:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Inez/Listen_To_Your_Heart/" title="Inez - Listen To Your Heart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know there's something in the wake of your smile <br>I get a notion from the look in your eyes <br>Yeah <br>Built the love, but that love falls apart <br>Your little peice of heaven turns too dark <br>Listen to your heart <br>When he's calling for you <br>Listen to your heart <br>There's nothing else you can do <br>I dont know where you're going and i don't know why <br>But listen to your heart <br>Before you tell him goodbye <br><br>Listen to your heart <br>Sometimes you wonder if this fight is worthwhile <br>The precious moments are a lost in the tide <br>Yeah <br>They're swept away and nothing is what it seems <br>The feeling of belonging to your dreams <br>Listen to your heart <br>When he's calling for you <br>Listen to your heart <br>There's nothing else you can do <br>I don't know where you're going and i don't know why <br>But listen to your heart <br>Before you tell him goodbye <br>Oh oh <br>Listen to your heart <br>Listen to your heart <br>When he's calling for you <br>Listen to your heart <br><br>There's nothing else you can do <br>I don't know where you're going and i don't know why <br>Listen to your heart <br>Before you tell him goodbye <br>And there are voices that want to be heard <br>So much to mention but you cant find the words <br>The sense of magic, the beauty that's been <br>When love was wilder than the wind <br>Oh oh <br>Listen to your heart <br>Listen to your heart <br>When he's calling for you calling for you <br>Listen to your heart <br>There's nothing else you can do <br>I don't where you're going and i don't know why <br>But listen to your heart <br>Before you tell him goodbye]]></content><category term="Inez" label="Inez"/><category term="Listen To Your Heart" label="Listen To Your Heart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/철원/살으리/</id><title>철원 - 살으리 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:59:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:59:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%A0%EC%9B%90/%EC%82%B4%EC%9C%BC%EB%A6%AC/" title="철원 - 살으리 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 생각에 길을 나서도 <br>내게 되돌아 오는 길 <br>그대 내 맘에 있는 이유로 <br>나는 날 사랑하고 있네 <br>나를 위하여 <br>나는 울지 않으리 <br>아파하지도 않으리 <br>그대 나에게 주었던 사랑을 <br>영원히 지키며 살으리 <br>사르리 사르리 <br>나의 영혼을 사르리 <br>살으리 살으리 <br>그대 사랑에 살으리 <br>그대 생각에 눈시울 적셔도 <br>나는 그대의 그림자 <br>그대 내 안에 사는 이유로 <br>나는 그댈 사랑하고 있네 <br>그댈 위하여 <br>나는 기도하리라 <br>나 오늘도 기도하리 <br>그대 나에게 주었던 사랑을 <br>영원히 지키며 살으리 <br>사르리 사르리 <br>나의 영혼을 사르리 <br>살으리 살으리 <br>그대 사랑에 살으리 <br>]]></content><category term="철원" label="철원"/><category term="살으리" label="살으리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Electric_Guest/Back_For_Me/</id><title>Electric Guest - Back For Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:59:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:59:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Electric_Guest/Back_For_Me/" title="Electric Guest - Back For Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Watched you drive away, you're back out on the road <br>Tried to make LA a second place for home <br>And I know we've got a thousand ways to go <br>And there's not much more I know I can control <br><br>Are you coming back for me <br>Hope you're coming back for me <br><br>Now you've got the time, remember who you are <br>Miles and miles from me, I feel it though you're far <br>And I know we've got a thousand ways to be <br>But it still won't do until you come for me <br><br>Are you coming back for me <br>Hope you're coming back for me <br>Coming back for me <br>Hope you're coming back for me <br><br>I always want you here <br>And I'm trying to find a reason, but I only want to hear <br><br>Coming back for me <br>Hope you're coming back for me <br>Coming back for me <br>Hope you're coming back for me <br><br>For now, I know I'm on my own <br>Until the day you call me home <br>For now, I know I'm on my own <br>Until the day you call me home]]></content><category term="Electric Guest" label="Electric Guest"/><category term="Back For Me" label="Back For Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GoldLink/Rough_Soul_Feat_April_George/</id><title>GoldLink - Rough Soul (Feat. April George) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:59:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:59:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/GoldLink/Rough_Soul_Feat_April_George/" title="GoldLink - Rough Soul (Feat. April George) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Had to go to LA for the winter <br>Had to vibe out <br>Just caught a tour to the <br>Real ni**a talk slick to ya <br>Told ya bring your girlfriend <br>tell her take her friends too <br>Telling Hollywood kinda weird <br>You don’t really like it <br>but you gotta play the <br>Yeah met ya last June <br>By next June we will <br>and f**k now <br>Fell in love at the wrong time <br>Spent a night at my high rise <br>Or hit me late on my hotline <br>Telling me you miss my homies <br>and your mama cry <br>Late night you’re <br>my boo thing yeah <br>You’re my <br>with the blue thing yeah <br>All praise to the most high leader <br>Dipped off in the heels <br>Girl you’re gone now <br>And oh baby <br>Don’t call me <br>don’t call me no more <br>Girl you’re gone now <br>And oh baby <br>Don’t call me <br>don’t call me no more <br>Went back to the homeland <br>Had to tell the ni**as <br>what I did in your hometown <br>Everybody know we probably <br>woulda made it last <br>But there you go <br>started tripping never <br>hit me back <br>Real ni**a went back <br>to the pimping <br>Started getting groovy <br>with the women I was hitting <br>Got a gold chain <br>and a nose ring <br>And a new watch <br>no tick but I always been a thug <br>Black boy with a black fade yeah <br>Got that when you did things <br>You was f**king <br>and you did dirt too <br>We was talking <br>but you never hit my phone booth <br>Moved up and I feel good s**t <br>Roll palm trees <br>and I made a hand for ya <br>Billboards around the city <br>with your face on it <br>But they ain’t never really know <br>what you been through <br>Stay dancing <br>where the hoes at huh <br>Why your homies <br>gotta go down huh <br>I ain’t trip <br>when I see you dance <br>at a show back in Feb <br>You trip but we don’t talk much <br>Girl you got me f**ked up <br>Real ni**a gotta get it <br>when he f**ked up <br>Fake ni**as like a new man <br>Just a little side joint <br>Always been a side joint <br>Alright joint <br>Girl you’re gone now <br>And oh baby <br>Don’t call me <br>don’t call me no more <br>Girl you’re gone now <br>And oh baby <br>Don’t call me <br>don’t call me no more <br>Girl you’re gone now <br>And oh baby <br>Don’t call me <br>don’t call me no more <br>Girl you’re gone now <br>And oh baby <br>Don’t call me <br>don’t call me no more <br>]]></content><category term="GoldLink" label="GoldLink"/><category term="Rough Soul (Feat. April George)" label="Rough Soul (Feat. April George)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/라라브라더스/겨울이다/</id><title>라라브라더스 - 겨울이다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:59:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:59:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%9D%BC%EB%9D%BC%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EB%8D%94%EC%8A%A4/%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8%EC%9D%B4%EB%8B%A4/" title="라라브라더스 - 겨울이다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[겨울이다 겨울이다 <br>기다렸던 나의 <br>겨울이 왔다 <br>라라브라더스 함께 <br>같이 소리 질러봐 <br>큰 소리로 세상을 향해 <br>다시 한 번 시작해보자 <br>ONE TWO LET'S GO <br>짜증나 정말 짜증나 <br>미치겠다 정말 추워서 <br>내 마음도 꽁꽁 <br>얼어 붙었죠 <br>나의 님은 어디 있나요 <br>짜증나 너무 짜증나 <br>온 세상이 커플 뿐이야 <br>정말 사랑하고 싶은 <br>이 겨울 내 반 쪽은 <br>어디 있을까 <br>이제 시작이야 <br>다시 시작이야 <br>외로웠던 과거 <br>모두 다 잊어 <br>소원 빌어보면 <br>나타나줄거야 <br>꿈에 그리던 사랑 <br>겨울이다 겨울이다 <br>기다렸던 나의 <br>겨울이 왔다 <br>움츠러든 어깰 펴고 <br>다시 일어나 <br>큰 소리를 질러봐 <br>겨울이다 겨울이다 <br>외로웠던 솔로들은 <br>모여라 <br>그깟 사랑 <br>어려운게 아니야 <br>활짝 마음 열어봐 <br>너무 지긋지긋 <br>방콕은 싫어 <br>솔로도 싫어 <br>이제는 나도 <br>가만 있지 않을거야 <br>내 눈 앞에 안 나타나면 <br>내가 너를 찾아서 <br>사랑 만들거야 <br>징글벨 아 징글벨 <br>아 종소리 하늘 높이 <br>울려 퍼지면 <br>두 손 잡고 내 품에 안고 <br>키스를 할거야 HO HO <br>하얀 눈이 오면 <br>하고 싶은 일들 <br>올해 겨울 다 <br>할 수 있을거야 <br>왠지 기분 좋아 <br>잘 될 것만 같아 <br>전부 다 이루어져라 <br>겨울이다 겨울이다 <br>기다렸던 나의 <br>겨울이 왔다 <br>움츠러든 어깰 펴고 <br>다시 일어나 <br>큰 소리를 질러봐 <br>겨울이다 겨울이다 <br>외로웠던 솔로들은 <br>모여라 <br>그깟 사랑 <br>어려운게 아니야 <br>활짝 마음 열어봐 <br>그깟 사랑 <br>어려운게 아니야 <br>활짝 마음 열어봐 <br>나의 겨울이 왔다 <br>]]></content><category term="라라브라더스" label="라라브라더스"/><category term="겨울이다" label="겨울이다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_Sweet_소울_스윗/Sweet_Holiday/</id><title>Soul Sweet (소울 스윗) - Sweet Holiday - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T16:59:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T16:59:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soul_Sweet_%EC%86%8C%EC%9A%B8_%EC%8A%A4%EC%9C%97/Sweet_Holiday/" title="Soul Sweet (소울 스윗) - Sweet Holiday - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[새하얀 햇살이 눈부신 <br>빛나는 오후와 <br>너의 Smile <br>눈빛 가득히 <br>너를 담으면 <br>맘에 번지는 포근함 <br>꿈보다 달콤한 순간들 <br>하루를 채우는 예쁜 말 <br>작은 목소리 <br>눈을 감으면 <br>사랑의 떨림이 스며와 <br>Sweet holiday <br>Sweetheart darling <br>내 맘을 다 녹여준 선물 <br>부드런 공기의 속삭임 <br>설레는 둘만의 <br>Sweetest time <br>나른한 오후를 두드린 <br>내 맘을 깨우는 목소리 <br>코 끝 스치는 <br>익숙한 향기 <br>매일 반가운 달콤함 <br>창밖에 흰 눈이 쌓이면 <br>커다란 소파에 기대어 <br>가까이 앉은 <br>꿈 같은 내게 <br>조심히 입맞춤 할 거야 <br>Sweet holiday <br>Sweetheart darling <br>내 맘을 다 녹여준 선물 <br>부드런 공기의 속삭임 <br>설레는 둘만의 <br>Sweetest time <br>]]></content><category term="Soul Sweet (소울 스윗)" label="Soul Sweet (소울 스윗)"/><category term="Sweet Holiday" label="Sweet Holiday"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scipinos_스키피노스/아수라_ASURA/</id><title>Scipinos (스키피노스) - 아수라 (ASURA) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:00:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:00:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scipinos_%EC%8A%A4%ED%82%A4%ED%94%BC%EB%85%B8%EC%8A%A4/%EC%95%84%EC%88%98%EB%9D%BC_ASURA/" title="Scipinos (스키피노스) - 아수라 (ASURA) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 눈깔이 <br>돌아가는 시점 <br>뭔가 단단히 <br>상처 받은 심정 <br>오랜만이야 이가 <br>갈리는 감정과 <br>죽여버리고 싶다는 <br>생각 속에 날 선 밤 <br>사랑해라 사랑해라 <br>그게 뭔데 Uh <br>잘해줘도 후회돼 <br>썩은 접대 Uh <br>4년동안 랩하면서 <br>어떻게 올라왔겠어 <br>나보다 앞선 놈 등짝 <br>찍으면서 왔지 Uh <br>같은 분야 남녀 없지 <br>그저 방해 되면 <br>죽이고 말지 살리지 않아 <br>이게 방식 <br>그저 방심 하며 웃어 <br>개무시 한 뒤 <br>격공하는 다른 앞뒤 <br>묻지마 살인 <br>그래 나는 이중인격 <br>다중인격의 다혈질 <br>일정량의 정신질환과 <br>잠 설침 <br>승부욕과 오기 <br>나루토 오의 <br>지는 꼴은 못 봐 <br>차라리 벗겨내라 표피 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>독기를 품었지 그래 아수라 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>모든걸 이겨내는 나는 아수라 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>독기를 품었지 그래 아수라 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>모든걸 이겨내는 나는 아수라 <br>나보고 가치만 <br>따진다고 했던 <br>날 모르는 사람이 <br>말 했던 <br>이병주는 Logout에서 <br>Log in해 <br>지금부터 이 Game의 <br>유저 그래 플레이어 <br>Ye 계속해서 느껴지는 고 <br>양감 <br>절대로 나는 되지 <br>못하죠 양반 <br>내게 만약에 총알과 <br>총이 있었다면 <br>조정간을 연발에다가 <br>놓고 난발 <br>동물에서 나름 인간 된 <br>불완전한 상태 <br>이 악무는 순간부터 <br>상식과 반대 <br>년이던 놈이던 들고 <br>있는 창과 방패 <br>부시는 건 일도 아냐 <br>전투준비 상태 <br>ah 틀을 넘어버린 생각과 <br>자만감 이상 다 <br>나를 수라도로 걷게 하는 <br>진정한 원동력 <br>Uh 심장을 뛰게 해주는 건 <br>사랑 따위가 아냐 <br>짓밟는 것 그게 다야 <br>아수라 아수라 아수라 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>독기를 품었지 그래 아수라 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>모든걸 이겨내는 나는 아수라 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>독기를 품었지 그래 아수라 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>모든걸 이겨내는 나는 아수라 <br>아수라 발발타 Ye <br>아수라 발발타 Ye <br>아수라 발발타 Ye <br>아수라 발발타 Ye <br>나는 성공해 성공해 <br>이겨 낼 거야 <br>지금의 내 현실 보다 <br>미래를 볼 거야 <br>내 삶은 변해 마음가짐에 <br>따라 변하지 그래서 <br>난 성공해 <br>매일 밤 6천만명이 <br>있는 무대에서 <br>랩하는 걸 생각해 <br>그때면 내 얼굴도 못 봐 <br>Yeah <br>아수라 아수라 <br>독기를 품었지 그래 아수라 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>모든걸 이겨내는 나는 아수라 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>독기를 품었지 그래 아수라 <br>아수라 아수라 <br>모든걸 이겨내는 나는 아수라 <br>]]></content><category term="Scipinos (스키피노스)" label="Scipinos (스키피노스)"/><category term="아수라 (ASURA)" label="아수라 (ASURA)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태사비애/Livelovelaugh_Feat_cinD/</id><title>태사비애 - Live.love.laugh (Feat. cinD) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:01:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:01:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%B9%84%EC%95%A0/Livelovelaugh_Feat_cinD/" title="태사비애 - Live.love.laugh (Feat. cinD) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[dream for your love <br>dream for yourself <br>그 꿈처럼 피어나는 향기가 <br>아름다워 너무 아름다워 <br>dream for your sun <br>dream for your moon <br>저 태양과 달빛처럼 환하게 <br>나를 보며 웃는 너 <br>사랑해 영원히 <br>넌 내게 하늘이준 선물이야 <br>반짝이는 밤하늘의 별처럼 <br>내 사랑을 비추는 달처럼 <br>I love u I want u <br>너무 소중 한 사람 <br>너는 내 운명 <br>I need u I wish u in my love <br>나는 너를 사랑해 <br>love you <br>you are my love my life <br>nothing can change it <br>stay with me forever <br>I love you <br>dream for your sea <br>dream for your sky <br>저 시원한 파도소리 들리니 <br>내 귓가에 속삭인 <br>너의 말 사랑해 <br>너를 위해 부르는 사랑노래 <br>하늘 위로 날아가는 새처럼 <br>사랑하는 사람의 꿈처럼 <br>I love u I want u <br>너무 소중한 사람 <br>너는 내 운명 <br>I need u I wish u in my love <br>나는 너를 사랑해 <br>love you <br>you are my love my life <br>nothing can change it <br>stay with me forever <br>I love you <br>사랑해 <br>you love me <br>나에겐 너뿐이야 <br>I want you need you <br>by myself <br>I need you babe babe <br>I need you babe babe <br>I love u I want u <br>너무 소중 한 사람 <br>너는 내 운명 <br>I need u I wish u in my love <br>나는 너를 사랑해 <br>love you <br>you are my love my life <br>nothing can change it <br>stay with me forever <br>I love you <br>dream for your sea <br>dream for your sky <br>저 시원한 파도소리 들리니 <br>내 귓가에 속삭인 <br>너의 말 사랑해 <br>너를 위해 부르는 사랑노래 <br>]]></content><category term="태사비애" label="태사비애"/><category term="Live.love.laugh (Feat. cinD)" label="Live.love.laugh (Feat. cinD)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daniel_Powter/Delicious/</id><title>Daniel Powter - Delicious - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:01:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:01:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Daniel_Powter/Delicious/" title="Daniel Powter - Delicious - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You look so delicious <br>The way your body moves <br>Cherry lipstick kisses <br>Sends me to the moon <br>You got me so excited <br>Come wrap your legs around me <br>Let's get on it <br><br>You're so delicious <br>Wanna take a bite <br>Baby it's on tonight <br>Let's stop wasting time <br>Just wanna touch you <br>Make you feel alright <br>I can do what you like <br>Cause baby I'm yours tonight <br>You're so delicious <br><br>You gotta work harder than that <br><br>Show me no mercy <br>I like the games you play <br>Now tie me to your bedpost honey <br>Keep me there all day <br>Legs that go to heaven <br>Driving me insane <br>Let's get on it <br><br>You're so delicious <br>Wanna take a bite <br>Baby it's on tonight <br>Let's stop wasting time <br>Just wanna touch you <br>Make you feel alright <br>I can do what you like <br>Cause baby I'm yours tonight <br>You're so delicious <br><br>Oh yeah <br>Now you feel good <br>And girl you look so fine <br>Now woo, I can hardly stand it <br>You know just how to make a grown man cry <br><br>You're so delicious <br>Wanna take a bite <br>Baby it's on tonight <br>Let's stop wasting time <br>Just wanna touch you <br>Make you feel alright <br>I can do what you like <br>Cause baby I'm yours tonight <br>You're so delicious <br><br>Oh wah ooh ooh <br>You're so delicious <br>Uh huh <br>Baby, baby, baby you're so delicious <br>Aw now <br>Oh wah ooh ooh <br>You're so delicious]]></content><category term="Daniel Powter" label="Daniel Powter"/><category term="Delicious" label="Delicious"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/진월/Slow_Down_Feat_Bear_Rap/</id><title>진월 - Slow Down (Feat. Bear Rap) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:01:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:01:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%84%EC%9B%94/Slow_Down_Feat_Bear_Rap/" title="진월 - Slow Down (Feat. Bear Rap) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하루도 <br>열심히 했어 baby <br>매일 새롭지 <br>어제와 다른 재미 wow <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now wow <br>우리 둘을 봐 <br>조금 다른 맛 <br>class on the top wow <br>오늘 하루도 <br>열심히 했어 baby wow <br>매일 새롭지 <br>어제와 다른 재미 wow <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now wow <br>우리 둘을 봐 <br>조금 다른 맛 <br>class on the top wow <br>이 모습이 난 참 <br>대견스럽지 못하지 많은 <br>사람들이 그래서일까 <br>나를 욕해 다들 <br>4년 동안 난 죽었구나 <br>더 뛰었지만 참 안 변해 <br>그간 나를 손가락질 한 <br>사람들 중 절반의 <br>진짜 맘은 너를 <br>위한거라 내가 <br>찢어 준거라며 <br>말 안 되는 소리들만 애기 <br>하잖아 지나가면 <br>그 중 반의 맘은 뭔가 <br>된 듯한 느낌 받나봐 <br>감흥 없는 말 <br>이젠 그만해 <br>맹독을 발라놓은 <br>혓바닥이 사람 마음을 <br>후벼 파는 참담한 <br>짓들 no talking <br>no touch me <br>no talking <br>no touch me <br>no talking <br>no touch me <br>no talking <br>no touch me <br>오늘 하루도 <br>열심히 했어 baby <br>매일 새롭지 <br>어제와 다른 재미 wow <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now <br>우리 둘을 봐 <br>조금 다른 맛 <br>class on the top wow <br>오늘 하루도 <br>열심히 했어 baby wow <br>매일 새롭지 <br>어제와 다른 재미 wow <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now wow <br>우리 둘을 봐 <br>조금 다른 맛 <br>class on the top wow <br>try jumping 높이 <br>be happy today <br>oh every good day <br>every good day <br>every good day <br>try jumping 높이 <br>be happy today <br>oh every good day <br>every good day <br>every good day <br>한번 돌아가 볼까 <br>꿈이 가득한 <br>그때 그 시절로 말야 <br>날 죽이려고 한 그 새끼들은 <br>여전히 날 죽이려고 하지 <br>you know <br>내가 말하는 건 절대로 <br>살인이 아니고 <br>정신적 murder <br>너도 한번 겪어봤다면 알겠지 <br>얼마나 무서운지 <br>다 아니까 일단 넣어둬 <br>고1 때 당했었지 <br>왕따란 거 <br>그렇게 난 가 봤었지 <br>밑바닥 uh <br>그리고 지금은 <br>광주의 정상 또 <br>우리가 안 될 거라던 <br>새끼들은 다 닥쳐 <br>fucked up <br>오늘 하루도 <br>열심히 했어 baby <br>매일 새롭지 <br>어제와 다른 재미 wow <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now wow <br>우리 둘을 봐 <br>조금 다른 맛 <br>class on the top wow <br>오늘 하루도 <br>열심히 했어 baby wow <br>매일 새롭지 <br>어제와 다른 재미 wow <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now <br>hater fucking now wow <br>우리 둘을 봐 <br>조금 다른 맛 <br>class on the top wow <br>try jumping 높이 <br>be happy today <br>oh every good day <br>every good day <br>every good day <br>try jumping 높이 <br>be happy today <br>oh every good day <br>every good day <br>every good day <br>]]></content><category term="진월" label="진월"/><category term="Slow Down (Feat. Bear Rap)" label="Slow Down (Feat. Bear Rap)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jonathan_Roy/Good_Things/</id><title>Jonathan Roy - Good Things - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:02:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:02:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jonathan_Roy/Good_Things/" title="Jonathan Roy - Good Things - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is just an imaginary conversation I had with myself <br>Last night around 12 o'clock <br>I said don't you call her and don't you make contact <br>Let it go that girl won't come back <br>So hard to listen to that <br>And just admit the truth <br>But she gone, get it through your head, it's only the first part <br>But she is gone and you will never guess <br>What is the worst part <br><br>It's when the good things happen to me <br>I use to call you up immediately <br>I got so many good things coming my way <br>But there is no one to call today <br>It's when the good things happen to me <br>I use to take your picture so you can see <br>And that's the first thing I use to do <br>And it's the worst thing there is about not being together with you <br>Together ohh <br><br>And this is just a next heart for my mind <br>It just keep spinning around all the time <br>Can't you make it stop <br>Can't you make it stop <br>I wanna know <br>But she is gone, get it through your head <br>It's only the first part <br>But she is gone <br>You will never guess what is the worst part <br><br>It's when the good things happen to me <br>I use to call you up immediately <br>I got so many good things coming my way <br>But there is no one to call today <br>It's when the good things happen to me <br>I use to take your picture so you can see <br>And that's the first thing I use to do <br>And it's the worst thing there is about not being together with you <br>Together <br>Only when the good things <br>Only when the good things <br>Only when the good things <br>Only when the good things <br>Only when the good things <br>Only when the good things <br><br>I got so many good things <br>I got no one to call <br>Good, good, good things <br>Yeahhh <br><br>It's when the good things happen to me <br>I use to call you up immediately <br>I got so many good things coming my way <br>But there is no one to call today <br>It's when the good things happen to me <br>I use to take your picture so you can see <br>And that's the first thing I use to do <br>And that's worst thing there is about not being together with you <br>Only when the good things <br>Only when the good things]]></content><category term="Jonathan Roy" label="Jonathan Roy"/><category term="Good Things" label="Good Things"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sara_Serena/Duele_Decir_Adios/</id><title>Sara Serena - Duele Decir Adios - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:02:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:02:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sara_Serena/Duele_Decir_Adios/" title="Sara Serena - Duele Decir Adios - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Me pregunto que hago aqui, llamandote <br>Porque siempre termino aqui, rogandote <br>Mi consciencia me dice, ya no debo estar aqui <br><br>Y yo arriesgandolo todo, solo por estar junto a ti <br>Que hacer si ya no existe solucion <br>Mi corazon llora, llora por ti <br>No existen palabras que puedan redimir <br>Mi corazon llora, buscando salir <br>Y el desamor se asoma, cuando llega el fin <br>Duele decir adios <br>Duele decir adios <br>Aqui estoy despues de prometer jamas volver <br>Si eres fuego, decido quemarme en tu piel <br>Mi consciencia me dice, ya no debo estar aqui <br>Y yo arriesgandolo todo, solo por estar junto a ti <br>Que hacer si ya no existe solucion <br>Mi corazon llora, llora por ti <br>No existen palabras que puedan redimir <br>Mi corazon llora, buscando salir <br>Y el desamor se asoma, cuando llega el fin <br>Duele decir adios <br>Duele decir adios <br>Es natural buscar un amor real <br>Renunciar a todo por la esperanza de amar <br>Aunque huela a peligro <br>y duela decir adios <br>Mi corazon llora, llora por ti <br>No existen palabras que puedan redimir <br>Mi corazon llora, buscando salir <br>Y el desamor se asoma, cuando llega el fin <br>Duele decir adios <br>Duele decir adios <br>Duele decir adios]]></content><category term="Sara Serena" label="Sara Serena"/><category term="Duele Decir Adios" label="Duele Decir Adios"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/THEY/U-RITE/</id><title>THEY. - U-RITE - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:05:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:05:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/THEY/U-RITE/" title="THEY. - U-RITE - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I ain't with the back and forth, I ain't back and forth, like <br>Fuck what you asking for, just back up off me, like <br>Pretty sure your man still back at home, he ain't that important, like <br>You ain't really seen it like that before, not like that before, you like <br><br>When you put it like that, like that, like that, u rite <br>Nigga think he got it like that, wanna act like that <br>Alright, I'm about to have to backtrack backtrack, track off that <br>U rite, u rite, u rite, u rite, u rite, yeah <br><br>Already know what you want <br>Bitch, why you keep hitting my phone <br>Fuck wit a nigga before, just wait 'til I get in my zone <br>Fuck all this silly talk <br>Marvin momma told me never hit it raw <br>Certain shit a nigga pick up on <br>You cannot trick me, the jig is up <br>Level up, bitch, like uh <br>Evidently you don't know da boy ain't no chump <br>Real nigga don't say nothin <br>I'ma roll up my skunk, then I post up like Duncan <br>When your nigga gon' give up <br>Keep it real girl, quit frontin' <br><br>When you put it like that, like that, like that, u rite <br>Nigga think he got it like that, wanna act like that <br>Alright, I'm about to have to backtrack backtrack, track off that <br>U rite, u rite, u rite, u rite, u rite, yeah <br><br>Rule 1 Never ever give a bitch a clue what you really tryna get into Two <br>Both her friends wanna come with me, tell her good things always come in 3s Three <br>Can't let you walk out that door 'til you show me what that pussy hittin' for Four <br>Not tryna fuck up the vibe, but you got be out by a quarter to 5, hoe Five, five, five <br>Say that she feelin' my aura but never been wit a nigga from Aurora <br>Thick like she El Salvadorian, face like she work at Sephora <br>Everything going accordingly until she started feeling too important <br>I couldn't do nothing for her <br>Before shawty left out the door, she said <br><br>When you put it like that, like that, like that, u rite <br>Nigga think he got it like that, wanna act like that <br>Alright, I'm about to have to backtrack backtrack, track off that <br>U rite, u rite, u rite, u rite, u rite, yeah <br><br>Bitch, u rite, bitch, I think u rite <br>I be like, Bitch, u rite, bitch, I think u rite <br>I be like, Bitch, u rite, bitch, I think u rite <br>I be like, Bitch, u rite <br>Bitch, u rite, bitch, I think u rite <br>I be like, Bitch, u rite, bitch, I think u rite <br>I be like, Bitch, u rite, bitch, I think u rite <br>I be like, Bitch, u rite]]></content><category term="THEY." label="THEY."/><category term="U-RITE" label="U-RITE"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하이틴_HIGHTEEN/Dreaming/</id><title>하이틴 (HIGHTEEN) - Dreaming - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:05:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:05:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%8B%B4_HIGHTEEN/Dreaming/" title="하이틴 (HIGHTEEN) - Dreaming - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 힘이 들 때 다가와 <br>내 귀에 속삭여준 너 <br>설레는 마음 <br>감출 수 없어 다시 찾아가 <br>우리에겐 꿈이 많아 <br>그 꿈을 위해 살아 <br>많고 많은 시련이 <br>우릴 지치게 해도 <br>이겨낼 수 있어 <br>언제나 내게 손짓해준 너 <br>I'm dreaming <br>언제나 눈을 뜨죠 <br>그대여 나를 봐요 <br>I'm dreaming <br>오늘도 꿈을 꾸죠 <br>저 구름 위를 걸어봐 <br>높이 날아 올라 <br>I'm dreaming <br>내 곁에만 있어줘 <br>너는 나를 믿어줘 <br>모두 헛된 꿈이라 말할때 <br>나에게 힘이 되준 너 <br>두근두근 난 멈출 수 없어 <br>널 향해 다가가 <br>내가 걷고있는 <br>이 길이 가끔 두려워 <br>하지만 이 기분 좋은 떨림 <br>느낄 수 있어 <br>이 음악 안에서 <br>I'm dreaming <br>언제나 눈을 뜨죠 <br>그대여 나를 봐요 <br>I'm dreaming <br>오늘도 꿈을 꾸죠 <br>저 구름 위를 걸어봐 <br>높이 날아 올라 <br>I'm dreaming <br>언제나 눈을 뜨죠 <br>그대여 나를 봐요 <br>I'm dreaming <br>오늘도 꿈을 꾸죠 <br>저 구름 위를 걸어봐 <br>높이 날아 올라 <br>I'm dreaming <br>그대 내 곁에 있어줘 <br>언제까지나 변치않길 바래 <br>]]></content><category term="하이틴 (HIGHTEEN)" label="하이틴 (HIGHTEEN)"/><category term="Dreaming" label="Dreaming"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더킹_THE_KING/찌질하게/</id><title>더킹 (THE KING) - 찌질하게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:05:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:05:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%82%B9_THE_KING/%EC%B0%8C%EC%A7%88%ED%95%98%EA%B2%8C/" title="더킹 (THE KING) - 찌질하게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 찌질하게 찌질하게 <br>문잘 보내요 <br>부질없게 부질없게 <br>기다리네요 <br>괜찮다는 말 한마디에 <br>오늘도 니 연락 기다리잖아 <br>그래 우리 친구로 <br>남아 지내자 <br>그래놓고 연락은 <br>왜 안 되는데 <br>넌 왜 날 무시하는 거야 <br>누구랑 어디서 <br>무얼 하는 거야 <br>자주 보잔 말 <br>친구로라도 보자고 한말 <br>그래놓고 그런 뒤로 <br>내 연락은 너한테 뭔데 <br>도대체 너 왜 안 받아 <br>전화 신호는 또 <br>왜 잘 가다 말아 <br>그래 그럼 말아 <br>내가 다신하나 봐라 <br>이 말도 얼마안가 <br>뱉은 말을 삼켜 <br>결국에 너한텐 <br>찌질한 엑스 <br>떠나갈 줄 나 몰랐기에 <br>나는 아직 준비가 안됐기에 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 우리 사이 <br>끝내 보낼 준비가 안됐어 <br>오늘도 찌질하게 찌질하게 <br>문잘 보내요 <br>부질없게 부질없게 <br>기다리네요 <br>괜찮다는 말 한마디에 <br>오늘도 니 연락 기다리잖아 <br>악 소리 질러 미안해 <br>악 만 남아 널 기다려 <br>악 하게 점점 변해가 <br>아아악 아아아악 악 BABY <br>난 니 생각보다 매력적인 <br>단호한 남자 <br>디저트도 도도하게 <br>단호박을 썰어먹지 <br>이런데도 나를 차겠다고 <br>나도 너 없어도 상관없어 단지 <br>너희 집에 두고 간 <br>내 칫솔 땜에 찾아왔지 <br>전화도 방문도 <br>소득이 없었지만 <br>그렇다고 소중한 <br>내 셔츠를 포기할 순 없지 <br>떠나갈 줄 나 몰랐기에 <br>나는 아직 준비가 안됐기에 <br>영원할 줄 알았던 우리 사이 <br>끝내 보낼 준비가 안됐어 <br>오늘도 찌질하게 찌질하게 <br>문잘 보내요 <br>부질없게 부질없게 <br>기다리네요 <br>괜찮다는 말 한마디에 <br>오늘도 니 연락 기다리잖아 <br>악 소리 질러 미안해 <br>악 만 남아 널 기다려 <br>악 하게 점점 변해가 <br>아아악 아아아악 악 BABY <br>난 안 그럴 줄 알았는데 <br>괜찮을 줄 알았는데 <br>바보처럼 멍하니 널 <br>기다려요 <br>악 소리 질러 미안해 <br>악 만 남아 널 기다려 <br>악 하게 점점 변해가 <br>아아악 아아아악 악 BABY <br>이제는 그만할게 그만 둘게 <br>기다리는 일 <br>But 넌 행복하게 행복하게 <br>잘 지내줘요 <br>괜찮다는 내 한마디는 <br>이제는 진짜니까 널 보낼게 <br>]]></content><category term="더킹 (THE KING)" label="더킹 (THE KING)"/><category term="찌질하게" label="찌질하게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더킹_THE_KING/바다너랑/</id><title>더킹 (THE KING) - 바다,너랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:05:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:05:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%82%B9_THE_KING/%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4%EB%84%88%EB%9E%91/" title="더킹 (THE KING) - 바다,너랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[빛났지 까만 <br>밤하늘도 함께여서 <br>파랬지 내 마음은 <br>함께한 그 바다처럼 <br>두 번은 없을 거야 <br>처음의 그 설레임은 <br>신고 온 신발 벗고 <br>한 발짝 내딛을 때 <br>떨리는 그 두려움 <br>파도가 몰아칠까 <br>빠르게 써내려간 <br>네 이름 아마 <br>여기였지 이쯤 <br>지워진 이름 <br>잊혀진 얼굴이 다시 <br>아른거리네 기억나니 <br>우리의 여름 <br>바다 너랑 함께였었던 <br>그 바다 너와 함께했었던 <br>구름 위를 걷는 느낌 <br>모래 위를 뛰는 기분 <br>너와 있으면 <br>정말 행복했는데 <br>바다 너랑 함께였었던 <br>그 바다 너와 함께했었던 <br>우리 추억만을 남겨두고 <br>떠나버린 여기 <br>너는 어떨까 가끔 <br>생각나는 걸 둘이 <br>난 그때부터 <br>바다가 시시해 <br>모래알보다도 눈부시게 <br>빛나던 너랑 <br>너 때문에 구름대신 높게 <br>떠있었던 마음 <br>가사에 온통 나랑 <br>너뿐인 것처럼 <br>내겐 그 바다에 <br>너와 나뿐인 것 같았어 <br>바다보다 바다를 보다 <br>뒤돌아서 날 봐주던 <br>너만 기억에 남았어 <br>너도 기억하고 있을까 <br>시간은 우릴 질투하고 <br>해도 구경을 닦달하는 <br>달에게 자리를 내주고 <br>별도 참견하던 밤에 <br>파도가 힐끗 눈치껏 숨겨준 <br>너와 나의 비밀들 <br>똑같은 표정 <br>똑같은 생각 <br>똑같은 말투 <br>한때는 그랬었지 우리말야 <br>보고파지는 네가 <br>바다 너랑 함께였었던 <br>그 바다 너와 함께했었던 <br>구름 위를 걷는 느낌 <br>모래 위를 뛰는 기분 <br>우리 둘만이 <br>정말 행복했는데 <br>바다 너랑 함께였었던 <br>함께였었던 <br>그 바다 너와 함께 했었던 <br>함께했었던 <br>우리 즐거웠었던 그곳에 <br>혼자 온 지금에 <br>괜히 생각나 <br>여기 지금 난 <br>조금은 쓸쓸 <br>]]></content><category term="더킹 (THE KING)" label="더킹 (THE KING)"/><category term="바다,너랑" label="바다,너랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더킹_THE_KING/기다렸어요/</id><title>더킹 (THE KING) - 기다렸어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:05:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:05:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%82%B9_THE_KING/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A0%B8%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="더킹 (THE KING) - 기다렸어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저기 그대가 보이네요 <br>나는 계속 기다렸어요 <br>그대도 이제 내가 보이나요 <br>먼 길 다녀오게 해서 미안해요 <br>나 때문에 곁에 있지 못하고 <br>나 때문에 쓸쓸했던 뒷모습 <br>이제는 그 어깨 안아줄게요 <br>바보처럼 표현하지 못하고 <br>바보처럼 상처 줬던 내 모습 <br>모든 걸 사랑해 줄 한 사람 <br>나 많이 기다렸어요 <br>오늘처럼 우리 행복한 날 <br>이제는 계속 웃어줄래요 <br>눈물 흘러도 <br>내가 닦아줄 수 있어요 <br>지난 날처럼 우리 <br>나 때문에 곁에 있지 못하고 <br>나 때문에 쓸쓸했던 뒷모습 <br>이제는 그 어깨 안아줄게요 <br>바보처럼 표현하지 못하고 <br>바보처럼 상처 줬던 내 모습 <br>모든 걸 사랑해 줄 한 사람 <br>나 많이 기다렸어요 <br>오늘처럼 우리 행복한 날 <br>이제는 계속 웃어줄래요 <br>눈물 흘러도 <br>내가 닦아줄 수 있어요 <br>지난 날처럼 우리 <br>후회하지 않았다면 <br>거짓말이겠죠 <br>그댈 보면 눈물이 먼저 나요 <br>지금 잡은 두 손 절대 놓지 말아요 <br>누구보다 소중한 내 한 사람 <br>나 많이 기다렸어요 <br>오늘처럼 우리 행복한 날 <br>이제는 계속 웃어줄래요 <br>눈물 흘러도 <br>내가 닦아줄 수 있어요 <br>지난 날처럼 우리 <br>나 기다렸어요 <br>그대란 한 사람 <br>]]></content><category term="더킹 (THE KING)" label="더킹 (THE KING)"/><category term="기다렸어요" label="기다렸어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더킹_THE_KING/재회/</id><title>더킹 (THE KING) - 재회 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:05:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:05:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%82%B9_THE_KING/%EC%9E%AC%ED%9A%8C/" title="더킹 (THE KING) - 재회 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랜만이야 다시 널 만난 게 <br>묻고 싶은 말 많지만 <br>오랜만이야 너는 잘 지냈니 <br>보고 싶어 보고 싶었어 <br>날 사랑한단 입술이 <br>날 안아주던 니 품이 <br>아직도 그립기만 해 <br>I'll let you go <br>나 없이도 잘 살아줘 <br>I'll let you go <br>가끔은 날 기억해줘 <br>가장 행복했던 추억으로 <br>사랑했던 나로 <br>너의 추억 속에서 나를 기억해줘 <br>날 사랑한단 입술이 <br>날 안아주던 니 품이 <br>아직도 그립기만 해 <br>I'll let you go <br>나 없이도 잘 살아줘 <br>I'll let you go <br>가끔은 날 기억해줘 <br>가장 행복했던 추억으로 <br>사랑했던 나로 <br>너의 추억 속에서 나를 기억해줘 <br>나는 어느새 어른이 되어있는데 <br>시간 지나도 그대로인 너 <br>내 옆엔 네가 없는데 <br>네 옆엔 다른 사람이 <br>왜 자꾸 눈물이 나는 걸까 <br>I'll let you go <br>나 없이도 잘 살아줘 <br>I'll let you go <br>가끔은 날 기억해줘 <br>가장 행복했던 추억으로 <br>사랑했던 나로 <br>너의 추억 속에서 나를 기억해줘 <br>]]></content><category term="더킹 (THE KING)" label="더킹 (THE KING)"/><category term="재회" label="재회"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더킹_THE_KING/너잖아/</id><title>더킹 (THE KING) - 너잖아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:05:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:05:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%82%B9_THE_KING/%EB%84%88%EC%9E%96%EC%95%84/" title="더킹 (THE KING) - 너잖아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 해야 될지 모르겠어 <br>헤어지잔 너의 말에 <br>내가 알던 너와는 다른 <br>분위기에 <br>너의 집 앞으로 <br>무작정 찾아가 <br>지금 네 앞에 서있는 난 <br>무슨 말을 꺼내야 할지 몰라 <br>난 <br>나 울고 있잖아 <br>그럼 안아주던 너잖아 <br>미안해 엉엉 울면 <br>안아주던 너잖아 <br>나 울고 있잖아 <br>그럼 안아주던 너잖아 <br>그런 너잖아 그런 너잖아 <br>어떻게 해야 할지 모르겠어 <br>말 없이 바라보는 너 <br>내가 알던 너와는 <br>다른 분위기에 <br>미안해 용서해줘 라고 말하며 <br>안으면 웃어줄 너인데 <br>한 발자국조차 갈 수가 없어 <br>난 <br>나 울고 있잖아 <br>그럼 안아주던 너잖아 <br>미안해 엉엉 울면 <br>안아주던 너잖아 <br>나 울고 있잖아 <br>그럼 안아주던 너잖아 <br>그런 너잖아 그런 너잖아 <br>힘겹게 네 손을 잡아보지만 <br>그만 하자라는 너의 말이 <br>무서워 온 몸이 <br>떨리고 아파 와 <br>거짓말인 것 같은데 <br>꿈 속 인 것처럼 <br>손에 힘이 안 들어가 <br>나 울고 있잖아 <br>나 울고 있잖아 <br>그럼 안아주던 너잖아 <br>미안해 엉엉 울면 <br>안아주던 너잖아 <br>나 울고 있잖아 <br>그럼 안아주던 너잖아 <br>그런 너잖아 <br>제발 가지마 <br>그런 너였잖아 <br>]]></content><category term="더킹 (THE KING)" label="더킹 (THE KING)"/><category term="너잖아" label="너잖아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더킹_THE_KING/새벽감성/</id><title>더킹 (THE KING) - 새벽감성 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:05:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:05:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%82%B9_THE_KING/%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1/" title="더킹 (THE KING) - 새벽감성 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쓸데없이 오늘도 <br>잠 못 이루고 <br>이 시간에 나는 왜 <br>나 왜 이러는 건데 <br>별 일 없이 내일도 <br>나 일해야 하는데 <br>이 시간에 나는 왜 <br>나 왜 이러는 건데 <br>새벽 4시 <br>I can do nothing <br>늦은 시간만큼 내게 <br>전화를 걸기엔 난 <br>늦은 거겠지 <br>속 이상해 술 마신 게 <br>아닌데 나 취한 것 같이 <br>아직도 난 니가 <br>옆에 있는 것 같이 <br>착각의 나래를 펼치는데 <br>분명 아침만 되면 <br>후회할 일요일 <br>지금 안 하면 평생 느낄 <br>월요일 아침 <br>그 생각에 핸드폰만 <br>바라보네 <br>니 번호를 누르고 난 <br>숨을 꼭 참네 <br>니가 보고 싶어 <br>니가 보고 싶어 <br>이 쉬운 말도 할 수 없는 <br>내가 너무 미운걸 yeah <br>새벽감성 터지는 이 밤에 <br>어디서 뭘 하고 있어 <br>어디서 뭘 하고 있어 <br>새벽감성 터지는 이 밤에 <br>난 달려가 내 마음은 <br>다시 너에게 <br>하 하염없이 내리는 <br>비 아래 다시 <br>시작하는 불씨같이 <br>목이 말라서 죽어버린 나 <br>뭇가지 달린 물방울 같이 <br>시간이 늦은 건지 <br>늦은 시간인지 <br>내가 늦은 건지 왜 <br>항상 후회는 늦는 거지 <br>달 없는 밤 추적추적 <br>내리는 비 아래 <br>휘적휘적 허우적대는 <br>내 꼴마저도 네가 <br>봐줬으면 좋겠다 <br>생각 하는 게 <br>너무 긴 새벽에 지쳐 <br>해를 기다려도 <br>너 말고는 떠오를게 없는 <br>난 오늘도 하루 종일 <br>새벽에 서있어 <br>니가 보고 싶어 <br>니가 보고 싶어 <br>니가 했던 말이 생각 나는 <br>내가 너무 미운 걸 yeah <br>새벽감성 터지는 이 밤에 <br>어디서 뭘 하고 있어 <br>어디서 뭘 하고 있어 <br>새벽감성 터지는 이 밤에 <br>난 달려가 내 마음은 <br>다시 너에게 <br>거울 앞에 앉지마 <br>슬픈 노래 틀지마 <br>불은 꺼놓지마 <br>아무 생각 하지마 <br>이 모든걸 안 해도 <br>난 니 생각나 <br>]]></content><category term="더킹 (THE KING)" label="더킹 (THE KING)"/><category term="새벽감성" label="새벽감성"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/더킹_THE_KING/이상하다/</id><title>더킹 (THE KING) - 이상하다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:05:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:05:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%94%ED%82%B9_THE_KING/%EC%9D%B4%EC%83%81%ED%95%98%EB%8B%A4/" title="더킹 (THE KING) - 이상하다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이상하다 이상해 <br>난 너뿐 이였는데 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>어느 날부터 모든 게 다 <br>우리 둘이 둘이가 아닌 <br>혼자 이고픈 맘이 맘이 맘이 <br>나한테 없는 줄 알았지 <br>이런 감정 <br>더 이상 네 손을 잡고 <br>난 걷질 않아 <br>마주보며 웃질 않아 <br>너와 둘이 둘이가 아닌 <br>널 향한 내 맘이 맘이 맘이 <br>I don't know I don't know it <br>내가 이상한 거니까 울지 마 <br>내가 잘못한 거니까 <br>I don't know I don't know it <br>지금 헤어지자는 건 아냐 <br>시간이 필요한 것뿐이야 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>처음엔 모든 게 다 궁금해 <br>지금은 네 모든 걸 다 잠그네 <br>입술로 막았던 네 입 <br>이젠 손으로 막고 <br>네가 기분이 나쁘네 <br>더 이상 네 손을 잡고 <br>난 걷질 않아 <br>마주보며 웃질 않아 <br>함께한 이 거리 거리 <br>거리 잠시만 따로 <br>Walking Walking Walking <br>yeah eh yeah eh <br>I don't know I don't know it <br>내가 이상한 거니까 울지 마 <br>내가 잘못한 거니까 <br>I don't know I don't know it <br>지금 헤어지자는 건 아냐 <br>시간이 필요한 것뿐이야 <br>지랄도 병인데 <br>애지간히 하세요 <br>그 애매한 표정을 <br>밟아볼까요 <br>아주 천사가 나셨어요 <br>얼굴만 봐도 속이 역해 <br>쏠리네요 <br>한 번 더 이빨 보이고 <br>웃고 있어봐 <br>그 이빨을 싹 다 <br>뽑아줄게요 <br>같잖은 표정을 또 <br>같잖게 포장하고 <br>같이하자고 서 짓는 <br>가짜 표정 <br>말 한마디마디 섞는 것도 <br>질려 지겨워 <br>내가 나쁜 새끼하고 <br>하고 싶은 대로해 <br>신경 써야 할 곳 너 말고도 <br>너무 많아 <br>시답잖은 투정에도 <br>매번 내가 져줬잖아 <br>니 눈에 눈물을 보고도 <br>아무렇지 않은 <br>내가 이상한 거지만 <br>미안하진 않아 <br>I don't know I don't know it <br>내가 이상한 거니까 울지 마 <br>내가 잘못한 거니까 <br>I don't know I don't know it <br>지금 헤어지자는 건 아냐 <br>시간이 필요한 것뿐이야 <br>I don't know I don't know it <br>내가 이상한 거니까 울지 마 <br>내가 잘못한 거니까 <br>I don't know I don't know it <br>지금 헤어지자는 건 아냐 <br>시간이 필요한 것뿐이야 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>이상하다 이상해 <br>]]></content><category term="더킹 (THE KING)" label="더킹 (THE KING)"/><category term="이상하다" label="이상하다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이어스_Ears/Take_Me/</id><title>이어스 (Ears) - Take Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:07:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:07:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%96%B4%EC%8A%A4_Ears/Take_Me/" title="이어스 (Ears) - Take Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모른 척 외면해도 <br>거울을 보는 이 기분 <br>어디가 같은 건지 <br>생각이나 말투가 말야 <br>같은 곳에 있을 때 <br>같은 말에 웃을 때 <br>서로의 머릿속에 <br>스쳐가지 말라고 말해 <br>그 말은 아직 남겨둔 채로 <br>아직 우린 서로 바라만 보는 게 <br>I feel alive I don’t care if it hurts <br>No one understand <br>how I feel right now <br>Take me <br>Take on me <br>Take on me <br>Take on me <br>너와 날 연결시킨 <br>그 고리의 이음새와 <br>네가 보여줄 곳의 <br>따듯함이 날 반기겠지 <br>같은 곳에 있을 때 <br>같은 말에 웃을 때 <br>서로의 가슴속은 <br>스쳐가지 말라고 말해 <br>그 말은 아직 남겨둔 채로 <br>아직 우린 서로 바라만 보는 게 <br>I feel alive I don’t care if it hurts <br>No one understand <br>how I feel right now <br>Take me <br>Take on me <br>Take on me <br>Take on me <br>]]></content><category term="이어스 (Ears)" label="이어스 (Ears)"/><category term="Take Me" label="Take Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Melissa_Manchester/Bright_Eyes/</id><title>Melissa Manchester - Bright Eyes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:08:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:08:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Melissa_Manchester/Bright_Eyes/" title="Melissa Manchester - Bright Eyes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bright eyes is here again <br>And I am so low, and so alone <br>Sweet lady night <br>Keep me from sunny's light <br>Slippin' through stone <br>I'm into bein' bone <br><br>I was raised on the good books of mornin' <br>And I learned how to laugh and get by <br>I was gamin' and pleasin' <br>With never a reason why <br><br>So the promise of heaven was broken <br>And I held on and I didn't care <br>Just a dance for a changer <br>A stranger to brush my hair <br><br>And I know I'm an angel who's fallen from the sky <br>And I shine like a star, I burn out, down to die <br>Crawlin' back to my hurt and my heart, hear me cry <br>Oh my heart, I cry <br>Oh my heart, I cry <br>Oh my heart, I cry <br><br>I must cry for the song of my mama <br>For the love lyin' somewhere in me <br>For the devil in dark night <br>Who needed the light to see <br><br>Touch me once if you like, make me over <br>I am lust, I am am sleek, and I'm good <br>But I'm startin' to shiver <br>Climb up and feel the sun <br><br>And I know I'm an angel who's fallen from the sky <br>And I shine like a star, I burn out, down to die <br>And I'm tryin' to get back to my hurt or my heart <br>Oh my heart, my heart <br>Oh my heart, my heart <br>Oh, Oh my heart I cry <br><br>Oh I cry <br>Ah, I cry <br>Ooh <br>I cry <br>I cry]]></content><category term="Melissa Manchester" label="Melissa Manchester"/><category term="Bright Eyes" label="Bright Eyes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Naughty_Boy/Shouldve_Been_Me_Acoustic_Feat_Kyla/</id><title>Naughty Boy - Should`ve Been Me (Acoustic) (Feat. Kyla) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:09:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:09:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Naughty_Boy/Shouldve_Been_Me_Acoustic_Feat_Kyla/" title="Naughty Boy - Should`ve Been Me (Acoustic) (Feat. Kyla) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need you bad <br>I need you bad <br>I need you I need you <br>I need you bad <br>I need you bad <br>I need you bad <br>I need you I need you <br>I need you bad <br>I needed a little space <br>Honest <br>thought that you'd <br>stay waiting <br>I made my last mistake <br>hmm-mmm <br>You're happy and I hate it <br>And now I know <br>that I spoke too soon <br>Seeing how fast <br>you made moves <br>I want you so bad <br>I want you back <br>but you're gone <br>All on my own <br>I miss you <br>I know it's too late <br>can't handle that truth <br>I want you so bad <br>I want you back <br>but you're gone <br>It should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been me <br>every time <br>I closed my eyes <br>Yeah I can see <br>those times <br>where I used to be <br>Well oh God <br>it should've been me <br>all along <br>Well this was that it seems <br>'Cause you don't think of me <br>that often <br>How could I let you leave me <br>yeah <br>Well it's too late to stop ya <br>And now I know <br>that I spoke too soon <br>Seeing how fast <br>you made moves <br>I want you so bad <br>I want you back <br>but you're gone <br>All on my own <br>I miss you <br>I know it's too late <br>can't handle that truth <br>I want you so bad <br>I want you back <br>but you're gone <br>It should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been me <br>every time <br>I closed my eyes <br>Yeah I can see <br>those times <br>where I used to be <br>Well oh God <br>it should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been <br>should've been me <br>It should've been me <br>should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been <br>should've been me <br>It should've been me <br>should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been me <br>all along <br>Hey <br>It should've been me <br>all along <br>I open my eyes <br>and I see is no dream <br>You're gone <br>I can see <br>those times <br>where I used to be <br>oh God <br>it should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been me <br>every time <br>I closed my eyes <br>Yeah I can see <br>those times <br>where I used to be <br>Well oh God <br>it should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been <br>should've been me <br>It should've been me <br>should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been <br>should've been me <br>It should've been me <br>should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been me <br>all along <br>It should've been me <br>all along <br>I open my eyes <br>and I see is no dream <br>You're gone <br>I can see <br>those times <br>where I used to be <br>Oh God <br>it should've been me <br>all along <br>]]></content><category term="Naughty Boy" label="Naughty Boy"/><category term="Should`ve Been Me (Acoustic) (Feat. Kyla)" label="Should`ve Been Me (Acoustic) (Feat. Kyla)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NeighborMood_네이버무드/Take_It_Back/</id><title>NeighborMood (네이버무드) - Take It Back - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:09:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:09:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NeighborMood_%EB%84%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%B2%84%EB%AC%B4%EB%93%9C/Take_It_Back/" title="NeighborMood (네이버무드) - Take It Back - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 마이크 앞에 서면 <br>모두다 they say wow <br>엄마집 창고 안에 보면 xxl <br>source 잡지들 <br>천장까지 쌓여 있어 <br>내게 힙합은 완벽했어 <br>like a mona lisa <br>가사를 쓸 때 <br>내 뇐 새 처럼 날아 <br>음악이 내 가위 <br>현실과의 고리를 잘라 <br>before the bidness <br>it was all joy <br>스내키챈 전에 <br>뭐가 있었지 hmm just roy <br>그 사람 사라지기전에 <br>찾아내야돼 <br>그때 느낀 희열 <br>상기시켜 줘야 해 <br>내 iphone 비행기 <br>모드로 바꿔 <br>pen 다시 잡고 <br>단어로 종이를 가꿔 <br>힙합 프로 다 끝나도 <br>난 여기 남을거야 <br>너도 나와 같다면 <br>버틸 수 있을 거야 <br>for the culture <br>and the love the art <br>2가지 때매 시작했어 <br>take it back to the start <br>Take it back to the <br>Take it back to the start <br>Take it back to the <br>Take it back to the art <br>Take it back to the <br>Take it back to the start <br>Take it back to the <br>Take it back to the art <br>Ok let’s take a trip way <br>back to the essence <br>The only asian rapper <br>in my scene with a presence <br>내 색에 대한 편견 <br>깨고 싶었어 <br>여기 온 순간부터 <br>그 목표를 잊었어 <br>The money and fame <br>처음으로 맛봤지 <br>길 잃고 통장 채우는 게 <br>내 주 관심 <br>거울 안에 있는 사람 <br>눈 마주치면 <br>진지하게 물어봐 <br>what do you believe in <br>내가 배열한 단어가 <br>누구에겐 약 <br>힘든 삶을 이겨 <br>낼 수 있는 링거 shot <br>타고난 재능 <br>안 쓰는 건 죄지만 <br>사용하는 이유가 더 중요해 <br>얼굴 닦으며 새 마음먹고 <br>Love for the art sparks rhymes <br>in my notebook <br>네 열정 꽃피워 주기 위해 <br>처음 시작했을 때 <br>그 이유로 I'm here <br>Take it back to the <br>Take it back to the start <br>Take it back to the <br>Take it back to the art <br>Take it back to the <br>Take it back to the start <br>Take it back to the <br>Take it back to the art <br>]]></content><category term="NeighborMood (네이버무드)" label="NeighborMood (네이버무드)"/><category term="Take It Back" label="Take It Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Malvo_말보/우리_둘이서/</id><title>Malvo (말보) - 우리 둘이서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-16T17:10:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-16T17:10:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Malvo_%EB%A7%90%EB%B3%B4/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EB%91%98%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%9C/" title="Malvo (말보) - 우리 둘이서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침을 맞이 할 땐 <br>너랑 나랑 <br>둘이 눈이 마주칠 땐 <br>오락 가락 <br>하던 내정신도 그땐 <br>말랑 말랑 <br>다시 또 멍해지는 것 같아 <br>다시 또 멍해지는 것 같아 <br>하루가 멀다 하고 <br>아니 한 시간이 <br>멀어 일분도 좀 멀어 <br>자꾸 원해 <br>뭐 그런 거 있잖아 <br>너를 내가 <br>아니 나를 니가 <br>꽉 안아줄 때 <br>그때의 안정감 ok <br>사인이 머릿속에 <br>빙글 뱅글 자꾸 <br>돌아가네 에 <br>딩동댕동 종이 막 <br>링딩동 울리네 <br>널 처음 보고 지금까지 <br>내가 할 수 만 있다면 <br>어디서든 울리고 싶어 <br>나 울리고 싶어 <br>자릴 못 잡고 둥둥 <br>떠다니던 날은 이제 <br>나 땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>세상 모든 곳이 <br>아름다워 보여 <br>알록 달록 알록 달록 <br>손길이 닫는 곳엔 <br>꽃이 피네 보여 <br>살랑 발랑 살랑 발랑 <br>네 입술이 언제부터 <br>그렇게 <br>이뻤던 건지 촉촉하고 <br>탐스럽게 <br>자꾸 날 홀려 시키지도 <br>않았는데 <br>정신이 쏠려 날 놀려 <br>약 올려 <br>그래도 나쁘지 않아 <br>템포를 올려 <br>어차피 다 가진 거야 <br>난 이미 all yours <br>Hold up <br>혹시 안 줄 거라면 빌려 줘 <br>이자는 매시간 매초 <br>빵빵하게 채워 줘 <br>약속해 여기 너랑 딱 <br>둘이 그린 그림 <br>이 대로 영원히 <br>불어난 가슴 안에 <br>가득 찬 love 이미 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>다른 사람 난 잘 몰라 <br>지금까지 내가 지냈던 <br>시간들은 거짓말 같아 <br>널 보고 있으면 <br>말이 필요 없이 <br>녹아버려 허니버터크림 슈가 <br>달콤해 달달 해 <br>예예예 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>땡땡 땡 땡땡땡 땡땡 때앵 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>우리 둘이서 <br>]]></content><category term="Malvo (말보)" label="Malvo (말보)"/><category term="우리 둘이서" label="우리 둘이서"/></entry></feed>