<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:30:46+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Petula_Clark/Christmas_Cards_Remastered/</id><title>Petula Clark - Christmas Cards (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:11:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:11:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Petula_Clark/Christmas_Cards_Remastered/" title="Petula Clark - Christmas Cards (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas cards, Christmas cards <br>Love to see the pretty Christmas cards <br>Bringing you sweet regards <br>Wishing you the best of happiness <br>Love to write to someone I'm thinking of <br>Love to write to the place and folks I love <br>Love to send them a message of good cheer <br>With words sincere when Christmas is here <br>When Christmas is here <br>Oh, Christmas cards, Christmas cards <br>Love to see the pretty Christmas cards <br>Bringing you sweet regards <br>Wishing you the best of happiness <br>Little cards with their trees all dressed in snow <br>Little cards with their friendly fires aglow <br>Little cards with their lovely winter scene <br>When all the world is sweet and serene <br>Is sweet and serene <br>Oh, Christmas cards, Christmas cards <br>Love to see the pretty Christmas cards <br>Bringing you sweet regards <br>Wishing you the best of happiness <br>Every card in it's little envelope <br>Bares a wish and a greeting of good hope <br>And the love with a card I send is true <br>And I'll renew each Christmas to you <br>Each Christmas to you <br>Oh, Christmas cards, Christmas cards <br>Love to see the pretty Christmas cards <br>Bringing you sweet regards <br>Wishing you the best of happiness <br>Wishing you the best of happiness]]></content><category term="Petula Clark" label="Petula Clark"/><category term="Christmas Cards (Remastered)" label="Christmas Cards (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Julie_London/Id_Like_You_For_Christmas_Remastered/</id><title>Julie London - I`d Like You For Christmas (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:11:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:11:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Julie_London/Id_Like_You_For_Christmas_Remastered/" title="Julie London - I`d Like You For Christmas (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'd like you for Christmas <br>Please make my wish come true <br>'Cause I'd dream trees and deck the hallways <br>if I knew you'd be mine for always <br>I won't be blue on Christmas <br>if old Saint Nick comes through <br>and he remembers that I'd like you for Christmas, New Year's, Easter too <br>She'd like you for Christmas <br>Please make my wish come true <br>'Cause she'd dream dreams and deck the hallways <br>if she knew you'd be hers for always <br>I won't be blue on Christmas <br>if old Saint Nick comes through <br>and he remembers that I'd like you for Christmas, New Year's, Easter too <br>New Year's, Easter too]]></content><category term="Julie London" label="Julie London"/><category term="I`d Like You For Christmas (Remastered)" label="I`d Like You For Christmas (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Connie_Francis/Babys_First_Christmas_Remastered/</id><title>Connie Francis - Baby`s First Christmas (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:11:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:11:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Connie_Francis/Babys_First_Christmas_Remastered/" title="Connie Francis - Baby`s First Christmas (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's baby's first Christmas <br>It's somethin' to see <br>Mommy and Daddy <br>Trimmin' baby's Christmas tree <br>Baby's big brother <br>Is busy with his toys <br>He's shinin' up the chimney <br>For Santa Claus <br><br>It's baby's first Christmas <br>And oh, what a joy <br>Shopping all around <br>For every pretty toy <br>It's a very special Christmas <br>A blessing from above <br><br>It's baby's first Christmas <br>A Christmas full of love <br><br>It's baby's first Christmas <br>And oh, what a joy <br>Shopping all around <br>For every pretty toy <br>It's a very special Christmas <br>A blessing from above <br>It's baby's first Christmas <br>A Christmas full of love]]></content><category term="Connie Francis" label="Connie Francis"/><category term="Baby`s First Christmas (Remastered)" label="Baby`s First Christmas (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Patti_Page/Christmas_Bells_Remastered/</id><title>Patti Page - Christmas Bells (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:11:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:11:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Patti_Page/Christmas_Bells_Remastered/" title="Patti Page - Christmas Bells (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The Christmas bells are ringing <br>The holly's at the windowpane <br>I hear the children singing <br>It's Christmas again <br>The fireplace is glowing <br>The stocking's on the Christmas tree <br>Then suddenly it's snowing <br>That's Christmas to me <br>Chimes ring in the steeple <br>Music fills the air <br>Crowds of smiling people <br>Greet you everywhere <br>When I awake at seven <br>I see you and the angels sing <br>You are my gift of heaven <br>When Christmas bells ring <br>The Christmas bells are ringing <br>The holly's at the windowpane <br>I hear the children singing <br>It's Christmas again <br>The fireplace is glowing <br>The stocking's on the Christmas tree <br>Then suddenly it's snowing <br>That's Christmas to me <br>Chimes ring in the steeple <br>Music fills the air <br>Crowds of smiling people <br>Greet you everywhere <br>When I awake at seven <br>I see you and the angels sing <br>You are my gift of heaven <br>When Christmas bells ring]]></content><category term="Patti Page" label="Patti Page"/><category term="Christmas Bells (Remastered)" label="Christmas Bells (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ella_Fitzgerald/Frosty_The_Snow_Man_Remastered/</id><title>Ella Fitzgerald - Frosty The Snow Man (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ella_Fitzgerald/Frosty_The_Snow_Man_Remastered/" title="Ella Fitzgerald - Frosty The Snow Man (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Frosty the snowman <br>Was a jolly happy soul <br>With a corncob pipe and a button nose <br>And two eyes made out of coal <br><br>Frosty the snowman <br>Is a fairytale they say <br>He was made of snow <br>But the children know <br><br>How he came to life one day <br>There must have been some magic <br>In that old silk hat they found <br>For when they placed it on his head <br><br>He began to dance around <br>Frosty the snowman <br>Was alive as he could be <br>And the children say <br><br>He could laugh and play <br>Just the same as you and me <br>Frosty the snowman <br>Knew the sun was hot that day <br><br>So he said let's run <br>And we'll have some fun <br>Now before I melt away <br>Down to the village <br><br>With a broomstick in his hand <br>Running here and there all around the square <br>Saying catch me if you can <br>He led them down the streets of town <br><br>Right to the traffic cop <br>And he only paused a moment when <br>He heard him holler stop <br>Frosty the snowman <br><br>Had to hurry on his way <br>But he waved goodbye <br>Saying don't you cry <br>I'll be back again some day <br><br>Thumpety thump thump <br>Thumpety thump thump <br>Look at frosty go <br>Thumpety thump thump <br>Thumpety thump thump <br>Over the hills of snow]]></content><category term="Ella Fitzgerald" label="Ella Fitzgerald"/><category term="Frosty The Snow Man (Remastered)" label="Frosty The Snow Man (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dinah_Washington/The_Lords_Prayer_Remastered/</id><title>Dinah Washington - The Lord`s Prayer (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dinah_Washington/The_Lords_Prayer_Remastered/" title="Dinah Washington - The Lord`s Prayer (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Our Father <br>Who art in heaven <br>Hallowed be Thy name <br>Thy kingdom come <br>Thy will be done <br>On earth as in heaven <br>Give us today <br>Our daily bread <br><br>And forgive our sins <br>As we forgive <br>Each one of those <br>Who sins against us <br>And lead us <br>Not to the time of trial <br>But deliver us from evil <br>For Thine is the kingdom <br>The power and the glory <br><br>Let all the people <br>Say amen <br>In every tribe <br>And tongue <br>Let every heart's <br>Desire be joined <br>To see the kingdom come <br>Let every hope <br>And every dream <br>Be born in love again <br>Let all the world <br>Sing with one voice <br>Let the people <br>Say amen]]></content><category term="Dinah Washington" label="Dinah Washington"/><category term="The Lord`s Prayer (Remastered)" label="The Lord`s Prayer (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ella_Fitzgerald/Jingle_Bells_Remastered/</id><title>Ella Fitzgerald - Jingle Bells (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ella_Fitzgerald/Jingle_Bells_Remastered/" title="Ella Fitzgerald - Jingle Bells (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dashing through the snow <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br>Through the fields we go <br>Laughing all the way <br>Bells on bob tail ring <br>Making spirits bright <br>What fun it is to ride and sing <br>A sleighing song tonight <br><br>Jingle bells, jingle bells <br>Jingle all the way <br>Oh what fun it is to ride <br>In a one horse open sleigh, O <br>Jingle bells, jingle bells <br>Jingle all the way <br>Oh what fun it is to ride <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br><br>A day or two ago <br>I thought I'd take a ride <br>And soon Miss Fanny Bright <br>Was seated by my side <br>The horse was lean and lank <br>Misfortune seemed his lot <br>We ran into a drifted bank <br>And there we got upsot <br><br>A day or two ago <br>The story I must tell <br>I went out on the snow <br>And on my back I fell <br>A gent was riding by <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br>He laughed at me as <br>I there sprawling laid <br>But quickly drove away <br><br>Now the ground is white <br>Go it while you're young <br>Take the girls along <br>And sing this sleighing song <br>Just bet a bob tailed bay <br>Two forty as his speed <br>Hitch him to an open sleigh <br>and crack You'll take the lead]]></content><category term="Ella Fitzgerald" label="Ella Fitzgerald"/><category term="Jingle Bells (Remastered)" label="Jingle Bells (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/Ill_Be_Home_For_Christmas_Originally_Remastered/</id><title>Frank Sinatra - I`ll Be Home For Christmas (Originally Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/Ill_Be_Home_For_Christmas_Originally_Remastered/" title="Frank Sinatra - I`ll Be Home For Christmas (Originally Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll be home for Christmas <br>You can plan on me <br>Please have snow and mistletoe <br>And presents 'neath the tree <br><br>Christmas eve will find me <br>Where the love light gleams <br>I'll be home for Christmas <br>And you'll be in my dreams <br><br>I'll be home this Christmas, darling <br>I'll be coming home to you <br>And there's nothing in the world <br>Gonna get in my way <br><br>I'll be home for Christmas <br>You can plan on me <br>Please have snow <br>And mistletoe <br>And presents 'neath the tree <br><br>Christmas eve will find me <br>Where the love light gleams <br>I'll be home for Christmas <br>And you'll be in my dreams <br>I'll be home for Christmas <br>Till then you'll be in my dreams]]></content><category term="Frank Sinatra" label="Frank Sinatra"/><category term="I`ll Be Home For Christmas (Originally Remastered)" label="I`ll Be Home For Christmas (Originally Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nat_King_Cole/Adeste_Fideles_Remastered/</id><title>Nat King Cole - Adeste Fideles (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nat_King_Cole/Adeste_Fideles_Remastered/" title="Nat King Cole - Adeste Fideles (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[O Come All Ye Faithful <br>Joyful and triumphant <br>O come ye, O come ye to Bethlehem <br>Come and behold Him <br>Born the King of Angels <br>O come, let us adore Him <br>O come, let us adore Him <br>O come, let us adore Him <br>Christ the Lord <br><br>Adeste fideles <br>Laeti triumphantes <br>Venite, venite in Bethlehem <br>Natum videte <br>Regem Angelorum <br><br>Venite adoremus <br>Venite adoremus <br>Venite adoremus Dominum]]></content><category term="Nat King Cole" label="Nat King Cole"/><category term="Adeste Fideles (Remastered)" label="Adeste Fideles (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/Mele_Kalikimaka_Remastered/</id><title>Bing Crosby - Mele Kalikimaka (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/Mele_Kalikimaka_Remastered/" title="Bing Crosby - Mele Kalikimaka (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mele Kalikimaka is the thing to say <br>On a bright Hawaiian Christmas day <br>That's the island greeting that we send to you <br>From the land where palm trees sway <br><br>Here we know that Christmas will be green and bright <br>The sun to shine by day and all the stars at night <br>Mele Kalikimaka is Hawaii's way <br>To say Merry Christmas to you <br><br>Mele Kalikimaka is the thing to say <br>On a bright Hawaiian Christmas day <br>That's the island greeting that we send to you <br>From the land where palm trees sway <br><br>Here we know that Christmas will be green and bright <br>The sun to shine by day and all the stars at night <br>Mele Kalikimaka is Hawaii's way <br>To say Merry Christmas to you <br><br>Here we know that Christmas will be green and bright <br>The sun to shine by day and all the stars at night <br>Mele Kalikimaka is Hawaii's way <br>To say Merry Christmas to you <br><br>Mele Kalikimaka is the thing to say <br>On a bright Hawaiian Christmas day <br>That's the island greeting that we send to you <br>From the land where palm trees sway <br><br>Here we know that Christmas will be green and bright <br>The sun to shine by day and all the stars at night <br>Mele Kalikimaka is Hawaii's way <br>To say Merry Christmas <br>A very Merry Christmas <br>A very, very, Merry, Merry Christmas to you]]></content><category term="Bing Crosby" label="Bing Crosby"/><category term="Mele Kalikimaka (Remastered)" label="Mele Kalikimaka (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billy_Eckstine/Christmas_Eve_Remastered/</id><title>Billy Eckstine - Christmas Eve (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billy_Eckstine/Christmas_Eve_Remastered/" title="Billy Eckstine - Christmas Eve (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll have a Blue Christmas without you <br>I'll be so blue just thinking about you <br>Decorations of red on a green Christmas tree <br>Won't mean a thing, if you're not here with me <br><br>And when those blue snowflakes start fallin' <br>That's when those blue memories start callin' <br>You'll be doin' all right, with your Christmas of white <br>But I'll have a blue, blue Christmas <br><br>I'll have a Blue Christmas that's certain <br>And when that blue heartache starts hurtin' <br>You'll be doin' all right, with your Christmas of white <br>But I'll have a blue, blue, blu, blue Christmas]]></content><category term="Billy Eckstine" label="Billy Eckstine"/><category term="Christmas Eve (Remastered)" label="Christmas Eve (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Zat_You_Santa_Claus__Remastered/</id><title>Louis Armstrong - Zat You, Santa Claus? (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Zat_You_Santa_Claus__Remastered/" title="Louis Armstrong - Zat You, Santa Claus? (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Zat You, Santa Claus? <br>Gifts I'm preparing for some Christmas sharing <br>But I pause because <br>Hanging my stocking I can hear a knocking <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus? <br>Sure is dark out, ain't the slightest spark out <br>'Pon my slackened jaw! <br>Who's there? Who is it stopping for a visit? <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus? <br>Are you bringing a present for me <br>Something pleasantly pleasant for me? <br>Then it's just what I've been waiting for <br>Would you mind slipping it under the door? <br>Cold winds are howling, or could that be growling? <br>My legs feel like straws <br>My my oh me my, kindly would you reply? <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus? <br>Hanging the stocking, I can hear a knocking <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus? <br>I say, who's there, who is it? Are you stopping for a visit? <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus? <br>Oh there, Santa, you gave me a scare <br>Now stop teasing cause I know you're there <br>We don't believe in no goblins today <br>But I can't explain why I'm shaking that way <br>Bet I can see ole Santa in the keyhole <br>I'll get to the cause <br>One peek and I'll try there; oh oh, there's an eye there! <br>'Zat you, Santa Claus? <br>Please, please, pity my knees! <br>Say that's you, Santa Claus]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Zat You, Santa Claus? (Remastered)" label="Zat You, Santa Claus? (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dickie_Valentine/Christmas_Alphabet_Remastered/</id><title>Dickie Valentine - Christmas Alphabet (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dickie_Valentine/Christmas_Alphabet_Remastered/" title="Dickie Valentine - Christmas Alphabet (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[C is for the candy trimmed around the Christmas tree <br>H is for the happiness with all the family <br>R is for the reindeer prancing by the window pane <br><br>I is for the icing on the cake as sweet as sugar cane <br>S is for the stocking hanging on the chimney wall <br>T is for the toys beneath the tree so tall <br>M is for the mistletoe where everyone is kissed <br>A is for the angels who make up the Christmas list <br>S is for the Santa who makes every kid his pet <br>Be good and he'll bring you everything in your Christmas alphabet! <br><br>Capital c is for the candy trimmed around the Christmas tree <br>H is for the happiness with all the family <br>R is for the reindeer prancing by the window pane <br>I is for the icing on the cake as sweet as sugar cane <br>S is for the stocking hanging on the chimney wall <br>T is for the toys beneath the tree so tall <br>M is for the mistletoe where everyone is kissed <br>A is for the angels who make up the Christmas list <br>S is for the Santa who makes every kid his pet <br>Be good and he'll bring you everything in your Christmas alphabet]]></content><category term="Dickie Valentine" label="Dickie Valentine"/><category term="Christmas Alphabet (Remastered)" label="Christmas Alphabet (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dean_Martin/Ive_Got_My_Love_To_Keep_Me_War_Remastered/</id><title>Dean Martin - I`ve Got My Love To Keep Me War (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dean_Martin/Ive_Got_My_Love_To_Keep_Me_War_Remastered/" title="Dean Martin - I`ve Got My Love To Keep Me War (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The snow is snowing and the wind it is blowing <br>But I can weather the storm <br>What do I care how much it may storm <br>I've got my love to keep me warm <br><br>I cannot remember the worst December <br>Just watch the icicles form <br>What do I care if icicles form <br>I've got my love to keep me warm <br><br>Off with my overcoat off with my gloves <br>Who needs an overcoat I'm burning with love <br>My heart's on fire and the flame grows higher <br>So I will weather the storm <br>What do I care how much it may storm <br>I've got my love to keep me warm <br><br>I thought you ought to know my heart's on fire <br>The flame it just leaps higher <br>So I will weather the storm <br>Why do I care how much it storms <br>I've got my love <br>To keep me warm <br>I've got my love to keep me warm]]></content><category term="Dean Martin" label="Dean Martin"/><category term="I`ve Got My Love To Keep Me War (Remastered)" label="I`ve Got My Love To Keep Me War (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Christmas_In_New_Orleans_Remastered/</id><title>Louis Armstrong - Christmas In New Orleans (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Christmas_In_New_Orleans_Remastered/" title="Louis Armstrong - Christmas In New Orleans (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Magnolia trees at night <br>Sparkling bright <br>Fields of cotton look wintery white <br>When it's Christmas time <br>In New Orleans <br><br>A barefoot choir in prayer <br>Fills the air <br>Mississippi folks <br>Are gathering there <br>When it's Christmas time <br>In New Orleans <br><br>You'll see a dixieland Santa Claus <br>Leading the band <br>To a good old Creole beat <br>And golly what a spirit <br>You can only hear it <br>Down on Basin Street <br>Your cares will disappear <br>When you hear <br>Hallelujah St. Nicholas is here <br>When it's Christmas time <br>In New Orleans <br><br>You'll see <br>A dixieland Santa Claus <br>Leading the band <br>To a good old Creole beat <br>And golly what a spirit <br>You can only hear it <br>Down on Basin Street <br>Your cares will disappear <br>When you hear <br>Hallelujah old St. Nicholas is here <br>When it's Christmas time <br>In New Orleans <br><br>When it's Christmas time in <br>It's Christmas time in in New Orleans]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Christmas In New Orleans (Remastered)" label="Christmas In New Orleans (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Christmas_Auld_Lang_Syne_Remastered/</id><title>Bobby Darin - Christmas Auld Lang Syne (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bobby_Darin/Christmas_Auld_Lang_Syne_Remastered/" title="Bobby Darin - Christmas Auld Lang Syne (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When mistletoe and tinsel glow <br>Paint a yuletide valentine <br>Back home I go to those I know <br>For a Christmas auld lang syne. <br><br>And as we gather 'round the tree <br>Our voices all combine <br>In sweet accord to thank the Lord <br>For a Christmas auld lang syne. <br><br>When sleigh bells ring and choirs sing <br>And the children's faces shine <br>With each new toy we share their joy <br>With a Christmas auld lang syne. <br><br>We sing His praise this day of days <br>And pray next year this time <br>We'll all be near to share the cheer <br>Of a Christmas auld lang syne. <br><br>"Merry Christmas everybody and a Happy New Year!" <br><br>In sweet accord we thank the Lord <br>For a Christmas auld lang syne.]]></content><category term="Bobby Darin" label="Bobby Darin"/><category term="Christmas Auld Lang Syne (Remastered)" label="Christmas Auld Lang Syne (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/Mistletoe_And_Holly_Remastered/</id><title>Frank Sinatra - Mistletoe And Holly (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/Mistletoe_And_Holly_Remastered/" title="Frank Sinatra - Mistletoe And Holly (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, by gosh, by golly <br>It's time for mistletoe and holly <br>Tasty pheasants, Christmas presents <br>Countrysides covered with snow <br><br>Oh, by gosh, by jingle <br>It's time for carols and Kris Kringle <br>Overeating, merry greetings <br>From relatives you don't know <br><br>Then comes that big night <br>Giving the tree the trim <br>You'll hear voices by starlight <br>Singing a Yuletide hymn <br><br>Oh, by gosh, by golly <br>It's time for mistletoe and holly <br>Fancy ties an' granny's pies <br>An' folks stealin' a kiss or two <br>As they whisper, "Merry Christmas" to you <br><br>Then comes that big night <br>Giving the tree the trim <br>You'll hear voices by starlight <br>Singing a Yuletide hymn <br><br>Oh, by gosh, by golly <br>It's time for mistletoe and holly <br>Fancy ties an' granny's pies <br>An' folks stealin' a kiss or two <br>As they whisper, "Merry Christmas" to you]]></content><category term="Frank Sinatra" label="Frank Sinatra"/><category term="Mistletoe And Holly (Remastered)" label="Mistletoe And Holly (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brook_Benton/This_Time_Of_The_Year_Remastered/</id><title>Brook Benton - This Time Of The Year (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Brook_Benton/This_Time_Of_The_Year_Remastered/" title="Brook Benton - This Time Of The Year (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas always comes this time of the year. <br><br>Little girls and little boys <br>Dream of worlds full of toys <br>This time of the year <br>When Christmas is near. <br><br>Evergreens are snowy white <br>Sleigh bells ring through the night <br>This time of the year <br>When Christmas is near. <br><br>And somewhere near a steeple <br>People kneel and pray <br>And choirs sing <br>Carols of Christmas day. <br><br>Santa Claus is on his way <br>Loads of joy, on his sleigh <br>This time of the year <br>When Christmas is near. <br><br>Hear the sleigh bells <br>Hear the sleigh bells <br>Hear the sleigh bells, ring.]]></content><category term="Brook Benton" label="Brook Benton"/><category term="This Time Of The Year (Remastered)" label="This Time Of The Year (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dean_Martin/Winter_Wonderland_Remastered/</id><title>Dean Martin - Winter Wonderland (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dean_Martin/Winter_Wonderland_Remastered/" title="Dean Martin - Winter Wonderland (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(Wonderland winter wonderland wonderland) <br>Sleigh bells ring are you listening <br>In the lane snow is glistening <br>A beautiful sight oh we're happy tonight <br>Walking in a winter wonderland <br><br>Gone away is the bluebird <br>Here to stay is a new bird <br>He's singing a song as we go along <br>Walking in a winter wonderland <br><br>Well in the meadow we can build a snowman <br>And pretend that he is Parson Brown <br>He'll say are you married we say no man <br>But you can do the job when you're in town <br><br>Later on we'll conspire as we dream by the fire <br>To face unafraid of the plans that we made <br>Walking in a winter wonderland <br><br>(In the meadow we can build a snowman) <br>And pretend he's a circus clown <br>We have lots of fun with Mr. Snowman <br>Until the other kiddies knock him down <br><br>Oh when it snows ain't it filling <br>Though your nose gets a chilling <br>We'll frolic and play the Eskimo way <br>Walking in a winter wonderland <br><br>(Wonderland wonderland)]]></content><category term="Dean Martin" label="Dean Martin"/><category term="Winter Wonderland (Remastered)" label="Winter Wonderland (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Johnny_Mathis/My_Kind_Of_Christmas_Remastered/</id><title>Johnny Mathis - My Kind Of Christmas (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Johnny_Mathis/My_Kind_Of_Christmas_Remastered/" title="Johnny Mathis - My Kind Of Christmas (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Winter night <br>In our town the roofs are white. <br>Windows bright with candlelight <br>That's my kind of Christmas. <br><br>Snowflakes fall <br>Holly hanging in the hall <br>Friendly neighbors come to call <br>That's my kind of Christmas. <br><br>That tall evergreen <br>Strung with silver lights in our front yard <br>An old-fashioned scene <br>like a painting on a Christmas card. <br><br>The season when <br>Christmas bells ring out again. <br>Peace on earth, goodwill to men <br>That's my kind of Christmas. <br><br>An old-fashioned scene <br>like a painting on a Christmas card. <br>The season when <br>Christmas bells ring out again. <br>Peace on earth, goodwill to men <br>That's my kind of Christmas]]></content><category term="Johnny Mathis" label="Johnny Mathis"/><category term="My Kind Of Christmas (Remastered)" label="My Kind Of Christmas (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perry_Como/That_Christmas_Feeling_Remastered/</id><title>Perry Como - That Christmas Feeling (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perry_Como/That_Christmas_Feeling_Remastered/" title="Perry Como - That Christmas Feeling (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the days of December are numbered <br>And the earth begs it's snowflakes to fall <br>That's the time of the year that Christmas is here <br>With peace and goodwill for all <br>How I love that Christmas feelin' <br>How I treasure it's friendly glow <br>See the way a stranger greets you <br>Just as though you'd met him Christmas's ago! <br><br>Christmas helps you to remember <br>To do what other folks hold dear <br>What a blessed place the world would be <br>If we had the Christmas feelin' all year]]></content><category term="Perry Como" label="Perry Como"/><category term="That Christmas Feeling (Remastered)" label="That Christmas Feeling (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/God_Rest_Ye_Merry_Gentlemen_Remastered/</id><title>Bing Crosby - God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/God_Rest_Ye_Merry_Gentlemen_Remastered/" title="Bing Crosby - God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[God rest you merry, gentlemen <br>Let nothing you dismay. <br>Remember Christ our Savior <br>Was born on Christmas Day; <br>To save us all from Satan's power <br>When we were gone astray. <br><br>(Oh tidings of comfort and joy) <br>(Comfort and joy) <br>(Oh tidings of comfort and joy) <br><br>In Bethlehem in Jewry <br>This blessed Babe was born <br>And laid within a manger <br>Upon this blessed morn <br>The which His Mother Mary <br>Did nothing take in scorn <br><br>(O tidings of comfort and joy) <br>(Comfort and joy) <br>(O tidings of comfort and joy) <br><br>From God our Heavenly Father <br>A blessed Angel came; <br>And unto certain Shepherds <br>Brought tidings of the same: <br>How that in Bethlehem was born <br>The Son of God by Name. <br><br>(O tidings of comfort and joy) <br>(Comfort and joy) <br>(O tidings of comfort and joy)]]></content><category term="Bing Crosby" label="Bing Crosby"/><category term="God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen (Remastered)" label="God Rest Ye Merry Gentlemen (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/Christmas_In_Killarney_Remastered/</id><title>Bing Crosby - Christmas In Killarney (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:12:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:12:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/Christmas_In_Killarney_Remastered/" title="Bing Crosby - Christmas In Killarney (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The holly green, the ivy green <br>The prettiest picture you've ever seen <br>Is Christmas in Killarney <br>With all of the folks at home <br><br>It's nice, you know, to kiss your beau <br>While cuddling under the mistletoe <br>And Santa Claus you know, of course <br>Is one of the boys from home <br><br>The door is always open <br>The neighbors pay a call <br>And Father John before he's gone <br>Will bless the house and all <br><br>How grand it feels to click your heels <br>And join in the fun of the jigs and reels <br>I'm handing you no blarney <br>The likes you've never known <br>Is Christmas in Killarney <br>With all of the folks at home]]></content><category term="Bing Crosby" label="Bing Crosby"/><category term="Christmas In Killarney (Remastered)" label="Christmas In Killarney (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nat_King_Cole/Theres_A_Train_Out_For_Dreamland_Remastered/</id><title>Nat King Cole - There`s A Train Out For Dreamland (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nat_King_Cole/Theres_A_Train_Out_For_Dreamland_Remastered/" title="Nat King Cole - There`s A Train Out For Dreamland (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This is our last dance together <br>Tonight soon will be long ago <br>And in our moment of parting <br>This is all I want you to know <br>There will be many other nights like this <br>And I'll be standing here with someone new <br>There will be other songs to sing, another fall, another spring <br>But there will never be another you <br>There will be other lips that I may kiss <br>But they won't thrill me like yours used to do <br>Yes, I may dream a million dreams <br>But how can they come true if there will never, ever be another you? <br>Yes, I may dream a million dreams <br>But how can they come true if there will never, ever be another you]]></content><category term="Nat King Cole" label="Nat King Cole"/><category term="There`s A Train Out For Dreamland (Remastered)" label="There`s A Train Out For Dreamland (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/While_The_Angelus_Was_Ringing_Remastered/</id><title>Frank Sinatra - While The Angelus Was Ringing (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/While_The_Angelus_Was_Ringing_Remastered/" title="Frank Sinatra - While The Angelus Was Ringing (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[While the Angelus was ringing, calling for the evening pray'r <br>I could hear the choir singing and I saw you standing there <br>Silently I stood beside you, how my heart was beating then <br>For my dreams have all come true, I was safely back with you <br>Never more to roam again <br>Then the great cathedral spire seemed to come alive and say <br>Through the voices of the choir, there will be a wedding day <br>Then a golden ray of sunlight, from a window in the sky <br>Shone upon us from above, heaven's blessing on our love <br>Now our love will never die <br><br>Then a golden ray of sunlight, from a window in the sky <br>Shone upon us from above, heaven's blessing on our love <br>Now our love will never die]]></content><category term="Frank Sinatra" label="Frank Sinatra"/><category term="While The Angelus Was Ringing (Remastered)" label="While The Angelus Was Ringing (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tennessee_Ernie_Ford/A_Rootin_Tootin_Santa_Claus_Remastered/</id><title>Tennessee Ernie Ford - A Rootin Tootin Santa Claus (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Tennessee_Ernie_Ford/A_Rootin_Tootin_Santa_Claus_Remastered/" title="Tennessee Ernie Ford - A Rootin Tootin Santa Claus (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[He's a rootin' tootin' Santa Claus <br>Ridin' reindeer through the sky <br>With his spurs a jingle janglin' <br>And his lasso swingin' high <br><br>He's a rootin' tootin' Santa Claus <br>Saddle bags all packed with toys <br>Through the chimney he will bring them all <br>To the dreaming girls and boys <br><br>Get along little reindeer, get along <br>Cover all the range tonight <br>It's a long long trail, an all-night trail <br>But you can bet your boots that Santa won't fail <br><br>He's a rootin' tootin' Santa Claus <br>And he's on his merry way <br>He will round up all your Christmas dreams <br>With a yippee yo kayah <br>Get along little reindeer, get along <br>Cover all the range tonight <br>It's a long long trail, an all-night trail <br>But you can bet your boots that Santa won't fail <br><br>He's a rootin' tootin' Santa Claus <br>And he's on his merry way <br>He will round up all your Christmas dreams <br>With a yippee yi yo kayah <br>Yippee yi yo kayah <br>Yippee yi yo kayah <br>Kayah]]></content><category term="Tennessee Ernie Ford" label="Tennessee Ernie Ford"/><category term="A Rootin Tootin Santa Claus (Remastered)" label="A Rootin Tootin Santa Claus (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Christmas_Night_In_Harlem_Remastered/</id><title>Louis Armstrong - Christmas Night In Harlem (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Christmas_Night_In_Harlem_Remastered/" title="Louis Armstrong - Christmas Night In Harlem (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hallelujah, Hallelujah, glory, Halle <br>What's all that noise <br>Hallelujah <br>Don't give up with that now <br><br>Glory, Halle <br>Who's that over in the corner <br>Hallelujah <br>I believe that's Mr Teagarden <br><br>Hey what you doin' up there, man <br>Last time I saw you <br>You were sayin' fare thee well to Harlem <br>I done bin wise g'wine <br>An' I ain't g'wine there n'more <br><br>You sho' come back the right time <br>It's Christmas up here <br>What d'ya mean up here <br>It's Christmas ev'rywhere <br><br>Yeah, but it ain't all Christmas <br>Like it's Christmas in Harlem <br>No <br><br>Ev'ry gal struttin' with her beau <br>Through the streets covered white with snow <br>Happy smiles er'ywhere you go <br>Christmas night in Harlem <br><br>Black and tans feelin' mighty good <br>In that old colored neighborhood <br>Here and now be it understood <br>Christmas night in Harlem <br><br>Ev'ryone is gonna sit up <br>Until after three <br>Ev'ryone will be all lit up <br>Like a Christmas tree <br><br>Come on now ev'ry coal black Joe <br>You just lead me t'the mistletoe <br>With a kiss and a hi de ho <br>Christmas night in Harlem <br><br>Hee, man, dog <br>What'd Santa Claus leave in your stockin' <br>Let me see, there's an orange, a jar <br>And, man, look at this slide trombone <br>Yeah, but it might not sound so pretty <br>Let me hear you tune it <br><br>Mr Mercer, I'm glad to be back in this festivity <br>Ah, you said it Mr T <br>It's Christmas night in Harlem <br>Well it's Christmas night in Harlem <br>Man, you drew the]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Christmas Night In Harlem (Remastered)" label="Christmas Night In Harlem (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perry_Como/Home_For_The_Holidays_Remastered/</id><title>Perry Como - Home For The Holidays (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perry_Como/Home_For_The_Holidays_Remastered/" title="Perry Como - Home For The Holidays (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, there's no place like home for the holidays <br>'Cause no matter how far away you roam <br>When you pine for the sunshine of a friendly gaze <br>For the holidays you can't beat home sweet home <br><br>I met a man who lives in Tennessee, he was heading for <br>Pennsylvania and some homemade pumpkin pie <br>From Pennsylvania, folks are travelling <br>Down to Dixie's sunny shore <br>From Atlantic to Pacific <br>Gee, the traffic is terrific <br><br>Oh, there's no place like home for the holidays <br>'Cause no matter how far away you roam <br>If you want to be happy in a million ways <br>For the holidays you can't beat home sweet home <br><br>Take a bus, take a train <br>Go and hop an aeroplane <br>Put the wife and kiddies in the family car <br>For the pleasure that you bring <br>When you make that doorbell ring <br>No trip could be too far <br><br>I met a man who lives in Tennessee, he was heading for <br>Pennsylvania and some homemade pumpkin pie some pumpkin pie <br>From Pennsylvania, folks are travelling <br>Down to Dixie's sunny shore <br>From Atlantic to Pacific <br>Gee, the traffic is terrific <br><br>Oh, there's no place like home for the holidays <br>'Cause no matter how far away you roam <br>If you want to be happy in a million ways <br>For the holidays you can't beat home sweet home <br>For the holidays you can't beat home sweet home]]></content><category term="Perry Como" label="Perry Como"/><category term="Home For The Holidays (Remastered)" label="Home For The Holidays (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/Santa_Claus_Is_Coming_To_Town_Remastered/</id><title>Bing Crosby - Santa Claus Is Coming To Town (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/Santa_Claus_Is_Coming_To_Town_Remastered/" title="Bing Crosby - Santa Claus Is Coming To Town (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You better watch out <br>You better not cry <br>Better not pout <br>I'm telling you why <br>Santa Claus is comin' to town, gather 'round <br><br>He's making a list <br>And checking it twice <br>He's gonna find out who's naughty and nice <br>Santa Claus is comin' to town <br><br>He sees you when you're sleeping <br>He knows when you're awake <br>He knows if you've been bad or good <br>So be good for goodness sake <br><br>You better watch out <br>You better not cry <br>Better not pout <br>I'm telling you why <br>Santa Claus is comin' to town <br><br>Little tin horns, little tin drums <br>Rudy toot toot and rummy tum tums <br>Santa Claus is comin' to town <br><br>And curly head dolls that cuddle and coo <br>Elephants, boats and kiddy cars too <br>Santa Claus is comin' to town <br><br>The kids and girls in boy land <br>Will have a jubilee <br>They're gonna build a toy land town <br>All around the Christmas tree <br><br>You better watch out, you better not cry <br>You better not pout, I'm telling you why <br>Santa Claus is comin' to town <br><br>He sees you when you're sleepin' <br>And he knows when you're awake <br>He knows when you've been bad or good <br>So be good for goodness sake <br><br>You better watch out <br>You better not cry <br>You better not pout <br>I'm telling you why <br>Santa Claus is comin' to town <br><br>You better watch out <br>You better not cry <br>Better not pout <br>I'm telling you why <br>Santa Claus is comin' to town <br><br>You mean, the big fat man with the long white beard <br>He's comin' to town]]></content><category term="Bing Crosby" label="Bing Crosby"/><category term="Santa Claus Is Coming To Town (Remastered)" label="Santa Claus Is Coming To Town (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peggy_Lee/Its_Christmas_Time_Again_Remastered/</id><title>Peggy Lee - It`s Christmas Time Again (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peggy_Lee/Its_Christmas_Time_Again_Remastered/" title="Peggy Lee - It`s Christmas Time Again (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Snowflakes fallin', church bells callin' <br>It's Christmas time again <br>Fires lighted, kids excited <br>It's Christmas time again <br>Now Santa's sleigh is on it's way, with candy canes and toys <br>And Wonderful things that Santa Claus brings <br>To good little girls and boys <br>Candle glow and mistletoe <br>It's Christmas Time Again <br>Stockings hung and carols sung <br>It's Christmas Time Again <br>There's thetree to trim <br>Our glasses brim with love and joy and cheer <br>To all a Merry Christmas, and a Happy New Year <br><br>There's thetree to trim <br>Our glasses brim with love and joy and cheer <br>To all a Merry Christmas, and a Happy New Year]]></content><category term="Peggy Lee" label="Peggy Lee"/><category term="It`s Christmas Time Again (Remastered)" label="It`s Christmas Time Again (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peggy_Lee/The_Christmas_Song_Merry_Christmas_To_You_Remastered/</id><title>Peggy Lee - The Christmas Song (Merry Christmas To You) (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peggy_Lee/The_Christmas_Song_Merry_Christmas_To_You_Remastered/" title="Peggy Lee - The Christmas Song (Merry Christmas To You) (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Chestnuts roasting on an open fire <br>Jack Frost nipping at your nose <br>Yuletide carols being sung by a choir <br>And folks dressed up like Eskimos <br><br>Everybody knows, a turkey and some mistletoe <br>Can help to make the season bright <br>Tiny tots with their eyes all aglow <br>Will find it hard to sleep tonight <br><br>They know that Santa's on his way <br>He's loaded lots of toys and goodies on his sleigh <br>And every mother's child is gonna spy <br>To see if reindeer really know how to fly <br><br>And so I'm offering this simple phrase <br>To kids from one to ninety two <br>Although it's been said many times, many ways <br>Merry Christmas to you <br><br>They know that Santa's on his way <br>With toys and goodies on his sleigh <br>And every mother's child is gonna spy <br>To see if reindeer really know how to fly <br><br>And so I'm offering this simple phrase <br>To kids from one to ninety two <br>Although it's been said many times, many ways <br>Merry Christmas to you]]></content><category term="Peggy Lee" label="Peggy Lee"/><category term="The Christmas Song (Merry Christmas To You) (Remastered)" label="The Christmas Song (Merry Christmas To You) (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chet_Atkins/Little_Drummer_Boy_Remastered/</id><title>Chet Atkins - Little Drummer Boy (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chet_Atkins/Little_Drummer_Boy_Remastered/" title="Chet Atkins - Little Drummer Boy (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come they told me, pa rum pum pum pum <br>A new born King to see, pa rum pum pum pum <br>Our finest gifts we bring, pa rum pum pum pum <br>To lay before the King, pa rum pum pum pum <br>Rum pum pum pum, rum pum pum pum <br><br>So to honor Him, pa rum pum pum pum <br>When we come <br><br>Little Baby, pa rum pum pum pum <br>I am a poor boy too, pa rum pum pum pum <br>I have no gift to bring, pa rum pum pum pum <br>That's fit to give the King, pa rum pum pum pum <br>Rum pum pum pum, rum pum pum pum <br><br>Shall I play for you, pa rum pum pum pum <br>On my drum <br><br>Mary nodded, pa rum pum pum pum <br>The ox and lamb kept time, pa rum pum pum pum <br>I played my drum for Him, pa rum pum pum pum <br>I played my best for Him, pa rum pum pum pum <br>Rum pum pum pum, rum pum pum pum <br><br>Then He smiled at me, pa rum pum pum pum <br>Me and my drum]]></content><category term="Chet Atkins" label="Chet Atkins"/><category term="Little Drummer Boy (Remastered)" label="Little Drummer Boy (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Ive_Got_My_Love_To_Keep_Me_Warm_Originally_Remastered/</id><title>Billie Holiday - I`ve Got My Love To Keep Me Warm (Originally Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billie_Holiday/Ive_Got_My_Love_To_Keep_Me_Warm_Originally_Remastered/" title="Billie Holiday - I`ve Got My Love To Keep Me Warm (Originally Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The snow is snowin' <br>The wind is blowin' <br>But I can weather the storm <br>What do I care how much it may storm <br>I've got my love to keep me warm <br><br>I can't remember <br>A worst December <br>Just watch those icicles form <br>What do I care if icicles form <br>I've got my love to keep me warm <br><br>Off with my overcoat <br>Off with my gloves <br>I need no overcoat <br>I'm burning with love <br>My heart's on fire <br>The flame grows higher <br>So I will weather the storm <br>What do I care how much it may storm <br>I've got my love to keep me warm <br><br>My heart's on fire <br>The flame grows higher <br>So I will weather the storm <br>What do I care how much it may storm <br>I've got my love to keep me warm]]></content><category term="Billie Holiday" label="Billie Holiday"/><category term="I`ve Got My Love To Keep Me Warm (Originally Remastered)" label="I`ve Got My Love To Keep Me Warm (Originally Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alma_Cogan/Christmas_Cards_Remastered/</id><title>Alma Cogan - Christmas Cards (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Alma_Cogan/Christmas_Cards_Remastered/" title="Alma Cogan - Christmas Cards (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas cards, Christmas cards <br>I love to see the pretty Christmas cards <br>Bringing you sweet regards <br>Wishing you the best of happiness <br>Love to write to someone I'm thinking of <br>Love to write to the place and folks I love <br>Love to send them a message of good cheer <br>With words sincere <br>When Christmas is here <br>Oh Christmas cards, Christmas cards <br>I love to see the pretty Christmas cards <br>Bringing you sweet regards <br>Wishing you the best of happiness <br>Little cards with their trees all dressed in snow <br>Little cards with their friendly fires aglow <br>Little cards with their lovely winter scene <br>When all the world is sweet and serene <br>Oh Christmas cards, Christmas cards <br>I love to see the pretty Christmas cards <br>Bringing you sweet regards <br>Wishing you the best of happiness <br>Every card in it's little envelope <br>Bares a wish and a greeting of good hope <br>And the love with a card I send is true <br>And I'll renew <br>Each Christmas to you <br>Oh Christmas cards, Christmas cards <br>I love to see the pretty Christmas cards <br>Bringing you sweet regards <br>Wishing you the best of happiness <br>Wishing you the best of happiness]]></content><category term="Alma Cogan" label="Alma Cogan"/><category term="Christmas Cards (Remastered)" label="Christmas Cards (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nat_King_Cole/Mrs_Santa_Claus_Remastered/</id><title>Nat King Cole - Mrs Santa Claus (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nat_King_Cole/Mrs_Santa_Claus_Remastered/" title="Nat King Cole - Mrs Santa Claus (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Who feeds the reindeer all their hay <br>Who wraps the gifts and packs the sleigh <br>Who's helping Santa every day <br>Mrs Santa Claus <br><br>Who keeps his red suit looking nice <br>Who does he turn to for advice <br>Who gives the brownies all their spice <br>Mrs Santa Claus <br><br>She pitter patters all around the workshop <br>The whole year long <br>Amid the happy clatter of the workshop <br>She sings a merry, merry Christmas song <br><br>Who reads the notes from girls and boys <br>Turns in the order for their toys <br>Fills every heart with wondrous joys <br>Mrs Santa Claus <br><br>She pitter patters all around the workshop <br>The whole year long <br>Amid the happy clatter of the workshop <br>She sings a merry, merry Christmas song <br><br>Who reads the notes from girls and boys <br>Turns in the order for their toys <br>Fills every heart with wondrous joys <br>Mrs Santa Claus <br>Mrs Santa Claus]]></content><category term="Nat King Cole" label="Nat King Cole"/><category term="Mrs Santa Claus (Remastered)" label="Mrs Santa Claus (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/Christmas_Dreaming_Remastered/</id><title>Frank Sinatra - Christmas Dreaming (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/Christmas_Dreaming_Remastered/" title="Frank Sinatra - Christmas Dreaming (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm doing <br>My Christmas dreaming <br>A little early this year <br>No sign of snow around <br>And yet I go around <br>Hearing jingle bells <br>Ringing in my ear <br><br>Your promise <br>Must be the reason <br>The happy season is here <br>So I'm doing <br>My Christmas dreaming <br>A little early this year <br><br>Your promise <br>Must be the reason <br>The happy season is here <br>So I'm doing <br>My christmas dreaming <br>A little early this year]]></content><category term="Frank Sinatra" label="Frank Sinatra"/><category term="Christmas Dreaming (Remastered)" label="Christmas Dreaming (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billy_Eckstine/Blue_Christmas_Remastered/</id><title>Billy Eckstine - Blue Christmas (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Billy_Eckstine/Blue_Christmas_Remastered/" title="Billy Eckstine - Blue Christmas (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll have a Blue Christmas without you <br>I'll be so blue just thinking about you <br>Decorations of red on a green Christmas tree <br>Won't mean a thing, if you're not here with me <br><br>And when those blue snowflakes start fallin' <br>That's when those blue memories start callin' <br>You'll be doin' all right, with your Christmas of white <br>But I'll have a blue, blue Christmas <br><br>I'll have a Blue Christmas that's certain <br>And when that blue heartache starts hurtin' <br>You'll be doin' all right, with your Christmas of white <br>But I'll have a blue, blue, blu, blue Christmas]]></content><category term="Billy Eckstine" label="Billy Eckstine"/><category term="Blue Christmas (Remastered)" label="Blue Christmas (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dean_Martin/Rudolph_The_Red-Nosed_Reindeer_Remastered/</id><title>Dean Martin - Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dean_Martin/Rudolph_The_Red-Nosed_Reindeer_Remastered/" title="Dean Martin - Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Rudolph Rudolph <br>Rudolph the red nose reindeer <br>Had a very shiny nose <br>And if you ever saw it <br>You would say it glows <br>All of the other reindeer <br>Used to laugh and call him names <br>They never let poor Rudy <br>Join in any reindeer games <br><br>Then one foggy Christmas eve <br>Santa came to say <br>Rudolph with your nose so bright <br>Won't you guide my sleigh tonight <br>Then how the reindeer loved him <br>As they shouted out with glee <br>Rudy the red nose reindeer <br>You'll go down in history <br><br>Rudolph the red nose reindeer <br>Had a very shiny nose <br>And if you ever saw it <br>You would say it glows <br>All of the other reindeer <br>Used to laugh and call him names <br>They never let poor Rudolph <br>Join in any reindeer games <br><br>Then one foggy Christmas eve <br>Santa came to say <br>Rudolph mit your nose so bright <br>Won't you guide mein sleigh tonight <br>Then how the reindeer loved him <br>As they shouted out with glee <br>Rudy the red beaked reindeer <br>You'll go down in history]]></content><category term="Dean Martin" label="Dean Martin"/><category term="Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer (Remastered)" label="Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Johnny_Mathis/What_Child_Is_This_Remastered/</id><title>Johnny Mathis - What Child Is This (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Johnny_Mathis/What_Child_Is_This_Remastered/" title="Johnny Mathis - What Child Is This (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What Child is this who, laid to rest On Mary's lap is sleeping <br>Whom angels greet with anthems sweet, While shepherds watch are keeping <br>This, this is Christ the King, Whom shepherds guard and angels sing <br>Haste, haste, to bring Him laud, The Babe, the Son of Mary <br><br>Why lies He in such mean estate, Where ox and ass are feeding <br>Good Christians, fear, for sinners here The silent Word is pleading <br>Nails, spear shall pierce Him through, The cross be borne for me, for you <br>Hail, hail the Word made flesh, The Babe, the Son of Mary <br><br>So bring Him incense, gold and myrrh, Come peasant, king to own Him <br>The King of kings salvation brings, Let loving hearts enthrone Him <br>Raise, raise a song on high, The virgin sings her lullaby <br>Joy, joy for Christ is born, The Babe, the Son of Mary]]></content><category term="Johnny Mathis" label="Johnny Mathis"/><category term="What Child Is This (Remastered)" label="What Child Is This (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Fisher/Here_Comes_Santa_Claus_Remastered/</id><title>Eddie Fisher - Here Comes Santa Claus (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eddie_Fisher/Here_Comes_Santa_Claus_Remastered/" title="Eddie Fisher - Here Comes Santa Claus (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Here comes Santa Claus <br>Here comes Santa Claus <br>Right down Santa Claus Lane <br>Vixen and Blitzen and all his reindeer <br>are pulling on the reins <br>Bells are ringing, children singing <br>All is merry and bright <br>Hang your stockings and say your prayers <br>'Cause Santa Claus comes tonight <br><br>Here comes Santa Claus <br>Here comes Santa Claus <br>Right down Santa Claus Lane <br>He's got a bag that is filled with toys <br>for the boys and girls again <br>Hear those sleigh bells jingle jangle <br>What a beautiful sight <br>Jump in bed, cover up your head <br>'Cause Santa Claus comes tonight]]></content><category term="Eddie Fisher" label="Eddie Fisher"/><category term="Here Comes Santa Claus (Remastered)" label="Here Comes Santa Claus (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ella_Fitzgerald/What_Are_You_Doing_New_Years_Eve_Remastered/</id><title>Ella Fitzgerald - What Are You Doing New Year`s Eve (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ella_Fitzgerald/What_Are_You_Doing_New_Years_Eve_Remastered/" title="Ella Fitzgerald - What Are You Doing New Year`s Eve (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe it's much too early in the game <br>Aah, but I thought I'd ask you just the same <br>What are you doing New Year's <br>New Year's Eve <br><br>Wonder whose arms will hold you good and tight <br>When it's exactly twelve o'clock that night <br>Welcoming in the New Year <br>New Year's Eve <br><br>Maybe I'm crazy to suppose <br>I'd ever be the one you chose <br>Out of a thousand invitations <br>You received <br><br>Aah, but in case I stand one little chance <br>Here comes the jackpot question in advance <br>What are you doing New Year's <br>New Year's Eve]]></content><category term="Ella Fitzgerald" label="Ella Fitzgerald"/><category term="What Are You Doing New Year`s Eve (Remastered)" label="What Are You Doing New Year`s Eve (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Paul_Anka/The_Christmas_Song_Remastered/</id><title>Paul Anka - The Christmas Song (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Paul_Anka/The_Christmas_Song_Remastered/" title="Paul Anka - The Christmas Song (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Chestnuts roasting on an open fire <br>Jack Frost nipping at your nose <br>Yule tide carols being sung by a choir <br>And folks dressed up like Eskimos <br><br>Everybody knows a turkey and some mistletoe <br>Help to make the season bright <br>Tiny tots with their eyes all aglow <br>Will find it hard to sleep tonight <br><br>They know that Santa's on his way <br><br>He's loaded lots of toys and goodies on his sleigh <br>And every mother's child is gonna spy <br>To see if reindeer really know how to fly <br><br>And so I'm offering this simple phrase <br>To kids from one to ninety two <br>Although it's been said many times, many ways <br>Merry Christmas to you]]></content><category term="Paul Anka" label="Paul Anka"/><category term="The Christmas Song (Remastered)" label="The Christmas Song (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sammy_Davis_Jr/Jingle_Bells_Remastered/</id><title>Sammy Davis Jr. - Jingle Bells (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sammy_Davis_Jr/Jingle_Bells_Remastered/" title="Sammy Davis Jr. - Jingle Bells (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jingle Bells <br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle all the way <br>Oh what fun it is to ride <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br><br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle all the way <br>Oh what fun it is to ride <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br><br>Dashing through the snow <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br>Over the fields we go <br>Laughing all the way <br>Bells on bop tails ring <br>Making spirts bright <br>What fun it is to <br>Ride a sleighing song tonight <br><br>Jingle Bells <br>Ji, Jingle Bells <br>Jingle all the way <br>Oh what fun it is to ride <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br>Ba la la la bop <br><br>Jingle Bells <br>Ji, Jingle Bells <br>Jingle all the way <br>Oh what fun it is to ride <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br><br>Dashing through the snow <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br>Over the fields we go <br>Laughing all the way <br>Bells on bop tails ring <br>Making spirts bright <br>What fun it is to <br>Ride a sleighing song tonight <br><br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle all the way <br>Oh what fun it is to ride <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br><br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle all the way <br>Oh what fun it is to ride <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br><br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle all the way <br>Oh what fun it is to ride <br>In a one horse open sleigh <br><br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle Bells <br>Jingle all the way <br>Oh what fun it is to ride <br>In a one horse open sleigh]]></content><category term="Sammy Davis Jr." label="Sammy Davis Jr."/><category term="Jingle Bells (Remastered)" label="Jingle Bells (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/White_Christmas_Remastered/</id><title>Bing Crosby - White Christmas (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/White_Christmas_Remastered/" title="Bing Crosby - White Christmas (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm dreaming of a white Christmas <br>Just like the ones I used to know <br>Where the treetops glisten <br>And children listen <br>To hear sleigh bells in the snow <br><br>I'm dreaming of a white Christmas <br>With every Christmas card I write <br>May your days be merry and bright <br>And may all your Christmases be white <br><br>I'm dreaming of a white Christmas <br>Just like the ones I used to know <br>Where the treetops glisten <br>And children listen <br>To hear sleigh bells in the snow <br><br>I'm dreaming of a white Christmas <br>With every Christmas card I write <br>May your days be merry and bright <br>And may all your Christmases be white]]></content><category term="Bing Crosby" label="Bing Crosby"/><category term="White Christmas (Remastered)" label="White Christmas (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/Youre_All_I_Want_For_Christmas_Remastered/</id><title>Bing Crosby - You`re All I Want For Christmas (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/Youre_All_I_Want_For_Christmas_Remastered/" title="Bing Crosby - You`re All I Want For Christmas (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're all I want for Christmas <br>All I want my whole life through <br>Each day is just like Christmas <br>Anytime that I with you <br><br>You're all I want for Christmas <br>And if all my dreams come true <br>Then I'll awake on Christmas mornin' <br>And find my stocking filled with you <br><br>You're all I want for Christmas <br>All I want my whole life through <br>Each day is just like Christmas <br>Anytime that I with you <br><br>You're all I want for Christmas <br>And if all my dreams come true <br>Then I'll awake on Christmas mornin' <br>And find my stocking filled with you <br>And find my stocking filled with you]]></content><category term="Bing Crosby" label="Bing Crosby"/><category term="You`re All I Want For Christmas (Remastered)" label="You`re All I Want For Christmas (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Cool_Yule_Remastered/</id><title>Louis Armstrong - Cool Yule (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:13:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:13:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Louis_Armstrong/Cool_Yule_Remastered/" title="Louis Armstrong - Cool Yule (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[From Coney Island to The Sunset Strip <br>Somebody's gonna make a happy trip <br>Tonight, while the moon is bright <br><br>He's gonna have a bag of crazy toys <br>To give the groanies of the girls and boys <br>So dig, Santa comes on big <br><br>He'll come a callin' when the snow's the most <br>When all you cats are sleepin' warm as toast <br>And you gonna flip when Old Saint Nick <br>a lick on the peppermint stick <br><br>He'll come a flyin' from a higher place <br>And fill the stocking by the fireplace <br>So you'll have a yule that's cool <br><br>Yeah, from Coney Island to The Sunset Strip <br>Somebody's gonna make a happy trip <br>Tonight, while the moon is bright <br><br>He's gonna have a bag of crazy toys <br>To give the groanies of the girls and boys <br>So dig, Santa comes on big <br><br>Come a callin' when the snow's the most <br>Cats are sleepin' warm as toast <br>And you gonna flip when the Old Saint Nick <br>a lick on the peppermint stick <br><br>He'll come a flyin' from the higher place <br>Fill the stockings by the fireplace <br>So you'll have a yule that's cool <br><br>Have a yule that's cool <br>Yeah, cool yule]]></content><category term="Louis Armstrong" label="Louis Armstrong"/><category term="Cool Yule (Remastered)" label="Cool Yule (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/The_Twelve_Days_Of_Christmas_Remastered/</id><title>Frank Sinatra - The Twelve Days Of Christmas (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:14:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:14:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/The_Twelve_Days_Of_Christmas_Remastered/" title="Frank Sinatra - The Twelve Days Of Christmas (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On the first day of Christmas my true love sent to me <br>Twelve lords leaping, Eleven ladies dancing, Ten pipers piping <br>Nine drummers drumming, Eight maids milking, Seven swans swimming <br>Six geese laying, Five gold rings <br>Four calling birds, Three french hens, Two turtle doves <br>And a partridge in a pear tree <br><br>On the first day of Christmas, we gave our loving dad my children gave to me <br>Twelve dozen kisses, Eleven jars of jelly, Ten silken hankies <br>Nine games of scrabble, Eight pairs of cufflinks, Seven books of fiction <br>Six golden lighters, Five ivory combs <br>Four mission lights, Three golf clubs, Two silken scarfs <br>And a most lovely lavender tie]]></content><category term="Frank Sinatra" label="Frank Sinatra"/><category term="The Twelve Days Of Christmas (Remastered)" label="The Twelve Days Of Christmas (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nat_King_Cole/The_Little_Christmas_Tree_Remastered/</id><title>Nat King Cole - The Little Christmas Tree (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:14:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:14:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Nat_King_Cole/The_Little_Christmas_Tree_Remastered/" title="Nat King Cole - The Little Christmas Tree (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Little Christmas tree <br>No one to buy you, give yourself to me <br>You're worth your weight in precious gold, you see <br>My little Christmas tree <br><br>Promise you will be <br>Nobody else's little Christmas tree <br>I'll make you sparkle, just you wait and see <br>My little Christmas tree <br><br>I'll put some tinsel in your hair <br>And you'll find that there's a strange new change <br>That you have never seen <br>I'll bring my boy a toy, he'll jump for joy <br>To see his bright new queen <br><br>With me you will go far <br><br>I'll show Saint Nick the tree you really are <br>And there'll be peace on earth <br>When Daddy lights your star <br>My little Christmas tree <br><br>With me you will go far <br>I'll show Saint Nick the tree you really are <br>And there'll be peace on Earth <br>When Daddy lights your star <br>My little Christmas tree <br><br>You're big enough for three <br>My little Christmas tree]]></content><category term="Nat King Cole" label="Nat King Cole"/><category term="The Little Christmas Tree (Remastered)" label="The Little Christmas Tree (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Harry_Belafonte/Marys_Boy_Child_Remastered/</id><title>Harry Belafonte - Mary`s Boy Child (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:14:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:14:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Harry_Belafonte/Marys_Boy_Child_Remastered/" title="Harry Belafonte - Mary`s Boy Child (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Long time ago in Bethlehem <br>So the Holy Bible say <br>Mary's boy child, Jesus Christ <br>Was born on Christmas day <br><br>Hark, now hear the angels sing <br>A new King born today <br>And man will live forever more <br>Because of Christmas day <br><br>While shepherds watched their flock by night <br>And see a bright new shining star <br>And hear a choir sing <br>The music seem to come from afar <br><br>Now Joseph and his wife Mary <br>Come to Bethlehem that night <br>And find no place to borne she child <br>Not a single room was in sight <br><br>Hark, now hear the angels sing <br>A new King born today <br>And man will live forever more <br>Because of Christmas day <br><br>By and by they find a little nook <br>In a stable all forlorn <br>And in a manger cold and dark <br>Mary's little boy was born <br><br>Hark, now hear the angels sing <br>A new King born today <br>And man will live forever more <br>Because of Christmas day]]></content><category term="Harry Belafonte" label="Harry Belafonte"/><category term="Mary`s Boy Child (Remastered)" label="Mary`s Boy Child (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perry_Como/Its_Beginning_To_Look_A_Lot_Like_Christmas_Remastered/</id><title>Perry Como - It`s Beginning To Look A Lot Like Christmas (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:14:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:14:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Perry_Como/Its_Beginning_To_Look_A_Lot_Like_Christmas_Remastered/" title="Perry Como - It`s Beginning To Look A Lot Like Christmas (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas <br>Everywhere you go <br>Take a look in the Five and Ten <br>Glistening once again <br>With candy canes and silver lanes aglow <br><br>It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas <br>Toys in every store <br>But the purdy est sight to see <br>Is the holly that will be on your own front door <br><br>A pair of Hop a long boots and a pistol that shoots <br>Is the wish of Barney and Ben <br>Dolls that will talk and will go for a walk <br>Is the hope of Janice and Jen <br>And Mom and Dad can hardly wait for school to start again <br><br>It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas <br>Everywhere you go <br>Now there's a tree in the Grand Hotel <br>One in the park as well <br>The sturdy kind that doesn't mind the snow <br><br>It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas <br>Soon the bells will start <br>And the thing that will make them ring <br>Is the carol that you sing <br>Right within your heart <br><br>A pair of Hop a long boots and a pistol that shoots <br>Is the wish of Barney and Ben <br>Dolls that will talk and will go for a walk <br>Is the hope of Janice and Jen <br>And Mom and Dad can hardly wait for school to start again <br><br>It's beginning to look a lot like Christmas <br>Soon the bells will start <br>And the thing that will make them ring <br>Is the carol that you sing <br>Right within your heart]]></content><category term="Perry Como" label="Perry Como"/><category term="It`s Beginning To Look A Lot Like Christmas (Remastered)" label="It`s Beginning To Look A Lot Like Christmas (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/Sleigh_Ride_Remastered/</id><title>Bing Crosby - Sleigh Ride (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:14:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:14:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bing_Crosby/Sleigh_Ride_Remastered/" title="Bing Crosby - Sleigh Ride (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just hear those sleigh bells jingling <br>Ring ting tingling too <br>Come on, it's lovely weather <br>For a sleigh ride together with you <br><br>Outside the snow is falling <br>And friends are calling Yoo hoo <br>Come on, it's lovely weather <br>For a sleigh ride together with you <br><br>Giddy yap, giddy yap, giddy yap <br>Let's go, Let's look at the show <br>We're riding in a wonderland of snow <br>Giddy yap, giddy yap, giddy yap <br>It's grand, just holding your hand <br>We're gliding along with a song <br>Of a wintry fairy land <br><br>Our cheeks are nice and rosy <br>And comfy cozy are we <br>We're snuggled up together <br>Like two birds of a feather would be <br><br>Let's take that road before us <br>And sing a chorus or two <br>Come on, it's lovely weather <br>For a sleigh ride together with you <br><br>There's a birthday party <br>At the home of Farmer Gray <br>It'll be the perfect ending a perfect day <br>We'll be singing the songs <br>We love to sing without a single stop <br>At the fireplace while we watch <br>The chestnuts pop Pop pop pop <br><br>There's a happy feeling <br>Nothing in the world can buy <br>When they pass around the coffee <br>And the pumpkin pie <br><br>It'll nearly be like a picture print <br>By Currier and Ives <br>These wonderful things are the things <br>We remember all through our lives <br><br>Just hear those sleigh bells jingling <br>Ring ting tingling too <br>Come on, it's lovely weather <br>For a sleigh ride together with you <br><br>Let's take that road before us <br>And sing a chorus or two <br>Come on, it's lovely weather <br>For a sleigh ride together with you]]></content><category term="Bing Crosby" label="Bing Crosby"/><category term="Sleigh Ride (Remastered)" label="Sleigh Ride (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/Have_Yourself_A_Merry_Little_Christmas_Remastered/</id><title>Frank Sinatra - Have Yourself A Merry Little Christmas (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:14:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:14:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Frank_Sinatra/Have_Yourself_A_Merry_Little_Christmas_Remastered/" title="Frank Sinatra - Have Yourself A Merry Little Christmas (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Have yourself a merry little Christmas <br>Let your heart be light <br>From now on our troubles <br>Will be out of sight <br><br>Have yourself a merry little Christmas <br>Make the Yuletide gay <br>From now on our troubles <br>Will be miles away, oh ooh <br><br>Here we are as in olden days <br>Happy golden days of yore, ah <br>Faithful friends who are dear to us <br>Gather near to us, once more, ooh <br><br>Through the years we all will be together <br>If the fates allow <br>Hang a shining star upon the highest bough <br>And have yourself a merry little Christmas now <br><br>Here we are as in olden days <br>Happy golden days of yore <br>Faithful friends who are dear to us <br>Gather near to us, once more <br><br>Through the years we all will be together <br>If the fates allow <br>Hang a shining star upon the highest bough, oh <br>And have yourself a merry little Christmas now, ooh <br><br>Merry Christmas <br>Merry Christmas]]></content><category term="Frank Sinatra" label="Frank Sinatra"/><category term="Have Yourself A Merry Little Christmas (Remastered)" label="Have Yourself A Merry Little Christmas (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dean_Martin/Let_It_Snow_Let_It_Snow_Let_It_Snow_Remastered/</id><title>Dean Martin - Let It Snow, Let It Snow, Let It Snow (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:14:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:14:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Dean_Martin/Let_It_Snow_Let_It_Snow_Let_It_Snow_Remastered/" title="Dean Martin - Let It Snow, Let It Snow, Let It Snow (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh, the weather outside is frightful <br>But the fire is so delightful <br>And since we've no place to go <br>Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow <br><br>It doesn't show signs of stopping <br>And I brought some corn for popping <br>The lights are turned way down low <br>Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow <br><br>When we finally kiss good night <br>How I'll hate going out in the storm <br>But if you really hold me tight <br>All the way home I'll be warm <br><br>The fire is slowly dying <br>And, my dear, we're still good bye ing <br>But as long as you love me so <br>Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow <br><br>When we finally kiss good night <br>How I'll hate going out in the storm <br>But if you really hold me tight <br>All the way home I'll be warm <br><br>The fire is slowly dying <br>And, my dear, we're still good bye ing <br>But as long as you love me so <br>Let it snow, let it snow, let it snow]]></content><category term="Dean Martin" label="Dean Martin"/><category term="Let It Snow, Let It Snow, Let It Snow (Remastered)" label="Let It Snow, Let It Snow, Let It Snow (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Johnny_Mathis/Silver_Bells_Remastered/</id><title>Johnny Mathis - Silver Bells (Remastered) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:14:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:14:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Johnny_Mathis/Silver_Bells_Remastered/" title="Johnny Mathis - Silver Bells (Remastered) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas makes you feel emotional <br>It may bring parties or thoughts devotional <br>Whatever happens or what may be <br>Here is what Christmas time means to me <br>City sidewalk, busy sidewalks <br>Dressed in holiday style <br>In the air there's <br>A feeling of Christmas <br>Children laughing, people passing <br>Meeting smile after smile <br>And on every street corner you'll hear <br>Silver bells, silver bells <br>It's Christmas time in the city <br>Ring a ling, hear them ring <br>Soon it will be Christmas day <br>City street lights <br>Even stop lights <br>Blink a bright red and green <br>As the shoppers rush home <br>With their treasures <br>Hear the snow crunch <br>See the kids bunch <br>This is Santa's big scene <br>And above all this bustle you'll hear <br>Silver bells, silver bells <br>It's Christmas time in the city <br>Ring a ling, hear them ring <br>Soon it will be Christmas day]]></content><category term="Johnny Mathis" label="Johnny Mathis"/><category term="Silver Bells (Remastered)" label="Silver Bells (Remastered)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/보스턴사운드/Desire_Feat_Eyz_Club_Edit/</id><title>보스턴사운드 - Desire (Feat. Eyz) (Club Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:16:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:16:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B3%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B4%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B4%EB%93%9C/Desire_Feat_Eyz_Club_Edit/" title="보스턴사운드 - Desire (Feat. Eyz) (Club Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I try sleep this tonight baby <br>but I don't wanna sleep <br>because I with you in tonight <br>I feel you everywhere <br>I'M gonna walk away outside <br>I try to rebulid up in mind <br>something crosses my mind <br>I'M stuck in your love <br>that is true <br>I Won't go home <br>this this tonight <br>I won't let it go <br>I won't stop this love <br>never again <br>can't stop desire <br>can't stop desire <br>I wanna you <br>do you need my love <br>how you feel <br>can't stop the feeling <br>I'll be your everything <br>this tonight baby <br>can you feel my heart baby <br>why don't you stay with me <br>I wanna be close to you tonight <br>tell me what you want <br>I'M gonna walk away outside <br>I try to rebulid up in mind <br>something crosses my mind <br>I'M stuck in your love <br>that is true <br>I Won't go home <br>this this tonight <br>I won't let it go <br>I won't stop this love <br>never again <br>can't stop desire <br>can't stop desire <br>I wanna you <br>do you need my love <br>how you feel <br>can't stop the feeling <br>I'll be your everything <br>this tonight baby <br>]]></content><category term="보스턴사운드" label="보스턴사운드"/><category term="Desire (Feat. Eyz) (Club Edit)" label="Desire (Feat. Eyz) (Club Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/보스턴사운드/Desire_Feat_Eyz_Chill_Edit/</id><title>보스턴사운드 - Desire (Feat. Eyz) (Chill Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:16:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:16:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B3%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B4%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B4%EB%93%9C/Desire_Feat_Eyz_Chill_Edit/" title="보스턴사운드 - Desire (Feat. Eyz) (Chill Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I try sleep this tonight baby <br>but I don't wanna sleep <br>because I with you in tonight <br>I feel you everywhere <br>I'M gonna walk away outside <br>I try to rebulid up in mind <br>something crosses my mind <br>I'M stuck in your love <br>that is true <br>I Won't go home <br>this this tonight <br>I won't let it go <br>I won't stop this love <br>never again <br>can't stop desire <br>I wanna you <br>do you need my love <br>how you feel <br>can't stop the feeling <br>I'll be your everything <br>this tonight baby <br>can you feel my heart baby <br>why don't you stay with me <br>I wanna be close to you tonight <br>tell me what you want <br>I'M gonna walk away outside <br>I try to rebulid up in mind <br>something crosses my mind <br>I'M stuck in your love <br>that is true <br>I Won't go home <br>this this tonight <br>I won't let it go <br>I won't stop this love <br>never again <br>can't stop desire <br>I wanna you <br>do you need my love <br>how you feel <br>can't stop the feeling <br>I'll be your everything <br>this tonight baby <br>]]></content><category term="보스턴사운드" label="보스턴사운드"/><category term="Desire (Feat. Eyz) (Chill Edit)" label="Desire (Feat. Eyz) (Chill Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/보스턴사운드/Desire_Feat_Eyz/</id><title>보스턴사운드 - Desire (Feat. Eyz) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:16:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:16:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B3%B4%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B4%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B4%EB%93%9C/Desire_Feat_Eyz/" title="보스턴사운드 - Desire (Feat. Eyz) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I try sleep this tonight baby <br>but I don't wanna sleep <br>because I with you in tonight <br>I feel you everywhere <br>I'M gonna walk away outside <br>I try to rebulid up in mind <br>something crosses my mind <br>I'M stuck in your love <br>that is true <br>I Won't go home <br>this this tonight <br>I won't let it go <br>I won't stop this love <br>never again <br>can't stop desire <br>I wanna you <br>do you need my love <br>how you feel <br>can't stop the feeling <br>I'll be your everything <br>this tonight baby <br>can't stop desire <br>I wanna you <br>do you need my love <br>how you feel <br>can't stop the feeling <br>I'll be your everything <br>this tonight baby <br>can you feel my heart baby <br>why don't you stay with me <br>I wanna be close to you tonight <br>tell me what you want <br>I'M gonna walk away outside <br>I try to rebulid up in mind <br>something crosses my mind <br>I'M stuck in your love <br>that is true <br>I Won't go home <br>this this tonight <br>I won't let it go <br>I won't stop this love <br>never again <br>can't stop desire <br>I wanna you <br>do you need my love <br>how you feel <br>can't stop the feeling <br>I'll be your everything <br>this tonight baby <br>can't stop desire <br>I wanna you <br>do you need my love <br>how you feel <br>can't stop the feeling <br>I'll be your everything <br>this tonight baby <br>can't stop desire <br>I wanna you <br>do you need my love <br>how you feel <br>can't stop the feeling <br>I'll be your everything <br>this tonight baby <br>can't stop desire <br>I wanna you <br>do you need my love <br>how you feel <br>can't stop the feeling <br>I'll be your everything <br>this tonight baby <br>]]></content><category term="보스턴사운드" label="보스턴사운드"/><category term="Desire (Feat. Eyz)" label="Desire (Feat. Eyz)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송래퍼/나와_Feat_Chawoo/</id><title>송래퍼 - 나와 (Feat. Chawoo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:16:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:16:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%9E%98%ED%8D%BC/%EB%82%98%EC%99%80_Feat_Chawoo/" title="송래퍼 - 나와 (Feat. Chawoo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아스팔트엔 10m마다 <br>시체가 널린 <br>가로등 켜질 시간 <br>노란 빛깔의 도시 <br>달의 토끼조차 쉬는 쌔까만 밤에 <br>잠에 들기도 안 들기도 <br>애매한 상태 <br>어느새 전화부에 있는 <br>엄지 손가락 <br>촉감이 왠지 <br>낚싯감이 걸릴 것 같아 <br>노심초사 끝에 <br>너에게 카톡을 보내 <br>지영아 술 먹을래 <br>나 남친 생겼어 <br>ok 나도 사실 잘 되가는 <br>여자 서너명 있고 <br>당장 나올 친구만 <br>합쳐도 덤프트럭 <br>너도 알지 오빠 원래 안 이러는 거 <br>결국에 또 전 여자친구에게 <br>전화를 걸었어 <br>절대로 취해서 이러는 건 아냐 <br>할 얘기가 많으니 잠깐만 나와 <br>왜 헤어지고 나서야 <br>너를 더 찾게 될까 <br>답장 없는 핸드폰 <br>시간만 흘러 째깍 <br>나 지금 너네 집 앞으로 <br>걸어가는 중이야 <br>넌 지금 어디니 <br>10분만이라도 만나줘 <br>싱숭생숭한 내 맘 <br>오늘은 말해야겠어 나와 <br>friday night friday night <br>혼자는 너무 외로운 <br>friday night <br>소화제 몇 알을 다 씹어도 <br>아직 건강할 우리 나이잖아 <br>아까부터 옆 테이블에 <br>자꾸 눈길이 가 <br>잘 빠진 옆 태 <br>농구공처럼 둥근 이마 <br>거울을 체크하지 수십 번 <br>긴장감은 불침번 <br>그녀에게 한 발짝 <br>가까워질수록 숨이 턱 <br>막혔지만 머쓱히 술잔을 권해 <br>혹시 남자친구 있으세요 <br>저 결혼 했는데요 <br>ok 저도 사심 없었고 <br>가정 평안하세요 <br>참 나와 보니 <br>우리도 영락없는 사내놈 <br>둘이 삽질만하다 <br>집에 가면 다행이죠 <br>어제도 술에 쩔어 <br>너네 집 앞에 갔었어 <br>아무리 다른 여자를 만나봐도 <br>결론은 너라는 <br>반복되는 싸이클 안 <br>이젠 의미 없어진 나의 낮과 밤들 <br>그렇게 오늘도 난 너네 집 앞이야 <br>나 지금 너네 집 앞으로 <br>걸어가는 중이야 <br>넌 지금 어디니 <br>10분만이라도 만나줘 <br>싱숭생숭한 내 맘 <br>오늘은 말해야겠어 나와 <br>friday night friday night <br>혼자는 너무 외로운 <br>friday night <br>그래 나야 술 취한 거 맞아 <br>사실 너한테 할 얘기도 없어 <br>그냥 나와 <br>이기적인 거 알아 <br>무시하는 게 맞아 <br>하지만 난 더 잃을 것도 없어 <br>그게 다야 <br>너한테 싸대기를 맞아도 <br>차라리 그게 낫겠네 <br>욕이라도 처 먹어야지 <br>뭐라도 남겠네 <br>하지만 오늘까진 <br>애매한 밤이니까 <br>뭐라도 해봐 <br>그래야 내일 남이니까 <br>나 지금 너네 집 앞으로 <br>걸어가는 중이야 <br>넌 지금 어디니 <br>10분만이라도 만나줘 <br>싱숭생숭한 내 맘 <br>오늘은 말해야겠어 나와 <br>friday night friday night <br>혼자는 너무 외로운 <br>friday night <br>fri fri fri friday night <br>fri fri fri friday night <br>fri fri fri friday night <br>fri fri fri friday night <br>fri fri fri friday night <br>fri fri fri friday night <br>]]></content><category term="송래퍼" label="송래퍼"/><category term="나와 (Feat. Chawoo)" label="나와 (Feat. Chawoo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송래퍼/빨래방_Feat_BK_입술세개/</id><title>송래퍼 - 빨래방 (Feat. BK, 입술세개) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:16:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:16:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%9E%98%ED%8D%BC/%EB%B9%A8%EB%9E%98%EB%B0%A9_Feat_BK_%EC%9E%85%EC%88%A0%EC%84%B8%EA%B0%9C/" title="송래퍼 - 빨래방 (Feat. BK, 입술세개) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혼자서 앉아있어 <br>텅 비어있는 빨래방 <br>기다리는 시간이 길지만 <br>i don't give a shit 이순간 <br>많은것들을 다시 생각해 난 <br>지금 느끼고 있는 이 생각 <br>혼자서 앉아있어 <br>텅 비어있는 빨래방 <br>가끔 멍하게 앉아 <br>사람 수를 세다 <br>초록불이 3번 바뀔때쯤 <br>그만두곤 해 <br>사실 별 소식없는 <br>핸드폰을 깨작 <br>만지다가 sns어플 <br>다 지우곤 해 <br>냉장고엔 어제 먹다 남은 <br>반쪽짜리 케익처럼 <br>누군가 날 베고 <br>내 속을 다 본듯해 <br>무기력해 맞아 요즘엔 <br>내 꿈을 경매장에 <br>내놓을까도 고민해 <br>새벽 가로등처럼 <br>밝은 내 방불은 <br>나방들이 쉬어가는 <br>동네 편의점 <br>너네한테 그런 <br>존재임에 감사해 <br>맞아 난 요즘 이런 <br>똥같은 생각도해 <br>정신차리고 내 <br>10년후를 그려봐도 <br>별 따기는 둘째치고 <br>별 볼일도 없는 학벌 <br>그냥 사업이나 <br>해볼까도 생각중이야 <br>백날 말해봐야 <br>지갑이 더 솔직하니까 <br>혼자서 앉아있어 <br>텅 비어있는 빨래방 <br>기다리는 시간이 길지만 <br>i don't give a shit 이순간 <br>많은것들을 다시 생각해 난 <br>지금 느끼고 있는 이 생각 <br>혼자서 앉아있어 <br>텅 비어있는 빨래방 <br>머리는 쓸데없는 <br>생각으로 꽉 차있네 <br>이건 쓸쓸한 계절탓으로 <br>돌리고 괜히 또 <br>쓱 읽었던 <br>만화를 꺼내들지 <br>잠시라도 떠날래 <br>상상으로 현실도피 <br>요즘은 그래 <br>나만 빼고 빠른듯해 <br>아니 오히려 나만이 <br>빠져서 멈춘듯해 <br>마냥 좋았던 결정 덕에 <br>매일이 걱정 <br>눈떠봐도 똑같은색 <br>모두다 검정 <br>송랩아 넌 나이라도 <br>어려서 괜찮아 <br>난 모레면 마흔 <br>오빠 소리 듣기도 힘들다 <br>언제까지 난 이렇게 <br>버틸 수 있을까 <br>무너졌을때 난 지금의 <br>날 버릴수 있을까 <br>빨래방 작은 텔레비젼에선 <br>나랑 상관없는 <br>얘기들만 떠드네 <br>나처럼 축축해진 <br>빨래를 담아내 <br>남은 동전으로 <br>로또나 사야지 <br>집에 가기전에 <br>혼자서 앉아있어 <br>텅 비어있는 빨래방 <br>기다리는 시간이 길지만 <br>i don't give a shit 이순간 <br>많은것들을 다시 생각해 난 <br>지금 느끼고 있는 이 생각 <br>혼자서 앉아있어 <br>텅 비어있는 빨래방 <br>집에 왔는데 내 기분처럼 <br>널저분한 빨랫감들 <br>귀찮지만 오늘도 <br>난 가야겠어 빨래방에 <br>보풀같은 마음 팍팍 털어줘 <br>실밥같은 하루 탈탈 말려줘 <br>꼬깃해진 지폐한장이 <br>내 삶인걸 <br>설마하는 복권한장이 <br>내 마음인걸 <br>혼자서 앉아있어 <br>텅 비어있는 빨래방 <br>기다리는 시간이 길지만 <br>i don't give a shit 이순간 <br>많은것들을 다시 생각해 난 <br>지금 느끼고 있는 이 생각 <br>혼자서 앉아있어 <br>텅 비어있는 빨래방 <br>]]></content><category term="송래퍼" label="송래퍼"/><category term="빨래방 (Feat. BK, 입술세개)" label="빨래방 (Feat. BK, 입술세개)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송래퍼/바지내려_Feat_비도승우_MC스나이퍼/</id><title>송래퍼 - 바지내려 (Feat. 비도승우, MC스나이퍼) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:16:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:16:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%9E%98%ED%8D%BC/%EB%B0%94%EC%A7%80%EB%82%B4%EB%A0%A4_Feat_%EB%B9%84%EB%8F%84%EC%8A%B9%EC%9A%B0_MC%EC%8A%A4%EB%82%98%EC%9D%B4%ED%8D%BC/" title="송래퍼 - 바지내려 (Feat. 비도승우, MC스나이퍼) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[ayo hold up hold up <br>한마디 할게 <br>여기 속보 송래퍼 <br>감성팔이 앨범 <br>떳어 키보더들아 <br>어서 다 어더더더 모여 <br>회사가 어쩌구 <br>0.5점 별점 눌러 <br>나는 동물원의 animal <br>다 구경났네 집 앞에 <br>철장열면 뒤질놈들 <br>입만 뻥긋 씨방새 <br>넌 절대 이해못해 <br>이 예술과 작품 <br>원래 눈은 모르지 <br>찐퉁과 짝퉁 what <br>내가 감성팔이래 <br>oh yeah <br>내 고향은 전라도 <br>개나리 밭 <br>나는 원래 촌놈 잘 들어 <br>멍청한 새꺄 <br>니가 빠는 랩퍼들이 <br>흑인 감성팔이라고 캌 퉤 <br>양키쉐키들한테 뺏긴 <br>한국힙합의 팬티 <br>질질싸서 순결마저 뺏김 <br>흑인백인 빨다보니 얘들 <br>국적은 다 shake it <br>새끼야 얼마나 <br>컷나보자 니 거시기 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>네가 계집애인지 아닌지나 <br>확인하게 바지내려 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>더러운 불알 두짝 사이에도 <br>땀이나게 바지내려 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>네가 계집애인지 아닌지나 <br>확인하게 바지내려 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>빨리 움직여 이 새끼야 <br>얼차려 바지내려 <br>까봐봐 바지 <br>내려봐봐 바지 <br>길고 짧은 건 <br>눈앞에 까고 재봐 병신 <br>남자는 목걸이 <br>굵기보다 자* 굵기 aight <br>your bitc**s taste like peach <br>맛나게 잘 먹었어 <br>돈의 맛보다 강력해 <br>* 의 맛 짜증날 때 <br>울리는 카톡처럼 <br>깐족 대지마 전화해 <br>바로 지금 당장 <br>난 없어 메르세데스 롤렉스 <br>근데도 다 따먹고 다녀 <br>fuckin' bitc** young rappers <br>beat는 내게 에이스 침대 <br>니들 flow는 뱅뱅사거리 <br>다 똑같애 <br>fuckin' 랩성괴 <br>뜨뜨뜨뜨뜨뜨뜨뜨뜨니 <br>딴엔 니가 진짜 같애 <br>다 *까 어린 꼰대 <br>내 삶은 어둡지만 <br>값비싼 주유소 <br>그 소유주 나란 <br>소 우주의 소유주는 <br>it's me <br>오늘 밤 넌 별똥별이나 보고 <br>소원 빌어 내게 <br>무릎 꿇고 빌어 <br>shit * 달린 소녀새끼 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>네가 계집애인지 아닌지나 <br>확인하게 바지내려 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>더러운 불알 두짝 사이에도 <br>땀이나게 바지내려 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>네가 계집애인지 아닌지나 <br>확인하게 바지내려 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>빨리 움직여 이 새끼야 <br>얼차려 바지내려 <br>남의 허물을 먼저 <br>보기보다 니자신을 봐봐 <br>너의 삐까뻔쩍한 <br>보석보다 밝지않는 가사 <br>정신 포경부터 <br>시켜싹 일단 꼬치까봐 <br>반항하면 다 벽돌물려 <br>주둥이차 빵빵 <br>남의 허물을 <br>보기보다 니자신을 봐봐 <br>너의 삐까뻔쩍한 <br>보석보다 밝지않는 가사 <br>정신 포경부터 <br>시켜싹 일단 꼬치까봐 <br>반항하면 다 벽돌물려 <br>주둥이차 빵빵 <br>대마초 한대 빨고 <br>교도소나 다녀 와야지 <br>초범은 집행유해니까 <br>한번쯤 가봐야지 <br>동네 건달형들 <br>칼침놓고 학교가듯이 <br>초짜래퍼 딱지떼려면 <br>경찰차 좀 타야지 <br>우울증약 처방받고 <br>대마빠는 새끼들 <br>그냥 씨발 대놓고해 <br>양키빠는 새끼들 <br>민증에다 빨간줄을 <br>그어놓고 자랑중 <br>비몽사몽 취해서 <br>다 예술가를 흉내중 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>네가 계집애인지 아닌지나 <br>확인하게 바지내려 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>더러운 불알 두짝 사이에도 <br>땀이나게 바지내려 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>네가 계집애인지 아닌지나 <br>확인하게 바지내려 <br>엎드려 뻗쳐 <br>빨리 움직여 이 새끼야 <br>얼차려 바지내려 <br>]]></content><category term="송래퍼" label="송래퍼"/><category term="바지내려 (Feat. 비도승우, MC스나이퍼)" label="바지내려 (Feat. 비도승우, MC스나이퍼)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송래퍼/제발_Feat_나들이/</id><title>송래퍼 - 제발 (Feat. 나들이) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:16:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:16:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%9E%98%ED%8D%BC/%EC%A0%9C%EB%B0%9C_Feat_%EB%82%98%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%B4/" title="송래퍼 - 제발 (Feat. 나들이) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[함성 꽉 찬 공연을 <br>끝내고 오는 길 <br>텅빈 정류장은 반갑게 <br>날 맞이하지 <br>바닥에 펼쳐있는 <br>수많은 감정들 중에 <br>빗자루로 치우지못한 <br>외로움을 줍네 <br>의심가득찬 눈으로 <br>보지마 제발 <br>내가 아프단걸 몰라 <br>저 우리 밖 세상은 <br>힘내란 말이 힘을 <br>보탤수있을까 <br>곱씹어 뒤집어 봐도 <br>결국 내 힘만 남잖아 <br>웃기지도 않은 <br>농담에 웃음짓고 <br>최신 유행어를 <br>어설프게 따라해도 <br>왜 난 행복하지 못한걸까 <br>그러면서도 <br>굳이 술자리에 나가는 <br>이유는 왜일까 <br>나만 배 떠난 <br>무인도에 갇혀있나 <br>아니면 사람사는 섬에 <br>나만 갇혀있나 <br>물음표로 끝난말인데 <br>대답은 물음표 <br>요즘은 뭐라도 뱉기 위해서 <br>숨을 쉬어 <br>제발 방문을 닫지마 <br>나를 데려가 <br>네게 짐일지라도 잠시 뿐이야 <br>오늘 나를 찾아왔을때 <br>눈을 감으면 <br>계속 멀어지잖아 <br>깊은 밤 나는 무얼 찾나 <br>저 골목길을 돌면 <br>어릴적 천원한장에 <br>울고웃던 친구들이 <br>나올것 같은데 <br>일부로 지갑을 열어도 <br>이젠 아무도 없네 <br>돈으로 사람 감정도 <br>사는데 나만 왜 <br>해가 뜨기전이 가장 <br>어둡다 하지만 <br>눈을 잃은 사람한텐 <br>그 말도 사치야 <br>어디든 데려가 받아 <br>내 술값 든 지갑 <br>내가 잘할게 제발 <br>나를 두고가지마 <br>제발 방문을 닫지마 <br>나를 데려가 <br>네게 짐일지라도 잠시 뿐이야 <br>오늘 나를 찾아왔을때 <br>눈을 감으면 <br>계속 멀어지잖아 깊은 밤 <br>나는 무얼 찾나 <br>사람 잔상이보여 <br>아침에 눈을 뜨면 <br>시끄러운 동네주민도 <br>살갑게보여 <br>밤새 헐 뜯고 욕하던 <br>옆집 중년 부부도 <br>손잡고 걸어가네 모두 <br>살만해보여 <br>난 그저 사랑이 받고 <br>싶었을뿐인데 <br>어린이 품에 안긴 <br>인형도 날 비웃고있네 <br>누구에겐 한마디가 <br>지루한 시 낭송 <br>또 누구에겐 숨구멍 <br>트이는 피난처 <br>오늘 나를 찾아왔을때 <br>눈을 감으면 <br>계속 멀어지잖아 깊은 밤 <br>나는 무얼 찾나 <br>]]></content><category term="송래퍼" label="송래퍼"/><category term="제발 (Feat. 나들이)" label="제발 (Feat. 나들이)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송래퍼/방파제_Feat_입술세개/</id><title>송래퍼 - 방파제 (Feat. 입술세개) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:17:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:17:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%9E%98%ED%8D%BC/%EB%B0%A9%ED%8C%8C%EC%A0%9C_Feat_%EC%9E%85%EC%88%A0%EC%84%B8%EA%B0%9C/" title="송래퍼 - 방파제 (Feat. 입술세개) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내가 너의 방파제가 되어서 <br>밀려드는 파도를 막아줄게 <br>형에게 말해줘 <br>say anything <br>형에게 말해줘 <br>say everything <br>we gon' be alright <br>왜 항상 밥먹을때 눈치를 봐 <br>왜 남자새끼가 인형을 <br>품에끼고 자냐 <br>왜 밖에서 쳐맞고서 <br>아닌척 집에 와 <br>아니긴 뭐가 아냐 <br>얼굴에 피 묻었잖아 <br>사실 동생아 이 형은 <br>그런 너가 너무 싫었어 <br>우린 매일 바빴던 <br>엄마의 된장찌개처럼 식었어 <br>신발있는 신발장 사람없는 집안 <br>굳게 닫힌 방문은 <br>니 발자국도 지웠어 <br>7살부터 변해버렸던 너의 성격 <br>옥상에서 떨어진 <br>사고현장이 선명하지만 <br>뒤의 내막은 아무도 몰랐네 <br>널 밀었던 친구의 <br>존재역시 몰랐네 <br>그 놈이 말하면 <br>죽인다고 했다며 <br>왜 말 안했어 <br>그때 너무 아팠다고 <br>몇년의 시간을 비춰왔던 <br>내 색안경은 <br>너의 머리흉터조차 <br>까맣게 칠했어 <br>형은 너무 쪽팔렸어 <br>우리가 가족인게 <br>너는 항상 숨기고 <br>싶었던 암호인게 <br>음악은 몰라도 <br>내 노래는 좋아했던 호영이야 <br>이젠 군대에서 듣겠네 <br>그래 못난 형이야 <br>내가 너의 방파제가 되어서 <br>밀려드는 파도를 막아줄게 <br>형에게 말해줘 <br>say anything <br>형에게 말해줘 <br>say everything <br>we gon' be alright <br>이래나 저래나 <br>우린 피를 나눈 형제 <br>이 뭐 같은 바깥 세상과 <br>씨름하네 평생 <br>다리에 힘풀려도 주저앉지마 <br>누구나 그때가 <br>결승점 코 앞이야 <br>그래 원망도 많이 했어 <br>가슴엔 알이뱄어 <br>항상 나는 너를 위한 <br>손과 발이됐어 <br>신발끈 묶어봐 <br>어릴적 그 날 처럼 <br>행진하는거야 <br>너가 신은 군화처럼 <br>이제 굳게 닫힌 방문을 나와 <br>달콤함은 어젯 밤에 <br>꿨던 꿈이 아냐 <br>동굴같은 방을 비추는 <br>핸드폰 조명과 <br>일기장속 세상은 <br>현실과 많이 달라 <br>오죽 괴로웠으면 <br>그래 거기에다 적었을까 <br>또 그 펜의 무게는 <br>얼마나 무거웠을까 <br>동생아 파도가 너를 덮칠때 <br>형이 방파제가 되어줄게 <br>쉬어도되 <br>내가 너의 방파제가 되어서 <br>밀려드는 파도를 막아줄게 <br>형에게 말해줘 <br>say anything <br>형에게 말해줘 <br>say everything <br>we gon' be alright <br>내가 너의 밀려드는 <br>형에게 말해줘 <br>형에게 말해줘 <br>내가 너의 밀려드는 <br>형에게 말해줘 <br>형에게 말해줘 <br>]]></content><category term="송래퍼" label="송래퍼"/><category term="방파제 (Feat. 입술세개)" label="방파제 (Feat. 입술세개)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송래퍼/Back_In_The_Day/</id><title>송래퍼 - Back In The Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:17:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:17:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%9E%98%ED%8D%BC/Back_In_The_Day/" title="송래퍼 - Back In The Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이젠 내 얘기를 <br>뱉을 차례지 <br>그때는 2007년 <br>난 중학생이 됐고 <br>교복은 꽉끼는 fit ya <br>학교종이 땡치면 <br>염색을 한 패거리들과 <br>사각정에 앉아 <br>뻐끔 뻐끔대 <br>god damn 그 다음날엔 <br>학주한테 걸렸지 <br>그 벌로 삭발을 했지만 <br>문제는 하나 더있지 <br>날 이렇게 부르더라 <br>mc 스나이퍼 <br>아마 그때가 <br>힙합을 듣게 된 시발점 <br>uh 암사동 노래방에선 <br>better than yesterday를 <br>달달 외우고 다녔어 <br>그 다음 날 또 내게 <br>붙은 새로운 별명 <br>그게 뭐냐고 <br>아직 쓰고 있잖아 <br>우리집에서 5분거리인 <br>배치기에 집 앞 <br>뭉 탁 나와라 <br>소리를 꽥꽥 지른 다음 <br>못참은 탁이 <br>창문에 욕을 할때도 <br>얼굴봐서 좋아죽던 <br>13살짜리 랩퍼 <br>매주 용돈을 모았네 <br>천원 세장를 꼬박 애껴 <br>샀던 씨디는 영어듣기 <br>대신 울려 고막에 <br>선생은 내가 멍청하대 <br>그 멍청이의 행보 <br>2절에 설명할게 <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>힙합 플레이야 랩잡에 <br>녹음물을 올렸던 시절 <br>지금보면 웃기지 <br>코흘리개 삐쩍 말랐던 <br>반항심 가득한 아이 <br>홍대공연 관객은 <br>열에서 열다섯명 사이 <br>조바심에 봤던 방탄소년단 <br>오디션은 의도치 <br>않게도 8강에 도달 <br>그때는 그게 <br>대박이었어 임마 <br>자녹게라는 알에서 <br>나온 강동구 rapstar <br>다음장 애기티는 벗고 <br>내가 고등학생 때 <br>축제공연 오디션 노래는 <br>슈프림팀의 땡땡땡 <br>ah 선생은 이런 장르는 <br>안된다면서 비보이팀의 <br>합류를 권하네 <br>그때 내가 했던 <br>프리스타일 랩중에 가사 <br>난 목소리를 팔지 <br>자존심 안팔아 <br>합격자 명단이 <br>학교 정문에 걸렸네 <br>난 결국 내팀을 <br>무대에 올렸네 <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>난 고3이 됐어 <br>년도로 치면 2012 <br>쇼미더머니는 평론가들이 <br>불지피기에 <br>딱 좋은 땔감이 됐지 <br>나도 역시 <br>출연을 고사했지만 <br>거울 속 날 봤지 <br>내 5년전 우상인 <br>mc 스나이퍼 <br>프로그램이 끝난 후 <br>난 다시 그의 손을 꽉 잡았어 <br>내 간절함을 모른 척 <br>할 수 없었다는 그 말 <br>내 심장은 요동쳤네 쿵쾅 <br>a 스나이퍼 사운드 <br>지하 작업실에서 <br>계약서를 받지 <br>내용은 됐고 난 믿었어 <br>30초만에 지장 찍었고 <br>물론 그 전에 우린 <br>30번 봤지 남자대 <br>남자로 회사밖에서 <br>알에서 나온 새끼는 <br>아비를 알아봤어 <br>선명해 일리닛과 <br>아웃사이더가 건넨 악수 <br>열아홉 소년에게 펼쳐진 <br>한편의 영화같은 다큐 <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>back in the day <br>go back to the past ya <br>back in the day <br>i wanna go back <br>]]></content><category term="송래퍼" label="송래퍼"/><category term="Back In The Day" label="Back In The Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/송래퍼/문을_열다/</id><title>송래퍼 - 문을 열다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:17:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:17:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%86%A1%EB%9E%98%ED%8D%BC/%EB%AC%B8%EC%9D%84_%EC%97%B4%EB%8B%A4/" title="송래퍼 - 문을 열다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[원래 사람관계라는게 <br>텅빈 우물같아서 <br>사이가 깊어지면 <br>언젠가는 넘치는 법 <br>난 상처가 다 곪아버린 <br>낡은 망부석 <br>언제든 전화해 <br>기다리고 있어 <br>남자끼리 술 한잔하면 <br>풀릴것도 알지만 <br>꺼리를 만드는게 <br>더 어려운건 왜일까 <br>요새는 프로필사진으로 <br>안부를 확인해 <br>새끼 잘 지내고있네 <br>난 꼰대같이 자존심만 <br>쎈 더러운 성격 <br>그래서 날 이해하는 <br>사람만 어울려 <br>근데 누가 내 앞에서 <br>니 욕을한다면 <br>난 한치의 고민없이 <br>걔를 때릴수있어 <br>난 니 앞에서만 <br>입꼬리를 내릴수있어 <br>하지만 가끔은 그것마저 <br>힘들수있어 <br>괜찮아 bro 니 <br>목소리만 들어도 <br>나보다 힘들 너를 위해 <br>취할수있어 <br>이게 나야 여자도 똑같지 <br>난 2년전에 서울서 <br>한 송이의 못다핀 <br>꽃을 찾았고 <br>너무나 아름다워서 <br>나만 볼수있게 <br>철장안에 가뒀어 <br>어쩌면 그게 너가 <br>시들어버렸던 이유지 <br>남자다운척을 하며 <br>자존심도 비웠지만 <br>정작 너가 원한건 <br>따듯한 햇살인걸 <br>난 기다리고있어 <br>서울 그곳에서 <br>난 따져보면 자존심이 <br>쎈것도 아냐 <br>혼자 남는게 두려운 <br>겁쟁이 일뿐 <br>불 같은 만남이 좋아서 <br>데인적도 많아 <br>이젠 치이고 치여서 <br>갈 길을 잃은 돌 <br>요즘엔 그래 <br>나부터 잘돼야해 <br>3평 남짓한 방 한칸에서 <br>난 밤을 더 새 <br>사랑했던 너를 위해 <br>사랑할 누굴 위해 <br>지친 나를 채찍질 <br>하면서 잠에서 깨 <br>어쩌면 이건 가족을 잃은 <br>수컷의 울음소리 <br>누구는 행복해 보이겠지 <br>나의 눈 웃음이 <br>하지만 넌 알지 <br>송승민이 어떤 놈인지 <br>겉으론 티 못내지 <br>불안함과 두근거림 <br>그래서 수도없이 많아 <br>숨 죽인 날들 <br>이젠 맘대로 구길래 <br>웃음뿐인 얼굴 <br>내 목소리가 진심으로 <br>네게 닿길 바래 <br>자 이제는 너네가 <br>내 얘기를 들어줄 차례 <br>]]></content><category term="송래퍼" label="송래퍼"/><category term="문을 열다" label="문을 열다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bard/길을_잃은_사람/</id><title>Bard - 길을 잃은 사람 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:18:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:18:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Bard/%EA%B8%B8%EC%9D%84_%EC%9E%83%EC%9D%80_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C/" title="Bard - 길을 잃은 사람 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[계절은 내 발 길을 재촉 하듯이 <br>오기가 무섭게 떠나가는 구나 <br>힘겨운 걸음을 떼어놓기도 전에 <br>모든 풍경들이 낯설어지는 구나 <br>나에게 오는 길이 너무 멀어서 <br>길을 잃고 헤맬까 <br>두려워지는 구나 <br>뒤돌아 볼 수도 없을 만큼 빠르게 <br>우리 하늘은 저무는 구나 <br>이리 고독한 거였나 <br>봄바람도 매섭구나 <br>너에게로 가까우려면 <br>너에게서 떠나야하는 구나 <br>]]></content><category term="Bard" label="Bard"/><category term="길을 잃은 사람" label="길을 잃은 사람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/홍삼트리오/기도/</id><title>홍삼트리오 - 기도 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:19:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:19:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%99%8D%EC%82%BC%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC%EC%98%A4/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84/" title="홍삼트리오 - 기도 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아~ 아~ 아~ 아~ <br>아~ 아~ 아~ 아~ <br><br>그리움에 불러보는 <br>아픈 내 가슴속에 맺힌 그녀 <br>나 언제나 한숨지며 그리워 할 때 <br>성모앞에 드리는 기도 <br>내님의 소식 전해주소서 <br><br>가버린 님 언제나 오시려나 <br>그리워 (그리워) <br>지친 마음 (지친 마음) <br>오늘도 기다리네 <br>아~ 아~ 아~ 아~ 기다리네 <br><br>그리움에 불러보는 <br>아픈 내 가슴속에 맺힌 그녀 <br>나 언제나 한숨지며 그리워 할 때 <br>성모 앞에 드리는 기도 <br>내님의 소식 전해주소서 <br><br>가버린 님 언제나 오시려나 <br>그리워 (그리워) <br>지친 마음 (지친 마음) <br>오늘도 기다리네 <br>아~ 아~ 아~ 아~ 기다리네 <br>기다리네 기다리네 <br>기다리네]]></content><category term="홍삼트리오" label="홍삼트리오"/><category term="기도" label="기도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한경애/옛시인의_노래/</id><title>한경애 - 옛시인의 노래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:19:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:19:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EA%B2%BD%EC%95%A0/%EC%98%9B%EC%8B%9C%EC%9D%B8%EC%9D%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="한경애 - 옛시인의 노래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마른나무 가지에서 떨어지는 <br>작은 잎새 하나 <br>그대가 나무라 해도 <br>내가 내가 잎새라 해도 <br>우리들의 사이엔 아무것도 <br>남은게 없어요 <br>그대가 나무라 해도 <br>내가 내가 잎새라 해도 <br>좋은날엔 시인의 눈빛 되어 <br>시인의 가슴이 되어 <br>아름다운 사연들을 태우고 <br>또 태우고 태웠었네 <br>뚜루루루 귓전에 맴도는 <br>낮은휘파람 소리 <br>시인은 시인은 노래 부른다 <br>그 옛날의 사랑 얘기를 <br><br>좋은날엔 시인의 눈빛 되어 <br>시인의 가슴이 되어 <br>아름다운 사연들을 태우고 <br>또 태우고 태웠었네 <br>뚜루루루 귓전에 맴도~는 <br>낮은 휘파람 소리 <br>시인은 시인은 노래 부른다 <br>그 옛날의 사랑 얘기를 <br>그 옛날의 사랑 얘기를]]></content><category term="한경애" label="한경애"/><category term="옛시인의 노래" label="옛시인의 노래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/배따라기/비와_찻잔_사이/</id><title>배따라기 - 비와 찻잔 사이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:19:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:19:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B0%EB%94%B0%EB%9D%BC%EA%B8%B0/%EB%B9%84%EC%99%80_%EC%B0%BB%EC%9E%94_%EC%82%AC%EC%9D%B4/" title="배따라기 - 비와 찻잔 사이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금 창 밖엔 비가 내리죠 <br>그대와 난 또 이렇게 둘이고요 <br>비와 찻잔을 사이에 두고 <br>할 말을 잃어 묵묵히 앉았네요 <br>지금 창 밖엔 낙엽이 져요 <br>그대 모습은 낙엽 속에 잠들고 <br>비와 찻잔을 사이에 두고 <br>할 말을 잃어 묵묵히 앉았네요 <br>그대 모습 낙엽 속에 있고 <br>내 모습은 찻잔 속에 잠겼네 <br>그대 모습 낙엽 속에 낙엽 속에 <br>낙엽 속에 잠겼어요 <br>지금 창 밖엔 비가 내리죠 <br>그대와 난 또 이렇게 둘이고요 <br>비와 찻잔을 사이에 두고 <br>할 말을 잃어 묵묵히 앉았네요 <br>지금 창 밖엔 낙엽이 져요 <br>그대 모습은 낙엽 속에 잠들고 <br>비와 찻잔을 사이에 두고 <br>할 말을 잃어 묵묵히 앉았네요 <br>그대 모습 낙엽 속에 있고 <br>내 모습은 찻잔 속에 잠겼네 <br>그대 모습 낙엽 속에 낙엽 속에 <br>낙엽 속에 잠겼어요 <br>그대 모습 낙엽 속에 있고 <br>내 모습은 찻잔 속에 잠겼네 <br>그대 모습 낙엽 속에 낙엽 속에 <br>낙엽 속에 잠겼어요]]></content><category term="배따라기" label="배따라기"/><category term="비와 찻잔 사이" label="비와 찻잔 사이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김세환/토요일_밤에/</id><title>김세환 - 토요일 밤에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:20:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:20:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B8%ED%99%98/%ED%86%A0%EC%9A%94%EC%9D%BC_%EB%B0%A4%EC%97%90/" title="김세환 - 토요일 밤에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[긴머리에 짧은치마 아름다운 그녀를 보면 무슨말을 하여야 할까 <br>오~토요일밤에~ 토~요일밤 토요일밤에 나 그대를 만나리~ <br>토~요일밤 토요일밤에~ 나 그대를 만~나리라 <br><br>세상에서 제일가는 믿음직한 그이를보면 무슨말을 하여야할까 <br>오~토요일밤에~ 토~요일밤 토요일밤에~ <br>나 그대를~만나리~ 토~요일밤 토요일밤에~ <br>나 그대를 만나리라~ <br><br>아름다운 노랫소리 멀리멀리 퍼져갈때 희망에찬 내일을위해 <br>오~토요일밤에~ 토요일밤 토요일밤에~ <br>나 그대~를 만나리~ 토~요일밤 토요일밤에~ <br>나 그대~를 만나리라 <br>토~요일밤 토요일밤에~ 나 그대를 만나리~]]></content><category term="김세환" label="김세환"/><category term="토요일 밤에" label="토요일 밤에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김현식/사랑했어요/</id><title>김현식 - 사랑했어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:20:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:20:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%ED%98%84%EC%8B%9D/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%96%88%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="김현식 - 사랑했어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[돌아서 눈 감으면 잊을까 <br>정든 님 떠나가면 어이해 <br>발길에 부딪히는 사랑의 추억 <br>두 눈에 맺혀지는 눈물이여 <br>이제 와 생각하면 당신은 <br>내 마음 깊은 곳에 찾아와 <br>사랑은 기쁨보다 아픔인 것을 <br>나에게 심어 주었죠 <br>사랑했어요 그땐 몰랐지만 <br>이 마음 다 바쳐서 <br>당신을 사랑했어요 <br>이젠 알아요 사랑이 무언지 <br>마음이 아프다는 걸 <br><br>돌아서 눈 감으면 잊을까 <br>정든 님 떠나가면 어이해 <br>발길에 부딪히는 사랑의 추억 <br>두 눈에 맺혀지는 눈물이여 <br><br>사랑했어요 그땐 몰랐지만 <br>이 마음 다 바쳐서 <br>당신을 사랑했어요 <br>이젠 알아요 사랑이 무언지 <br>마음이 아프다는 걸 <br><br>돌아서 눈 감으면 잊을까 <br>정든 님 떠나가면 어이해 <br>발길에 부딪히는 사랑의 추억 <br>두 눈에 맺혀지는 눈물이여 <br>발길에 부딪히는 사랑의 추억 <br>두 눈에 맺혀지는 눈물이여]]></content><category term="김현식" label="김현식"/><category term="사랑했어요" label="사랑했어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/YD_와이디/Realize/</id><title>YD (와이디) - Realize - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:20:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:20:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/YD_%EC%99%80%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94/Realize/" title="YD (와이디) - Realize - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔 드는 생각인데 <br>이 모든 끝엔 <br>뭐가 있을지 궁금해 <br>yeah <br>이미 지나온 날들 <br>들춰보기엔 <br>먼지 쌓여서 눈이 따가워 <br>속상해서 술 한잔 하고 <br>act like I'm okay <br>realize that i was fake <br>realize that i was fake <br>gotta know what is real <br>갈피를 못잡고 해매이는 <br>저녁 노을에 비친 그림자도 <br>위기감을 느껴서 흔들거려 <br>스물여섯 <br>막다른 길 위에 접어들어 <br>요샌 시간가는게 <br>나도 가끔 놀래 <br>스쳐갔던 말이 <br>딱 맞아 떨어지네 <br>너도 이쯤 되면 일주일이 <br>하루같을꺼라던 말을 <br>듣고나서 속으론 <br>뭔 말인지 <br>나만 뒤처지는 느낌 <br>알게 모르게 <br>찾아오는 긴장감 속 왠지 <br>소름이 돋네 날씨 때문인지 <br>계절이 변할때쯤엔 <br>기분탓에 걸렸었던 감기 <br>huh 꾀병이였지 <br>뭐 남들 다 입고 타는 거 <br>갖고 싶어서 <br>배아파 했던거였지 뭐 <br>허세 가득한 몇 년전 <br>내 모습을 보면 <br>쓰레기통처럼 <br>부질없었던 내 속 <br>가끔 드는 생각인데 <br>이 모든 끝엔 <br>뭐가 있을지 궁금해 <br>yeah <br>이미 지나온 날들 <br>들춰보기엔 <br>먼지 쌓여서 눈이 따가워 <br>속상해서 술 한잔 하고 <br>act like I'm okay <br>realize that i was fake <br>realize that i was fake <br>고민끝에 결정 했던건 <br>오직 내 길을 걷는 것 <br>자유롭고싶어 <br>한쪽을 포기하려 애썼고 <br>무겁던 짐을 선택했었어 <br>그래서 내 안에 <br>모든걸 비웠고 <br>i mean i gotta go <br>아직 늦지 않았다고 <br>날 놓아주지않던 거울속 <br>내 자신과 타협하며 <br>다독이고 타일러 <br>악순환의 반복이 <br>모든게 끝이나길 바라며 <br>남탓하긴 싫어하는 <br>내 성격이 때론 <br>감당이 안될 때가 <br>많았었지 물론 <br>진짜와 가짜를 <br>구별하려 했었던 <br>그 과정에서 생겼던 <br>몇가지 conflict <br>좋은게 좋은 거라 <br>여기다보니 <br>멀리해야 했었던것들 <br>그때서 깨달았지 <br>솔직히 궁금해지네 <br>이 모든끝에 가면 <br>뭐가 남는건지 <br>gotta know what is real <br>가끔 드는 생각인데 <br>이 모든 끝엔 <br>뭐가 있을지 궁금해 <br>yeah <br>이미 지나온 날들 <br>들춰보기엔 <br>먼지 쌓여서 눈이 따가워 <br>속상해서 술 한잔 하고 <br>act like I'm okay <br>realize that i was fake <br>realize that i was fake <br>realize that i was fake <br>]]></content><category term="YD (와이디)" label="YD (와이디)"/><category term="Realize" label="Realize"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/YD_와이디/일기장_Journey/</id><title>YD (와이디) - 일기장 (Journey) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:20:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:20:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/YD_%EC%99%80%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94/%EC%9D%BC%EA%B8%B0%EC%9E%A5_Journey/" title="YD (와이디) - 일기장 (Journey) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루가 지나갈때 <br>지나쳤었던 거울 속 <br>내 모습 이유 모를 죄책감에 <br>외면했었던건 어제의 내 모습 <br>이것또한 지나 갈꺼라 <br>믿었었던건 내 안에 그려둔 <br>자기합리화에 익숙해져 <br>어리석었던 몇 년전 내 모습 <br>밥 한끼 아껴먹고 <br>시간앞에선 무뎌졌던 그때가 <br>지금은 몇 글자 끄적이면서 <br>고개를 끄떡이고 <br>피해망상이 날 괴롭힐때 <br>난 그들을 멀리했고 <br>아니나 다를까 연락없던 <br>놈들은 간을보면서 <br>내 주변을 핧기 시작했고 <br>uh 초등학교때 억지로 했던 <br>습관들이 이제와서 <br>눈물나게 그립네 <br>다시 한 번 써볼라고 <br>이 모든게 언제까지 내옆에 <br>남아있을지 녹슨 때 묻은 <br>과거지만 그안에 초심은 <br>변하지않았겠지 란 <br>작은 희망을 오늘도 찾으려고 해 <br>난 또 적으려고해 뭘 더 바래 <br>이젠부턴 일기를 쓰는게 <br>내 일이고 <br>어제와 내일을 구분하는건 <br>눈을 떴을때 임시적인 <br>느낌으로부터 <br>날 기억하려 오늘 일기에 <br>나를 담아논 후에야 <br>가까스로 눈을 감어 <br>문방구 공책에 적어놨었던 <br>일기장 남아있겠지 <br>그안에 적어놨었던 내 불만 <br>다시 펼쳐보네 <br>한번 더 날 뒤돌아보네 <br>어딘가 숨어있겠지 <br>억울했던 그때 눈물자국이 <br>문방구 공책에 적어놨었던 <br>일기장 남아있겠지 <br>그안에 적어놨었던 내 꿈과 <br>열정을 되새겨보네 <br>날 한번 더 다듬어보네 <br>어딘가 숨어있겠지 <br>그때의 노력의 땀방울이 <br>반복되는 daily routine <br>시간에 맡긴 채 <br>세월앞에 무감각해졌고 <br>억지로 한 후회 <br>쉽게 꺼지지않았던 <br>불같은 내 성격탓에 <br>타들어가면서 날 감싸줬던 <br>엄마 심장안에 <br>재가 쌓였고 <br>난 그 죄를 몰랐고 <br>어제를 떠나긴 싫고 <br>오늘을 살고싶던 내 <br>모습이 선명해질때쯤엔 <br>흐려져갔던 내 실수 가득한 <br>날들을 떠올리면서 <br>hash tag <br>better day is coming up <br>내일 날씨는 맑음으로 <br>표시해 <br>uh 설레는 마음은 어느새 <br>사라졌고 어떤 내일을 <br>버텨낼지 고민하는 <br>내 모습을 일기장에 도저히 <br>남기기 싫었어 <br>난 그게 싫어서 <br>내 식대로 살아왔고 <br>그게 어찌됐던간에 <br>여러번 밑바닥을 찍게 만들었고 <br>텅 빈 불꺼진 방안에서 <br>허공에 손을 <br>휘둘러보다 부딫쳐봐야 <br>내 위치를 아는 법이라고 <br>일기를 적었던적 있겠지 <br>어딘가 부딫친 상처의 <br>흉터를 남긴채로 <br>나도 모르게 남아있었던 <br>그때의 일기 <br>문방구 공책에 적어놨었던 <br>일기장 남아있겠지 <br>그안에 적어놨었던 내 불만 <br>다시 펼쳐보네 <br>한번 더 날 뒤돌아보네 <br>어딘가 숨어있겠지 <br>억울했던 그때 눈물자국이 <br>문방구 공책에 적어놨었던 <br>일기장 남아있겠지 <br>그안에 적어놨었던 내 꿈과 <br>열정을 되새겨보네 <br>날 한번 더 다듬어보네 <br>어딘가 숨어있겠지 <br>그때의 노력의 땀방울이 <br>]]></content><category term="YD (와이디)" label="YD (와이디)"/><category term="일기장 (Journey)" label="일기장 (Journey)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gmc/Tic_Toc_Feat_Four20/</id><title>Gmc - Tic Toc (Feat. Four20) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:21:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:21:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Gmc/Tic_Toc_Feat_Four20/" title="Gmc - Tic Toc (Feat. Four20) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느덧 하나 둘 셋 <br>나이를 먹다보니깐 <br>시간은 좀 더 빠르게 <br>흘러가네 나도 모르게 <br>어느덧 교복을 <br>벗어 던진지도 <br>엊그제 같은데 <br>벌써 사계절이 흘렀네 <br>항상 부지런히 <br>움직이는 초침이 <br>단 하루만 <br>멈췄으면 해 솔직히 <br>일상이 똑같은 <br>시간의 노예 <br>넘기 힘든 고개 <br>점점 불러가는 똥배 <br>이러면 안 되는걸 <br>자각해도 <br>사람들은 시간 속 <br>압박감에 포기하곤 해 <br>모두가 성공만 <br>바라보고선 걸어 <br>벌어야지 라는 생각에 <br>인생을 걸어 <br>하지만 쉽게 <br>흘러가지 않는 삶이 <br>원망스럽고 끝에 <br>좌절하기 십상이지 <br>이젠 뭐라도 보여줄 때 <br>나를 사랑하는 <br>사람들이 모여들게 <br>이제는 보여줄게 <br>걱정하지 말고 <br>나를 믿어도 돼 <br>어느덧 하나 둘 셋 <br>나이를 먹다보니깐 <br>시간은 좀 더 빠르게 <br>흘러가네 나도 모르게 <br>어느덧 하나 둘 셋 <br>나이를 먹다보니깐 <br>시간은 좀 더 빠르게 <br>흘러가네 나도 모르게 <br>나도 모르게 <br>started from 밑바닥 <br>어차피 다 지난날 <br>더 이상 뒤는 보지 않아 <br>앞으로가 prime time <br>앞날만 보고 달려도 <br>시간이 촉박한데 <br>뭐가 무섭다고 <br>내가 눈을 감아 <br>어차피 한번뿐인 <br>인생 끝은 가봐야지 <br>남자라면 깃발은 <br>정상에 박아야지 <br>쉽지 않다는건 <br>누구보다 잘 알기에 <br>머릿속에 시끄럽게 <br>우는 siren <br>그래서 안주 하지 않아 <br>겸손한 자세로 <br>임하고 매사에 <br>최선을 다하는 것뿐 <br>깊숙이 숨겨진 꿈 <br>단단히 잠겨진 문 <br>을 열기위한 열쇠고린 <br>힙합 단 하나뿐 <br>인생은 짧고 <br>예술은 길듯 <br>누구하나 죽는다고 <br>깨지지 않는 rhythm <br>그 흐름을 자연스럽게 <br>따라가다 보면 <br>완성 되있을거야 <br>내 삶의 build <br>어느덧 하나 둘 셋 <br>나이를 먹다보니깐 <br>시간은 좀 더 빠르게 <br>흘러가네 나도 모르게 <br>어느덧 하나 둘 셋 <br>나이를 먹다보니깐 <br>시간은 좀 더 빠르게 <br>흘러가네 나도 모르게 <br>나도 모르게 <br>모두가 성공하길 원해 난 <br>이제는 시간에 <br>쫒기지 말고 살아가 <br>모두가 성공하길 원해 난 <br>이제는 시간에 <br>쫒기지 말고 살아가 <br>]]></content><category term="Gmc" label="Gmc"/><category term="Tic Toc (Feat. Four20)" label="Tic Toc (Feat. Four20)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/COG/Who/</id><title>C.O.G - Who - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:23:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:23:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/COG/Who/" title="C.O.G - Who - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[didn't think a man like me <br>could fall like this <br>what's been and what's been <br>done how did it come to this <br>pleasing <br>i was pleading for a case <br>don't nobody ever told me this <br>a fine line between right or wrong <br>forgive me for my sins <br>you think i'm on to <br>something baby <br>you see me in the <br>morning going crazy <br>do we define the meaningless <br>or is it me tripping on illusions <br>who am i talking to <br>who am i talking to <br>who am i talking to <br>a reminiscence of <br>what's left is you <br>who am i talking to <br>pleading for a minute <br>seeing things existing <br>who am i talking to <br>baby this ain't rocket science <br>get it through you <br>maybe we can turn the clock <br>counterclockwise <br>set it to the moon <br>이기적인 척 하고싶어 <br>믿기 싫은 신을 원망하며 <br>남 탓하기 딱 좋은 날에 나 대 나 <br>술한잔을 눈물로 채워 <br>and i know what it is <br>what i not to do <br>and i know what it is <br>what i got to do <br>but the mood really <br>killing me nice <br>and this moet really <br>ain't helping my vibe <br>내가 원하는건 이거 <br>그렇다고 남는건 미련 <br>이런지도 벌써 몇번 <br>셀수없이 오늘도 밤을 세워 <br>기쁠땐 기뻐야해 <br>다 잃고 난 뒤에 <br>회상해봐야 뭐해 <br>오늘도 니 생각에 취해야해 <br>이제 쯤이면 질릴텐데 <br>왜 갈수록 삶은 더 흑백이돼 <br>i lost my conscious <br>being too cautious <br>around you got a little nauseous <br>but that was just the <br>childish kid getting active <br>and you took it wrongly <br>어쩔수 없지 널 탓 하지 않지 <br>i was a fool for believing in magic <br>그 딴건 없지 <br>넌 너데로 걸어갔지 <br>난 눈을 가린체 그대로 서 있지 <br>그 시절 땜에 아직 <br>과거 속에 살어 <br>그리움을 심고 난 기다려 <br>you think i'm on to <br>something baby <br>you see me in the <br>morning going crazy <br>do we define the meaningless <br>or is it me tripping on illusions <br>who am i talking to <br>a reminiscence of <br>what's left is you <br>who am i talking to <br>some say love is unconditional <br>but why's it like endless <br>conditions and rules <br>picture perfect moments <br>smeared when thoughts unfold <br>시간이 지날수록 <br>삼켜놨던 눈물은 <br>하염없이 밤새 쌓여 <br>it's good for a time but like <br>we know time is on the fly <br>on it's own and we follow <br>and we follow <br>started out as strangers <br>worked our way up <br>that's the danger <br>calling each other babe <br>on the phone with you all day <br>너 하나만 바라본 내게 <br>돌아온 건 하나 없네 <br>affection and obsession <br>flirting in between i'm stressing <br>and i'm confessing <br>these sleepless nights are endless <br>imagine you in my presence <br>forgetting <br>who am i talking to <br>who am i talking to <br>who am i talking to <br>]]></content><category term="C.O.G" label="C.O.G"/><category term="Who" label="Who"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이해인/스르륵/</id><title>이해인 - 스르륵 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:24:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:24:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%ED%95%B4%EC%9D%B8/%EC%8A%A4%EB%A5%B4%EB%A5%B5/" title="이해인 - 스르륵 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어느새 나의 마음에 <br>조용히 스며들은 너 <br>조그만 티도 안 내고 <br>사랑에 조금 둔해서 <br>남자를 아직 몰라서 <br>전혀 눈치 못 챘던 나 <br>스르륵 나의 일상에 <br>스르륵 나의 마음에 <br>언제나 반복되던 내 하루를 <br>꾸미고 또 설레이게 해 <br>스르륵 스며드네 <br>You <br>어디서 무얼 하든지 <br>어디를 가든지 <br>네 향기로 가득해 <br>스르륵 스며드네 <br>You <br>네가 처음이어서 더 좋아 <br>온통 네 색깔로 칠한 <br>내 모습 좋아 <br>오늘은 무슨 일일까 <br>매일 듣는 네 목소린데 <br>왜 항상 새로운 걸까 <br>늘 같이 걷던 길인데 <br>늘 함께 가던 카펜데 <br>너로 인해 늘 새로워 <br>스르륵 나의 일상에 <br>스르륵 나의 마음에 <br>언제나 반복되던 내 하루를 <br>꾸미고 또 설레이게 해 <br>스르륵 스며드네 <br>You <br>어디서 무얼 하든지 <br>어디를 가든지 <br>네 향기로 가득해 <br>스르륵 스며드네 <br>You <br>네가 처음이어서 더 좋아 <br>온통 네 색깔로 칠한 <br>내 모습 좋아 <br>어디서 무얼 하든지 <br>어디를 가든지 <br>네 향기로 가득해 <br>스르륵 스며드네 <br>You <br>네가 처음이어서 더 좋아 <br>온통 네 색깔로 칠한 <br>내 모습 좋아 <br>네가 있어서 따뜻해 <br>스르륵 스며 들었네 <br>너의 품 안에 <br>]]></content><category term="이해인" label="이해인"/><category term="스르륵" label="스르륵"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rise_to_be_Alive_라이즈_투_비_얼라이브/내가_믿는_것들은/</id><title>Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브) - 내가 믿는 것들은 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:25:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:25:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rise_to_be_Alive_%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EC%A6%88_%ED%88%AC_%EB%B9%84_%EC%96%BC%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%8C/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EB%AF%BF%EB%8A%94_%EA%B2%83%EB%93%A4%EC%9D%80/" title="Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브) - 내가 믿는 것들은 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 자리에 난 변한 것 없이 그대로 <br>서 있는 난 남겨진 것조차 없나 <br>Hey my dear <br>난 아직 그대로인데 <br>Say my prayer <br>모두 다 걸어가고 있네 <br>And I I believe <br>난 바라지 못하고 바랄 수 없었던 <br>날에 대한 내 바램과 기억은 <br>하나의 길이 되어 <br>I believe I believe <br>Here I now <br>I can make it better than one <br>벽 앞에선 문이 닫혔다 믿게되지 <br>Hey my dear <br>난 아직 그대로인데 <br>Sing my prayer <br>모든 건 움직이네 <br>And I I believe <br>난 바라지 못하고 바랄 수 없었던 <br>날에 대한 내 바램과 기억은 <br>하나의 길이 되어 <br>And I I believe <br>난 바라지 못하고 바랄 수 없었던 <br>날에 대한 내 바램과 기억은 <br>하나의 길이 되어 <br>내가 서있는 이 길의 끝에서 <br>우린 다시 한번 더 <br>believe <br>And I I believe <br>난 바라지 못하고 바랄 수 없었던 <br>날에 대한 내 바램과 기억은 <br>하나의 길이 되어 <br>And I I believe <br>I believe <br>난 바라지 못하고 바랄 수 없었던 <br>날에 대한 내 바램과 기억은 <br>하나의 길이 되어 <br>I believe I believe <br>]]></content><category term="Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브)" label="Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브)"/><category term="내가 믿는 것들은" label="내가 믿는 것들은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rise_to_be_Alive_라이즈_투_비_얼라이브/Suffocate/</id><title>Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브) - Suffocate - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:25:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:25:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rise_to_be_Alive_%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EC%A6%88_%ED%88%AC_%EB%B9%84_%EC%96%BC%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%8C/Suffocate/" title="Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브) - Suffocate - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Please see now <br>i'm fucking dying <br>my broken wings are <br>tied in your eyes <br>please kill me now <br>i can't understand <br>i cannot breathe cause you <br>pull me down <br>eyes observation <br>your lies for cover up <br>you dis-guise <br>me and getting me down <br>God please give me just <br>Five seconds for breath <br>To sur-vive <br>You're letting me drown <br>Oh please don't <br>Get Back <br>just let me out <br>Why you keep me <br>in your blind room <br>I am suffocating <br>in your hands <br>Hey god <br>there goes my dream <br>I'll pay now <br>if you bring me back <br>Like a shot through the silent <br>night Your fucking arrows are <br>stick in my Mind <br>Oh please don't <br>Get back <br>just let me out <br>Why you keep me <br>in your blind room <br>I am suffocating <br>in your hands <br>you'll never get me alive <br>unless you take my last breath <br>please shot me stuff me babe <br>you smile on me <br>and still i'm suffocate <br>Why you keep me <br>in your blind room <br>I am suffocating <br>in your hands <br>you'll never get me alive <br>unless you take my last breath <br>please shot me stuff me babe <br>you smile on me <br>and still i'm suffocate <br>suffocate <br>]]></content><category term="Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브)" label="Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브)"/><category term="Suffocate" label="Suffocate"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rise_to_be_Alive_라이즈_투_비_얼라이브/Crazy/</id><title>Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브) - Crazy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:25:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:25:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Rise_to_be_Alive_%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EC%A6%88_%ED%88%AC_%EB%B9%84_%EC%96%BC%EB%9D%BC%EC%9D%B4%EB%B8%8C/Crazy/" title="Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브) - Crazy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[See what i see that's not me <br>that is a shadow inside of me <br>nothing helps for my dream <br>too much voices in my head <br>주위를 둘러보아도 <br>보이지 않는 어둠에 <br>내 귀는 열려있지만 <br>내 모든 건 묶여있어 <br>I'm crazy <br>It drives me to the end <br>There's no trust and no belief <br>You make me crazy and insane <br>It's time to kill myself <br>I'm crazy I'm crazy <br>I cannot stand anymore <br>I'm crazy I'm crazy <br>눈 감고 지우려 해봐도 <br>빛처럼 선명한 기억 <br>귀를 막아보아도 <br>주위를 막은 차가운 벽 <br>I'm crazy <br>It drives me to the end <br>There's no trust and no belief <br>You make me crazy and insane <br>It's time to kill myself <br>I'm crazy I'm crazy <br>I cannot stand anymore <br>I'm crazy I'm crazy <br>there's no one we can trust <br>there's no one we can believe <br>there's nothing we can take <br>there's nowhere we can hide <br>I'm crazy <br>It drives me to the end <br>There's no trust and no belief <br>You make me crazy and insane <br>It's time to kill myself <br>I'm crazy I'm crazy <br>I cannot stand anymore <br>I'm crazy I'm crazy <br>I cannot stand anymore <br>]]></content><category term="Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브)" label="Rise to be Alive (라이즈 투 비 얼라이브)"/><category term="Crazy" label="Crazy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/사우스라잇/지음/</id><title>사우스라잇 - 지음 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:26:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:26:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EC%8A%A4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9E%87/%EC%A7%80%EC%9D%8C/" title="사우스라잇 - 지음 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어린 내 기억 속 <br>내 가장 친한 친구 <br>내게 많은걸 <br>가르쳐준 내 친구 <br>학교 가는 길에 <br>난 항상 너의 집 앞에 <br>기다렸지 자전거 타고 <br>유난히 키가 작고 <br>왜소했던 체구 <br>하지만 누구보다 <br>남자답던 성격을 <br>나는 키만 컸던 아이 <br>겁이 많은 아이 <br>하지만 너와 함께라면 <br>외로웠구나 너무 많이 <br>많이 도망쳤어 <br>난 너를 버리고 <br>꿈에 나오더라 <br>그때 그 모습 그대로 <br>난 잘 지내고 있고 <br>넌 잘 지내야 해 <br>우리의 학교가 <br>달라진 그때부터 <br>몸이 멀어지면 <br>마음도 멀어져 <br>그렇게 서로 <br>몸이 자라고 <br>우리 둘 사이는 <br>예전 같지 않았지 <br>어느 순간 <br>널 피하게 되는 <br>내 모습을 <br>느낀 후로 <br>서로 멀어진걸 느껴 <br>시간이 지나고 <br>그 시절 내 실수를 난 <br>아직도 후회하네 미안해 <br>외로웠구나 너무 많이 <br>많이 도망쳤어 <br>난 너를 버리고 <br>꿈에 나오더라 <br>그때 그 모습 그대로 <br>난 잘 지내고 있고 <br>넌 잘 지내야 해 <br>외로웠구나 너무 많이 <br>많이 도망쳤어 <br>난 너를 버리고 <br>꿈에 나오더라 <br>그때 그 모습 그대로 <br>난 잘 지내고 있고 <br>외로웠구나 너무 많이 <br>많이 도망쳤어 <br>난 너를 버리고 <br>꿈에 나오더라 <br>그때 그 모습 그대로 <br>난 잘 지내고 있고 <br>넌 잘 지내야 해 <br>]]></content><category term="사우스라잇" label="사우스라잇"/><category term="지음" label="지음"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/사우스라잇/Blossom_Feat_주한철_Of_Gloomy_Season/</id><title>사우스라잇 - Blossom (Feat. 주한철 Of Gloomy Season) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:26:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:26:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EC%8A%A4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9E%87/Blossom_Feat_%EC%A3%BC%ED%95%9C%EC%B2%A0_Of_Gloomy_Season/" title="사우스라잇 - Blossom (Feat. 주한철 Of Gloomy Season) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 상상 속에서 <br>너와 내 사이에 피는 꽃 <br>길을 잃어버린 나에겐 <br>마치 등대 같은걸 <br>똑바로 쳐다볼 수 없는 <br>눈이 부신 꽃 <br>정말 신이 있다면 마치 <br>이런 모습일걸 <br>이렇게 따듯한 <br>금방 꺼질 듯한 <br>너무도 선명한 <br>눈부신 빛으로 <br>내 맘에 물들어 <br>깊게 스며들어 <br>녹아버린 듯한 <br>얼어있던 내 맘 <br>이렇게 따듯한 <br>금방 꺼질 듯한 <br>너무도 선명한 <br>눈부신 빛으로 <br>내 맘에 물들어 <br>깊게 스며들어 <br>녹아버린 듯한 <br>얼어있던 내맘 <br>이렇게 따듯한 <br>금방 꺼질 듯한 <br>너무도 선명한 <br>눈부신 빛으로 <br>내 맘에 물들어 <br>깊게 스며들어 <br>녹아버린 듯한 <br>얼어있던 내맘 <br>]]></content><category term="사우스라잇" label="사우스라잇"/><category term="Blossom (Feat. 주한철 Of Gloomy Season)" label="Blossom (Feat. 주한철 Of Gloomy Season)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/사우스라잇/Flare_Feat_Syler/</id><title>사우스라잇 - Flare (Feat. Syler) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:27:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:27:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EC%8A%A4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9E%87/Flare_Feat_Syler/" title="사우스라잇 - Flare (Feat. Syler) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[끝내 내겐 아무것도 <br>No way <br>이젠 끝이 없는 길만 보여 <br>Gon be this way <br>이제 떠나 편히 쉴래 <br>My bad <br>그래 결국 내가 부족한거 <br>I know <br>그만 할래 모두 <br>내려 놓을래 <br>이미 높은 님은 <br>귀를 막고 듣지 않아 <br>So i try to say <br>that there's nothing <br>and no more <br>그래 결국 내가 부족한거 <br>I know <br>못해 이젠 아무것도 못해 <br>What ever you want <br>So just cry <br>So just cry <br>just cry <br>그만 할래 모두 <br>내려 놓을래 <br>이미 높은 님은 <br>눈을 감고 뜨지 않아 <br>So i try to say <br>that there's nothing <br>and no more <br>그래 결국 내가 부족한거 <br>I know <br>don't worry about that <br>난 상관하지 않네 <br>모든 잣대 <br>So i try to say <br>that there's nothing <br>듣기 싫으면 듣지마 <br>세상은 원래 <br>내 편이 없는게 당연해 <br>근데 뭐 어떻게 <br>해볼 수 있겠어 <br>다 부질없는 거지 뭐 <br>한가지 방법이 있다면 <br>Searching for the dream huh <br>불을 밝혀 그리고 <br>그걸 쫓아가 <br>해답은 그 너머에 <br>영원한 포만감 <br>못해 이젠 아무것도 못해 <br>What ever you want <br>So just cry <br>So just cry <br>just cry <br>못해 이젠 아무것도 못해 <br>What ever you want <br>So just cry <br>So just cry <br>just cry <br>]]></content><category term="사우스라잇" label="사우스라잇"/><category term="Flare (Feat. Syler)" label="Flare (Feat. Syler)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/사우스라잇/Matthew_22_39/</id><title>사우스라잇 - Matthew 22:39 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:27:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:27:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%82%AC%EC%9A%B0%EC%8A%A4%EB%9D%BC%EC%9E%87/Matthew_22_39/" title="사우스라잇 - Matthew 22:39 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[십자가의 무게 <br>더 무거워져 가네 <br>이 사실을 모르는게 <br>분명해 분명해 <br>나는 그를 닮길 원해 <br>그게 제일 첫 번째 <br>이 사실을 뒤로한게 <br>분명해 분명해 <br>Please listen to what Jesus says <br>Please listen to what Jesus says <br>Please listen to what Jesus says <br>Please listen to what Jesus says <br>여긴 없어 죄 없는게 <br>죄가 없다면 돌을 던져 <br>이 사실을 잊어버린게 <br>분명해 분명해 <br>주는 품에 안으시네 <br>감싸줘야 할 무지개 <br>차별 말고 절실하게 <br>기도해 기도해 <br>Please listen to what Jesus says <br>Please listen to what Jesus says <br>Please listen to what Jesus says <br>Please listen to what Jesus says <br>]]></content><category term="사우스라잇" label="사우스라잇"/><category term="Matthew 22:39" label="Matthew 22:39"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/코랄로/사랑을_말해/</id><title>코랄로 - 사랑을 말해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:27:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:27:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BD%94%EB%9E%84%EB%A1%9C/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%84_%EB%A7%90%ED%95%B4/" title="코랄로 - 사랑을 말해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[조심스레 비친 햇살 <br>살랑살랑 부는 바람 <br>오랫동안 기다린 바람 <br>터벅터벅 길을 따라 <br>하염없이 걷다보면 <br>그리던 널 볼 수 있겠지 <br>그땐 우리 다시 함께 <br>저녁을 먹고 <br>얼굴을 부비며 <br>사랑을 말해 <br>그땐 우리 다시 함께 <br>저녁을 먹고 <br>얼굴을 부비며 <br>사랑을 말해 <br>저녁을 먹고 <br>얼굴을 부비며 <br>사랑을 말해 <br>]]></content><category term="코랄로" label="코랄로"/><category term="사랑을 말해" label="사랑을 말해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/디케이_DK/ILL_BE_THERE_ODD_FISH_Remix/</id><title>디케이 (DK) - I`LL BE THERE (ODD FISH Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:27:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:27:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%94%94%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4_DK/ILL_BE_THERE_ODD_FISH_Remix/" title="디케이 (DK) - I`LL BE THERE (ODD FISH Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's a shine in the dark <br>now I find it myself <br>I'll be there for you <br>Runnin' babe <br>runaway <br>when a wonderful place <br>I'll be there for you <br>I'll be there for you <br>I'll be there for you <br>I'll be there for you <br>It's a shine in the dark <br>now I find it myself <br>I'll be there for you <br>for you <br>]]></content><category term="디케이 (DK)" label="디케이 (DK)"/><category term="I`LL BE THERE (ODD FISH Remix)" label="I`LL BE THERE (ODD FISH Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/디케이_DK/ILL_BE_THERE_OWNR_Remix/</id><title>디케이 (DK) - I`LL BE THERE (OWNR Remix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:27:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:27:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%94%94%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4_DK/ILL_BE_THERE_OWNR_Remix/" title="디케이 (DK) - I`LL BE THERE (OWNR Remix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's a shine in the dark <br>now I find it myself <br>I'll be there for you <br>A whole new world <br>I can show you my all in head <br>what can I do for you <br>Runnin' babe <br>runaway <br>when a wonderful place <br>I'll be there for you <br>Hang it on <br>when you smile with your face <br>what can I do for you <br>Save my life <br>My love my heart and all <br>Fly to sky <br>so blue it's you <br>It's a shine in the dark <br>now I find it myself <br>I'll be there for you <br>A whole new world <br>I can show you my all in head <br>what can I do for you <br>Runnin' babe <br>runaway <br>when a wonderful place <br>I'll be there for you <br>Hang it on <br>when you smile with your face <br>what can I do for you <br>Save my life <br>My love my heart and all <br>Fly to sky <br>so blue it's you <br>Save my life <br>My love my heart and all <br>Fly to sky <br>so blue it's you <br>I'll be there for you <br>for you <br>for you <br>I'll be there for you <br>for you <br>for you <br>I'll be there for <br>Save my life <br>My love my heart and all <br>Fly to sky <br>so blue it's you <br>]]></content><category term="디케이 (DK)" label="디케이 (DK)"/><category term="I`LL BE THERE (OWNR Remix)" label="I`LL BE THERE (OWNR Remix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/디케이_DK/ILL_BE_THERE_Feat_우예린/</id><title>디케이 (DK) - I`LL BE THERE (Feat. 우예린) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:27:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:27:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%94%94%EC%BC%80%EC%9D%B4_DK/ILL_BE_THERE_Feat_%EC%9A%B0%EC%98%88%EB%A6%B0/" title="디케이 (DK) - I`LL BE THERE (Feat. 우예린) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's a shine in the dark <br>now I find it myself <br>I'll be there for you <br>A whole new world <br>I can show you my all in head <br>what can I do for you <br>Runnin' babe <br>runaway <br>when a wonderful place <br>I'll be there for you <br>Hang it on <br>when you smile with your face <br>what can I do for you <br>Save my life <br>My love my heart and all <br>Fly to sky <br>so blue it's you <br>I'll be there for you <br>for you <br>for you <br>I'll be there for you <br>for you <br>for you <br>I'll be there for <br>It's a shine in the dark <br>now I find it myself <br>I'll be there for you <br>A whole new world <br>I can show you my all in head <br>what can I do for you <br>Runnin' babe <br>runaway <br>when a wonderful place <br>I'll be there for you <br>Hang it on <br>when you smile with your face <br>what can I do for you <br>Save my life <br>My love my heart and all <br>Fly to sky <br>so blue it's you <br>I'll be there for you <br>for you <br>for you <br>I'll be there for you <br>for you <br>for you <br>I'll be there for <br>]]></content><category term="디케이 (DK)" label="디케이 (DK)"/><category term="I`LL BE THERE (Feat. 우예린)" label="I`LL BE THERE (Feat. 우예린)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/H-Line/잘_있어_Feat_임영신/</id><title>H-Line - 잘 있어 (Feat. 임영신) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:27:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:27:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/H-Line/%EC%9E%98_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4_Feat_%EC%9E%84%EC%98%81%EC%8B%A0/" title="H-Line - 잘 있어 (Feat. 임영신) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이제는 그 말이 <br>나올 때 됐나봐 <br>너도 똑같이 느꼈을까 <br>혹시 나만 그렇게 <br>너와의 이별을 <br>혼자서만 준비했나봐 <br>만나서 애길 해도 <br>이제 예전 같지 <br>않다는 걸 알아 <br>때론 내가 낯설기만 <br>느꼈을지 몰라 넌 <br>잘 있으란 말밖에 <br>못해서 미안해 <br>이말 밖에 할 수 없나봐 <br>이기적이라고 <br>나쁜 놈이라고 <br>생각해도 돼 넌 착하니까 <br>그동안 참았던 <br>애기를 할거야 <br>그러니까 잘들어야 해 <br>만나서 애길 해도 <br>난 더는 잘해줄 <br>자신이 없어 <br>울고 설득해봐도 <br>난 너에게 끝이 났어 <br>잘 있으란 말밖에 <br>못해서 미안해 <br>이말 밖에 나오질 않아 <br>이기적이라고 <br>나쁜 놈이라고 <br>생각해도 돼 넌 착하니까 <br>솔직히 말할게 <br>우리 헤어지자 <br>잘 있으란 말밖에 <br>못해서 미안해 <br>이말 밖에 나오질 않아 <br>이기적이라고 <br>나쁜 놈이라고 <br>생각해도 돼 넌 착하니까 <br>]]></content><category term="H-Line" label="H-Line"/><category term="잘 있어 (Feat. 임영신)" label="잘 있어 (Feat. 임영신)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이아름/내_마음_베어내어/</id><title>이아름 - 내 마음 베어내어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:28:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:28:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%84%EB%A6%84/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C_%EB%B2%A0%EC%96%B4%EB%82%B4%EC%96%B4/" title="이아름 - 내 마음 베어내어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 마음 베어내어 <br>저 달을 만들고저 <br>까만 밤하늘에 <br>동그랗게 뜨게 허여 <br>그대 계신 곳에 <br>환하게 비추리 <br>내 마음 베어내어 <br>저 달을 만들고저 <br>까만 밤하늘에 <br>동그랗게 뜨게 허여 <br>그대 계신 곳에 <br>환하게 비추리 <br>내 마음 베어내어 <br>저 달을 만들고저 <br>까만 밤하늘에 <br>동그랗게 뜨게 허여 <br>그대 계신 곳에 <br>환하게 비추리 <br>]]></content><category term="이아름" label="이아름"/><category term="내 마음 베어내어" label="내 마음 베어내어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이세라/내가_사는_이유_Inst/</id><title>제이세라 - 내가 사는 이유 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:28:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:28:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8%EB%9D%BC/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EC%82%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0_Inst/" title="제이세라 - 내가 사는 이유 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will always be there for you <br>눈이 부시게 아름다워요 <br>살며시 내게 짓는 미소는 <br>차가웠던 내 맘에 <br>그대의 두 손에선 <br>따스함을 느끼죠 <br>흘러 넘치는 행복이라 <br>혹시라도 달아나 버릴까 <br>그리워도 조금만 <br>마음보다 느리게 <br>그렇게 너의 곁에 있을게 <br>Remember you <br>언제까지나 <br>내가 사는 이유 <br>항상 너 하나뿐야 <br>내게 가장 소중한 <br>사랑 너뿐이란 걸 <br>너도 알고 있는지 <br>모든걸 주어도 <br>아깝지 않아 너에게 <br>이런 내 맘 알고 있는지 <br>매일 그리운 너 <br>매일 보고 싶은 너 <br>좋은 사람은 하나야 너 <br>혼자 걸어 가는 길 위에서 <br>문득 니 생각에 웃음지어도 <br>네가 듣고 싶은 말 <br>아직 못 해주는 건 <br>내 마음과 조금 다를까 봐 <br>Remember you <br>언제까지나 <br>내가 사는 이유 <br>항상 너 하나뿐야 <br>아픈 내 맘 숨기며 <br>너만 바라보는 날 <br>나를 알고 있는지 <br>너를 알기 전에 하루는 <br>허전함에 또 슬픔만 <br>너를 알고 난 내 하루는 <br>그리움뿐이야 <br>그게 너라서 너무 행복해 <br>Remember you <br>언제까지나 <br>내가 사는 이유 <br>항상 너 하나뿐야 <br>우리 멀리 떨어져 <br>아픈 날이 온대도 <br>항상 여기서 기다릴게 <br>모든 걸 주어도 <br>아깝지 않아 너에게 <br>이런 내 맘 알고 있는지 <br>매일 그리운 너 <br>매일 보고 싶은 너 <br>좋은 사람은 하나야 너 너 <br>]]></content><category term="제이세라" label="제이세라"/><category term="내가 사는 이유 (Inst.)" label="내가 사는 이유 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제이세라/내가_사는_이유/</id><title>제이세라 - 내가 사는 이유 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:28:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:28:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B8%EB%9D%BC/%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80_%EC%82%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0/" title="제이세라 - 내가 사는 이유 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I will always be there for you <br>눈이 부시게 아름다워요 <br>살며시 내게 짓는 미소는 <br>차가웠던 내 맘에 <br>그대의 두 손에선 <br>따스함을 느끼죠 <br>흘러 넘치는 행복이라 <br>혹시라도 달아나 버릴까 <br>그리워도 조금만 <br>마음보다 느리게 <br>그렇게 너의 곁에 있을게 <br>Remember you <br>언제까지나 <br>내가 사는 이유 <br>항상 너 하나뿐야 <br>내게 가장 소중한 <br>사랑 너뿐이란 걸 <br>너도 알고 있는지 <br>모든걸 주어도 <br>아깝지 않아 너에게 <br>이런 내 맘 알고 있는지 <br>매일 그리운 너 <br>매일 보고 싶은 너 <br>좋은 사람은 하나야 너 <br>혼자 걸어 가는 길 위에서 <br>문득 니 생각에 웃음지어도 <br>네가 듣고 싶은 말 <br>아직 못 해주는 건 <br>내 마음과 조금 다를까 봐 <br>Remember you <br>언제까지나 <br>내가 사는 이유 <br>항상 너 하나뿐야 <br>아픈 내 맘 숨기며 <br>너만 바라보는 날 <br>나를 알고 있는지 <br>너를 알기 전에 하루는 <br>허전함에 또 슬픔만 <br>너를 알고 난 내 하루는 <br>그리움뿐이야 <br>그게 너라서 너무 행복해 <br>Remember you <br>언제까지나 <br>내가 사는 이유 <br>항상 너 하나뿐야 <br>우리 멀리 떨어져 <br>아픈 날이 온대도 <br>항상 여기서 기다릴게 <br>모든 걸 주어도 <br>아깝지 않아 너에게 <br>이런 내 맘 알고 있는지 <br>매일 그리운 너 <br>매일 보고 싶은 너 <br>좋은 사람은 하나야 너 너 <br>]]></content><category term="제이세라" label="제이세라"/><category term="내가 사는 이유" label="내가 사는 이유"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peabody/Stupid_Boy/</id><title>Peabody - Stupid Boy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:29:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:29:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Peabody/Stupid_Boy/" title="Peabody - Stupid Boy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's a story of 'I don't know's <br>White lies and hidden blows <br>In a bar our stage is set <br>But the characters you haven't met <br><br>A crucial fact I didn't know <br>The punker chick was beginning to show <br>This is how my troubles start <br>But for now, just give me a bass guitar <br><br>See the one that eats like a pig <br>He's alright and he's pretty big <br>That's his girlfriend to his left <br>She looks familiar but we haven't met <br><br>Oh Christ, what do you know <br>That's the girl I met at the show <br>Hey man, what are you sayin' <br>Let's get out of here the way we came <br><br>I'm just a stupid boy <br>I'm full of alcohol <br>Oh god, I should've known <br>I should've stayed at home <br><br>This time I can't account <br>I must have blacked it out <br>I just came out tonight <br>I cannot fuckin' fight you <br><br>I think he saw the look on her face <br>Mouth wide open, what a bitter taste <br>But then he added up two and two <br>Now he's coming at me and you <br><br>I swear to god, man, I didn't know <br>We were off our tits at a show <br>I'm sure she loves you, you're really ace <br>I'm sure he wants to punch me in the face <br><br>I'm just a stupid boy <br>I'm full of alcohol <br>Oh god, I should've known <br>I should've stayed at home <br><br>This time I can't account <br>I must have blacked it out <br>I just came out tonight <br>I cannot fuckin' fight you <br><br>Hey, I didn't know <br>Hey, I didn't know <br><br>I'm just a stupid boy <br>I'm full of alcohol <br>Oh god, I should've known <br>I should've stayed at home <br><br>This time I can't account <br>I must have blacked it out <br>I just came out tonight <br>I cannot fuckin' fight you <br><br>Goodnight, you, goodnight]]></content><category term="Peabody" label="Peabody"/><category term="Stupid Boy" label="Stupid Boy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지효진/이렇게_아플줄은/</id><title>지효진 - 이렇게 아플줄은 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:29:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:29:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%ED%9A%A8%EC%A7%84/%EC%9D%B4%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C_%EC%95%84%ED%94%8C%EC%A4%84%EC%9D%80/" title="지효진 - 이렇게 아플줄은 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지난 시간들이 <br>영화처럼 스쳐가 <br>이젠 돌이킬 수 없는 <br>시간 속을 살아가 <br>기억조차 나지 않는 <br>오늘 같은 밤이면 내겐 <br>나를 잃어가 <br>그 때는 몰랐어 <br>이렇게 아플 줄은 <br>사랑하면 할수록 <br>더 행복해지는 줄로만 <br>근데 왜이리 가슴이 <br>찢어져 우는 건지 <br>모든 걸 돌리려고 <br>애써 그렇게는 안돼 <br>마음속으로 <br>항상 외치는 말 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>다시 꺼내볼 수 없는 <br>그 말 사랑해 사랑해 <br>바라보고 있고 싶어 <br>더 이상은 볼 수가 없는 <br>가슴이 아려와 <br>이렇게 아플 줄은 <br>아무것도 손에 <br>잡히지 않아 <br>멍하니 하늘만 <br>잠깐의 목소리라도 <br>들을까 싶어서 <br>찾아간 그 거리 <br>집 앞에 서성이고만 있어 <br>마음속으로 <br>항상 외치는 말 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>다시 꺼내볼 수 없는 <br>그 말 사랑해 사랑해 <br>바라보고 있고 싶어 <br>더 이상은 볼 수가 없는 <br>이젠 알 거 같아 <br>아파하던 맘도 <br>아니라는 걸 <br>우리 이제 더는 서로 <br>기억할 일 다신 없단 걸 <br>뜨거워진 눈물 감추려 <br>애쓰던 나를 돌아봐 <br>다신 사랑 <br>하기가 겁이 나잖아 <br>마음속으로 <br>항상 외치는 말 <br>사랑해 사랑해 <br>다시 꺼내볼 수 없는 <br>그 말 사랑해 사랑해 <br>바라보고 있고 싶어 <br>더 이상은 볼 수가 없는 <br>]]></content><category term="지효진" label="지효진"/><category term="이렇게 아플줄은" label="이렇게 아플줄은"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Moritz_Garth/Kaltes_Wasser/</id><title>Moritz Garth - Kaltes Wasser - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:30:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:30:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Moritz_Garth/Kaltes_Wasser/" title="Moritz Garth - Kaltes Wasser - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jeden Tag, von fruh bis spat, wenn ich die gewohnten Runden dreh, bin ich eigentlich zufrieden mit mir selbst <br>Doch ab und da denke ich spontan, die Routine hindert mich daran, der zu sein der ich wirklich bin <br><br>Dann sammle und besinn ich mich, auf den Moment und innerlich stell ich mich vorne an den Beckenrand <br>Und ich brech aus, spring ins kalte Wasser, spure wie der Puls in meinen Adern wieder bebt <br>Und ich brech aus, spring ins kalte Wasser, spure wie die Kalte meinen Geist wieder belebt <br><br>Ich fahre raus zum alten Bad und ich nehm das schone alte Rad, das ich mal am Wegesrand gefunden hab <br>Durch das Loch am alten Zaun und dann noch vorbei am grossen Baum und an der verbluhten Wiese bleib ich steh'n <br><br>Ohhh dann sammle und besinn ich mich auf den Moment und stelle mich bis ganz nach vorne an den Beckenrand <br><br>Und ich breche aus, spring ins kalte Wasser, spure wie der Puls in meinen Adern wieder bebt <br>Ich breche aus, spring ins kalte Wasser, spure wie die Kalte meinen Geist wieder belebt <br>Ich breche aus, spring ins kalte aus und sinke bis zum Grund <br>Und ich tauche auf <br><br>Und ich tauche auf <br><br>Ich breche aus, spring ins kalte Wasser, spure wie der Puls in meinen Adern wieder bebt <br>Ich breche aus, spring ins kalte Wasser, spure wie die Kalte meinen Geist wieder belebt <br>Ich tauche auf]]></content><category term="Moritz Garth" label="Moritz Garth"/><category term="Kaltes Wasser" label="Kaltes Wasser"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/조심_조심/</id><title>트니트니 - 조심 조심 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:30:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:30:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EC%A1%B0%EC%8B%AC_%EC%A1%B0%EC%8B%AC/" title="트니트니 - 조심 조심 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(얘들아~ 위험해 쿵~ 아야야야) <br>친구들과 부딪히지 않게 조심해봐요 (고래) <br>친구들과 부딪히지 않게 조심해봐요 (새우) <br>요리조리 보고 조심조심 조심 <br>요리조리 보고 조심 또 조심 (유후) <br>(얘들아~ 조심해 쿵~ 아야야야~) <br>친구들과 부딪히지 않게 조심해봐요 (고래) <br>친구들과 부딪히지 않게 조심해봐요 (새우) <br>요리조리 보고 조심조심 조심 <br>요리조리 보고 조심 또 조심 <br>친구들을 피해봐 봐 봐]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="조심 조심" label="조심 조심"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/꾸륵꾸륵/</id><title>트니트니 - 꾸륵꾸륵 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:30:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:30:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EA%BE%B8%EB%A5%B5%EA%BE%B8%EB%A5%B5/" title="트니트니 - 꾸륵꾸륵 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(하하하 아이 간지러워 <br>간지럽단 말이야 하하하) <br>꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 <br>꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 뿌웅~뿌웅~뿌웅~ <br>꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 <br>꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 뿌웅 <br>커다란 고래 친구야 <br>방귀를 방귀를 뀌어줘요 <br>조그만 조그만 새우를 탈출 시켜줘요 <br>(하하하 아이 간지럽단 말이야 간지러워) <br>꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 <br>꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 뿌웅~뿌웅~뿌웅~ <br>꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 <br>꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 꾸륵 뿌웅 <br>커다란 고래 친구야 <br>방귀를 방귀를 뀌어줘요 <br>조그만 조그만 새우를 탈출시켜줘~요]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="꾸륵꾸륵" label="꾸륵꾸륵"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/깜깜한_똥구멍/</id><title>트니트니 - 깜깜한 똥구멍 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:30:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:30:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EA%B9%9C%EA%B9%9C%ED%95%9C_%EB%98%A5%EA%B5%AC%EB%A9%8D/" title="트니트니 - 깜깜한 똥구멍 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(어? 여기가 어디지? 어? 안 보여) <br>어둑 어둑 깜깜해요 <br>어둑 어둑 깜깜해요 <br>어둑 어둑 냄새나요 <br>어둑 어둑 냄새나요 <br>여기가 어딜까요 커다란 똥구멍 <br>여기가 어~딜까요 커다란 똥구멍 <br>(어? 축축해~ 어? 추워~) <br>어둑 어둑 깜깜해요 <br>어둑 어둑 깜깜해요 <br>어둑 어둑 냄새나요 <br>어둑 어둑 냄새나요 <br>여기가 어딜까요 커다란 똥구멍 <br>여기가 어~딜까요 커다란 똥구멍]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="깜깜한 똥구멍" label="깜깜한 똥구멍"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/간질간질/</id><title>트니트니 - 간질간질 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:30:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:30:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EA%B0%84%EC%A7%88%EA%B0%84%EC%A7%88/" title="트니트니 - 간질간질 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(하하하 아이 간지러워 <br>간지럽단 말이야 하하하) <br>간질간질간질 간질간질간질 <br>간질간질간질 에취 에취 에취 <br>간질간질간질 간질간질간질 <br>간질간질간질 에취 <br>커다란 고래 친구야 <br>재채기 재채기해줘요 <br>조그만 조그만 새우를 탈출 시켜줘요 <br>(하하하 아이 간지럽단 말이야 간지러워) <br>간질간질간질 간질간질간질 <br>간질간질간질 에취 에취 에취 <br>간질간질간질 간질간질간질 <br>간질간질간질 에취 <br>커다란 고래 친구야 <br>재채기 재채기해줘요 <br>조그만 조그만 새우를 탈출시켜줘~요]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="간질간질" label="간질간질"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/깜깜한_콧구멍/</id><title>트니트니 - 깜깜한 콧구멍 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:30:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:30:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EA%B9%9C%EA%B9%9C%ED%95%9C_%EC%BD%A7%EA%B5%AC%EB%A9%8D/" title="트니트니 - 깜깜한 콧구멍 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(어? 여기가 어디지? 어? 안 보여~) <br>어둑 어둑 깜깜해요 <br>어둑 어둑 깜깜해요 <br>어둑 어둑 무서워요 <br>어둑 어둑 무서워요 <br>여기가 어딜까요 커다란 콧구멍 <br>여기가 어~딜까요 오른쪽 콧구멍 <br>(어? 축축해~ 어? 추워~) <br>어둑 어둑 깜깜해요 <br>어둑 어둑 깜깜해요 <br>어둑 어둑 무서워요 <br>어둑 어둑 무서워요 <br>여기가 어딜까요 커다란 콧구멍 <br>여기가 어~딜까요 오른쪽 콧구멍]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="깜깜한 콧구멍" label="깜깜한 콧구멍"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/고래와_새우/</id><title>트니트니 - 고래와 새우 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:30:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:30:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EA%B3%A0%EB%9E%98%EC%99%80_%EC%83%88%EC%9A%B0/" title="트니트니 - 고래와 새우 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[푸르른 푸르른 바다에 <br>푸르른 푸르른 바다에 <br>커다란 고래 한 마리와 작은 새우 한 마리가 <br>푸르른 푸르른 바다에 <br>푸르른 푸르른 바다에 <br>커다란 고래 한 마리와 작은 새우 한 마리가 <br>고래 고래 고래 고래 고래 고래 고래 <br>헤엄치다 새우 새우 새우 새우 새우 새우？새우 <br>헤엄치다 <br>어라 어라 어라 어라 어라 어라 어라 <br>조심조심 <br>부딪쳤네 푸르른 푸르른 바다에 <br>푸르른 푸르른 바다에 <br>커다란 고래 한 마리와 작은 새우 한 마리가 <br>푸르른 푸르른 바다에 <br>푸르른 푸르른 바다에 <br>커다란 고래 한 마리와 작은 새우 한 마리가 <br>고래 고래 고래 고래 고래 고래 고래 <br>헤엄치다 새우 새우 새우 새우 새우 새우？새우 <br>헤엄치다 <br>어라 어라 어라 어라 어라 어라 어라 <br>조심조심 <br>부딪쳤네]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="고래와 새우" label="고래와 새우"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/트니트니/몬스터_해머/</id><title>트니트니 - 몬스터 해머 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-19T14:30:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-19T14:30:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88%ED%8A%B8%EB%8B%88/%EB%AA%AC%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0_%ED%95%B4%EB%A8%B8/" title="트니트니 - 몬스터 해머 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[(으~~~~~~아) <br>몬스터 쾅쾅 몬스터 쾅쾅 <br>나는 나는 몬~스터 해머 <br>몬스터 쾅쾅 몬스터 쾅쾅 <br>용감한 몬~스터 해머 <br>열려라 참깨야 띠로롱 <br>띠로롱 띠로롱 <br>띠로롱 <br>열려라 참깨야 띠로롱 <br>띠로롱 띠로롱 <br>띠로롱 <br>몬스터 쾅쾅 몬스터 쾅쾅 <br>나는 나는 몬~스터 해머 <br>몬스터 쾅쾅 몬스터 쾅쾅 <br>용감한 몬~스터 해머 <br>열려라 참깨야 띠로롱 <br>띠로롱 띠로롱 <br>띠로롱 <br>열려라 참깨야 띠로롱 <br>띠로롱 띠로롱 <br>띠로롱 <br>몬스터 쾅쾅 몬스터 <br>쾅쾅 몬스터 쾅쾅]]></content><category term="트니트니" label="트니트니"/><category term="몬스터 해머" label="몬스터 해머"/></entry></feed>