<feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:13+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Fascists/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Fascists - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Fascists/" title="지미 스트레인 - Fascists - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Manufactured individuality <br>standardized and toned identity <br>Get in the line and follow the goal <br>set by the leaders of power <br><br>Homeworks called success, happiness <br>look for the manual, find the cure for life <br>Born to surrender, ready to follow <br>taught to depend, told to shut up <br><br>Identical choices and faces <br>Live and die inside the same cells <br>All share the same goals and falls <br>Copied and pasted journey of life <br><br>Pretension and vanity <br>became everybody’s life style <br>Duplication and uniformity <br>became every fucking body’s religion <br><br>Being the tiniest fragment of majority <br>is better than being the top of outcast minority <br>The system aiming to make the generic citizens <br>stabilize and strengthen the neo-caste <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Fascists" label="Fascists"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Fever_Land/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Fever Land - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Fever_Land/" title="지미 스트레인 - Fever Land - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[the fever land, the lake of blood under the ground <br><br>bleeding wings are fallen <br>legs are galloping on the skin <br>floundering through the pit of death <br>lives are but waste to bury <br><br>flesh, grinded by capitalism <br>souls, torn apart by industrialism <br>crushed, mixed with blood and tears <br>living and dying, buried alive <br><br>the liquor of wrath, the river of wraith <br><br>hearts buried during the day <br>pump the blood through the night <br>genocide heating the ground <br>massacre of glory, kill frenzy <br>hearts buried during the day <br>pump the blood through the night <br>buried alive, heating the ground <br>through the night, oh, fever land <br><br>the tools of self-justification <br>the best and the worst inventions <br>privilege of being human, uber-mortal <br>inherited rights to be violent <br><br>the fever land, the lake of blood under the ground <br>the fever land, the marsh of cries under the muddy feet <br>the fever land, the unforgivable sins of the chosen mortals <br>the fever land, the sanguinary achievement of... <br>modernization <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Fever Land" label="Fever Land"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Reds/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Reds! - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Reds/" title="지미 스트레인 - Reds! - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Separated, into north and south <br>divided into, left and right <br>paint the truth, in red and hide <br>welcome to neo-colonialism <br><br>Wield the sword, to keep the power <br>nod and wink to bring in violence <br>make'em RED, to get'em DEAD <br>welcome to neo-liberalism <br><br>discrimination behind the veil of ideologies <br>another cold war, driven by corporatocracy <br><br>Reds! From left to the right <br>From bottom to the top, and you call us <br>Reds! From left to the right <br>I know what you are scared of <br>Reds! From left to the right <br>From bottom to the top, and you call us <br>Reds! From left to the right <br>I know why you try to paint us, Red! <br><br>Liars decide what should be true <br>religions are old new tool to control <br>paint justice in red and hide <br>follow and obey neo-dictatorship <br><br>Push the naysayers to the left cliff <br>step on the dead and push to the north <br>tag the askers public enemies <br>hail to the big brother and kill the rest <br><br>You see, I ain't scared, you come try to paint me <br>You see, we aren't scared, you come try to paint us <br>Red! <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Reds!" label="Reds!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Crossing/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Crossing - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Crossing/" title="지미 스트레인 - Crossing - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Though I’ve always tried to give you the best things <br>all I have in my hands now is nothing but despair <br>No money, no fame, no bed of roses I can promise <br>but here, I give you the best thing I have,.. I give you,.. <br><br>My time <br>those endless nights, I did endure the hunger for you <br>projecting your image on the empty wall, dreaming, missing <br>Spent on the sorrows of not having you by my side <br>time, the best thing I have, filled with desperate serenade, I scream <br><br>Then let me burn, inside you <br>so I can shine your world <br>Then let me cry, here for you <br>so I can keep on living <br><br>Love <br>That's what makes you cry you say, my dear <br>Anger and hunger, growing on your absence, keep me awake <br>Lost this heart, so content once yet torn apart now; <br>it leads me, through the endless ocean of longing <br><br>I know we’ve been apart for way too long <br>but even the courses of fate will cross in time <br>I will be standing through the test of time <br>here I give you this song, the best thing I’ve got <br><br>Here, I'll always be here <br>Here, I'll be waiting for you <br>Here, the fraction of time I’ve killed <br>Hear, my cry, screaming of my heart <br><br>Then let me die, in your hands <br>so I have my salvation <br>And let me pray, for our dreams to come true <br>so my life can go on <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Crossing" label="Crossing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Agari/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Agari - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Agari/" title="지미 스트레인 - Agari - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[this ship is sinking into damnation <br>cursed and messed up, goddamned nation <br>shocked, scared, frightened, murdered <br>everybody’s got the mouth to shut <br><br>you better have your eyes blind <br>it ain't no fucking beautiful life <br>you tell me what you really want <br>but remember you will end up as they want <br><br>once a wise man said; History is a gallery of pictures <br>in which there are few originals and many copies <br><br>Behold the marching of slaves <br>Behold the fest of puppets <br>Hear the whistle of dogs in uniforms <br>Keep calm and follow me blind! <br>Behold the fallen media <br>Be happy to be entertained <br>Follow and enjoy as they say <br>아가리 닥치고 가만히 있으라 <br><br>The country is run by liars and <br>traitors and tens of millions of spectators <br>Fill the land of oblivion with <br>the monuments of concrete and glass <br><br>Hail the triumphant throne over <br>the blood and cries of the forgotten <br>Erase, kill, cover, burn and hide <br>keep the nation fucked till you die <br><br>once a wise man said; Society is endangered <br>not by the great profligacy of a few, but by the laxity of morals amongst all <br><br>bury the questioner, spread the silence <br>let the wind of power blow out the candles <br><br>It will be okay not because it’s gonna change or better <br>but because everybody will bear and forget everything again <br><br>*Quotes by Alexis de Tocqueville <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Agari" label="Agari"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Strain/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Strain - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Strain/" title="지미 스트레인 - Strain - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Crisis, when all the things we believed are <br>questioned about its meaning and value <br>Origin, when all the reasons are distorted, <br>faded and buried in the desolated reality <br><br>Dreams, hopes, changes, passion <br>all fall apart into the void <br>Weapons lose the reason to exist; <br>the world needs no soldiers to fight <br>The perfect sum of inequality, monopoly <br>And justice for all the people with money and power <br><br>But we hold our hands and march <br>We hold our chins up and high <br>We sing our songs of the night <br>In time, we’ll be dancing in the rain <br><br>Crisis, when all the things we have done <br>fail to bring a change, all is wasted <br>Origin, the lost question and answer <br>Where all the flowers we sprinkled have gone? <br><br>Revolution, evolution, future <br>all fall apart into the void <br>Flags lost the wind to wave them <br>the world isn’t worth fighting for anymore <br>Suffer if bearable, let the useless die <br>The perfect amount of pain awaiting <br>And justice for all the people with money and power <br><br>This STRAIN, this STRAIN, be the STRAIN, in this raining crisis <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Strain" label="Strain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/No_Country_For_Young_Man/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - No Country For Young Man - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/No_Country_For_Young_Man/" title="지미 스트레인 - No Country For Young Man - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It’ll let them die in the cold ocean <br>It’ll let them kill without hesitation <br>but it won't give you any solution <br>and this is not the country for you <br><br>It'll make you conspiracy theorist <br>It'll make you believe its lies <br>It'll hire forces to sit you down and shut up <br>and this is not the country for you <br><br>This isn’t a country but a battlefield of hierarchies <br><br>No country for the awakened <br>No country for the poor <br>No country for the right one <br>No country, no country for you, young man <br><br>It’ll let them die on the freezing streets <br>It’ll push them until they kill themselves <br>but it won't give you any answers <br>and this is not the country for you <br><br>It'll make you a slave of growing debts <br>It'll drug you with false hopes and dreams <br>It'll hire forces to isolate you until you die <br>and this is not the country for you <br><br>It’s inevitable fate, it’ll pass in the end <br>It’s because you’re young, it’ll be okay, it will tell you <br>You’ll like it if you are not looking for the truth <br>but the answer for the question it gave you <br>You’ll grow old, filling the emptiness in you <br>with pathetic questions in the end <br><br>Where all my life has gone? <br>For what have I wasted my life? <br>But it’s all too late! <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="No Country For Young Man" label="No Country For Young Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Finally/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Finally - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Finally/" title="지미 스트레인 - Finally - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[you know the feeling when you finally, quite accidentally found something you've been searching for but couldn't find it and so you gave up. <br>you know, like a photograph, some real special photo of you and other people...you know that the photo exists but couldn’t find it, and it seems like you lost it somewhere, somewhere near, somewhere you’re familiar with but you just couldn’t find it, so you decide that you’ve lost that photo somewhere you can’t search,.. which is a tragedy but bad things happen all the time to everyone, so you can at least accept it as a truth or reality, a tragic one, because after the painful process of searching and wandering, you need some rest,.. like even though it’s tragic, once it become a part of reality then you can move on. you couldn’t find the photo but at least you could find some dark peace and get the right to move on. <br>then as if you forgot the existence of the picture, you just live your life as you should. to some people, you act like you’ve never even tried or struggled to find the picture, like nothing ever happened. you live like that and time just flies, but deep inside you, really really deep inside you, you know that you lost the picture that must be found, cause you can’t lie to yourself, cause you can’t fake your own satisfaction. you cannot negotiate the true desire, so every once in a while, like when you’re drunk or... say when you have a big cleaning day, you try to find that picture again, keep telling yourself that you’re not gonna find that picture because you lost it somewhere else while repeating ‘i’ve got to find that photo, I know it's somewhere in this room, I know I can do this, I know i’ll find it in the end...’ <br>but you fail to do so, again, you go back to the track, live the life without picture. <br>then, all of sudden, I mean really, just suddenly, the picture just comes up from the most ridiculous place, you can’t say the picture is found, it’s like it’s been created from nowhere right on time of your finding. the photograph you’ve searched for all your life is like being born right at the moment. bamm! here i’am! the photo yells at you, the reality, the truth yells at the same time, the photo exists and you were right, you’ve been always right all the time, but the reality you had to be in so far, wasn’t. <br>you hold that picture and the memories all coming back to you. you’re happy and relieved,. but it’s still one hell of a weird sensation, in a good way. <br><br>this is what I felt, this is how I felt,. first time I saw you. <br>because I felt that I wasn’t seeing you for the first time, <br>...instead I felt I found you, finally. <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Finally" label="Finally"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/All_The_Saints/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - All The Saints - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/All_The_Saints/" title="지미 스트레인 - All The Saints - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I stayed up through the night; bright sun says hi to me <br>I saw people hurrying into the hustle and bustle of the day <br>Men and women already working; bag-carrying kids heading to schools <br>Everybody's doing to give life to this concrete world <br><br>People are chatting, birds are singing <br>Engines are running, hearts are beating <br>Trees are shining, winds are blowing <br>He's walking, she's running <br>Everybody's different but they do it all the same <br>Doing a noble part to keep the life going <br><br>All the saints, All the saints <br>You're all the saints, everybody <br>All the saints, All the saints <br>You're all the saints, every day, baby <br><br>I thought this world would be darker and deadlier than ever before <br>Progress is Big Foot, hope’s the Loch Ness monster, talked about but never seen <br>Everything around me shall fall apart and just get worse <br>I thought I should stop dreaming, but I know I was wrong <br><br>People are chatting, birds are singing <br>Engines are running, hearts are beating <br>Trees are shining, winds are blowing <br>He's walking, she's running <br>Busy footsteps sound better than any prayer I’ve heard <br>Nothing's more sacred than keeping it alive, you know <br><br>The choices you make, not the names on the cards, tell who you really are <br>What you did and are doing now, not where you're from, tell what you believe <br>Listen to the sound of people, the people without badges or crowns <br>Listen to the sound of people, everyday heroes, real life dreamers <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="All The Saints" label="All The Saints"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/This_Beat/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - This Beat - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/This_Beat/" title="지미 스트레인 - This Beat - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tears and sweat hanging on your chin <br>Crying and yelling holding on your lips <br>It's hard to stand but you're trying your best <br>This is driving you crazy, yeah, it's crazy <br><br>Despair is everywhere <br>and another failure is waiting there <br>you think this is not fair <br>but close your eyes and, my dear <br><br>Listen to your heart, beating so loud <br>even when you give up and run away <br>Remember your heart, beating so loud <br>even when you’re scared and hide away <br><br>Regrets again, now you're trying to turn your back <br>Biting lips, it's hard to accept, no <br>It's hard to stand but you're trying your best <br>This is driving you crazy, yeah, it's crazy <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="This Beat" label="This Beat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Oando/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Oando - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Oando/" title="지미 스트레인 - Oando - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[i want to be a dictator in your world <br>listen to nobody but you <br>cause you are already a dictator <br>in my world, in my mind, of my soul <br><br>i don't want you to stand out from others <br>cause you're not standing on the same ground <br>i don't want you to be special than any other <br>cause you can be compared to no other <br><br>so just like me, yeah i should be <br>the one and only <br>so just like you, baby you're already <br>the one and only <br><br>i don't want to be a lonely monument <br>like a stuffed animal covered with dust <br>i'd rather be unerasable scar <br>on your skin, in your heart, of your soul <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Oando" label="Oando"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Lake/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Lake - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Lake/" title="지미 스트레인 - Lake - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody has a past he never wants to talk about <br>like a stone dropped in the water <br>The bygone days make the wave sometimes <br>no one can remove the stone or mend the troubled lake <br><br>But you can hold the wave for today <br>build the wall and stop the wave <br>So save the moment, and please save me <br>build the wall and stop the wave <br><br>If you love me, then keep the distance <br>farther to your past, closer to your dream <br>Like the stars hanging far away in the darkness <br>who can reach us only by their light <br><br>But you can hold the wave for today <br>build the wall and stop the wave <br>So save yourself precious, and please save me <br>build the wall and stop the wave <br><br>May you be the brightest star shining in the highest sky <br>Let me be your lake that never ever waves <br>but just reflects the very best of you <br>so you can see how beautiful you are <br>I’ll be the lake <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Lake" label="Lake"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Marionette/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Marionette - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Marionette/" title="지미 스트레인 - Marionette - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's the master of life <br>behind the mask of smile <br>She's the heroine of the stage <br>her role, an adorable asian doll <br><br>A happy one, a great one, a nice one <br>pet owners can say whatever they want <br>While his over protection is suffocating <br>she becomes more fragile behind the glass <br><br>She's a marionette with too many wires <br>She's a chapel of too many choirs <br>She’s the one who has been a bad liar <br>Forgive her, but she just started the fire <br>Forgive her, but she gotta cut the wires <br><br>He loves his doll so much <br>babies it all the time in the name of love <br>That love would have killed her if she were real <br>He becomes an owner and she’s a property <br><br>He tells others to take care of her <br>never notices that he sounded like a warden <br>Promises, rings, kisses and kids <br>now all reflects on the show window <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Marionette" label="Marionette"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Strangers_In_Heaven/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Strangers In Heaven - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Strangers_In_Heaven/" title="지미 스트레인 - Strangers In Heaven - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let’s leave before warmth <br>and easiness hold us here; <br>We need to walk on the untrodden roads <br>to take roots somewhere <br><br>In the noisy world we have met <br>and grown secret longing together; <br>To the serene home in our hearts <br>we will go back hand in hand <br><br>We're strangers in heaven <br>Let the world become the hell where no one can run away <br>We're strangers in heaven <br>Let all the rest fall apart, you know I only care about you <br><br>I shall be walking and you shall be dreaming <br>as we used to do <br>Cry when you feel like crying <br>don’t try too hard to stand tall <br><br>In this falling world <br>it’s only natural that we’re feeling lonely <br>Hope shall beam on us only <br>when we sit face to face with despair <br><br>Let all the rest fall apart, you know I only <br>You know I only care about you <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Strangers In Heaven" label="Strangers In Heaven"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Roadkill/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Roadkill - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Roadkill/" title="지미 스트레인 - Roadkill - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Fallen economy hired me <br>Job searching is the job for me <br>Twenty-four/Seven, there's no time to rest <br>My dark future makes me feel sick like no other <br><br>Lethargy and defeat are my new friends <br>Wasted resumes are sour and salty and I got drunk <br>Mix a cocktail of anxiety and solitude and more <br>I am an alcoholic, dreaming of working <br><br>It’s tough and rough and so hard to stand on my feet <br>No right to complain I’ve got, so I just sob inside <br>I am a roadkill on the highway of competition <br>I'm not the only jobless dying from overwork <br><br>I think I studied a lot <br>I believe I've learned even more <br>Twenty-four/Seven, I never stopped to rest <br>I guess I've done it all, but why am I not happy at all? <br><br>To be a part of the corporate machinery <br>To be a part of the war of life as mercenary <br>To be the winners running away (at the first win) <br>To be the dreamers who no longer need to dream <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Roadkill" label="Roadkill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/은과_네온과_유황의_시_AgNeS/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - 은과 네온과 유황의 시 (AgNeS) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/%EC%9D%80%EA%B3%BC_%EB%84%A4%EC%98%A8%EA%B3%BC_%EC%9C%A0%ED%99%A9%EC%9D%98_%EC%8B%9C_AgNeS/" title="지미 스트레인 - 은과 네온과 유황의 시 (AgNeS) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[살기 위한 몸부림에 먼지가 일어 <br>말라버린 입안에 네 이름을 머금고 <br>그리움 한 모금 삼킬 때 어디선가 <br>들려오는 너의 속삭임에 다시 나는 <br><br>미소로 메이크업을 하고 건조한 타인들의 숲으로 <br>이를 악물고 그렇게 뛰어 들지 <br>지금 흐르는 이 눈물을 참고 모아서 <br>언젠가 너의 창에 별로 빛내 주리라 <br><br>나를 믿어, AgNeS, 새처럼 날아가는 약속이지만 <br>나를 봐줘, AgNeS, 향기 없는 꽃 같은 꿈이더라도 <br>그대와 함께라면, 그대만 있어준다면 <br>그대와 함께라면, 그대가 잡아준다면 <br>그걸로 나는 좋아 <br><br>우린 좋은 차도 좋은 집도 없이 <br>서로라는 향기에 취해 겁도 없이 <br>눈을 감아도 어둡지 않고 목소리는 커져 <br>귀를 막아도 들리는 속삭임에 취해 <br><br>빈속을 행복으로 채우고 건조한 타인들의 숲으로 <br>괜찮은 듯 웃으며 그렇게 들어가지 <br>앞만 보며 달리는 경주마 같은 삶 <br>괜찮아 내겐 네가 있는 곳이 곧 앞이기에 <br><br>나를 믿어, AgNeS, 새처럼 날아가는 약속이지만 <br>나를 봐줘, AgNeS, 향기 없는 꽃 같은 꿈이더라도 <br>그대와 함께라면, 그대만 있어준다면 <br>그대와 함께라면, 그대가 잡아준다면 <br>그걸로 충분해 <br><br>銀처럼 날 지켜주는 사람아 <br>고독의 밤을 가르는 Neon의 등대여 <br>내 안에 타오르는 환희의 硫黃이여 <br>당신은 완벽한 한 편의 詩 <br><br>나를 잡아, AgNeS, 허공 속에 텅 빈 멜로디라도 <br>나를 불러, AgNeS, 아무도 듣지 못할 외침이라도 <br>그대와 함께라면, 그대만 있어준다면 <br>그대와 함께라면, 그대가 잡아준다면 <br>그걸로 나는 좋아 <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="은과 네온과 유황의 시 (AgNeS)" label="은과 네온과 유황의 시 (AgNeS)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/War/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - War - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/War/" title="지미 스트레인 - War - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[the storm is coming, the end is near <br>this time i'll let you cry cause no one will ever hear <br>is it our color, is it what we believe <br>is it our land or something under there <br>whatever it is, sin or bad luck <br>we're being violated and punished way too much <br><br>just like greed and truth, just like hyper-crisy <br>love and empathy show only on the display of apathy <br><br>it's called war, and it's a cold war <br>on the face of a child, on the roof of the poor <br>drop the shadow of death <br>in the name of god, in the hands of the rich <br>destroy and tear down everything we killed and died for <br><br>the media are bleaching the blood stains on their robe <br>this time i'll let you cry cause they'll shut the door <br>they’ll pick the victims, they’ll pick who to blame <br>they're the crime itself, they're the shame <br>whatever happens, headlines will define what to be true <br>we'll be buried under the pictures on the front page <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="War" label="War"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Peace_Of_Mind/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Peace Of Mind - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Peace_Of_Mind/" title="지미 스트레인 - Peace Of Mind - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[for my father who lost his mother, and my mom who lost her father <br><br>You're not getting stronger or slower <br>you're not growing, but just getting old <br>you gotta set aside a spot for sorrow <br>so you can live with it and have peace of mind <br><br>We only grow when we're in sorrow <br>We only move when we need a place to stay <br>and we can be complete, only when we're broken <br>to find what really matters, we have to lose everything <br><br>You'll try to get rid of it, hope it's gone <br>but it'll be with you until you’re gone <br>Sorrow won't follow you, it won't hunt you down: <br>it'll always be you searching for peace of mind <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Peace Of Mind" label="Peace Of Mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Clouds_And_Heaven/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Clouds And Heaven - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Clouds_And_Heaven/" title="지미 스트레인 - Clouds And Heaven - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Have you ever dreamed of flying <br>walking through the fragrant clouds <br>all the blue above and beneath <br>let the ocean be the mirrored <br>heaven <br><br>Have you ever dreamed of flying <br>walking through the mist of skies <br>all the blue under and over <br>let the wind be the best friend of <br>heaven <br><br>On the border-less canvas of blue <br>let's walk away until we disappear <br>away, far away from all the despair <br>and all those silly things we fought for <br><br>Have you ever dreamed of flying <br>walking on the clouds into the darkness <br>where the night kisses the day <br>now you may cry, let it be the rain <br>it's heaven <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Clouds And Heaven" label="Clouds And Heaven"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Crazy_Strange_Love/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Crazy Strange Love - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Crazy_Strange_Love/" title="지미 스트레인 - Crazy Strange Love - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love can't be completed by promises <br>It’s complete incompletion till the end <br>lack of you makes me miss you more <br>it's already perfect as imperfection <br><br>Crazy, Strange, you know it’s love <br>Crazy, Strange, you know it’s all because of love <br><br>Life may be a trip, a boring business trip <br>but you're the one who turned it into a picnic <br>you know our love makes us do some crazy things <br>how strange once it starts, it just lasts, and never ends. <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Crazy Strange Love" label="Crazy Strange Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Dont_Promise_Me/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Don`t Promise Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:03:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:03:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Dont_Promise_Me/" title="지미 스트레인 - Don`t Promise Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t promise me anything <br>that you will never kever <br>Don’t promise me anything <br>that you don’t really care <br>Don’t promise me anything <br>that I don’t want you to do <br>Don’t promise me anything <br>that you don’t really know about <br><br>I know, that you’re saying it just to make me happy, baby <br>I see, that’s nice of you and it’s pretty sweet, but you see, <br>It’s not, something that I really want <br><br>If you really love me <br>then don’t promise me bed of roses <br>If you really love me <br>don’t say our love will last forever <br>All I need is just one day to be with you <br>and promise me now/baby, that it’s gonna be today <br><br>Don’t promise me anything <br>that you’re gonna break someday <br>Don’t promise me anything <br>that you will forget in the end <br>Don’t promise me forever love <br>I don’t need love outlive myself <br>Don’t promise me anything <br>Now it really drives me crazy <br><br>I know, when I see your eyes that you really mean it or not <br>I see, we make mistakes but it’s okay, we’re not perfect <br>It’s fine, everything will be better I know, so don’t say sorry, <br>don’t say sorry <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Don`t Promise Me" label="Don`t Promise Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Anti-Social/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Anti-Social - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Anti-Social/" title="지미 스트레인 - Anti-Social - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[i don't want to share <br>i don't want to like <br>i don't want no flag <br>i don't want to follow <br><br>and i guess i'm self-centered <br>and i guess i'm deaf and blind <br>and i guess i'm sick of saying amen <br>and i guess i'm an anti-social <br><br>i don't know your name <br>i don't know your pain <br>i don't know your gain <br>i don't know what you're saying <br><br>and i guess i'm self-centered <br>and i guess i'm deaf and blind <br>and i guess i'm sick of saying amen <br>and i guess i'm an anti-social <br><br>i'll be white when you go black <br>i'll be black when you go white <br>i'll be grey when it's raining <br>i'll be shining when it's dark outside <br><br>and i guess i'm self-centered <br>and i guess i'm deaf and blind <br>and i guess i'm sick of saying amen <br>and i guess i'm an anti-social <br><br>you don't have to judge me cause i've done it my way <br>you don't need to hate me cause time flies away <br>you don't have to love me cause i'm not your kinda boy <br>you don't need to remember me cause i'll be gone away <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Anti-Social" label="Anti-Social"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Today/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Today - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Today/" title="지미 스트레인 - Today - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wished today not to come <br>or brand new sun would reveal unsolved problems <br>I wished today I wouldn't wake up <br>or the veil would be removed, showing the empty stage <br>while I gaze at the silence in auditorium <br>until I lose my eyes and words <br><br>So let me sleep more <br>I won't dream, I won't run away <br>So leave me behind the curtain <br>the world's not ready for me, neither am i <br><br>I wished today to be the same <br>as yesterday and before, so i might do better this time <br>I wished today no sun would come up <br>nothing grew, nothing awoke, just drunk by the endless night <br>and only the stars would shine, and we could be more merciful <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Today" label="Today"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Genie/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Genie - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Genie/" title="지미 스트레인 - Genie - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was wondering in the night <br>didn't know that I was looking for the princess <br>I had couple of drinks and danced <br>didn't know the night was going to be priceless <br><br>You came into my life and lightened it up <br>you brought Sultan’s magic and made me complete <br>You came into my life and brightened it up <br>you became a part of me <br><br>Not everything, you can not have in the world <br>but you have everything of me, of me <br>Not the best things, you can not have in life <br>but you have the best of me, of me <br><br>I was searching for the treasure island <br>and you got me there before I ask <br>Gathering all shining particles of time <br>we spent together <br><br>love is not inside the lamp, life is not inside the room <br>you’re the light so come out and shine, <br>life is on the road come out and own it, i’ll be with you <br><br>don't go back to the lamp but stay with me <br>don't be a fairy tale sprite but a spirit free <br>don't go back to the lamp but stay with me <br>now I cannot let you go <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Genie" label="Genie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Time_2_Cry/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Time 2 Cry - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Time_2_Cry/" title="지미 스트레인 - Time 2 Cry - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[you're hurt and wounded <br>and coming home alone <br>wanting nobody but missing <br>everybody, and it's okay, it's okay <br><br>you're burnt and lost <br>and praying to be good again <br>loving nobody but missing <br>anybody to hold, and it's okay <br><br>talk to the world that you're hurt and wounded <br>say it out loud that you're just a man <br>tell him it's time to cry, tell her it's time to cry <br>yeah, it's time to cry <br><br>you're breathing cold air <br>and living in the cruel city <br>lying on the bed calling for <br>regrets and memories, it's okay <br><br>you're dreaming a dream <br>and forgetting you're lost and alone <br>trying to find the question <br>that you were looking for, it's okay <br><br>talk to the world that you've got something to regret <br>say it out loud that you're just a man <br>tell him it's time to cry, tell her it's time to cry <br>yeah, it's time to cry <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Time 2 Cry" label="Time 2 Cry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Dicks_Daughter/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Dick`s Daughter - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Dicks_Daughter/" title="지미 스트레인 - Dick`s Daughter - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[we kiss democracy goodbye tonight <br>baby, I know it's not your kinda lovin' <br>just let your body move under the candlelights <br>dance to the sound of crying and yelling <br><br>at the head of the parade is not some leader <br>but some prima donna of the puppet show <br>no need to see, no need to hear, no no <br>you don't need anybody to enjoy but yourself <br><br>Dicks' Daughter, Dick's Daughter <br>decades of lonely nights are gone forever tonight <br>Dicks' Daughter, Dick's Daughter <br>to the enemies, the damages are done tonight <br><br>Dicks' Daughter, Dick's Daughter <br>queen of betrayals, princess of darkness <br>Dicks' Daughter, Dick's Daughter <br>come sit tight on the throne of blood as your daddy did <br>yeah <br><br>we paint the enemies red, paint'em red <br>you're the law and sexier than "Judge Dread" <br>let them have your fake tears to tear <br>their hearts apart and fall into despair <br><br>let the dogs build the walls to block the screams <br>a million candles they light up to celebrate <br>the birth of the new dicks and disgrace <br>blow the candles, why bother, they don't give a dare <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Dick`s Daughter" label="Dick`s Daughter"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Lgbtqia/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Lgbtqia - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Lgbtqia/" title="지미 스트레인 - Lgbtqia - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love Grows By The Quests In Abhorrences <br>what we fight against is not indifference <br>love was there before the rules ever made <br>and you know it was there before the word itself <br><br>it's the hatred not the difference that creates a monster, oh, no <br>before the stereotypes blind us forever <br>open your eyes and see the truth <br><br>you don't even have to pick, no one asks you to become one <br>let them be as they were born, LGBTQIA! <br>you don't even have to pick, no one asks you to become one <br>let them be as they want to be, LGBTQIA! <br>Love Grows By The Quests In Abhorrences, LGBTQIA! <br><br>you know there are more than just one color <br>diversity in the ray makes the rainbow <br>let all the people enjoy the equality <br>and don't let the majority become the justice <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Lgbtqia" label="Lgbtqia"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/거인_The_Giant/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - 거인 (The Giant) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/%EA%B1%B0%EC%9D%B8_The_Giant/" title="지미 스트레인 - 거인 (The Giant) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 너무 커져서 이제 <br>발자국을 남기지 않고 <br>걸을 수 없어 <br>아무런 흔적 없이 그렇게 <br>사라지려면 한 걸음 더 가까이 <br>파도를 향해 걷는 거야 <br>갈채와 같은 소리, 오랜 친구 같은 바람 <br><br>우리 함께 했던 시간들 <br>허름한 유적으로라도 남을 수만 있다면 <br>밤하늘 닮은 저 바다를 향해 <br>나는 뒤돌아보지 않는 석상이 되리 <br><br>나는 이렇게나 자랐는데 <br>이 많은 별들은 여전히 <br>그렇게 나를 내려다봐 <br>손닿는 건 하나도 없는데 <br>다가갔을까 한 걸음이라도 <br>밤은 말없이 검기만 해 <br><br>우리 함께 했던 순간들 <br>빛나는 별자리로 새길 수만 있다면 <br>밤하늘 닮은 저 바다를 향해 <br>나는 걷고 걸어 별들에 안긴 섬이 되리 <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="거인 (The Giant)" label="거인 (The Giant)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/상자_Boxes/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - 상자 (Boxes) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/%EC%83%81%EC%9E%90_Boxes/" title="지미 스트레인 - 상자 (Boxes) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[애 아빠는 앉아 쉴 상자를 찾고 <br>애 엄마는 곁에 누울 상자를 찾고 <br>할아버지는 눈 감을 상자를 찾고 <br>할머니는 하루를 살아낼 상자를 찾는다 <br><br>회사원은 돌아갈 상자를 찾고 <br>젊은이는 머무를 상자를 찾고 <br>나는 노래하며 놀 상자를 찾고 <br>울 엄마는 아들의 상자를 찾는다 <br><br>돈 많은 이는 커다란 상자를 찾고 <br>돈 없는 이는 쫓겨나지 않을 상자를 찾고 <br>나는 울림 좋은 상자를 찾는데 <br>울 아빠는 아들의 상자를 찾는다 <br><br>누군가는 꼿꼿하게 누울 상자를 찾고 <br>누군가는 하얀 재로 채울 상자를 찾을 때 <br>나는 이미 추억 가득한 상자를 찾았는데 <br>엄마 아빠는 아직도 아들의 상자를 찾는다 <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="상자 (Boxes)" label="상자 (Boxes)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/봄_Spring/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - 봄 (Spring) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/%EB%B4%84_Spring/" title="지미 스트레인 - 봄 (Spring) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄은 우연처럼 다가와 <br>결국 운명으로 남아요 <br>잠시 머물렀던 자리가 <br>불에 덴 것만 같아요 <br><br>봄이 붙잡았던 나의 손은 <br>잃어버린 온기가 그리워 <br>함께 걸었던 길 위에서 <br>이방인은 걸음을 멈춰요 <br><br>그래, 넌 내가 찾아 헤맨 답이었어 <br>그래, 넌 내 안에 불던 바람이었어 <br>그래, 넌 내 계절의 시작이었어 <br>그래, 넌 내가 찾던 그리움이었어 <br><br>봄이 울기 시작하면 <br>여름이 다가오는 거예요 <br>내가 아무리 울어도 <br>시간은 봄을 데려가요 <br><br>긴 적막의 겨울과 <br>소란스런 여름 사이 <br>눈을 뜨는 봄의 당부 <br>돌아올 테니 기다려 달라고 <br><br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="봄 (Spring)" label="봄 (Spring)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Vagabond/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Vagabond - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Vagabond/" title="지미 스트레인 - Vagabond - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[갈 길은 먼데 걷는 법을 잊었어요 <br>길 위에 서서 다시 길을 잃었어요 <br>떠나온 곳은 어딘지, 가야할 곳은 어딘지 <br>여행은 그렇게 방랑이 됐어요 <br><br>해가 지고 밤이 깊어지면 <br>숨어있던 꿈들이 하늘을 채우고 <br>머리 위에서 당신이 별자리가 될 때 <br>삶은 또다시 낯선 길에 놓이네 <br><br>한 걸음, 또 한 걸음, 걸음을 세지 마오 <br>하나, 둘, 서이 너이, 별을 세지 마오 <br>정말 소중한 건 숫자 될 수 없음을 <br>그대, 언제쯤 알려나 <br>어리석은 방랑자여 <br><br>술을 끊으면 건강해질 수 있지만 <br>술을 마셔야 또 하루를 살 수 있어요 <br>세상은 술을 사지도 않으면서 <br>쉬지 않고 안주를 내어 놓아요 <br><br>한 걸음, 또 한 걸음, 걸음을 세지 마오 <br>하나, 둘, 서이 너이, 별을 세지 마오 <br>정말 소중한 건 결코 셀 수 없음을 <br>그대, 언제쯤 알려나 <br>어리석은 방랑자여 <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Vagabond" label="Vagabond"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/찰나_The_Fleeting_Moment/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - 찰나 (The Fleeting Moment) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/%EC%B0%B0%EB%82%98_The_Fleeting_Moment/" title="지미 스트레인 - 찰나 (The Fleeting Moment) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈을 감으면 사라지는 이 순간처럼 <br>눈을 뜨면 잊히는 어제처럼 <br>아버지와 함께 걷던 그 날들은 <br>뒤돌아보니 모두 찰나였다 <br><br>긴 시간동안 살아있음을 잊고 <br>죽음을 고민하며 삶을 허비했네 <br>고독에 몸부림치던 긴 밤들은 <br>뒤돌아보니 모두 찰나였다 <br><br>삶은 손금을 따라 떠나는 산책 <br>나 비틀거린 덕에 너를 만났네 <br>가지이고 뿌리인 이 길을 따라 <br>나 쉬지 않았기에 여기 있네, 여기에 있네 <br><br>우리 안의 뜨거웠던 불꽃도 <br>시가 되어 날아가 버린 숨결도 <br>기억나지 않는 이름들처럼 <br>뒤돌아보니 모두 찰나였다 <br><br>베개를 적시던 슬픈 공상들이 <br>눈앞에 꽃이 되어 만발한 오늘 <br>나의 사랑도 그리움도 모두 다 <br>뒤돌아보니 모두 찰나였다 <br><br>찰나일거다 결국 모두 다 <br>날아갈 향기다 우리 모두가 <br>사라질 온기다 머지않아서 <br>찰나일거다 참 다행이다 <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="찰나 (The Fleeting Moment)" label="찰나 (The Fleeting Moment)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/어른_The_Grown-Up/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - 어른 (The Grown-Up) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/%EC%96%B4%EB%A5%B8_The_Grown-Up/" title="지미 스트레인 - 어른 (The Grown-Up) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어른이 되었을 때가 언제냐고 물으면 <br>말 할 수 없는 비밀을 갖게 된 때라 하리라 <br>어른이 되었을 때가 언제냐고 물으면 <br>위로 받지 못할 슬픔을 알게 된 때라 하리라 <br><br>어른이 되었을 때가 언제냐고 물으면 <br>비밀과 슬픔과 외로움이 익숙해진 때라 하리라 <br>어른이 되었을 때가 언제냐고 물으면 <br>언제 이렇게 되었는지 기억나지 않게 된 때라 하리라 <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="어른 (The Grown-Up)" label="어른 (The Grown-Up)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/홍옥_Ruby-Red_Apple/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - 홍옥 (Ruby-Red Apple) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/%ED%99%8D%EC%98%A5_Ruby-Red_Apple/" title="지미 스트레인 - 홍옥 (Ruby-Red Apple) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[화려한 빛들이 밤을 몰아내고 <br>새로운 것들이 어둠을 채워도 <br>허물고 세우고 또 허물어 봐도 <br>끝내 가릴 수 없는 허무여 <br><br>낯선 현실에서 마주하는 낯익은 가면들 <br>휴지 한 장 태우지 못하는 가짜 불꽃들 <br><br>세상의 온도가 지금보다 높던 때 <br>카바이드 불빛 아래서 반짝이던 눈이여 <br>베어 물으면 이제는 눈물이 날 것만 같은 <br>오! 홍옥의 붉음이여 <br><br>붉은 흙을 덮은 검은 카펫 <br>차가운 심장과 재가 된 희망 <br>디스토피아의 얼굴과 희망의 디스플레이 <br>추락의 상속과 절망의 유전을 보라 <br><br>기적의 강 위로 노을이 질 때 <br>비로소 고개를 드는 삶의 숙제여 <br><br>세상의 온도가 지금보다 높던 때 <br>카바이드 불빛 아래서 반짝이던 눈이여 <br>베어 물으면 이제는 눈물이 날 것만 같은 <br>오! 홍옥의 붉음이여 오! 그 피 같은 붉음이여 <br>오! 홍옥의 붉음이여 오! 향기롭던 심장이여 <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="홍옥 (Ruby-Red Apple)" label="홍옥 (Ruby-Red Apple)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/공항_Airport/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - 공항 (Airport) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/%EA%B3%B5%ED%95%AD_Airport/" title="지미 스트레인 - 공항 (Airport) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[짐은 무거워도 걸음은 가볍게 <br>정든 풍경들이 사라지기 전에 <br>높은 천장 가득 사람들의 소리 <br>이별과 재회가 나누는 이야기 <br><br>안도와 위로와 약속과 기도와 <br>그리움과 반가움 모두 한 곳에 모여 <br><br>만나기 위해 떠나 또 <br>떠나기 위해 만나 또 <br>그리워 하려 떠나 또 <br>그렇게 다시 만나 또 <br><br>바다 멀리서 너도 저 달을 보겠지 <br>보고 싶을 땐 잠시 눈을 감아 <br><br>구름 뒤의 별들처럼 보이지 않아도 <br>넌 내 안에서 항상 빛나는 걸 <br><br>당부와 감사와 아쉬움과 미안함 <br>떠나기 전이지만 난 벌써 네가 그리워 <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="공항 (Airport)" label="공항 (Airport)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/백수의_과로사_Death_Of_An_Overworking_Jobless/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - 백수의 과로사 (Death Of An Overworking Jobless) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/%EB%B0%B1%EC%88%98%EC%9D%98_%EA%B3%BC%EB%A1%9C%EC%82%AC_Death_Of_An_Overworking_Jobless/" title="지미 스트레인 - 백수의 과로사 (Death Of An Overworking Jobless) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[일 없는 나는 오늘도 할 일 찾아 쉬질 못해 <br>거절과 좌절의 굴레 속 이 몸은 녹초 <br><br>패배와 무기력을 벗 삼아 불안과 고독에 취해버리네 <br>힘들지만 힘들다고 말 할 수 없어 더 힘든 <br>차가운 위로에 기댔다가 불안과 고독에 취해버리네 <br>경쟁의 길 위에 객사, 백수의 과로사 <br><br>날 취하게 하는 너의 취직 날 울리는 너의 위로 <br>혼자 돌아오는 귀갓길 가로등도 슬피 우네 <br><br>패배와 무기력을 벗 삼아 불안과 고독에 취해버리네 <br>미안하단 말하기가 더 미안해 할 수 없는 <br>차가운 위로에 잠시 기댔다가 불안과 고독에 취해버리네 <br>꿈의 산 오르다 실족사, 백수의 과로사 <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="백수의 과로사 (Death Of An Overworking Jobless)" label="백수의 과로사 (Death Of An Overworking Jobless)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Maybe/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Maybe - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Maybe/" title="지미 스트레인 - Maybe - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[진짜 민주주의는 자본주의가 어떤 방법을 취하든 인권을 존중한다는 뜻이거든 <br>근데 한국 사람은 민주주의라고 하면 자본주의를 지키는 것인 줄 알아 <br><br>민주주의 하나의 체제가 무너지는 것은 곧 인간이 짐승처럼 되어버리는 것이나 같아 <br>앞으로의 세계는 인간이 진정 행복할 수 있는 곳이 되기 힘들 거야 <br>좋은 차와 좋은 집을 갖고 물질적으로 행복하게 살 수는 있겠지만 <br>인간이 인간답게 행복한 사회가 되긴 어려워 <br><br>자본주의에서나 어느 체제에서나 인간은 욕심이 많은 동물이야 <br>그런데 여기서는 자기 생각에 반대하는 사람들을 공산당으로 몰아버리니, 앞이 캄캄하지 <br><br>But nothing's wasted yet <br>maybe we just feel so empty and lost <br>And we're not alone, no <br>maybe just far away from each other <br>So let's sing together quietly, my friends <br>until what we fancy becomes reality <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Maybe" label="Maybe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Im_Coming_Home/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - I`m Coming Home - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Im_Coming_Home/" title="지미 스트레인 - I`m Coming Home - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I’m coming home <br>as my tears have dried <br>I’ve lost everything I had once <br>now I’ve found the truth <br><br>I’m coming home <br>where my heart belongs <br>where your heart stayed once <br>now I need it so much <br><br>The place where we spent time together, <br>rain or sunshine <br>It’s the place telling me what I really need <br>in my life <br><br>I’ll wait for you <br>time will fly as it used to be <br>I’ll grow old and weak <br>but I won’t give up <br><br>Memories will fade away <br>all those regrets and mistakes <br>I may forget your face <br>but I’ll know when you come <br><br>The place where we spent time together, <br>rain or sunshine <br>It’s the place telling me what you really meant <br>in my life <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="I`m Coming Home" label="I`m Coming Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Adobe/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Adobe - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Adobe/" title="지미 스트레인 - Adobe - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[As I smoothed out the wrinkles around my mother's eyes <br>Photoshop hid kindly what a bad boy had done to her <br>So I owed the american software company for covering my regret <br>She was smiling with no hint of touch-up; <br>I was hoping undoing the boy’s doing <br><br>Deeper skies and darker nights, <br>brighter days bring them all come alive <br>She was smiling with no hint of touch-up; <br>I was hoping undoing the boy’s doing <br><br>As I look at the smoothed face of mine without the wrinkles <br>I hope my good boy won't hold himself responsible for <br>the lines, my own prizes and trophies I earned with my own effort <br>But smile and remove my wrinkles with photoshop; <br>It's better my boy undoing the time's doing <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Adobe" label="Adobe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/What_Time_Does_To_Us/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - What Time Does To Us - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/What_Time_Does_To_Us/" title="지미 스트레인 - What Time Does To Us - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The stickers on my cell phone are falling <br>children's stickers that I bought for you <br>People used to ask who put them there <br>My nieces and nephews, I would say <br><br>Heart's falling, sky's fading <br>Dinosaurs’re almost gone out of the planet <br>Nothing can linger on and I <br>guess this is what time does to us <br>We're no longer together; <br>being EX’s make it hard to live <br>like we used to and I <br>guess this is what time does to us <br><br>The pictures I took of you long ago are torn <br>images open the doors to the past <br>People would ask who tore it like that <br>It's me and no one but me, I would say <br><br>This is what time does to us <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="What Time Does To Us" label="What Time Does To Us"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Kite/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Kite - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Kite/" title="지미 스트레인 - Kite - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm gonna treat you <br>like I hate you <br>I'm gonna leave you <br>like I'm mad at you <br>But that's not true <br>no, that's not true <br><br>I'm gonna kiss you <br>like I love you <br>I'm gonna hold you <br>like I miss you <br>and that is true <br>yeah, that is true <br><br>Not too close, not too far <br>not to break, not to lose <br>like a kite in the sky <br>If my love grows too far <br>then it's time to cut the string <br>and let you go, let it all go <br><br>I'm gonna tell you <br>that i hate you <br>I'm gonna tell you <br>that i don't need you <br>but that's not true <br>no, that's not true <br><br>I'm gonna leave you <br>while you're sleeping <br>i'm gonna leave you <br>my heart and soul <br>but that's no good <br>I know, that's no use <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Kite" label="Kite"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/See_You_On_The_Other_Side/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - See You On The Other Side - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/See_You_On_The_Other_Side/" title="지미 스트레인 - See You On The Other Side - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You may want to know why I take all the troubles <br>why I don't take the easy way, the way you go <br>You may wonder why I choose the hardest way <br>and waste my time, crying in the middle of the night <br><br>But don’t you know that we all have <br>our own routes and speeds <br>of climbing up the mountains? <br><br>You may want to know why I'm going so slowly <br>why I don’t get the easy prizes, the way you do <br>You may wonder why I am not all out or all in <br>yet I'm doing my best, maybe I'm just doing it slow <br><br>But don’t you know that we all have <br>our own winds and boats <br>of sailing on the ocean of life? <br><br>Maybe I'm digging a lake <br>not the wells others drill <br>Maybe I'm a flower blooming at night <br>making stars and the moon sweet <br>So please don't worry about me and <br>see you on the other side <br><br>See you on the other side <br>I'll be fine, so don't worry <br>See you on the other side <br>I'll be alright, so don't worry about me <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="See You On The Other Side" label="See You On The Other Side"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Happy_Birthday/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Happy Birthday - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Happy_Birthday/" title="지미 스트레인 - Happy Birthday - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You said it means nothing to you <br>because it's not the real date but what's given to you <br>All I know it's good to have you <br>here on earth, on my mind and in my life <br><br>Life was white canvas with dots sprinkled all over to find <br>the meaning I was lost and wandered everywhere <br>Then you came to me and put the nameless stars together <br>you drew a map showing where the dreams come true <br><br>You know how to put things together, <br>lines become roots and branches of trees <br>growing deep inside the land of destiny <br>and reaching far up to the havens of dreams <br><br>Let them grow bigger and taller until <br>their love shower through spring sunshine <br>and longings come back fresh in pouring rain <br>and we will all be born again <br>,..now happy birthday <br><br>You don't have to come see me; <br>you have never left me <br>all I want is you’re free <br>where you're, with or without me <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Happy Birthday" label="Happy Birthday"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/The_House_I_Loved/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - The House I Loved - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/The_House_I_Loved/" title="지미 스트레인 - The House I Loved - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a house I loved <br>I loved it since my first day there <br>Well, I was born in the house <br>grew up in my first love <br><br>There's a house I lived in <br>I thought I'd never leave there <br>Grown up tall, I left my first love <br><br>There's a house I loved <br>It was a friend and a nest for me <br>Well, I was a student and I learned how to love <br><br>It was big and I was small then <br>Well, I’m sad to see it small and weak <br>A house that has always lived in me <br><br>As the days in my memories <br>outnumber the days remaining <br>I see my house getting old and falling <br>Not much time left for me <br>Too much love left in me <br>I regret because I know it's too late <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="The House I Loved" label="The House I Loved"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/지미_스트레인/Tell_Me_A_Lie/</id><title>지미 스트레인 - Tell Me A Lie - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:04:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:04:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%B8_%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B8/Tell_Me_A_Lie/" title="지미 스트레인 - Tell Me A Lie - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[tell me a lie <br>i'll forgive whatever it is <br>if there's any <br>tell me a lie <br>so i can go to sleep <br>so i can live in the dreams <br>tell me a lie <br>that's what i need to hear <br>that's what i want to hear <br>i don't need to hear the truth <br>i don't wanna know what's right <br>just tell me a lie <br>just give me what i need <br>come tell me a lie <br><br>tell me it's gonna be okay <br>tell me you'll always be by my side <br>tell me you love me as much i do <br>tell me your love will last forever <br>promise me forever <br>when it's clear than ever <br>that it's hard to get together <br>when we both know that it's over <br>then, <br><br>tell me a lie <br>just tell me a lie <br>i'll love you always <br>i'll love you more than now <br>this is not a lie <br>cuz i know there's nothing i can do <br>but to love you forever <br>so it's okay for you to lie <br>so tell me a lie <br>this is the time, don't miss it, <br>now tell me a lie, it's okay <br>tell me a lie <br>]]></content><category term="지미 스트레인" label="지미 스트레인"/><category term="Tell Me A Lie" label="Tell Me A Lie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DelMo_델모/WENS_Feat_Don_Malik/</id><title>Del.Mo (델모) - W.E.N.S (Feat. Don Malik) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:05:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:05:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/DelMo_%EB%8D%B8%EB%AA%A8/WENS_Feat_Don_Malik/" title="Del.Mo (델모) - W.E.N.S (Feat. Don Malik) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흔들리는 생각 <br>때문에 휘청이는 젠가 <br>요즘 몸소 느끼는 체감 <br>확실히 난 변했어 죄다 <br>건조한 공기에 닿은 <br>얼굴은 되게 하얘 <br>오늘밤은 더욱 차갑네 <br>광대한 열정에 찬 꿈으로 가득해 <br>닥치고 넌 좀 듣기나 해 <br>오 거친 못 바닥을 걷고 있어 <br>나는 모험가 처럼 이곳에 <br>군림하지 다 군림하지 다 <br>다 똑같이 <br>노래하지 <br>다 똑같이 <br>노래하지 <br>몇 알이면 뇌랑 같이 녹아 이번 <br>적막이 더 깊어질 때 <br>섬같이 멀어지지 <br>너와 이 곳 과 내 거리감 <br>떠오르고 말아 몇마디도 채 <br>남기지 못했었던 우리의 거리가 <br>무너지지 말자고 금간 생각들에게 <br>말하면 퍽이나 날 위해 버텨 주겠네 <br>노래해 주겠니 <br>들끓는 젊음이 던져 주는 <br>슬픔에 대해 <br>우릴 위한 가사를 쓸 때엔 <br>왠지 모르게 속상해져서 싫다가도 <br>다 그렇게 살 듯 해서 입장 바꿔 <br>불안을 토해내면 내가 겪은 긴장감 또 <br>두려움은 답답함으로 한번 치환 하고 <br>취한다고 마신 술은 <br>마취제처럼 얼얼해 <br>풀리면 더 아프겠다 <br>그래도 잔을 꺾어 내 <br>역할은 얼른 걔들이 말하는 어른 돼서 <br>무뎌지는 거야 <br>마취주사도 안 먹힐 때까지 <br>다 똑같이 <br>노래하지 <br>다 똑같이 <br>노래하지 <br>다 똑같이 <br>노래하지 <br>다 똑같이 <br>노래하지 <br>다 똑같이 <br>노래하지 <br>다 똑같이 <br>]]></content><category term="Del.Mo (델모)" label="Del.Mo (델모)"/><category term="W.E.N.S (Feat. Don Malik)" label="W.E.N.S (Feat. Don Malik)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shawn_Mendes/Treat_You_Better/</id><title>Shawn Mendes - Treat You Better - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:08:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:08:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shawn_Mendes/Treat_You_Better/" title="Shawn Mendes - Treat You Better - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I won't lie to you <br>I know he's just not right for you <br>And you can tell me if I'm off <br>But I see it on your face <br>When you say that he's the one that you want <br>And you're spending all your time <br>In this wrong situation <br>And anytime you want it to stop <br><br>I know I can treat you better than he can <br>And any girl like you deserves a gentleman <br>Tell me why are we wasting time <br>On all your wasted crying <br>When you should be with me instead <br>I know I can treat you better <br>Better than he can <br><br>I'll stop time for you <br>The second you say you'd like me to <br>I just wanna give you the loving that you're missing <br>Baby, just to wake up with you <br>Would be everything I need and this could be so different <br>Tell me what you want to do <br><br>'Cause I know I can treat you better than he can <br>And any girl like you deserves a gentleman <br>Tell me why are we wasting time <br>On all your wasted crying <br>When you should be with me instead <br>I know I can treat you better <br>Better than he can <br><br>Better than he can <br><br>Give me a sign <br>Take my hand, we'll be fine <br>Promise I won't let you down <br>Just know that you don't <br>Have to do this alone <br>Promise I'll never let you down <br><br>'Cause I know I can treat you better than he can <br>And any girl like you deserves a gentleman <br>Tell me why are we wasting time <br>On all your wasted crying <br>When you should be with me instead <br>I know I can treat you better <br>Better than he can <br><br>Better than he can <br><br>Better than he can]]></content><category term="Shawn Mendes" label="Shawn Mendes"/><category term="Treat You Better" label="Treat You Better"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shawn_Mendes/Theres_Nothing_Holdin_Me_Back/</id><title>Shawn Mendes - There`s Nothing Holdin` Me Back - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:08:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:08:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shawn_Mendes/Theres_Nothing_Holdin_Me_Back/" title="Shawn Mendes - There`s Nothing Holdin` Me Back - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wanna follow there where she goes <br>I think about her and she knows it <br>I wanna let her take control <br>'Cause everytime that <br>she gets close yeah <br>She pulls me in enough <br>to keep me guessing <br>And maybe I should stop <br>and start confessing <br>Confessing yeah <br>Oh I've been shaking <br>I love it when you go crazy <br>You take all my inhibitions <br>Baby there's nothing <br>holding me back <br>You take me places that <br>tear up my reputation <br>Manipulate my decisions <br>Baby there's nothing <br>holding me back <br>There's nothing holding me back <br>There's nothing holding me back <br>She says that she is never afraid <br>Just picture everybody naked <br>She really doesn't like to wait <br>Not really into hesitation <br>Pulls me in enough <br>to keep me guessing <br>And maybe I should stop <br>and start confessing <br>Confessing <br>Oh I've been shaking <br>I love it when you go crazy <br>You take all my inhibitions <br>Baby there's nothing <br>holding me back <br>You take me places that <br>tear up my reputation <br>Manipulate my decisions <br>Baby there's nothing <br>holding me back <br>There's nothing holding me back <br>'Cause if we lost our minds and <br>we took it way too far <br>I know we'd be alright <br>I know we'd be alright <br>If you are by my side <br>and we stumbled in the dark <br>I know we'd be alright <br>I know we'd be alright <br>'Cause if we lost our minds and <br>we took it way too far <br>I know we'd be alright <br>I know we'd be alright <br>If you are by my side <br>and we stumbled in the dark <br>I know we'd be alright <br>I know we'd be alright <br>Oh I've been shaking <br>I love it when you go crazy <br>You take all my inhibitions <br>Baby there's nothing <br>holding me back <br>You take me places that <br>tear up my reputation <br>Manipulate my decisions <br>Baby there's nothing <br>holding me back <br>There's nothing holding me back <br>I feel so free <br>when you're with me baby <br>Baby there's nothing <br>holding me back]]></content><category term="Shawn Mendes" label="Shawn Mendes"/><category term="There`s Nothing Holdin` Me Back" label="There`s Nothing Holdin` Me Back"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/버션/K3_삼촌은_월드스타_Feat_다현_민규/</id><title>버션 - K3 (삼촌은 월드스타) (Feat. 다현, 민규) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:08:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:08:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%84%EC%85%98/K3_%EC%82%BC%EC%B4%8C%EC%9D%80_%EC%9B%94%EB%93%9C%EC%8A%A4%ED%83%80_Feat_%EB%8B%A4%ED%98%84_%EB%AF%BC%EA%B7%9C/" title="버션 - K3 (삼촌은 월드스타) (Feat. 다현, 민규) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이곳은 너무 좁았지 <br>내가 서있기에 턱 <br>없이 부족했던 무대들과 <br>네 팬들과 shit 비주얼 <br>이미 난 순회 공연을 마치고 왔어 <br>108개의 번뇌를 마치고 각성 uh <br>사람들이 날 몰라봐도 나 <br>리듬위로 올라타 <br>어차피 난 인정받고 <br>돈은 충분히 벌었지 <br>이곳은 안돼 <br>그래서 난 떠났어 <br>east west north south <br>입맛대로 골라서 <br>비주얼 hiphop <br>절대 날 <br>untouchable <br>건들면 난 미쳐 <br>찾고있니 jesus <br>다시 돌아온 이곳은 그대로지 <br>다수의 랩퍼들은 아직도 삐애로지 <br>fillin' ma philasophy <br>나를 그리워했던 <br>아이들 항상 물어 언제 오냐고 <br>삼촌 언제와 <br>조금만 기다려 곧 갈게 그리고 <br>몇일 뒤 한국행 비행기를 탔네 <br>월드스타 컴백무대 stage on <br>east west north south <br>어디까지갈지도 <br>몰랐지만 오늘도 비행기에서 잤네 <br>어떤 무대에서도 난 잘해 <br>월드스타 컴백무대 stage on <br>east west north south <br>어디까지갈지도 <br>몰랐지만 오늘도 비행기에서 잤네 <br>어떤 무대에서도 난 잘해 <br>한류스타에 한 이빠진 월드 스타 <br>해시태그 따위 없어도 <br>하트가 몇천개 난 충분해 <br>가질대로 가졌고 <br>잃을것도 없네 <br>오늘도 헤네시 xo 건배 <br>여기저기 안팔아도 난 잘 벌어 <br>삼촌만 믿어 <br>내가 바로 너의 리더 <br>나는 계속해서 가고 <br>두배속해서 가지 <br>이미 리듬을 타고있어 <br>뱃속에서까지 <br>신은 없지만 팁은 있어 <br>돈이있고 기분있어 <br>나는 충분히 벌었고 <br>I show you the money <br>승이 전부라면 난 <br>승휘를 가졌지 <br>모두욕심내고 있는 <br>선아는 못갖지 <br>난 혼줄 내주러왔어 <br>비주얼 hiphop <br>yellow asian 나의 시작은 지하 <br>but now I'm on the top <br>그리고 fill so fine <br>이제 무서울거 없고 <br>난 두려울게 없네 uh <br>월드스타 컴백무대 stage on <br>east west north south <br>어디까지갈지도 <br>몰랐지만 오늘도 비행기에서 잤네 <br>어떤 무대에서도 난 잘해 <br>월드스타 컴백무대 stage on <br>east west north south <br>어디까지갈지도 <br>몰랐지만 오늘도 비행기에서 잤네 <br>어떤 무대에서도 난 잘해 <br>월드스타 컴백무대 stage on <br>east west north south <br>어디까지갈지도 <br>몰랐지만 오늘도 비행기에서 잤네 <br>어떤 무대에서도 난 잘해 <br>월드스타 컴백무대 stage on <br>east west north south <br>어디까지갈지도 <br>몰랐지만 오늘도 비행기에서 잤네 <br>어떤 무대에서도 난 잘해 <br>]]></content><category term="버션" label="버션"/><category term="K3 (삼촌은 월드스타) (Feat. 다현, 민규)" label="K3 (삼촌은 월드스타) (Feat. 다현, 민규)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/최지민/찾을게/</id><title>최지민 - 찾을게 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:08:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:08:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B5%9C%EC%A7%80%EB%AF%BC/%EC%B0%BE%EC%9D%84%EA%B2%8C/" title="최지민 - 찾을게 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그댄 행복이 지나쳐서 <br>꿈일지도 모른다며 <br>불안해 하면서도 <br>눈을 떼질 못했죠 <br>가끔씩 세상에서 <br>깊이 숨어 버린대도 <br>날 찾을 당신을 알기에 <br>두렵지 않았죠 <br>이 밤은 너무나 짧고 <br>오가는 길은 그대밖에 모르니 <br>내 그림자에 그대 걸음 얹어서 <br>조금만 더 내 곁에 있어줘요 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>울음이 터져 이 말밖에는 못해 <br>갈 거면 날 데려가 <br>왜 내 손을 떼어내는 거야 <br>그대여 내 그대여 <br>날 혼자 두지 말아줘요 <br>눈을 다시 떴을 때 <br>내 곁에 있어요 <br>이 밤은 너무나 짧고 <br>오가는 길은 그대밖에 모르니 <br>내 그림자에 그대 걸음 얹어서 <br>조금만 더 내 곁에 있어줘요 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>울음이 터져 이 말밖에는 못해 <br>갈 거면 날 데려가 <br>왜 내 손을 떼어내는 거야 <br>그대여 내 그대여 <br>날 혼자 두지 말아줘요 <br>눈을 다시 떴을 때 <br>내 곁에 있어요 <br>도착한 그곳에서 <br>설령 길을 잃어도 <br>괜찮아 그땐 내가 <br>그대를 찾을게 <br>뒤를 돌아 손이 닿았네 <br>날 잊어 잊어야 해 <br>그렇게 말을 했지만 <br>사실은 잊혀지길 <br>원치 않았다 <br>겨우내 닿은 손에 <br>온기는 이제 없지만 <br>그조차 함께라서 <br>그저 좋은데 <br>사랑해 널 사랑해 <br>이 말을 하러 여기에 왔어 <br>하늘 아래 더 이상 <br>외롭지 않게 해줄게 <br>그대여 괜찮아요 <br>모든 걸 버린 게 아니예요 <br>내 전부를 얻으러 <br>여기 온 걸요 <br>내 세상을 찾으러 여기 왔어요 <br>]]></content><category term="최지민" label="최지민"/><category term="찾을게" label="찾을게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BIG_LAM_빅슬램/FUCK/</id><title>BIG $LAM (빅슬램) - F.U.C.K - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:08:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:08:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BIG_LAM_%EB%B9%85%EC%8A%AC%EB%9E%A8/FUCK/" title="BIG $LAM (빅슬램) - F.U.C.K - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ay day 난 green bottle <br>잡고서 chill <br>Asian 같지 않은 내 groove and feel <br>내 Ambition 니가 손대기엔 뜨겁지 <br>얼마를 주던가 멋 없으면 <br>절대 안하니 <br>Fuck yo 악수 <br>Fuck yo 작품 <br>Fuck yo 관점 <br>Fuck yo Track Fuck yo Rap <br>Yeah I want some money 많은 돈 <br>근데 내 행보 먼저 <br>다지길 원해 나 원체 <br>니들 하는 짓이 뭐가 됐든 <br>관심도 전혀없어 <br>엮일라 하지말고 <br>니꺼나 더 빨어 Fuck Boi <br>Yeah I'm right here ay <br>지켜 my way ay I stay gridin' ay <br>마이크앞 wildin' 이름 바꿨더니 또 <br>병신들이 날 평가해 <br>보여줄게 내가 뭘 쏟아부을지 so <br>Fuck yo 악수 <br>Fuck yo 작품 <br>Fuck yo 관점 <br>Fuck yo Track Fuck yo Rap <br>짝퉁래퍼들의 Doomsday <br>내 혀로 너를 썰래 <br>조용히 니 뒤에 붙어 <br>숨통 끊고서 movin' <br>내 트랙은 Scary movie <br>시체가 된 너네 <br>드래그해 쓰레기차에 유기 <br>and I'm cruzin <br>콧구멍엔 PND Swallow the XNY <br>니넨 진짜로 접해본적 없지 <br>fuckin Trap shit <br>Fuckin Trap shit <br>I had a drink shit <br>I had a smoke shit yeahhhhhhh <br>Dollar $ign 적고 마저 적어 L A M <br>지 인생 못사는 병신들 <br>개소린 계속 돼 <br>피를 끼얹어 줄께 <br>니 머릿속 그린 그림 yeah <br>실눈 뜨고 봐도 너넨 <br>전부 겁쟁이 yeahh <br>Dollar $ign 적고 마저 적어 L A M <br>지 인생 못사는 병신들 <br>개소린 계속 돼 <br>피를 끼얹어 줄께 <br>니 머릿속 그린 그림 yeah <br>실눈 뜨고 봐도 너넨 <br>전부 겁쟁이 yeahh <br>Fuck yo 악수 <br>Fuck yo 작품 <br>Fuck yo 관점 <br>Fuck yo Track Fuck yo Rap <br>]]></content><category term="BIG $LAM (빅슬램)" label="BIG $LAM (빅슬램)"/><category term="F.U.C.K" label="F.U.C.K"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/I_Praise_You_Jesus_Remaster/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - I Praise You Jesus (Remaster) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/I_Praise_You_Jesus_Remaster/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - I Praise You Jesus (Remaster) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아낌없이 내어주신 그의 사랑 <br>주 사랑인걸 주 뿐이란 걸 <br>나를 위해 희생하신 그의 사랑 <br>주 사랑인걸 주 뿐이란걸 <br>아낌없이 내어주신 그의 사랑 <br>주 사랑인걸 주 뿐이란 걸 <br>나를 위해 희생하신 그의 사랑 <br>주 사랑인걸 주 뿐이란걸 <br>홀로 나만을 바라보다 <br>외로움과 긴 한숨만 남아 <br>어디로 갈지 헤매이다 <br>내 앞에 서있는 그 분 보네 <br>지쳐있던 나를 괴로웠던 나를 <br>혼자였던 나를 <br>나를 일으키시네 <br>지쳐있던 나를 쓰러졌던 나를 <br>일으키시네 <br>아낌없이 내어주신 그의 사랑 <br>주 사랑인걸 주 뿐이란 걸 <br>나를 위해 희생하신 그의 사랑 <br>주 사랑인걸 주 뿐이란걸 <br>세상의 많은 돈과 명예보다 <br>비교할 수 없는 기쁨을 주시는 <br>주님의 그 큰 사랑만은 <br>무엇과도 비교할수 없네 <br>지쳐있던 나를 괴로웠던 나를 <br>혼자였던 나를 <br>나를 일으키시네 <br>지쳐있던 나를 쓰러졌던 나를 <br>일으키시네 <br>아낌없이 내어주신 그의 사랑 <br>주 사랑인걸 주 뿐이란 걸 <br>나를 위해 희생하신 그의 사랑 <br>주 사랑인걸 주 뿐이란걸 <br>내 맘에 눈물은 마르고 <br>내 안의 믿음이 나를 세우고 <br>주님의 그 사랑이 나의 맘에 <br>위로와 자유함 주셨네 <br>아낌없이 내어주신 그의 사랑 <br>주 사랑인걸 주 뿐이란 걸 <br>나를 위해 희생하신 그의 사랑 <br>주 사랑인걸 주 뿐이란걸 <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise you jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise the name of Jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise you jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise the name of Jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise you jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise the name of Jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise you jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise the name of Jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise you jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise the name of Jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise you jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>we just praise the name of Jesus <br>I praise you jesus <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="I Praise You Jesus (Remaster)" label="I Praise You Jesus (Remaster)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/하루를/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 하루를 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%ED%95%98%EB%A3%A8%EB%A5%BC/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 하루를 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[얼마나 참아야 할까 <br>얼마나 더 견뎌야 할까 <br>하루를 또 하루를 견디며 <br>보낸 시간이 더 힘든데 <br>눈가에 맺힌 눈물도 <br>어깨위에 올려진 멍에도 <br>이제는 모두 벗어버리고 <br>이 길 끝에서 웃으며 걸을게 <br>너의 작은 꿈을 간직할게 <br>우리 잡은 두 손 꼭 놓지 않을게 <br>절망의 끝에서 하늘을 봐 <br>언제나 내가 함께 할테니 <br>눈가에 맺힌 눈물도 <br>어깨위에 올려진 멍에도 <br>이제는 모두 벗어버리고 <br>이 길 끝에서 웃으며 걸을게 <br>너의 작은 꿈을 간직할게 <br>우리 잡은 두 손 꼭 놓지 않을게 <br>절망의 끝에서 하늘을 봐 <br>언제나 내가 함께 할테니 <br>이 힘든 시간이 모두 지나가면 <br>희망의 기억들을 만들거야 <br>너의 작은 꿈을 간직할게 <br>너의 작은 꿈을 간직할게 <br>우리 잡은 두 손 꼭 놓지 않을게 <br>절망의 끝에서 하늘을 봐 <br>언제나 내가 함께 할테니 <br>너의 작은 꿈을 간직할게 <br>우리 잡은 두 손 꼭 놓지 않을게 <br>절망의 끝에서 하늘을 봐 <br>언제나 내가 함께 할테니 <br>이곳에서 넌 혼자가 아냐 <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="하루를" label="하루를"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/주_은혜가_Remaster/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 주 은혜가 (Remaster) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%A3%BC_%EC%9D%80%ED%98%9C%EA%B0%80_Remaster/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 주 은혜가 (Remaster) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주 은혜가 내 안에 임하네 <br>두 손들고 잠잠히 맞이해 <br>거룩한 빛 내 영을 온전히 비추사 <br>어두움 변해 밝음이 가득해 <br>주의 은혜가 흐르네 영원히 <br>그의 눈길이 나의 삶을 인도하며 <br>그의 품만이 나의 영혼 살게 하네 <br>영원한 생명의 예수 <br>그 분 만이 나의 이유 <br>주의 은혜가 흐르네 영원히 <br>주의 은혜가 내 안에 영원히 <br>하늘가는 밝은 길이 내 앞에 있으니 <br>슬픈 일을 많이 보고 늘 고생하여도 <br>하늘영광 밝음이 어둔 그늘 헤치니 <br>예수 공로 의지 하여 항상 빛을 보도다 <br>항상 빛을 보도다 <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="주 은혜가 (Remaster)" label="주 은혜가 (Remaster)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/New_Day/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - New Day - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/New_Day/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - New Day - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바로 지금이야 Bye 예전의 나 <br>새로워진 삶에 Song for you <br>어두웠던 지난 일 기억 Don't worry <br>새로워진 삶에 Starting new <br>걱정은 버려 Stop 매일 새로운 날 <br>주께 감사해 <br>아픔은 잊어 Stop 새롭게 시작해 <br>Sing praise <br>찬양해 우리 주님께 <br>주께 감사해 새 날 주신 <br>경배해 우리 주님께 새 날 주신 주께 <br>새 날을 주신 주를 찬양 <br>기쁨의 찬양 주께 영광 <br>소리를 높여 주를 찬양 <br>기쁨의 찬양 주님께 영광 <br>걱정은 버려 Stop 매일 새로운 날 <br>주께 감사해 <br>아픔은 잊어 Stop 새롭게 시작해 <br>Sing praise <br>찬양해 우리 주님께 <br>주께 감사해 새 날 주신 <br>경배해 우리 주님께 새 날 주신 주께 <br>새 날을 주신 주를 찬양 <br>기쁨의 찬양 주께 영광 <br>소리를 높여 주를 찬양 <br>기쁨의 찬양 주님께 영광 <br>새 날을 주신 주를 찬양 <br>기쁨의 찬양 주께 영광 <br>소리를 높여 주를 찬양 <br>기쁨의 찬양 주님께 영광 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 할렐루야 높이세 <br>모든 영광 모든 존귀 <br>모든 찬송 주님께 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 할렐루야 높이세 <br>모든 영광 모든 존귀 <br>모든 찬송 주님께 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 할렐루야 높이세 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 할렐루야 주님께 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 할렐루야 높이세 <br>할렐루야 할렐루야 할렐루야 주님께 <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="New Day" label="New Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/주께_노래해_Sing_Remaster/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 주께 노래해 (Sing) (Remaster) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%A3%BC%EA%BB%98_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98%ED%95%B4_Sing_Remaster/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 주께 노래해 (Sing) (Remaster) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모든 민족 열방 백성 <br>주께 나와 경배 드리네 <br>이제 주를 높이리라 <br>나 가진 것 모두 버리고 <br>존귀한 주님을 <br>영원히 높이세 <br>Sing 주께 노래해 <br>마음을 열고 기쁜 소리로 <br>주의 성소에서 <br>Sing 주께 노래해 <br>넘치는 사랑 울려 퍼지게 <br>주의 성소에서 Sing <br>모든 민족 열방 백성 <br>주께 나와 경배 드리네 <br>이제 주를 높이리라 <br>나 가진 것 모두 버리고 <br>존귀한 주님을 <br>영원히 높이세 <br>Sing 주께 노래해 <br>마음을 열고 기쁜 소리로 <br>주의 성소에서 <br>Sing 주께 노래해 <br>넘치는 사랑 울려 퍼지게 <br>주의 성소에서 Sing <br>우리 입을 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>마음 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>거룩한 손 높이 들리 <br>주의 성소에서 <br>우리 입을 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>마음 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>거룩한 손 높이 들리 <br>Sing Sing Sing <br>우리 입을 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>마음 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>거룩한 손 높이 들리 <br>주의 성소에서 <br>우리 입을 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>마음 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>거룩한 손 높이 들리 <br>Sing Sing Sing <br>우리 입을 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>마음 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>거룩한 손 높이 들리 <br>주의 성소에서 <br>우리 입을 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>마음 열어 찬양 드리세 <br>거룩한 손 높이 들리 <br>Sing Sing Sing <br>Sing 주께 노래해 <br>마음을 열고 기쁜 소리로 <br>주의 성소에서 <br>Sing 주께 노래해 <br>넘치는 사랑 울려 퍼지게 <br>주의 성소에서 Sing <br>주께 노래해 <br>마음을 열고 기쁜 소리로 <br>주의 성소에서 <br>Sing 주께 노래해 <br>넘치는 사랑 울려 퍼지게 <br>주의 성소에서 Sing <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="주께 노래해 (Sing) (Remaster)" label="주께 노래해 (Sing) (Remaster)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/잠언_8：17_Proverbs_8：17/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 잠언 8：17 (Proverbs 8：17) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%9E%A0%EC%96%B8_8%EF%BC%9A17_Proverbs_8%EF%BC%9A17/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 잠언 8：17 (Proverbs 8：17) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 사랑하는 자여 <br>나의 사랑을 입고 <br>나를 간절히 찾는 자여 <br>나를 만날 것이라 <br>나를 <br>나의 사랑하는 자여 <br>내가 영원히 너와 <br>영원히 찾는 자 함께 하리라 <br>약속하리라 아멘 아멘 <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="잠언 8：17 (Proverbs 8：17)" label="잠언 8：17 (Proverbs 8：17)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/주의_나라가_Remaster/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 주의 나라가 (Remaster) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%98_%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC%EA%B0%80_Remaster/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 주의 나라가 (Remaster) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지치고 쓰러진 내게 <br>빛으로 찾아 오셔서 <br>주의 능력의 팔로 날 안아주시며 <br>큰 위로와 평안 주시네 <br>어두움 속에 있던 나 <br>그 손을 내게 펴시며 <br>그 영원한 사랑 그 크신 은혜 <br>주의 말씀 따라서 나아가네 <br>주의 나라가 임하시며 <br>주의 영광이 온 땅 가득해 <br>내 삶속에 힘이 되시는 <br>내 상한 마음을 <br>주 위로 하시네 <br>어두움 속에 있던 나 <br>그 손을 내게 펴시며 <br>그 영원한 사랑 그 크신 은혜 <br>주의 말씀 따라서 나가리 <br>주의 나라가 임하시며 <br>주의 영광이 온 땅 가득해 <br>내 삶속에 힘이 되시는 <br>내 상한 마음을 <br>위로 하시네 <br>주의 나라가 임하시며 <br>주의 영광이 온 땅 가득해 <br>내 삶속에 힘이 되시는 <br>내 상한 마음을 <br>주 위로 하시네 <br>내 상한 마음을 <br>주 위로 하시네 <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="주의 나라가 (Remaster)" label="주의 나라가 (Remaster)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/기도/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 기도 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EA%B8%B0%EB%8F%84/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 기도 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오 내 주여 나의 맘 받으소서 <br>사랑의 주 나의 영 드립니다 <br>무릎 꿇고 주님 앞에 기도하니 <br>주여 나와 동행하여 주옵소서 <br>온전히 맡깁니다 오 내 주여 <br>십자가 소망을 주신 주여 <br>그 사랑 품에 간직하게 <br>하옵소서 오직 주만 따르오니 <br>인도하여 주소서 내 주님 <br>오 내 주여 내 기도 들으소서 <br>주의 얼굴 숨기지 마옵소서 <br>신실하신 주님 앞에 기도하니 <br>주여 내게 응답하여 주옵소서 <br>온전히 맡깁니다 오 내 주여 <br>십자가 소망을 주신 주여 <br>그 사랑 품에 간직하게 <br>하옵소서 오직 주만 따르오니 <br>인도하여 주소서 내 주님 <br>십자가 소망을 주신 주여 <br>그 사랑 품에 간직하게 <br>하옵소서 오직 주만 따르오니 <br>인도하여 주소서 내 주님 <br>인도하여 주소서 주님 <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="기도" label="기도"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/주만_따르리/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 주만 따르리 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/%EC%A3%BC%EB%A7%8C_%EB%94%B0%EB%A5%B4%EB%A6%AC/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - 주만 따르리 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[소리 높여 주를 찬양해 <br>큰 소리로 주께 외치세 <br>모든 것의 주관자 그는 예수 <br>새 노래로 주를 찬양해 <br>우리 모두 주께 외치세 <br>승리로 이끄시는 그는 예수 <br>소리 높여 주를 찬양해 <br>큰 소리로 주께 외치세 <br>모든 것의 주관자 그는 예수 <br>새 노래로 주를 찬양해 <br>우리 모두 주께 외치세 <br>영원한 생명을 주신 <br>예수 그리스도 <br>내게 자유함 주셨고 <br>기뻐 찬양케 하셨네 <br>보이지 않아도 곁에 계신 주 <br>내 손 잡고서 <br>인도해 주시네 <br>기뻐 찬양하리라 즐거이 주께 <br>소리 높여 주를 찬양해 <br>큰 소리로 주께 외치세 <br>모든 것의 주관자 그는 예수 <br>새 노래로 주를 찬양해 <br>우리 모두 주께 외치세 <br>승리로 이끄시는 그는 예수 <br>내게 자유함 주셨고 <br>기뻐 찬양케 하셨네 <br>보이지 않아도 곁에 계신 주 <br>내 손 잡고서 <br>인도해 주시네 <br>기뻐 찬양하리라 즐거이 주께 <br>보이지 않아도 곁에 계신 주 <br>내 손 잡고서 <br>인도해 주시네 <br>기뻐 찬양하리라 즐거이 주께 <br>주만 따르리 주 경배하리 <br>내 주만 영원히 사랑하네 <br>주만 따르리 주 경배하리 <br>내 주만 영원히 찬양하네 <br>주만 따르리 주 경배하리 <br>내 주만 영원히 찬양하네 <br>주만 따르리 주 경배하리 <br>내 주만 영원히 찬양하네 <br>주만 따르리 주 경배하리 <br>내 주만 영원히 찬양하네 <br>주만 따르리 주 경배하리 <br>내 주만 찬양 <br>자유함 주셨고 <br>기뻐 찬양케 하셨네 <br>보이지 않아도 곁에 계신 주 <br>내 손 잡고서 <br>인도해 주시네 <br>기뻐 찬양하리라 즐거이 주께 <br>보이지 않아도 곁에 계신 주 <br>내 손 잡고서 <br>인도해 주시네 <br>기뻐 찬양하리라 즐거이 주께 <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="주만 따르리" label="주만 따르리"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/Persuaded_난_확신해/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - Persuaded (난 확신해) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/Persuaded_%EB%82%9C_%ED%99%95%EC%8B%A0%ED%95%B4/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - Persuaded (난 확신해) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 통해 하신 일들 <br>난 확신해 결코 돌아서지 않아 <br>주님을 따라 걸어가리 <br>날 새롭게 하신 그 분을 따르리 <br>I'm persuaded 온 마음 다해 <br>나의 모든 것 주께 드리리 <br>그 분을 따르리 다짐 하였네 <br>온 힘 다해 나 나아가리 <br>매일 주님과 함께 걷기 원하네 <br>주께서 날 위해 행하신 일들 <br>날 자유케 하니 기쁨 얻었네 <br>I'm persuaded 온 마음 다해 <br>나의 모든 것 주께 드리리 <br>그 분을 따르리 다짐 하였네 <br>나 믿음으로 걸어가리라 <br>나 방황할 때 주 항상 함께 하네 <br>내 기도 들으시는 주님께 <br>두 손 높이 들고 찬양 할렐루야 <br>I'm persuaded 온 마음 다해 <br>나의 모든 것 주께 드리리 <br>그 분을 따르리 다짐 하였네 <br>No turning back no oh no <br>온 맘을 다하여 갑니다 <br>그 분을 향해 <br>주님만을 향해 갑니다 <br>no oh no <br>온 맘을 다하여 갑니다 <br>그 분을 향해 <br>주님만을 향해 갑니다 <br>No oh no 헛된 시간을 <br>보내지 않으리 <br>새로워진 나 <br>주님만을 향해 갑니다 <br>I'm determined to go <br>I'm persuaded to go <br>온 맘을 다하여 나 갑니다 <br>한 걸음씩 yeah <br>주님만을 향해 갑니다 <br>I'm persuaded 온 마음 다해 <br>나의 모든 것 주께 드리리 <br>그 분을 따르리 다짐 하였네 <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="Persuaded (난 확신해)" label="Persuaded (난 확신해)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_클레이_브라운/We_Win_승리했네/</id><title>Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - We Win (승리했네) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Clay_Brown_%ED%81%B4%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B8%8C%EB%9D%BC%EC%9A%B4/We_Win_%EC%8A%B9%EB%A6%AC%ED%96%88%EB%84%A4/" title="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운) - We Win (승리했네) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주님의 말씀으로 <br>우리는 승리했네 <br>어린 양의 피와 주님 주신 <br>약속으로 승리했네 <br>승리를 주신 예수 <br>다 함께 소리 외치세 <br>두 손을 높이 들고서 외치세 <br>승리를 주신 주께 <br>We win 승리 주신 주께 <br>찬양 그 이름 높이세 <br>We win 주로 인해 <br>모든 것 가능해 We win <br>주님의 말씀으로 <br>우리는 승리했네 <br>어린 양의 피와 주님 주신 <br>약속으로 승리했네 <br>승리를 주신 예수 <br>다 함께 소리 외치세 <br>두 손을 높이 들고서 외치세 <br>승리를 주신 주께 <br>We win 승리 주신 주께 <br>찬양 그 이름 높이세 <br>We win 주로 인해 <br>모든 것 가능해 We win <br>We win 승리 주신 주께 <br>찬양 그 이름 높이세 <br>We win 주로 인해 <br>모든 것 가능해 We win <br>Oh 승리를 얻었네 우린 승리했네 <br>Oh 승리를 얻었네 주님으로 인해 <br>Oh 승리를 얻었네 우린 승리했네 <br>Oh 승리를 얻었네 주님으로 인해 <br>Oh 승리를 얻었네 우린 승리했네 <br>Oh 승리를 얻었네 주님으로 인해 <br>Oh 승리를 얻었네 우린 승리했네 <br>Oh 승리를 얻었네 주님으로 <br>We win 승리 주신 주께 <br>찬양 그 이름 높이세 <br>We win 주로 인해 <br>모든 것 가능해 We win <br>]]></content><category term="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)" label="Clay Brown (클레이 브라운)"/><category term="We Win (승리했네)" label="We Win (승리했네)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PS/내게_와줘/</id><title>PS - 내게 와줘 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/PS/%EB%82%B4%EA%B2%8C_%EC%99%80%EC%A4%98/" title="PS - 내게 와줘 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알고 있니 <br>이별 앞에 선 <br>할 수 있는 게 없어 <br>말해주지 못 해서 <br>도와주지 못 해서 <br>미안하다고 말하고 싶었지만 <br>네게 보낸 메시지 <br>네가 못 봤으면 해 <br>나도 모르게 보낸 <br>변덕이야 <br>몰랐었어 <br>다시 보내고 <br>있는 문자 지워 <br>말해주지 못 해서 <br>도와주지 못 해서 <br>미안하다고 말하고 싶어서 <br>네게 보낸 메시지 <br>네가 못 봤으면 해 <br>그저 꿈속에서 너를 만나고 <br>잠시 남아 반가워할게 <br>다신 못 보겠지 <br>사랑하다 이젠 못해 <br>말해주지 못 해서 <br>도와주지 못 해서 <br>미안하다고 말하고 싶었지만 <br>네게 보낸 메시지 <br>네가 못 봤으면 해 <br>나도 모르게 보낸 변덕이야 <br>]]></content><category term="PS" label="PS"/><category term="내게 와줘" label="내게 와줘"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/David_Guetta/Another_Life_Radio_Mix_Feat_Ester_Dean/</id><title>David Guetta - Another Life (Radio Mix) (Feat. Ester Dean) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/David_Guetta/Another_Life_Radio_Mix_Feat_Ester_Dean/" title="David Guetta - Another Life (Radio Mix) (Feat. Ester Dean) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm waking up, thingking how we used to be <br>I still hang on to our tied up dreams <br>I wish we could turn back the hands of time <br>Replace the poison that you left onto my mind <br><br>Maybe we'll meet again in another life <br>Maybe we're better in another paradise <br>Maybe we will meet again <br>Maybe we will fall again <br><br>In another life <br>In another life <br><br>I can't imagine what this life would be <br>We holdin' on to fading memories <br>I love you, you love me, but this love set you free <br>But if you choose to leave, well I hope we'll meet <br><br>Maybe we'll meet again in another life <br>Maybe we're better in another paradise <br>Maybe we will meet again <br>Maybe we will fall again <br><br>In another life <br><br>Maybe we'll meet again in another life <br>Myabe we're better in another paradise <br>Maybe we will meet again <br>Maybe we wll fall again <br><br>In another life <br>In another life <br>In another life]]></content><category term="David Guetta" label="David Guetta"/><category term="Another Life (Radio Mix) (Feat. Ester Dean)" label="Another Life (Radio Mix) (Feat. Ester Dean)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/타예타/알고_있어/</id><title>타예타 - 알고 있어 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%80%EC%98%88%ED%83%80/%EC%95%8C%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4/" title="타예타 - 알고 있어 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흔들리는 눈빛에 <br>굳어버린 너의 얼굴 <br>그만 헤어지길 바라니 <br>묻는 널 볼 수가 없어 <br>나 먼저 일어설게 <br>다신 날 볼 수 없게 <br>떠날래 <br>안 된다고 소리친대도 <br>우린 여기까진가 봐 <br>잘 지내야 돼 <br>하루 종일 너만 <br>생각이 나잖아 <br>이미 모든 게 <br>다 끝난 사인데 <br>왜 이러는 거야 <br>제발 좀 그만해 <br>자꾸만 너 왜 이래 <br>이제 와 안 된다고 <br>소리친대도 <br>우린 여기까진가 봐 <br>잘 지내야 돼 <br>알고 있어 우리 <br>다시 안 되는 거 <br>애써 얘기하지 않아도 <br>괜찮아 눈물만 나와 <br>]]></content><category term="타예타" label="타예타"/><category term="알고 있어" label="알고 있어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Ridin/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Ridin` - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Ridin/" title="Shy Glizzy - Ridin` - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You know what the fuck it is <br>Glizzly gang nigga mo fucka <br>Yeah <br><br>All ma niggas like to trap with me <br>All ma niggas like to jog with me <br>And all of ma niggas do not ride with me <br>If shit go down then they go ride for me <br>You know why cause they ma niggas <br>All a dem got pistols shit go down and they gon kill you <br>I be with some niggas, all hitters <br>Glizzly gang the mob bitch it can't get no realer <br><br>The CEO nigga what you know <br>Bitch i'm from New York free Earl and free Low <br>We get a lot a dough ma with the bow <br>I'm ridin for ma brother won't say let me out though <br>Natural born killer, might put you on the shitter <br>I don't go nowhere without glizzly by my liver <br>These niggas just brothers they only talk on twitter <br>Seen them in person they more friendly that my sister <br>All my niggas fly, all my niggas high <br>You get outta line my niggas put you in the sky <br>All ma niggas trap they be baking pies <br>Don't know bout your niggas but my niggas down to ride <br>Uhhh <br><br>All ma niggas like to trap with me <br>All ma niggas like to jog with me <br>And all of ma niggas do not ride with me <br>If shit go down then they go ride for me <br>You know why cause they ma niggas <br>All a dem got pistols shit go down and they gon kill you <br>I be with some niggas, all hitters <br>Glizzly gang the mob bitch it can't get no realer <br><br>I can't forget Dae Dae my lil nigga was a savage <br>Any give day he woulda let you pussy niggas have it <br>Spent a brick for ma chain so everyday i'm wearing it <br>Cut the lights off big bling chain karats <br>I haven't dropped a medal since they dropped the fire bird <br>Bitch getting on my nerves i'm just tryna cop a bird <br>Pull up to the club and i'm with ma nigga swerve <br>We might take your girl but don't worry we gonn swerve <br>You never keep the yae where you mother fucking stay <br>That's ma nigga A bout dem trips down to the A <br>I got niggas in the Bay I ain't never seen they face <br>I just know they ship the weight then I make sure they get paid <br><br>All ma niggas like to trap with me <br>All ma niggas like to jog with me <br>And all of ma niggas do not ride with me <br>If shit go down then they go ride for me <br>You know why cause they ma niggas <br>All a dem got pistols shit go down and they gon kill you <br>I be with some niggas, all hitters <br>Glizzly gang the mob bitch it can't get no realer <br><br>We did this for the area <br>Yah mean <br>Boy Dram]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Ridin`" label="Ridin`"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Money_Problems_Feat_Yo_Gotti/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Money Problems (Feat. Yo Gotti) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Money_Problems_Feat_Yo_Gotti/" title="Shy Glizzy - Money Problems (Feat. Yo Gotti) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I feel fucking awful <br>I feel fucking awful, awww <br><br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>One of these niggas gonna make me rob 'em <br>I can't do what I want <br>And I feel fucking awful <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>One of these niggas gonna make me rob 'em <br><br>Damn, I'm going through it <br>Me and my right hand man just got into <br>Cause he up, and I ain't got no cash <br>And that boy done spent his last on a piece of ass <br>Rap game ain't doing shit <br>And everybody broke, So I can't hit a lick <br>OG fronting me a half a brick <br>I fucked my whole sack up at Saks 5th <br>I got a bad bitch, I swear bitch cost <br>I break her little heart <br>Every time I fall off <br>But, she don't never go no where <br>Cause she know daddy ball <br>And when daddy get right back <br>Then, she gonna have it all <br><br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>One of these niggas gonna make me rob 'em <br>I can't do what I want <br>And I feel fucking awful <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>One of these niggas gonna make me rob 'em <br><br>Moms just called, She said Son the rents due <br>Before she lose her house <br>I'll lose my fucking mental <br>Nigga, I don't care who you subgent too <br>Give me all the money man <br>I'm trynna be gentle <br>Lil bruh in high school <br>He like to get high too <br>Glad his feet grew <br>Now he can't start wearing my shoes <br>Mad as shit, I can't get around how I want too <br>Caught the train before I became this big rap dude <br>And for my birthday I wanna Rolex <br>I hope and pray I catch you slippin' with a Rolex <br>You can't tell I'm fucked up from my videos <br>That's because I always luck up for my videos <br><br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>One of these niggas gonna make me rob 'em <br>I can't do what I want <br>And I feel fucking awful <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>I got money problems <br>One of these niggas gonna make me rob 'em]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Money Problems (Feat. Yo Gotti)" label="Money Problems (Feat. Yo Gotti)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Im_A_Star_Feat_Flow_Gudda_Gudda/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - I`m A Star (Feat. Flow, Gudda Gudda) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Im_A_Star_Feat_Flow_Gudda_Gudda/" title="Shy Glizzy - I`m A Star (Feat. Flow, Gudda Gudda) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[OG Big Rankin <br>Two fifty plus <br>My nigga DJ stick a bush <br>It's a classic, nigga <br>This one of my hottest tape for 2014 <br><br>Yesterday I was standing on the block <br>We went through, a couple niggas got shot <br>We got away, had to hit it on the cops <br>Now today I'm a motherfucking star <br>Yesterday I was standing on the block <br>We went through, a couple niggas got shot <br>We got away, had to hit it on the cops <br>Now today I'm a motherfucking star <br>I'm a star, I'm a star, I'm a star <br>I'm a star, I'm a motherfucking star <br>I'm a star, I'm a star, I'm a star <br>I'm a star, I'm a motherfucking star <br><br>Glizzy Glizzy, I'm a motherfucking star <br>Ridin 'round with that fucking AR <br>Praying I don't have to pull this bitch apart <br>And send a bastard right to his fucking pa <br>What you write <br>Bitch it's Glizzy gang over every god damn gang <br>Hey flow Say he got the flame <br>We gonna go blow out his brains <br>Perfect aim I'm convinced, don't need no God damn range <br>Menace to Society, I feel just like got damn Caine <br><br>Holy shit, ran in the mix and almost pop my chain <br>I get higher than a staircase, rob a nigga bare face <br>If I ain't got my pistol, bitch, I gotta use my shank <br>You can send me to Angola, I would do my time with Frank <br>Like Glizzy said, free the gang, yep, all my niggas crooks <br>Trying to beat the case myself <br>I'm still gonna put some on your books <br>And buy all ya niggas Js, some retro number ones <br>Swap kicks under the table in the visitation room <br>Real nigga though, play pussy get fucked like a gigolo <br>All my niggas locked up lones, snitch niggas pop at home <br>We got that audio dope, bitch take it or leave it <br>Fuck taxing on bricks, bitch, we're taxing on features <br><br>Yesterday I was standing on the block <br>We went through, a couple niggas got shot <br>We got away, had to hit it on the cops <br>Now today I'm a motherfucking star <br>Yesterday I was standing on the block <br>We went through, a couple niggas got shot <br>We got away, had to hit it on the cops <br>Now today I'm a motherfucking star <br>I'm a star, I'm a star, I'm a star <br>I'm a star, I'm a motherfucking star <br>I'm a star, I'm a star, I'm a star <br>I'm a star, I'm a motherfucking star <br><br>Yes, I am a star, I said I am a star <br>Pull up in the hood in my new car and they in awe <br>Standing near the stove, bout to whip me up a brick <br>That's why I whip it, whip it, whip it till I whip another whip <br>Glizzy gang and LAT, we do this for the streets <br>Same clothes for five days, I've been hustling all week <br>Have a thing for 12 5, 25 for the whole book <br>Full pot sitting under fire, that's how the stove look <br>Hit it with the fork, can I hit it with the 44 <br>And I hit it with the soda, watch me come back with the scorch <br>Youngest on the porch and they're looking for the locks <br>I get money and I'm gone, definition of a boss <br><br>Yesterday I was standing on the block <br>We went through, a couple niggas got shot <br>We got away, had to hit it on the cops <br>Now today I'm a motherfucking star <br>Yesterday I was standing on the block <br>We went through, a couple niggas got shot <br>We got away, had to hit it on the cops <br>Now today I'm a motherfucking star <br>I'm a star, I'm a star, I'm a star <br>I'm a star, I'm a motherfucking star <br>I'm a star, I'm a star, I'm a star <br>I'm a star, I'm a motherfucking star]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="I`m A Star (Feat. Flow, Gudda Gudda)" label="I`m A Star (Feat. Flow, Gudda Gudda)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Im_On_Fire/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - I`m On Fire - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:09:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:09:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Im_On_Fire/" title="Shy Glizzy - I`m On Fire - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One time for Benny <br>Nigga been down since day one <br>Real nigga in this bitch <br>Rest in peace, Stew, aka Twin Glocks <br>There's a lot of young niggas runnin' around here <br>Calling their selves bosses <br>But <br><br>I could have been a lawyer or a doctor <br>I said fuck that, I need mula, I'm a robber <br>You ain't gon' be sure what you grow up, you a liar <br>I'm on fire, I'm on fire <br>x2 <br><br>All a nigga know is this the street shit <br>Fuck my teacher, she a ho, she ain't teach me shit <br>She told me, boy you know you ain't gon' be shit <br>I linked up with the plug, and he threw me bricks <br>I'm a dope boy, you a broke boy <br>You be rapping bout this life shit ain't no joke, boy <br>If you disrespect my team then you get smoked, boy <br>See, it ain't 'bout who you is, it's who you know, boy <br>If the feds come and get you what you gon' do <br>You gon' let em take you down, or take your whole crew <br>Wit you, is you gon' stay true <br>Cause that's what real niggas do <br>Ooh <br><br>I could have been a lawyer or a doctor <br>I said fuck that, I need mula, I'm a robber <br>You ain't gon' be sure what you grow up, you a liar <br>I'm on fire, I'm on fire <br>x2 <br><br>I could have went to Howard but I am a trapper <br>I didn't go to Howard till I became a rapper <br>They tell me that my papa who I take after <br>A nigga killed my papa, so I was a bastard <br>My mama couldn't understand what gotten into me <br>Dropped out of school just to sell cocaine and weed <br>I got my GED in the Penitentiary <br>I keep some legs a me like a fucking centipede <br>I rob you for your phone or your foams <br>I'm wrong <br>Smoking on that strong, but my mind gone <br>I'm so dope, sipping dope outta Styrofoam <br>I want that gas that see a ghost <br>Bitch be gone <br><br>I could have been a lawyer or a doctor <br>I said fuck that, I need mula, I'm a robber <br>You ain't gon' be sure what you grow up, you a liar <br>I'm on fire, I'm on fire <br>x2]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="I`m On Fire" label="I`m On Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Living_It_Up_Feat_Young_Thug_Peewee_Longway/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Living It Up (Feat. Young Thug, Peewee Longway) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Living_It_Up_Feat_Young_Thug_Peewee_Longway/" title="Shy Glizzy - Living It Up (Feat. Young Thug, Peewee Longway) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Trap house jumpin' junkies <br>Trying to bust it down <br>Just got me a rollie damn <br>I just bust it down <br>She a nag nag damn right she busting down <br>Hunnit gas bags I can't wait to bust it down <br><br>They're living up,living up,living up <br>Living up,living up,living up,living up <br>Living up,living up,living up,living up <br>Living up,living up,living up,living up <br>Living up,living up,living up,living up <br>Living up,living up <br><br>King of the town <br>Muah, Kiss the crown <br>Work in the fender, rollers gotta bust 'em down <br>Looking like samoli is the way we running now <br>All hunnit rounds, raa, bust 'em, bust 'em down <br>Glizzy, Glizzy baby <br>Thugger, Thugger, Hey <br>Whats up long way <br>I had a long day <br>Clowns coming in all the way from LA <br>Puttin' work in ,trying to get to LA <br>Breathe nigga, This weed ain't got no seeds <br>Nigga, Bow down to your knees <br>I got what you need,nigga <br>Them pounds and the keys,nigga <br>I do not believe niggas <br><br>Trap house jumpin' junkies <br>Trying to bust it down <br>Just got me a rollie damn <br>I just bust it down <br>She a nag nag damn right she busting down <br>Hunnit gas bags I can't wait to bust it down <br><br>We're living it up <br>Yeah, we just pouring fours in a cup <br>These pussy niggas know they real messed up <br>No chuck but I got on Chuck Taylors <br>My dope white but I ain't no waiter <br>But i'll serve, Heard you got ya' own paper <br>Okay I heard, I make my young niggas stay <br>Down and run it up and now they worth <br>And they dont need glasses to see I'm <br>Loading on Steve Urkle <br>OG kush mixed in with purple, Yeah I'm <br>Falling off the edge, I'm leaning <br>I ain't talking bout no cops but all my niggas fed <br>Eating, Bitch we full <br>Wealthy is poor <br><br>Trap house jumpin' junkies <br>Trying to bust it down <br>Just got me a rollie damn <br>I just bust it down <br>She a nag nag damn right she busting down <br>Hunnit gas bags I can't wait to bust it down <br><br>We just livin' me, Young Thuga and Shy Glizzy <br>Bustin' down to drizzy, bust down on the rollie <br>Rollie, I Dont bop with glizzy, Fucking different bitches <br>That never OG was stitious <br>Junkies busting down the trenches when we get them chickens <br>Im just living <br>A bitch treat me like mrbently <br>Stop crying out bad wolf OG bitch this is how we livin' <br>Wrap it up around they shit, set it off for them bitches <br><br>Trap house jumpin' junkies <br>Trying to bust it down <br>Just got me a rollie damn <br>I just bust it down <br>She a nag nag damn right she busting down <br>Hunnit gas bags I can't wait to bust it down]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Living It Up (Feat. Young Thug, Peewee Longway)" label="Living It Up (Feat. Young Thug, Peewee Longway)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/I_Cant_Trust_Myself/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - I Can`t Trust Myself - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/I_Cant_Trust_Myself/" title="Shy Glizzy - I Can`t Trust Myself - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They say them broke boys do anything for some wealth <br>Nigga shoot by yourself you don't need no help <br>I can't trust myself, I can't trust myself <br>So fuck I look like trusting anybody else <br>I can't trust myself x6 <br>So fuck I look like trusting anybody else <br><br>See its this nigga name Shy, he so fuckin' fly <br>Glizzy don't fuck with shy <br>Cause shy he think he That Guy <br>But Glizzy Be wit some dudes and all they do is lie <br>They were on a bad movie, trying to move to the Chi <br>Dope boy named Detroit, but he ain't from Detroit <br>Why the fuck they call him Detroit, he a D boy <br>I'm scarred for life lift up my shirt and show my key loins <br>Just met this goofy bitch, I told her my name Leroy <br>Who is young jefe, he got that fuckin yay <br>He ah come piss on ya grave, he don't fucking play <br>Told Migo I need bricks, yeah, andale <br>He said, boy, I need chips, frito lay <br><br>They say them broke boys do anything for some wealth <br>Nigga shoot by yourself you don't need no help <br>I can't trust myself, I can't trust myself <br>So fuck I look like trusting anybody else <br>I can't trust myself x6 <br>So fuck I look like trusting anybody else <br><br>Streets hottest youngin', I'm the hottest youngin' <br>Streets hottest youngin', I'm the hottest youngin' <br>Streets hottest youngin', I'm the hottest youngin' <br>Cold winter, fuck is up with all these hot ass youngins <br>Streets hottest youngin', I'm the hottest youngin' <br>Cold winter, fuck is up with all these hot ass youngins <br>I think I wanna take a trip to London <br>I wanna stick my dick in Lauren London <br>Niggas stealin' from they homeboys <br>God damn <br>You need to get ya own boy Get ya own nigga <br>OG by the zone, I'm stoned boy <br>Meet me at the Cross Roads, like Bone boys <br>Call me Mr Can I Take Ya Order <br>Every plug want me to meet they daughter <br>They like my chest and nuts, like Morris Get It <br>I'm swimming in they guts like fuckin' Walrus <br><br>They say them broke boys do anything for some wealth <br>Nigga shoot by yourself you don't need no help <br>I can't trust myself, I can't trust myself <br>So fuck I look like trusting anybody else <br>I can't trust myself x6 <br>So fuck I look like trusting anybody else]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="I Can`t Trust Myself" label="I Can`t Trust Myself"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/She_Like_Me_Feat_Migos_Quavo_Offset/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - She Like Me (Feat. Migos, Quavo, Offset) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/She_Like_Me_Feat_Migos_Quavo_Offset/" title="Shy Glizzy - She Like Me (Feat. Migos, Quavo, Offset) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm in the R8, that's the Audi <br>I got the AR, right beside me <br>I hopped out, on the stallion <br>She look like she belong on the islands <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br><br>Bitch I pull up in that Audi <br>So much gold like I'm from Saudi <br>Trapping them O's got me drowsy <br>Hating ass niggas they lousy <br>Call me Big Glizzy or Mister G <br>Cuban links on, look like Mister T <br>Uh, Cazals on these niggas can't see me <br>I think I'm Stevie <br>I tell the truth and these niggas welling <br>This shit is bigger than Rayful Edmond <br>Screaming omerta can't do no telling <br>I cut your ass like a watermelon <br>Three hour ride just to see my children <br>Bands in my to make it look cooler <br>Picassi Rolex, no not a Muller <br>Diamonds in this bitch say hugamuga <br>She can't keep her eyes off the don <br>I'm wearing this crown, it's a don <br>Bad bitch right here in my arms <br>Shawty she know she the bomb <br>I blow shit up like Saddam <br>I got more bait than LeBron <br>These are Christian Louboutin <br>I don't know if you're too fond <br><br>I'm in the R8, that's the Audi <br>I got the AR, right beside me <br>I hopped out, on the stallion <br>She look like she belong on the islands <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br><br>Oh I, oh I think they like me <br>But I don't got on a white tee <br>Walk in the mall and they go pandemonium <br>Bitches, yeah they running after me <br>Why they got so much excitement <br>Cause Migos, Shy Glizzy in present tense <br>I thank the plug, he showed me guidance <br>We wrap it, pack it, it's already sealed <br>I take the pot, I got the finger fuckin' <br>It's a million dollars in the dope bucket <br>I got the trap game, I got the rap game <br>I am the cashier, hand out the gold tokens <br>I know they like it cause my diamonds fighting <br>Got my pinky ring looking like ice hockey <br>Rebuild the trap like I'm Bob the Builder <br>Smoke so much gas you might need a filter <br>Can't double seal, I don' trust refillers <br>Come try my dope, it's so finger licking <br>Pull up to the trap with Justin Bieber <br>Just to pick up the gas pack in the beamer <br>They calling my wrist the new Stanley Steemer <br>Young niggas on the block, they cutting off femurs <br>Bitches want me in a two seater <br>They was sucking and fucking, you should have seen em <br><br>I'm in the R8, that's the Audi <br>I got the AR, right beside me <br>I hopped out, on the stallion <br>She look like she belong on the islands <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br><br>My bitch is a stallion come from the islands <br>Got birds in the trunk and they sing like the Isleys <br>You niggas don't like me, I know they despise me <br>When I see em pull out the pistol it's a riot <br>I didn't go to high school I went to the trap university <br>Aventador, chop the top like a surgery <br>Made a 30 off a coca key <br>Hollows sting like a bumble bee <br>I heard that she like it when the diamonds dripping <br>33 birds in the trunk, Scottie Pippen <br>Louboutin low top a king cobra <br>My arm got the hammer, no baking soda <br>Your bitch got that wet, the Pacific Ocean <br>Stretch her, bend her over like aerobics <br>Your bitch on her knees, eat the latex <br>She a dirty bitch so we have safe sex <br>I like she ducking, these prices my diamonds <br>Mike Tyson burn a nigga like it is Niacin <br>I play with keys and you play with violins <br>Black on black violence cause you wasn't solid <br>Got the fire in my pocket, no lighter <br>Your bitch is coming straight off the dope, she no rider <br>Pass the lil bitch to my partners like flyers <br>Like my attire, I didn't have to buy her <br>Whipping the brick, put it under the dryer <br>I got babies, they don't need pacifiers <br>You cuffing that bitch that my niggas done hit <br>She sucking the dick you need to go retire <br><br>I'm in the R8, that's the Audi <br>I got the AR, right beside me <br>I hopped out, on the stallion <br>She look like she belong on the islands <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me <br>I think she like me, I think she like me]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="She Like Me (Feat. Migos, Quavo, Offset)" label="She Like Me (Feat. Migos, Quavo, Offset)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/I_Did_It/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - I Did It - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/I_Did_It/" title="Shy Glizzy - I Did It - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jefe Free 3 Shit don't stop , People do <br><br>Just because you breathing that don't mean you living <br>My Little bro said because you breathing that don't mean you living <br>And there hasn't been a lot of killing or no drug dealing <br>Niggas been kicking it with snitches what the fuck is this <br>Got all these all these strangers up in my business fuck the fame <br>can't let it change the way that i'm living <br>Shout out to my fans they stay down and i did it <br>Hell nah that ain't my message i killed him <br><br>Little bruh got caught in the jam but he still living <br>He ain't have to hit the gas but he still did it <br>Fuck the popos boy this K got me a meal ticket <br>Boy I just got me a mill ticket <br>All this pain im going insane I gotta deal with it <br>hey Fuck all my enemies and no that nigga not my nigga he's a frenemie <br>I keep my gun on me, that 100 round you im goin spray <br>So Icey boy my diamonds cost a hundred k <br>I just left the store and all i bought was baking soda <br>Get 20 thousand for a show, imagine all that coca <br>And Boy my house so cold that bih so cold like Minnesota <br>Fuck all these niggas know they tryna fuck me over <br><br>Just because you breathing that don't mean you living <br>My Little bro said because you breathing that don't mean you living <br>And there hasn't been a lot of killing or no drug dealing <br>Niggas been kicking it with snitches what the fuck is this <br>Got all these all these strangers up in my business fuck the fame <br>can't let it change the way that i'm living <br>Shout out to my fans they stay down and i did it <br>Hell nah that ain't my message i killed him <br><br>Fuck a dart case I just gave the lawyer 5K <br>Told him do whatever it take just make it fly away <br>You get da picture you took a screenshot turn it sideways <br>Streets hottest Youngin bitch im hotter then your fire place <br>All my niggas they be thuggin out the trap house <br>You see i actually just be what you rap about <br>And I be ridin threw your hood with my Mac out <br>Yo bitch be ridin we so good I blow her back out <br>All this damn stressin and im still finessing <br>Bah bah keep that smith n western <br>Glizzy Glizzy bitch yea im a living legend <br>I still haven't learned my lesson <br><br>Just because you breathing that don't mean you living <br>My Little bro said because you breathing that don't mean you living <br>And there hasn't been a lot of killing or no drug dealing <br>Niggas been kicking it with snitches what the fuck is this <br>Got all these all these strangers up in my business fuck the fame <br>can't let it change the way that i'm living <br>Shout out to my fans they stay down and i did it <br>Hell nah that ain't my message i killed him]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="I Did It" label="I Did It"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Prey_For_Me/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Prey For Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Prey_For_Me/" title="Shy Glizzy - Prey For Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Its Glizzy, Glizzy baby I'm a trapper baby <br>All In ya city stopping traffic baby2x <br>I fuck all ya bitches, no thats not my baby <br>I'm bout that cash money just like slim and baby <br>They finally see I'm getting out the hood now <br>Niggas actin' like it's all good now <br>I used to steal cars I got my own now <br>Play wit' me I bet yo brains get blown out <br>I am DC, nigga I run DC <br>Them rap niggas they ain't really from DC <br>They look at me and they see what they wanna be <br>I know they plottin' so I keep my gun on me <br>Look at my niggas, hittas they a come and get ya <br>You's a ugly actor boy Forest Whitaker <br>I gets lots of cheese, just like a tortilla <br>My whole gang in cages, I need more gorillas <br>Niggas talkin' bout killin' me, so I keep my artillery <br>Run up on Glizzy I'll turn yo ass to rotisserie <br>My bitch dumb like Hilary but we got a great history <br>You thinkin' bout dissin' me, I'll send yo ass on delivery <br>I remember when it wasn't no hope for the future <br>If those ain't my guys, those shooters <br>Don't let these rappers fool ya, they faker than they jeweler <br>That asalamaleka but that KE hallelujah <br>Hold up <br>Prey For Me <br>Big Glizzy Nigga <br><br>Im goin' in again <br><br>Never been to the white house just the house wit' the white <br>Play wit' one of my niggas gon have to fight fa' ya life <br>Double G in the hood, just like roaches and mice <br>Eating off of one pie no you can't have a slice <br>I was coolin' on south beach met a bitch she from cuba <br>She apart of the cartel, say her uncle the ruler <br>Rob a nigga for his bands and spend that shit at the jeweler <br>Just make sure you mask up and keep that shit off computers <br>It was hot dogs and beans now its hunnit dollar wings <br>I had hoes and matches now I'm a fucking diesel fien <br>Them rap niggas kept on sellin' me dreams <br>Got my bands up now I'm the Mark Cuban of this team <br>I was gon' catch one of them, come to my city I'm gunnin' em <br>I hope I punish them before I kill one of them <br>All excite my <br>Mama like I'm proud of him <br>Then found out it ain't shit <br>Thankful I'm not one of them2x <br>Prey For Me]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Prey For Me" label="Prey For Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/First_48/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - First 48 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/First_48/" title="Shy Glizzy - First 48 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Young Jefe homes <br>Uh <br><br>These niggas so scary <br>Won't let them bury me <br>That's why I keep my 30 I shoot like Curry <br>And boy I'm getting money I'm getting money <br>These niggas hilarious I think they funny <br>Empty out his pockets he on easter bunny <br>My bitch she trying to play me but I'm not no dummy <br>Oh I got some louis shit can't wait to swag it up <br>I just left the dealership can't wait to gas it up <br>Boy I got a lot of pounds can't wait to bag em up <br>My new bitch from out of town you know she bad as fuck <br>What I just spent in Lenox could've bought a Audi truck <br>I told her she can get it but she can't stay out the clubs <br>Put her on to designer now I can't find her <br>The way she used rock my mic, I should have signed her <br>If I knew she was gone be a hoe I would have fined her <br>50 on my Glizzy chain I'm just gone blind her <br>I'm balling just like 23 way back in '93 <br>I'm so high right now feel like I'm on my balcony <br>Every time I hear po po's, feel like they after me <br>I bet I blow more money than yo favorite athlete <br>And my dog Yayo get more bitches than you peons <br>Every time I'm in the A, they treat me like I'm Deon <br>Glizzy Gang and Neon niggas know we be on <br>I know one thing, they ain't on the shit that we on <br>Got niggas on the Boulevard and niggas on the Crest <br>Got too much respect if you play then you get left <br>I'm in this bitch with long and we smoking stuffed crust <br>Damn I had a long day I need somewhere to run <br><br>Feeling just like Kane swerving in that new mustang <br>Bitch play with my name smack her with my Jefe ring <br>Got my bad habits from uncle Pootie Tang <br>Chasing after cabbage but I ran into the fame <br>Tre seven my block, you can't come there after dark <br>Murder Murder Murder 3 gone shoot you with the Glock <br>This summer we back Glizzys walking round with knots <br>Pistols on our hip won't be them niggas getting got <br>I just left from Saks spent some racks and that's a fact <br>Momma get that call and she gone have a heart attack <br>That's why I stay strapped loaded like I'm from Iraq <br>How that nigga run up and get hit up in his back <br>Lay that ass down let that sucka feel them rounds <br>Hit him 9 more times ask him how he like the sound <br>Lay that ass down pussy cat goin' meow <br>Wetting up my almost drowned <br>Atlanta jugging pounds in an Uber downtown <br>Bitch don't want to maneuver, take her ass downtown <br>Fuckin' that bitch no lay ups sorry I don't wanna lounge <br>First 48 these niggas promise I won't make a sound]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="First 48" label="First 48"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/From_The_Get_Go_Feat_Glizzy_Gang/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - From The Get Go (Feat. Glizzy Gang) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/From_The_Get_Go_Feat_Glizzy_Gang/" title="Shy Glizzy - From The Get Go (Feat. Glizzy Gang) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yo yo <br>Be careful <br>Suckers <br><br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br>Don't make me send that walking 30 to your front door <br>Baby Gli got that Choppa better get low <br>Pack mob big guns and them bankrolls <br>We'll bust a nigga head and get the case closed <br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br><br>Bitch it's Glizzy two times I got a bankroll <br>Call my migo he got thangs in the durango <br>Thug life I never said I was an angel <br>I be fucking up the watch just like I'm Tango <br>Glizzy Gangin' yeah I'm the fuckin head huncho <br>I took your ass to Medellin and let you meet Pablo <br>Time is money bitch I ain't got not time to argue <br>I keep a lotta racks on me like Wells Fargo <br>Bitch I'm hoppin out tha benzo wearin tha Kenzo <br>Big Glizzy with that big fucking extendo <br>I was starin at the window fuck Nintendo <br>I seen some Dope boys and a bunch of fuckin' bimbos <br><br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br>Don't make me send that walking 30 to your front door <br>Baby 3 got that Choppa better get low <br>Pack mob big guns and them bankrolls <br>We'll bust a nigga head and get the case closed <br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br><br>Connected in and respected <br>Disrespect you need detectives <br>Nigga ain't no question I'm toting my Smith and Wesson <br>This bitch show 30 my standing clip that's extra <br>Real young niggas them other niggas they extra <br>OG believe me I put more work in than my OGs <br>You better ask about me <br>I got some niggas that'll wack yo ass about me <br>Matter fact don't even ask about me <br>It's all murda ain't no racks around me <br>Mobs chilling a lotta straps a lotta racks round me <br>A lotta drugs a lotta plugs a lotta killas round me <br>Yeah from the get go <br>This young nigga been a pitbull <br>You better ask about me <br><br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br>Don't make me send that walking 30 to your front door <br>Baby 3 got that Choppa better get low <br>Pack mob big guns and them bankrolls <br>We'll bust a nigga head and get the case closed <br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br><br>Niggas know we been thuggin from the get go <br>Rob it tight <br>Got mob tasks and get you knocked off if I want to <br>By time I was three I knew how to work a pistol <br>Hunned rounds drum it'll let the shit go <br>Who the fuck is that roll down the window <br>Our papers now so I can turn up how I want to <br>Magic Johnson that bitch hold 32 <br>Beefin with my bruva yeah we got beef too <br>Show love ain't get the same love fuck people <br>Last of a dying breed these niggas see thru <br>Tote my glizzys like they mofuckin legal]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="From The Get Go (Feat. Glizzy Gang)" label="From The Get Go (Feat. Glizzy Gang)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Long_Time/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Long Time - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Long_Time/" title="Shy Glizzy - Long Time - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br><br>Ok i've been sippin on a dirty shit <br>That hoe been sniffin she ain't innocent she a dirty bitch <br>These rappers keep talkin this dirty shit <br>When will one a you niggas come get a thirty six <br>Effe i just left for manny yeah <br>Blow that big fat Brooks the call him butter B <br>Am one of the realest niggas you'll ever seen <br>I've been rockin vvs since i was seventeen <br>And if it ain't a cush you bet not send it <br>My only cush a comin but that ain't none a my biness <br>Clowns in the trash cans glissy do the dishes <br>Dont nobody nobody fuck with my kitchen <br><br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br><br>I've been out here trappin for a long time <br>All these bitches on mah dick cause i'm on now <br>Just coming in breaking down as it touch down <br>Them court days turn to tort days now <br>These ain't no gimmick bitches going down <br>We got thirties we got fifties we got hundred rounds <br>Whole lotta rounds well run you down <br>Well run in your town ask nobody make a sound <br>Nobody can replace mah bitch the way she hold me down <br>She gonna buss these Glocks and she gone hold these pounds <br>Hold these pounds hey baby hold the pounds <br>If they send me down the road she gone hold me down <br><br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time <br>Choppin for a long time <br>I've been out here choppin for a long time]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Long Time" label="Long Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Out_The_Block/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Out The Block - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Out_The_Block/" title="Shy Glizzy - Out The Block - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I keep my pistol on guard if you run up you get shot <br>Put him in a box give no fuck about no op <br>My niggas got locks so I'm screamin fuck the cops <br>All this dope money bitch I got it out the block <br>Bottles been popped bitch I got it out the block <br>Don't you see my watch yeah I got it out the block <br>Gotta keep my Glock when I'm standing on the block <br>Everything I got yeah I got it off the block <br><br>OK bitches by the three and I'm in here with my heat <br>Drinkin on that lean and I'm not gon hardly sleep <br>I had a long day running round with GG <br>I came to the A just to talk about them Ps <br>Cash on deck you don't have to send no mas <br>I got to spend a bus boy go head and fill it up <br>40 cal with them hollows better fill em up <br>Lookin at my chain I might have to hit him up <br>I just got a call that my youngin caught a rap <br>Same nigga whole hood thought he was a rat <br>They can't keep it G no more unless you getting charges <br>Wonder how he came home he told on everybody <br><br>I keep my pistol on guard if you run up you get shot <br>Put him in a box give no fuck about no op <br>My niggas got locks so I'm screamin fuck the cops <br>All this dope money bitch I got it out the block <br>Bottles been popped bitch I got it out the block <br>Don't you see my watch yeah I got it out the block <br>Gotta keep my Glock when I'm standing on the block <br>Everything I got yeah I got it off the block <br><br>Shout out to the few niggas that still keep it real <br>Them niggas who ain't snitchin rather sit they ass in jail <br>The popos can't be worried that they took no fuckin deal <br>I got a situation I ain't got no fuckin deal <br>Before I was a rapper I had 20 and a flow <br>This rap shit ain't too bad I get 20 for a show <br>Change up on my niggas now my niggas all I know <br>Boy yo ass a pussy you get chained up for a ho <br>I been on my bullshit ain't been feelin like myself <br>But shit, I don't feel like no one else <br>I'mma slam on a nigga I don't need nobody help <br>Never will I be a hater I hear that's bad for your health <br><br>I keep my pistol on guard if you run up you get shot <br>Put him in a box give no fuck about no op <br>My niggas got locks so I'm screamin fuck the cops <br>All this dope money bitch I got it out the block <br>Bottles been popped bitch I got it out the block <br>Don't you see my watch yeah I got it out the block <br>Gotta keep my Glock when I'm standing on the block <br>Everything I got yeah I got it off the block]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Out The Block" label="Out The Block"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Awwsome/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Awwsome - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Awwsome/" title="Shy Glizzy - Awwsome - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Swish, I'm balling <br>I'm so awesome <br>Old bitch keep calling <br>She think I'm awesome <br>Jackboys wanna rob me <br>I'm so awesome <br>Out here like a possum <br>I'm so, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br><br>Oh my fucking God, pull up in that, oh my gosh <br>You niggas so soft, get that arrow out your heart <br>You can be a boss or you can get a job <br>You do not go hard, you's a motherfucking fraud <br>Young Jefe, I got boats you can sail away <br>Dope boy, you are not my friend, you need to get away <br>Call up my driver tell him scoop me in his Escalate <br>Night Sunday, bet 1000 bucks on Tampa Bay <br>Got a lot of spots like a motherfucking cheetah <br>All we do is trap, my OGs still got beepers <br>Bad little kitty momma took my ass to jeepers <br>Tryna get a ticket like no money in the meter <br><br>Swish, I'm balling <br>I'm so awesome <br>Old bitch keep calling <br>She think I'm awesome <br>Jackboys wanna rob me <br>I'm so awesome <br>Out here like a possum <br>I'm so, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br><br>Make these niggas sick, chicken noodle soup <br>Chickens in my coupe, it's a fucking chicken coop <br>Young nigga a fool, I just saw the boo <br>My bitch, she so cute, that's my little boo <br>She from down in Austin, her family balling <br>Baby, I'm a stunter, just like Stone Cold Steve Austin <br>One bitch gave me blue balls, I think she from Slauson <br>Walking around with two dogs, boom, John Wallin <br>Higher then a blimp, leaning like a pimp <br>40 by my Fendi, got me walking with a limp <br>I'm not signing no bitch unless she nasty like Lil Kim <br>I got a lot of weight and I do not go to the gym <br><br>Swish, I'm balling <br>I'm so awesome <br>Old bitch keep calling <br>She think I'm awesome <br>Jackboys wanna rob me <br>I'm so awesome <br>Out here like a possum <br>I'm so, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Awwsome" label="Awwsome"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Lil_Mama_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Lil Mama (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Lil_Mama_Feat_Ty_Dolla_ign/" title="Shy Glizzy - Lil Mama (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Woah, Young Jefe holmes <br>Load 'em up <br><br>She look good with me <br>She gonna thug with me <br>She hold it down, take her to go meet the plug with me <br>Make her put that shit on then go hit the club with me <br>Think it's the hood in me, made her fall in love with me <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br><br>Glizzy you're a trap nigga, why the fuck you rap <br>How much did you make today Cause bitch I made a lot <br>Got some nat nats in the A and in the Chi I got some thots <br>If she ain't lil mama then she can't come to the spot <br>Esse I'm a boss, I'm a motherfuckin' boss <br>Shout out your favorite rapper, he's a motherfuckin' fraud <br>Lil mama used to stall now she like me cause I ball <br>Round of applause, got her clappin' for your boy <br>Dappered down, they know I'm the motherfuckin' coldest <br>I bought this bitch some Louboutin's, I barely even knew her <br>Got a four of red, I'm bout to pour up in a soda <br>Play with me your ass dead, you already know it <br><br>She look good with me <br>She gonna thug with me <br>She hold it down, take her to go meet the plug with me <br>Make her put that shit on then go hit the club with me <br>Think it's the hood in me, made her fall in love with me <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br><br>I just bought a scrollin' through my <br>Got a phone thug text from a bim <br>Got a phone call said my bitch cheatin' <br>Got a phone call said the homie snitchin' <br>Bitch get on my nervous, put her on detention <br>If you ain't got jump there, then you ain't official <br>Dolla $ign and Shy Glizzy realest in the city <br>If she ain't got an ass then she got some titties <br>I just stunt the mall and I spent a lot <br>I just hit the gate runnin' from the cops <br>Every time this beat drop she make that pussy pop <br>Got an kitchen, water whippin' out the rock <br><br>She look good with me <br>She gonna thug with me <br>She hold it down, take her to go meet the plug with me <br>Make her put that shit on then go hit the club with me <br>Think it's the hood in me, made her fall in love with me <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br>That's my lil mama, lil mama, lil mama <br><br>Ohhh, lil mama, lil mama <br>Lil mama, lil mama, ohhhh]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Lil Mama (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)" label="Lil Mama (Feat. Ty Dolla $ign)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Thank_You/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Thank You - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Thank_You/" title="Shy Glizzy - Thank You - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I shouldn't have out the shades on <br>Keep all that too <br>Jefe <br><br>Yours Truly <br>Versace Shades <br>I feel like Biggie in This Bitch <br>Thank You <br><br>Come on and let a real nigga sing to you <br>Stop letting all these rappers prank you <br>I like to sip purp, I smoke dank too <br>Running out the jungle, I'm a bengal <br>Thank you, thank you, thank you, Thank you, Thank you x3 <br>For listening to a real nigga <br><br>I never in my whole life felt this much pain <br>Riding through your ghetto trying to bust your nigga's brain <br>Meek just hit my phone and said he bought a glitzy chain <br>He told me lil bruh I know you about to kill the game <br>Guess what, I just got a fuckin call from mack maine <br>He told me Birdman want me to be in Rich Gang <br>My OG don't do shit he just like bricks and champagne <br>And you won't see his face if you don't get a whole thing <br>Talk to to everyday, he don't ask the kid for shit <br>Cuz got 60 niggas crying over 6 <br>Don't look at my IG and be like shawty he the lick <br>Run up you'll get hit, whole lotta guns, I don't know the name of this shit <br><br>Come on and let a real nigga sing to you <br>Stop letting all these rappers prank you <br>I like to sip purp, I smoke dank too <br>Running out the jungle, I'm a bengal <br>Thank you, thank you, thank you, Thank you, Thank you x3 <br>For listening to a real nigga <br><br>I just bought a dog and named him 40 <br>You know I keep that dog , this a 40 <br>Check your shorty, she out here having orgy's <br>And ya'll love shorty, all y'all going to see Maury <br>These niggas hate me cuz I got my bands up <br>I'm gonna keep going til my niggas in a mansion <br>Bitch from france she say bon jour you're so handsome <br>Fancy restaurants what me to pull my pants up <br>I just seen my jeweler a couple days ago <br>They hate me when I do that lazy flow <br>You say you love how That ain't your lady tho <br>Sold a quarter, spent a quarter on a bracelet tho <br><br>Come on and let a real nigga sing to you <br>Stop letting all these rappers prank you <br>I like to sip purp, I smoke dank too <br>Running out the jungle, I'm a bengal <br>Thank you, thank you, thank you, Thank you, Thank you x3 <br>For listening to a real nigga]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Thank You" label="Thank You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Glizzy_Feat_Young_Thug_Peewee_Longway/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Glizzy (Feat. Young Thug, Peewee Longway) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Glizzy_Feat_Young_Thug_Peewee_Longway/" title="Shy Glizzy - Glizzy (Feat. Young Thug, Peewee Longway) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Im Shy, Im Glizzy x2 <br>Im Shy, My Jewelry's Glistening <br>My Jewelry's Gli Gli <br>Its Glizzy Its Glizzy <br>My Jewelry's Fucking Glistening <br>Look at it Bitch We bout' <br>Nigga's Play with Thug, They ass Goin' Come up Missing <br>Niggas Play with Shy, They ass Goin' Come up Missing <br>Niggas Play with MPA, They come up Missing They Come up Missing <br><br>Play bout mine, my niggas goin' take yo' smile, My niggas goin take yo' life <br><br>Who give a fuck who in or down <br><br>Im Shy, Im Shy, Dont Ask me why my Diamonds goin bIing bling bow <br><br>Heard Longway talking in the crowd <br><br>Dont speak no Englo, Bitch Im on Molly <br><br>Boot Up Boot Up Boot Up Boot Up Boot Up <br><br>Im gone bust She gone Bust We gone Bust BUST BUST BUST BUST BUST <br><br>My troot is on boots <br>They hawk yo' bitch down and she boost through the roof <br>Im flying to DC and they shoot me the boot <br>Passed out so many I leave scene with a coupe <br>My diamonds are glistening ain't none of them missing <br>I catch yo bitches and they pussy no kitten <br>They kinda like me so I know that they dissen <br>I catch them in the club, and water their melon <br>Im Shy, Im Glizzy x2 <br>Im shy, Im shy my jewelry's Glizzy <br>Its Glizzy Its Glizzy My jewelry's fucking Glizzy <br>Its Glizzy, Its glistening, look at it bitch we bout' <br>Nigga's play with thots, they ass goin' come up missing <br>Niggas play with shots, they ass goin' come up missing <br>Niggas play with MPA, they come up missing They come up missing <br><br>Ok im leaning like a kick stand, I shoot my pistol like a Piston <br><br>Young Jefe I do not talk to Assistance My Jewelry's Glizzy, My fucking Jewelry's Glistening <br><br>Ran Shotgun with Thugger Leave yo' ass front cover <br><br>New bitch Straight from Russia Dirty Bitch ain't using no rubber <br><br>Fucking with Peewee Longway Hefner, Fucking with Peewee Longway Hefner <br><br>Pddddd, Leave a message, A choo, God Bless You <br><br>Ooo She want Crispy, and that Beat like oooh I ain't into Steve Wonder, but she sing the Blues <br><br>Oooo ooo ooooo Young Thugger, Peewee Longway, Shy Glizzy them Dudes <br><br>Im Shy, Im Glizzy x2 <br><br>Im Shy, My Jewelry's Glistening <br><br>My Jewelry's Gli Gli <br><br>Its Glizzy Its Glizzy <br><br>My Jewelry's Fucking Glistening <br><br>Look at it Bitch We bout' <br><br>Nigga's Play with Thots, They ass Goin' Come up Missing <br><br>Niggas Play with Shots, They ass Goin' Come up Missing <br><br>Niggas Play with MPA, They come up Missing They Come up Missing]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Glizzy (Feat. Young Thug, Peewee Longway)" label="Glizzy (Feat. Young Thug, Peewee Longway)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Funeral/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Funeral - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Funeral/" title="Shy Glizzy - Funeral - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I want all shooters at my funeral <br>Only real niggas at my funeral <br>It's gonna be 10000 bitches at my funeral <br>Niggas gonna have them pistols at my funeral <br>Its gone be some superstars at my funeral <br>Driving in exotic cars to my funeral <br>Niggas that whip that brick of hard at my funeral <br>You might get your ass robbed at my funeral <br><br>They tell me stay up out the streets niggas trying to kill me <br>This all I know I was born with this shit in me <br>I don't leave the house if I don't have the semi <br>My niggas ain't pouring no remy, they don't even drink Remy <br>Im all around the globe, just me and benny <br>We couting benji's bitch we bout to cop some bentley <br>Bentleys, just to be specific <br>Shoulda seen this bitch I had last night, she so terrific <br>And she know I'm a fucking menace <br>She look like Taraji P Henson <br>Bury me in all white linen <br>Bet you they won't say a pussy did it <br><br>I want all shooters at my funeral <br>Only real niggas at my funeral <br>It's gonna be 10000 bitches at my funeral <br>Niggas gonna have them pistols at my funeral <br>Its gone be some superstars at my funeral <br>Driving in exotic cars to my funeral <br>Niggas that whip that brick of hard at my funeral <br>You might get your ass robbed at my funeral <br><br>Im thinking about my granny, her name is Ann <br>Just lost her daughter and her son did not become a man <br>Got damn, everybody love miss ann <br>She done been through so much pain, she don't give a damn <br>Gotta stay strong for my fam, I made myself a man <br>But If i don't, who the fuck gonna take care of my fam <br>My uncle in a wheelchair, I'm trying to get him a lam <br>Momma keep talking about her bills, thats why Im out here hustling <br>I ain't stunt on these niggas like I really wanna <br>I ain't fuck all these bitches that I really wanna <br>I don't see these bitch niggas just like stevie wonder <br>When I die all i Want is <br><br>I want all shooters at my funeral <br>Only real niggas at my funeral <br>It's gonna be 10000 bitches at my funeral <br>Niggas gonna have them pistols at my funeral <br>Its gone be some superstars at my funeral <br>Driving in exotic cars to my funeral <br>Niggas that whip that brick of hard at my funeral <br>You might get your ass robbed at my funeral]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Funeral" label="Funeral"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Everything_Golden/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Everything Golden - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Everything_Golden/" title="Shy Glizzy - Everything Golden - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I called my old bitch and asked her can I come over <br>She said it's past 12 Glizzy ain't shit open <br>Seen me on TV now she say she just joking <br>Bitch go get my CD I ain't jumping in the ocean <br>I ain't jumping your in your ocean <br>Bitch go get my CD I ain't jumping in your ocean <br>Everything golden <br>She can't take the ride if she do not have the token <br><br>OK i'm hopping out that Rover <br>Glizzy Glizzy bitch I spent 100K on gold Glizzy Glizzy bitch <br>Its time I let these bitches know <br>First time I got some head I was eleven years old <br>She know i'm puffing on that og <br>Bought that bitch around trip <br>She talking like she know me Bitch you don't know me <br>Boy your diamonds got her slowly <br>Bet she wouldn't say no if she see you with a rollie <br>And all my old hoes fuck with lames <br>They mad cos I won't fuck em dirty ho just want a name <br>And I never been to the range <br>But if a nigga try me ama bust like Jesse James <br>Bang bang bang <br><br>I called my old bitch and asked her can I come over <br>She said it's past 12 Glizzy ain't shit open <br>Seen me on TV now she say she just joking <br>Bitch go get my CD I ain't jumping in the ocean <br>I ain't jumping your in your ocean <br>Bitch go get my CD I ain't jumping in your ocean <br>Everything golden <br>She can't take the ride if she do not have the token <br><br>You see my kicks they golden just bought a whip its golden <br>Got a bitch from Oakland she say this dick is golden <br>She like her bottles golden she don't drink no Moet <br>She wear that Bond No9 <br>But man I swear that shit is potent <br>These bitches so extra, they be flexing <br>Always playing big till they see you with the next bitch <br>Got a bitch from Texas she so sexy <br>We be sipping mud and she say this dick is excellent <br>I remember one night I was stranded <br>Tried to hit my old bitch and that dumb bitch didn't answer <br>So one night she was flipping through her channels <br>She see me on TV I no longer have my Samsung, bitch <br><br>I called my old bitch and asked her can I come over <br>She said it's past 12 Glizzy ain't shit open <br>Seen me on TV now she say she just joking <br>Bitch go get my CD I ain't jumping in the ocean <br>I ain't jumping your in your ocean <br>Bitch go get my CD I ain't jumping in your ocean <br>Everything golden <br>She can't take the ride if she do not have the token]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Everything Golden" label="Everything Golden"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Guns__Roses/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Guns & Roses - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Guns__Roses/" title="Shy Glizzy - Guns & Roses - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Guns and Roses <br>Them niggas don't love you,nigga <br>Guns and Roses <br>Them bitches don't love you,nigga <br>Guns and Roses <br>Them ain't your friends,nigga <br>Guns and Roses <br>That bitch might fuck your friends,nigga <br><br>Guns and Roses x 8 <br><br>That loyalty, you owe it <br>If you love someone you show it <br>Im too real and you know it <br>Ball your feelings up and throw it <br>That 40 cal I tote it <br>This molly got me rollin' <br>You niggas be hoeing <br>Come to your block and go bonin' <br>37th where i'm from <br>E'rybody got a gun <br>I just got some dope today <br>And I gave my aunt a bump <br>Yeah I'm smoking on that gas <br>Nigga pull up to the pump <br>Choppa came with a drum <br>Ba rumpa bum bum <br>Police took away my friends <br>Or they life came to an end <br>These niggas not my friends <br>They just want some of my ends <br>Im flyer than the wind <br>Everything I do I win <br>Boy you on your last limb <br>I seen more weight than a Gym <br>Ridin round with the plug <br>He got drugs in the armrest <br>Take a nigga chain let my grandmother pawn that <br>Streets Hottest Youngin' call the labels <br>Make em' bump that <br>Streets goin crazy, why the fuck he ain't signed yet <br><br>Guns and Roses <br>Them niggas don't love you,nigga <br>Guns and Roses <br>Them bitches don't love you,nigga <br>Guns and Roses <br>Them ain't your friends,nigga <br>Guns and Roses <br>That bitch might fuck your friends,nigga <br><br>Guns and Roses x 8 <br><br>Young Nigga I seen it all <br>Matter fact, I want it all <br>Knew a lot of niggas who fell, Shit I even took a fall <br>I tried to pick up a ball, crowd didn't cheer at all <br>Pull up in a stolen car <br>They treatin me like a star <br>Now everything I want be mine <br>I tell your girl I'm the man <br>Self Made motherfucker, even got it on my hands <br>Knew he wasn't my man <br>Shit we ain't come from the sand <br>I thought we was taking bands <br>And that nigga took the stand <br>Im out here chasin' paper <br>Give a Fuck about a hater <br>Had a nigga in The Fader and the fuckin' city Paper <br>I shoot just like a Laker <br>I'm a fucking hit maker <br>Might hit Meekah later <br>We some fuckin' dream chasers <br>And bitch you ain't my bitch <br>You be on niggas dick <br>Wanna kill the boy that dissed <br>But a nigga might snitch <br>And I done hung out on a lot of niggas zips <br>I know when they come out and when them guns on they hip <br><br>Guns and Roses <br>Them niggas don't love you,nigga <br>Guns and Roses <br>Them bitches don't love you,nigga <br>Guns and Roses <br>Them ain't your friends,nigga <br>Guns and Roses <br>That bitch might fuck your friends,nigga <br><br>Guns and Roses x 8]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Guns & Roses" label="Guns & Roses"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Celebration_Feat_Bobby_Shmurda/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Celebration (Feat. Bobby Shmurda) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Celebration_Feat_Bobby_Shmurda/" title="Shy Glizzy - Celebration (Feat. Bobby Shmurda) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Burr burr burr my ice is colder <br>Young nigga I ain't gettin' out the Rover <br>I came in here with 50 soldiers <br>We got 50 bitches on the sofa <br>It's a fuckin' celebration <br>They hatin' cuz a young nigga done made it <br>It's a fuckin' celebration <br>They hatin' cuz a young nigga done made it <br><br>All this cash and they can't take it <br>I ain't even have no graduation <br>This OG got me levitatin' <br>I forgot to take my medication <br>Your bitch, she wanna give me top <br>Aha she guh cuz I won't beat the box <br>Go get my Cuban out the freezer box <br>Jefe shoot the Glock, just like a red fox <br>Ace of Spades, tell your bitch to come this way <br>Pistols in the body, do you wanna play <br>You won't see a million niggas under me <br>I'm chasin' the millions just like Money May <br><br>Burr burr burr my ice is colder <br>Young nigga I ain't gettin' out the Rover <br>I came in here with 50 soldiers <br>We got 50 bitches on the sofa <br>It's a fuckin' celebration <br>They hatin' cuz a young nigga done made it <br>It's a fuckin' celebration <br>They hatin' cuz a young nigga done made it <br><br>Bobby but my last name Shmurda <br>Since '08, bitch, we've been bangin' burners <br>Baby bro fightin' attempted shmurdas <br>Free Lil Flock, he put that S in Shmurda shhh, bow <br>Drop that body, then it's adios <br>I see you fuckers like he gotta go <br>Don't fuck with me, I smoke a lotta dope <br>Come fuck with us, we get a lotta dough <br>Get so much pussy, gotta time it slow <br>I'm gettin' pussy from the finest hoes <br>It's too much texas, I'm replying slow <br>If you ain't tryna fuck, well bitch Geronimo <br><br>Burr burr burr my ice is colder <br>Young nigga I ain't gettin' out the Rover <br>I came in here with 50 soldiers <br>We got 50 bitches on the sofa <br>It's a fuckin' celebration <br>They hatin' cuz a young nigga done made it <br>It's a fuckin' celebration <br>They hatin' cuz a young nigga done made it]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Celebration (Feat. Bobby Shmurda)" label="Celebration (Feat. Bobby Shmurda)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Head_Huncho_Feat_Migos_Quavo_Offset/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Head Huncho (Feat. Migos, Quavo, Offset) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Head_Huncho_Feat_Migos_Quavo_Offset/" title="Shy Glizzy - Head Huncho (Feat. Migos, Quavo, Offset) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody know we got the birds on the truck load <br>Fuck with Glizzy Gang and Migos shoot ya like a free throw <br>Everybody know she don't want nothin' but a blue bankroll <br>Everybody know young nigga, boss nigga, head huncho <br>Head huncho, head huncho <br>'Bout the blue bankroll, we'll cut your head off, head huncho <br>Head huncho, head huncho <br>Young nigga, young nigga, flexed up, bossed up, head honcho <br><br>We is the realest young niggas, fuck niggas we do not fuck with em <br>Black and white all of my Rari's, pulling up looking like Pilgrims <br>He coming up short with the money, sorry we kidnap the children <br>Pull up in the Bentley, I'm riding around got his kids in the Bentley <br>What am I sippin', double trouble, color purple, I'm drinkin', no sealin' <br>We had to go get it <br>Whether it's kickin' in doors or we coming through ceilings <br>Migos and Shy Glizzy, when we come together, we makin' a milli <br>Huncho in my city, you run up on me then we open fire quickly <br>Do you know what it take to be a huncho <br>What would you do, what would you do <br>Head huncho young nigga making boss moves <br>Pull out the chopper I aim it that you better move <br><br>Everybody know we got the birds on the truck load <br>Fuck with Glizzy Gang and Migos shoot ya like a free throw <br>Everybody know she don't want nothin' but a blue bankroll <br>Everybody know young nigga, boss nigga, head huncho <br>Head huncho, head huncho <br>'Bout the blue bankroll, we'll cut your head off, head huncho <br>Head huncho, head huncho <br>Young nigga, young nigga, flexed up, bossed up, head honcho <br><br>Bitch my name is Young Jefe <br>I got the OG and the ratchet <br>God damn ATL too happy <br>Pull up on yo ass like a taxi <br>I am not the one to worry with a problem <br>Boy yo ass gotta run <br>Ram truck with the shooters in the trunk <br>And they dressed up like a nun <br>Quavo said we don't need label <br>Young rich niggas we stable <br>Can I borrow some sugar Miss Mable <br>We in the bando with no cable <br>The hood they treat me like Jesus <br>Breakin' one out in a grey coupe <br>I think I'm John Gotti in grapefruit <br>I hop out the Porsche in a grey suit <br><br>Everybody know we got the birds on the truck load <br>Fuck with Glizzy Gang and Migos shoot ya like a free throw <br>Everybody know she don't want nothin' but a blue bankroll <br>Everybody know young nigga, boss nigga, head huncho <br>Head huncho, head huncho <br>'Bout the blue bankroll, we'll cut your head off, head huncho <br>Head huncho, head huncho <br>Young nigga, young nigga, flexed up, bossed up, head honcho <br><br>Head huncho, they calling me Pablo <br>Italian plug, eating Maggiano's <br>Pull out the chopper, knock em down like dominos <br>Spinning my wrist around the pot like a merry go <br>It's cartel, when it comes to dawgs, you get knocked out <br>Bullets the same size as a golf ball <br>You niggas is bitchin' and my niggas they pull up extentions <br>They hit you fuck niggas you gonna need stitches <br>45 in my britches, you niggas been talking that life <br>When you know you ain't seen it <br>Giuseppe steppin', got me walkin' on lizards <br>Ice on the top of my bezel, a blizzard <br>Walk in the mall, I can buy what I want <br>Keep down the cryin', I kidnap his aunt <br>I'm a big dog and you lil niggas runts <br>Beat em with the pistols, smoke em like joints <br>Laser beam sit on his head, it's on point <br>Rubbin' money in my hand like its ointment <br>When I talk to the boss make em appointment <br>Can't trap on my block, fuck nigga get extorted <br>Fuckin' your bitch, better go talk to Maury <br>Reptile my Louboutins, walkin' safari <br>Alley oop dunkin yo bitch like Charles Barkley <br>44 bulldog, don't make it start barking <br><br>Everybody know we got the birds on the truck load <br>Fuck with Glizzy Gang and Migos shoot ya like a free throw <br>Everybody know she don't want nothin' but a blue bankroll <br>Everybody know young nigga bought me a head huncho <br>Head huncho, head huncho <br>'Bout the blue bankroll, we'll cut your head off, head huncho <br>Head huncho, head huncho <br>Young nigga, young nigga, flexed up, bossed up, head honcho]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Head Huncho (Feat. Migos, Quavo, Offset)" label="Head Huncho (Feat. Migos, Quavo, Offset)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/U_Hear_Me/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - U Hear Me - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/U_Hear_Me/" title="Shy Glizzy - U Hear Me - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Uh <br>I hustle <br>I hustle <br>And they goin' respect this cuz niggas ain't hustlin' <br>You hear me <br>Uh <br>Real nigga though <br>You hear me <br>I hustle <br>I hustle <br>And they goin' respect this cuz niggas ain't hustlin' <br>You hear me <br><br>While they havin' fun <br>I be in the field <br>Fuck throwin' ones <br>Bitch I gotta pay for milk <br>I had to cop a foreign <br>Had to see how it feel <br>Still ain't got a license <br>Strapped, no seatbelts <br>Runnin' with some niggas <br>And they swear that they down <br>Mama been warned me <br>She said Son they some clowns <br>Niggas get paranoid <br>When they hear some sounds <br>Hope we don't get jammed <br>Or my ass going' down <br>And you don't gotta snake me <br>Cuz I am a man <br>I hate to break it down <br>But everybody ain't the man <br>Niggas love me down <br>Cuz we came from the sand <br>Now we can't even get down <br>Cuz that shit might hurt my brand <br><br>You hear me <br>These niggas don't hustle <br>I hustle <br>You hear me <br>They don't hear me though <br>Aw <br><br>Moms trying to move <br>Baby bro need a car <br>So I gotta go hard <br>Baby boy be a star <br>Im niggas way out <br>But they want me in a box <br>From what I recall <br>It was just me and the Glock <br>Glizzy gang <br>You ain't a glizzy <br>If you ain't got a glizzy <br>How you a glizzy <br>And you ain't shot a glizzy <br>You hear me <br>They tripping' <br>They silly <br>How you broke nigga <br>You be with Glizzy <br>You hear me <br>Come on man <br>2011 I was getting on the bus <br>Beefin' with the world <br>Could've got my ass bust <br>Tried to give my niggas something different <br>Called trust <br>They actin' all stuck up <br>Like a niggas ain't just touch <br>What the fuck <br><br>I'm outta here <br>You hear me <br>I don't know about these niggas <br>But I'm outta here <br>You hear me]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="U Hear Me" label="U Hear Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Going_Thru_It_Feat_Boosie_Baddass/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Going Thru It (Feat. Boosie Baddass) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Going_Thru_It_Feat_Boosie_Baddass/" title="Shy Glizzy - Going Thru It (Feat. Boosie Baddass) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been going through some shit <br>Don't ask me why I be with the niggas that I be with <br>Or why I ain't posting pictures <br>That's cause I'm still in the trenches <br>Don't ask me why a nigga didn't blow up or why I didn't show up <br>Fuck all that bullshit I'ma po' up <br>Going through some shit, I've been going thru some shit <br>Lately I've been going through some shit <br>I'm going through some shit <br><br>I think I need to get away my bitch she needed time <br>And I just missed another plate, that mean I lost some M's <br>I know people have said , I'm sorry if I lost some fans <br>But y'all plan that shit with Ben, so go and take that up with him <br>But then I told myself man I really need some help <br>Gotta get that wealth, I can't end up on a shelf <br>Street hottest youngin', make them bad bitches melt <br>Style knock em out, swag champ with my belt <br>I've been going thru it, I've been going stupid <br>The pack ain't too good, fuck it am gonna still move it <br>Say they don't like my music but they still gonna groove it <br>Got a gun and don't use it, nigga fuck is you stupid <br><br>Don't ask me why I be with the niggas that I be with <br>Or why I ain't posting pictures <br>That's cause I'm still in the trenches <br>Don't ask me why a nigga didn't blow up or why I didn't show up <br>Fuck all that bullshit I'ma po' up <br>Going through some shit, I've been going thru some shit <br>Lately I've been going through some shit <br>I'm going through some shit <br><br>I've been going through some shit, still pissin' in a cup <br>Several people on my place, sometimes I want to get the fuck <br>These expressions on mah face from trying to beat this hard time <br>On parole still be with mah nigga charge with hard crime <br>Feel like they cursing me niggas promise they gonna murder me <br>So i keep black ricky his extension is dirty piece <br>Baby mamma drama don't wanna argue i want peace <br>Gee mah daughter a teenager hope she don't fall for niggas like me <br>Look don't even talk to me am in mah zone <br>You gonna talk behind mah back when i leave so leave me alone <br>Mind yo bidness make yo move get out mah way keep it pushin <br>Real niggas go thru it cuz niggas pussies <br><br>Don't ask me why I be with the niggas that I be with <br>Or why I ain't posting pictures <br>That's cause I'm still in the trenches <br>Don't ask me why a nigga didn't blow up or why I didn't show up <br>Fuck all that bullshit I'ma po' up <br>Going through some shit, I've been going thru some shit <br>Lately I've been going through some shit <br>I'm going through some shit]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Going Thru It (Feat. Boosie Baddass)" label="Going Thru It (Feat. Boosie Baddass)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Winning_Feat_Zaytoven/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Winning (Feat. Zaytoven) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Winning_Feat_Zaytoven/" title="Shy Glizzy - Winning (Feat. Zaytoven) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Smoking out the bad wood busting in the church <br>Gun squad pull up and we hoppin ova fences <br>A nigga play wit my nigga we poppin expenses <br>Put you ass out and get you fuck out mah mansions <br>Mah niggas got sense but try niggas they ain't livin <br>Hear they lost the case but we still motherfucking winning <br>It hurt they lil heart to see us motherfucking winning <br>I can't see them niggas they ain't mother fucking winning <br>Smoking all that pounds and i'm loaded with that rounds <br>Mah younger he a hound hell smoke you ounce <br>Don't ask me bout em clowns i don't know what you talkin bout <br><br>Real D C mah whole family from the south <br>They see me out here solo they just wanna take a photo <br>Soon i say yo yo gigi shooting at yo photo <br>Everyone have bolo take em way back to the hobo <br>Plugin in they goggle spending they money on them rubbers <br>Will blue honnies mah destine tusung ain't go do nothin <br>They know am go shoot something <br>I never have nothing and they never go stop somethin <br>I can't play they game cuz i already won <br><br>Smoking out the bad wood busting in the church <br>Gun squad pull up and we hoppin ova fences <br>A nigga play wit my nigga we poppin expenses <br>Put you ass out and get you fuck out mah mansions <br>Mah niggas got sense but try niggas they ain't livin <br>Hear they lost the case but we still motherfucking winning <br>It hurt they lil heart to see us motherfucking winning <br>I can't see them niggas they ain't mother fucking winning <br>Smoking all that pounds and i'm loaded with that rounds <br>Mah younger he a hound hell smoke you ounce <br>Don't ask me bout em clowns i don't know what you talkin bout <br><br>I pray for better days i don't smoke no purple hays <br>Put her on her face i know i got to fuck that waist <br>Don't let Get that chopper or i might make a mistake <br>Placka placka chalk done know daddy being great <br>These niggas looking weak always what's the T <br>They scared to get in the street so they rather chase the freak <br>Couple hundred G's on me they metal detectors go beeb <br>Yo bitch think i'm lookin sweet not bitch you know am looking sweet <br>When you was being a rapper i was trying to be richie porter <br>Here real chappiego have that money for that lawyer <br>George town with mah buyers now we got that water <br>Pull up to mah block and i'll make sure somebody serve yah <br><br>Smoking out the bad wood busting in the church <br>Gun squad pull up and we hoppin ova fences <br>A nigga play wit my nigga we poppin expenses <br>Put you ass out and get you fuck out mah mansions <br>Mah niggas got sense but try niggas they ain't livin <br>Hear they lost the case but we still motherfucking winning <br>It hurt they lil heart to see us motherfucking winning <br>I can't see them niggas they ain't mother fucking winning <br>Smoking all that pounds and i'm loaded with that rounds <br>Mah younger he a hound hell smoke you ounce <br>Don't ask me bout em clowns i don't know what you talkin bout]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Winning (Feat. Zaytoven)" label="Winning (Feat. Zaytoven)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/3_Milli/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - 3 Milli - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/3_Milli/" title="Shy Glizzy - 3 Milli - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This shit ain't easy <br>Y'all already know how I'm rockin' <br>Tre Seven <br>Bang Bang <br>And nigga it's the Glizzy Gang <br><br>I'm coolin' with my glizzies glizzies, bow <br>And bitch we run the city we run the city <br>Nigga I'm 3 milli aww, I'mma catch your grandmother and shoot her in her titties blew blew blew blew <br>Don't be fuckin' with my glizzies glizzies bad boys like Diddy BOW <br>Keep talkin' bout designer lil nigga you filthy bang bang <br>You keep that shit 3 hunna bang bang I keep that shit 3 milli bang bang <br>Catch you ridin' around in that Audi I'mma hit you with this semi skurt BOW <br><br>Chief Keef don't wanna be him nahh this bitch nigga made me tweet him aww <br>I can't wait to see him can't wait you keep it 3 hunna, I keep this shit 3 M's bang bang <br>You sound like you 40 aww and you only 17 years old lil nigga <br>Nigga I gotta 40 BOW I'm only 19 and ballin' like I'm D Rose swoosh <br>You told me I'm tweakin tweakin nigga watch what you tweetin' watch what you tweetin' <br>All my belts designer, do you wanna Fendi beatin' aww <br>How you gon tweet a diss song and you don't even know me don't know me <br>Sosa got himself in this so now Sosa owe me <br>Talkin' 'bout a soft ass DC nigga huh bet you won't come and do no shows in DC nigga never <br>I'm the streets hottest youngin FIRE and it's 'bout to get chilly aww <br>Fuck a 3 hunna nigga I'm 3 milli bang bang <br><br>I'm coolin' with my glizzies glizzies, bow <br>And bitch we run the city we run the city <br>Nigga I'm 3 milli aww I'mma catch your grandmother and shoot her in her titties blew blew blew blew <br>Don't be fuckin' with my glizzies glizzies bad boys like Diddy BOW <br>Keep talkin' bout designer lil nigga you filthy bang bang <br>You keep that shit 3 hunna bang bang I keep that shit 3 milli bang bang <br>Catch you ridin' around in that Audi I'mma hit you with this semi skurt BOW <br><br>You wanna go to war Come on You wanna go to war We take you to war, okay <br><br>Ion like <br>Sneak Dissers that's that shit I don't like <br>Ay Keef, I thought you ain't like sneak disses either nigga <br>Fake ass young nigga <br>Look <br><br>Big 30s that's that shit I really like BOW <br>Lil dirty niggas, that's that shit I don't like I don't like <br>Beefin' all on twitter, that's that shit I don't like don't like <br>Ain't even livin' already tryna lose ya life aww <br>Gucci with tennis shoes, that's that shit I don't like don't like <br>I got on Jimmy Choo's, that's that shit your bitch like bitch like <br>Dick riding, that's that shit I don't like don't like <br>Look up to niggas eatin' ass shawdy you a dike ugh <br>Nigga you ain't no migo why the fuck they call you Sosa Sosa <br>In jail we played spades, bluffin' niggas played poker what you know <br>Stop talkin' like you out here, nigga you on house arrest <br>Run up in yo house and lay yo whole fuckin' house to rest blew blew blew blew <br>Young street nigga, all I do is get money <br>I don't like these niggas, I think these niggas funny <br>I never been to Chicago, but my favorite team the Bulls my bulls <br>Ain't eatin' off this rap shit, my trap keep me full mm <br>You want 5 m's for a verse verse that's my shoes and shirt shirt <br>Give my young nigga 5 hunna, he a put you in a hearse get at me <br>Had my niggas fuckin' with you, now they out to get you to get cha <br>I just shitted, now gon spend 3 hunna on some tissue aww <br><br>Ion likeee <br>Ion likeee <br>Bang Bang]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="3 Milli" label="3 Milli"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/White_Girl_Feat_Lil_Durk/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - White Girl (Feat. Lil Durk) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/White_Girl_Feat_Lil_Durk/" title="Shy Glizzy - White Girl (Feat. Lil Durk) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In love with a white girl <br>She's soft as powder <br>I get hard around her <br>I whip her right here <br>She French, I'm a coke boy <br>Don't fuck with broke boys <br>She know I'm a dope boy <br>She said get me dope, boy <br><br>I seen 15 bricks today <br>You make 15 bucks an hour <br>Robbin ass niggas in the kitchen, playing with flour <br>I got all this power, you a fucking coward <br>My bitch come from France, oh, she like my Eiffel Tower <br>Ooww <br>My plug got them blocks , just like LuLu <br>I supply your block, I give you work and tell you do you <br>You no fool, you know that the Glizzy Gang will shoot you <br>We're not backing down, we not run from shit but woo woo <br>Cocaine, that's my bitch, we not run from shit but woo woo <br>Cocaine, that's my bitch, oh, she made me rich <br>I wanna be like rich these niggas wanna be like mitch <br>In the kitchen, when I cook a wankle wankle wip <br>Free my dawg they book 'em just like Michael Michael Vick <br><br>In love with a white girl <br>She's soft as powder <br>I get hard around her <br>I whip her right here <br>She French, I'm a coke boy <br>Don't fuck with broke boys <br>She know I'm a dope boy <br>She said get me dope, boy <br><br>Trips from Puerto Rico <br>Fucking with my Migos <br>Bitch, they sing like Ne Yo <br>This shit do not come with cheat codes <br>Lil' over seas ho <br>Wish I had a trio <br>Feisty like a lion, I forgot she was a Leo <br>She come from the slums <br>Grew up on first of the month <br>Know how to shoot a gun <br>Her father fought in Vietnam <br><br>She so fucking fine, yeah, she so fucking fine <br>She have a lot of niggas <br>She say I'm the dopest one <br><br>I got a lot of guns <br>I got a lot of paper <br>Won't nobody find ya body <br>Boy I got A lot of acres <br>I give these niggas tips <br>Ooh yall shouldve been some waiters <br>My Wrists like dirty checks <br>Ooh I shouldve been A banker <br><br>In love with a white girl <br>She's soft as powder <br>I get hard around her <br>I whip her right here <br>She French, I'm a coke boy <br>Don't fuck with broke boys <br>She know I'm a dope boy <br>She said get me dope, boy]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="White Girl (Feat. Lil Durk)" label="White Girl (Feat. Lil Durk)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/The_Plan_Feat_Zaytoven/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - The Plan (Feat. Zaytoven) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/The_Plan_Feat_Zaytoven/" title="Shy Glizzy - The Plan (Feat. Zaytoven) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All this money out here why fuck is these niggas playin <br>These niggas in mah way I need a mansion in Atlanta <br>And if I fuck with you Ima throw you extra grams <br>Please tell your favorite rapper to stay off my Instagram <br>I don't have a plan i just know i want a benz <br>Why is niggas playin' I don't think I understand <br>Nobody can't owe me shit I need mah money in mah hand <br>It's time to sit the team down and ask them what they plan <br><br>Ok hald up stop planning need to put on yo minds <br>Niggas wants to diss me put on they librans <br>You don't wanna shoot me you just wanna take that stand <br>Trick me out mah future tryin' to put me in that can <br>Bitch a not no stake block shout out benny C <br>One that gives mah tatoos am not scared a needles <br>Pull up on a bare hoe scoot i got mah bidness <br>Run and make his ass blow boom does it equal <br>Now they call me big glizzy i come from the trenches <br>Mah niggas got big glizzy promise they gonna play fare <br>Aren't even safe here you might catch a case here <br>Keep it on yo waist you might get erase here <br><br>All this money out here why fuck is these niggas playin <br>These niggas in mah way I need a mansion in Atlanta <br>And if I fuck with you Ima throw you extra grams <br>Please tell your favorite rapper to stay off my Instagram <br>I don't have a plan i just know i want a benz <br>Why is niggas playin' I don't think I understand <br>Nobody can't owe me shit I need mah money in mah hand <br>It's time to sit the team down and ask them what they plan <br><br>See I can hear my track also i can hit the bank <br>You can keep the hood give me the big house with the lake <br>Flyin in there touch that down almost put the pain <br>Don't ask me if mah diamonds is VVS its fucking fake <br>My gucci bad as fuck we look like J LO and puff <br>I told her that if she love me then loyalty is a must <br>I get that money back and let them suckers chase the buck <br>Black killers play the front so get your niggas out the cut <br>And nigga what i just hit a lick we up <br>All these crispy hundreds damn i got a paper cut <br>Hundred on my truck i just put a hundred up <br>Fuck a hundred out there act like i don't give a fuck <br><br>All this money out here why fuck is these niggas playin <br>These niggas in mah way I need a mansion in Atlanta <br>And if I fuck with you Ima throw you extra grams <br>Please tell your favorite rapper to stay off my Instagram <br>I don't have a plan i just know i want a benz <br>Why is niggas playin' I don't think I understand <br>Nobody can't owe me shit I need mah money in mah hand <br>It's time to sit the team down and ask them what they plan]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="The Plan (Feat. Zaytoven)" label="The Plan (Feat. Zaytoven)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Better_Days_Feat_Goo_Glizzy/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Better Days (Feat. Goo Glizzy) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:10:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:10:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Better_Days_Feat_Goo_Glizzy/" title="Shy Glizzy - Better Days (Feat. Goo Glizzy) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I heard somebody say life is like a battery, gotta have ya positives gotta have ya negatives aye <br><br>Better days aye <br>I was thugging at a young agee uht uht uht uht uh <br>Pull up on ya block and make a earth quake <br>I know niggas tryna murk me, i don't go no where with out my 30 bitches acting thirsty <br>Im just tryna see my nigga birthday <br><br>Niggas hate me in the worse way, and bitch and a murder case ain't the worst case <br>Who the fuck mad up hard times anyway and lord knows i pray for better days And fuck you cowards tried to take my life away <br>Cause bitch I been thuggin since the 1st grade <br>Lil nigga rep my turf just like my first name <br>Make me pull up on yo block and make it hurricane <br>No mistake , I'ma shooter you a fake <br>30 on me, nigga you could go today <br>But I'm just tryina see my next birthday <br><br>Better days aye <br>I was thugging at a young agee uht uht uht uht uh <br>Pull up on ya block and make a earth quake <br>I know niggas tryna murk me, i don't go no where with out my 30 bitches acting thirsty <br>Im just tryna see my nigga birthday <br><br>Little bitch they call me Jefe <br>Driver scoop me up in that Escalade <br>These niggas tryina test me <br>So shit bout to get messy <br>All these niggas acting tough now <br>Till they get hit with these slug rounds <br>Glizzy glizzy bitch they show me love now <br>I got the drugs I know the plug now <br>I was out there on that corner <br>Band camp, like Broner <br>I got what you want now <br>Baby I can turn you to a stoner <br><br>Better days aye <br>I was thugging at a young agee uht uht uht uht uh <br>Pull up on ya block and make a earth quake <br>I know niggas tryna murk me, i don't go no where with out my 30 bitches acting thirsty <br>Im just tryna see my nigga birthday]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Better Days (Feat. Goo Glizzy)" label="Better Days (Feat. Goo Glizzy)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/John_Wall_Feat_Lil_Mouse/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - John Wall (Feat. Lil Mouse) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:11:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:11:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/John_Wall_Feat_Lil_Mouse/" title="Shy Glizzy - John Wall (Feat. Lil Mouse) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hundred thousand up in my wall racks <br>Fuck I look like signin' Let me sign y'all <br>Bitch I know you better answer when the don call <br>Or I'ma hit my second bitch like John Wall <br>John Wall, John Wall <br>I'm ballin' on these niggas like I'm John Wall <br>John Wall, John Wall <br>I keep me 2 pistols, call me John Wall <br><br>All these niggas stallers, I'm a damn starter <br>Big Glizzy, baby, I'm a shot caller <br>All my niggas look like they just left from ball hoggin' <br>And your niggas look like they just left the beauty parlor <br>It don't cost a fuckin' cent to keep it real <br>Shit don't make no sense, these niggas ain't street for real <br>Young boy you so ill, shoot your ass like Bill <br>Glizzy Gang no chill, better keep your steel <br>I'm not committed, I got 2 bitches <br>I got a couple send me nude pictures <br>They say don't no nigga kick it the way you kick it <br>I think I might hop in the shoe business <br><br>Hundred thousand up in my wall racks <br>Fuck I look like signin' Let me sign y'all <br>Bitch I know you better answer when the don call <br>Or I'ma hit my second bitch like John Wall <br>John Wall, John Wall <br>I'm ballin' on these niggas like I'm John Wall <br>John Wall, John Wall <br>I keep me 2 pistols, call me John Wall <br><br>Fuck I look like signin' Let me sign y'all <br>All these diamonds in my chain, I just might blind y'all <br>I keep 2 shooters with me, call me John Wall <br>You wanna act, he grab that MAC and he gon' blam y'all <br>Magic Johnson in that clip but he let 9 off <br>All these shooters on my roster shoot like John Wall <br>Me and Glizzy in that 'Rari with the top off <br>Stephen Curry and that Glock 4 shoot your top off <br>I got a hundred Franklins in my Balmain <br>In my hood, them shorties shootin' like a gun range <br>Niggas runnin', hoppin' gates when them guns aim <br>Ridin' 'round, blowin' gas, call it propane <br><br>Hundred thousand up in my wall racks <br>Fuck I look like signin' Let me sign y'all <br>Bitch I know you better answer when the don call <br>Or I'ma hit my second bitch like John Wall <br>John Wall, John Wall <br>I'm ballin' on these niggas like I'm John Wall <br>John Wall, John Wall <br>I keep me 2 pistols, call me John Wall]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="John Wall (Feat. Lil Mouse)" label="John Wall (Feat. Lil Mouse)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Free_The_Gang_Feat_Plies/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Free The Gang (Feat. Plies) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:11:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:11:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Free_The_Gang_Feat_Plies/" title="Shy Glizzy - Free The Gang (Feat. Plies) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nigga tell me earlier 'yea man im trynna <br>Um I'm trynna alleviate something' I say Get <br>Yo bitchass off the phone, don't ever call us <br>Talking about you trynna squash something <br>For us, Nigga we a we on't do no squashing nothing <br>You heard me <br>Yeaaah <br>Im trynna alleviate something because this a this a life <br>Or death situation here, What you so what you <br>Trynna say <br>Yeaaah <br>Damn, nigga better off fighting aids or cancer than <br>Fucking wit anything over this way, You heard me <br>Laughs <br>Love yall niggas doe, Ima hit y'all tomar these <br>People finna' lock us down you heard me <br>Yeaaah <br>Damn man, Ya'll stay tight out there man <br>Man, Leave a message for them people man <br>All y'all gotta do is put suspenders on them big slack <br>Ass nigggas, I told you what they out here doing, slackin' <br>You hear me, Put them suspenders on they asses <br>And keep em' up you heard me <br>Yeaaah <br>Thats what you gah' do you gah' preach to em' <br>You heard me <br>Yeaaah <br>They on't say amen, Yea I know what to do, Baptize they ass <br>Hahaha <br>Laughs Forreal man, Love y'all man <br>Love you too <br><br>You see the thing about these niggas <br>Yelling real nigga this and real nigga that <br>Most of these fuck niggas dont know the definition <br>Of a real motherfuckin' nigga doe <br>See I gots to give it up to these young niggas <br>Thats taking penitentiary nigga <br>Niggas in the same outfit for 3 days on the block <br>Trying to get that set, nigga <br><br>You threw your life away, threw your life away <br>You was just here yesterday, you went and threw your life away <br>They took your life away, took your life away <br>Man I hope and pray the streets don't take my life away <br>x2 <br><br>Screaming Free the Gang <br>Y'all don't feel my pain <br>Fuck your bling bling, they got all my boys in chains <br>Every single one of them done bust a nigga brains <br>Nigga Bang Bang, we the fucking murder team <br>Who would've thought it all started with some throwback topics We had some BB guns we ain't never used to wrestle <br>Y'all niggas is rap dudes, we know that is not you <br>We not gon' attack you, someone just gon clap you <br>I don't fuck with no one else, I'm from 37th street <br>Out here thuggin' by myself, don't nobody mess with me <br>We at different pedigree, you can't get the recipe <br>I am living so fast you can't even get next to me <br><br>You threw your life away, threw your life away <br>You was just here yesterday, you went and threw your life away <br>They took your life away, took your life away <br>Man I hope and pray the streets don't take my life away <br>x2 <br><br>Niggas ask me erry' day, nigga <br>When I'm gon leave da streets alone <br>Told them niggas never nigga <br>I'm tryin to bring C Murder home <br>Three of my closest partners gone <br>Added all their time up, 122 years <br>Think my niggas been lyin' or somethin' <br>I used to fear da feds, nigga <br>No, not no fucking more <br>Cuz they the ones that's roping niggas <br>You pussy niggas, who telling tho <br>Same nigga that is poppin' bottles <br>Same nigga that is riding foreign <br>Same nigga that playin real <br>Be the same nigga thats tellin on ya <br>Salute to the niggas who didn't tell <br>All the niggas worldwide <br>Never respected a fuck nigga <br>The ones who snitched to cut they time <br>Leave me and my niggas alone <br>Let the real niggas ball <br>You want to tell somethin' <br>Tell the world that you a fuck nigga dawg <br><br>You threw your life away, threw your life away <br>You was just here yesterday, you went and threw your life away <br>They took your life away, took your life away <br>Man I hope and pray the streets don't take my life away <br>x2 <br><br>Where are the damn clothes <br>I go away one second <br>They say the streets ain't got no paper <br>I see it now <br>Glizzy Gang, bang bang <br>Man I hope and pray the streets, don't take my life away <br>Man I hope, I pray the streets don't take my life awa]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Free The Gang (Feat. Plies)" label="Free The Gang (Feat. Plies)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Awwsome_Remix_Feat_2_Chainz_AAP_Rocky/</id><title>Shy Glizzy - Awwsome Remix (Feat. 2 Chainz, A$AP Rocky) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:11:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:11:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Shy_Glizzy/Awwsome_Remix_Feat_2_Chainz_AAP_Rocky/" title="Shy Glizzy - Awwsome Remix (Feat. 2 Chainz, A$AP Rocky) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Swish, I'm balling <br>I'm so awesome <br>Old bitch keep calling <br>She think I'm awesome <br>Jackboys wanna rob me <br>I'm so awesome <br>Out here like a possum <br>I'm so, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br><br>Oh my fucking God, pull up in that, oh my gosh <br>You niggas so soft, get that arrow out your heart <br>You can be a boss or you can get a job <br>You do not go hard, you's a motherfucking fraud <br>Young Jefe, I got boats you can sail away <br>Broke boy, you are not my friend, you need to get away <br>Call up my driver tell him scoop me in his Escalate <br>Night Sunday, bet 1000 bucks on Tampa Bay <br>Got a lot of spots like a motherfucking cheetah <br>All we do is trap, my OGs still got beepers <br>Bad little kitty momma took my ass to jeepers <br>Tryna get a ticket like no money in the meter <br><br>Swish, I'm balling <br>I'm so awesome <br>Old bitch keep calling <br>She think I'm awesome <br>Jackboys wanna rob me <br>I'm so awesome <br>Out here like a possum <br>I'm so, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br><br>Cell phone ringing, trap bunkin <br>In DC getting money, DMV one hundred <br>Hair hanging down to my stomach <br>And I'm making play like DeShaun <br>And I'm ballin' out like John Wall <br>I just brought me a pound of gas <br>I'mma smoke joints till it's all gone <br>Okay awwsome, in a Porsche eating lobster <br>2 chains on with crosses, lipstick stain on boxers <br>I ain't with the losses, the process is nonsense <br>Whip, sit in all set, might give her the sausage <br>Me and Skooly rock, top down, toolie cocked <br>Hit her with the dick, leave her with a beauty mark <br>She say we all the same, I say bitch come hit this reefer <br>She say that I don't like them niggas, I say I don't like 'em either <br><br>Swish, I'm balling <br>I'm so awesome <br>Old bitch keep calling <br>She think I'm awesome <br>Jackboys wanna rob me <br>I'm so awesome <br>Out here like a possum <br>I'm so, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br><br>A$AP tatted on my belly like I'm Makaveli <br>That peanut butter product probably why they acting jelly <br>You actin' petty, packin' daily cause my chain heavy <br>Flaco be in DC like I'm Wayne Perry <br>I beat that, speak that awwsome <br>She wanna have a foursome <br>She know more friends so call some <br>Call them often for the moresome <br>Exhaust 'em, boss 'em, toss 'em <br>Loss 'em like abortion <br>Window shopping notion <br>Wasted times important <br>Problems with it cost 'em <br>All you boys fugazy, I got hoes for days <br>My rugged lookin' J's bout as stainless as my braids <br>But I'm paid, shout glizzy <br>DMV that's NYC, TX, LA we talk fly shit <br>Get off my dick if you don't like this <br>Cause I'm like <br><br>Swish, I'm balling <br>I'm so awesome <br>Old bitch keep calling <br>She think I'm awesome <br>Jackboys wanna rob me <br>I'm so awesome <br>Out here like a possum <br>I'm so, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome <br>I'm so fucking awesome, I'm so awesome]]></content><category term="Shy Glizzy" label="Shy Glizzy"/><category term="Awwsome Remix (Feat. 2 Chainz, A$AP Rocky)" label="Awwsome Remix (Feat. 2 Chainz, A$AP Rocky)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vadi_Akbar/Tanya_Jadi_Rasa/</id><title>Vadi Akbar - Tanya Jadi Rasa - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:11:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:11:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vadi_Akbar/Tanya_Jadi_Rasa/" title="Vadi Akbar - Tanya Jadi Rasa - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[sudah lama kupercaya <br>cinta hanya sebuah kata <br>tak nyata makna didalamnya <br><br>dusta cipta adam dan hawa <br>dan kau datang mengubah hampir segalanya <br>karna hadirmu membawa tanya <br>ku bermimpi dengan mata yang terbuka <br>ku melayang diatas awan tanpa terbang <br>ku tlah jatuh cinta tanpa kah harus berusaha <br>kau ubah tanya menjadi rasa <br>dududu <br>kucari arti dari semua ini <br>rasa tinggi karna kau disini <br>kau beri kesempatan hati <br>tuk kembali mencintai <br>dan kau datang mengubah hampir segalanya <br>karna hadirmu membawa tanya <br>ku bermimpi dengan mata yang terbuka <br>ku melayang diatas awan tanpa terbang <br>ku tlah jatuh cinta tanpa kau harus berusaha <br>kau ubah tanya menjadi nyata <br>lalala lalala lalala lalala <br>huhuhuhu uuuu <br>kau ubah tanya menjadi rasa <br>ku bermimpi dengan mata yang terbuka <br>ku melayang diatas awan tanpa terbang <br>uwoooo <br>aku melayang <br>ku tlah jatu cinta tanpa kau harus berusaha <br>huu oooo <br>kau mengubah segalanya kau ubah tanya menjadi rasa <br>houoo ooo]]></content><category term="Vadi Akbar" label="Vadi Akbar"/><category term="Tanya Jadi Rasa" label="Tanya Jadi Rasa"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eny/ET_이소라/</id><title>Eny - E.T (이.소.라) - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:11:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:11:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Eny/ET_%EC%9D%B4%EC%86%8C%EB%9D%BC/" title="Eny - E.T (이.소.라) - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[항상 생각해왔어 <br>느낌이 어떨지 <br>변한다는 게 본다는 게 <br>수많은 해와 달이 지나 <br>너도 점점 달라져가겠지 <br>난 여전히 그대론데 <br>떠나 보내는 게 <br>그걸 봐야 된다는 게 <br>한번이 아닌 평생인데 <br>어떻게 참아야 해 <br>그걸 어떻게 참아야 해 <br>Dear god please please help me <br>Would you please gift of death to me <br>혼자인 것 같아 같이 있어도 난 <br>왜 먼 일을 저 먼 곳을 <br>나만 상상하고 있는 걸까 <br>혼자일 것 같아 같이 살아도 난 <br>항상 그랬듯 이미 겪었듯 <br>나는 왜 나만 그래야만 하는 건지 <br>맺어짐의 반복 <br>그 맺음의 끝은 <br>끝맺음인 것을 <br>들어냈을 때쯤 <br>친구들의 웃음소리는 <br>각자의 사연 뒤로 숨고 <br>영원을 약속했던 <br>그녀의 작은 손도 <br>이제는 내 손 안에선 <br>온기를 지웠고 <br>또다시 반복하고 <br>Dear god please please help me <br>Would you please gift of death to me <br>혼자인 것 같아 같이 있어도 난 <br>왜 먼 일을 저 먼 곳을 <br>나만 상상하고 있는 걸까 <br>혼자일 것 같아 같이 살아도 난 <br>항상 그랬듯 이미 겪었듯 <br>나는 왜 나만 그래야만 하는 건지 <br>같이 있어도 난 <br>같이 있어도 난 <br>혼자인 것 같아 같이 있어도 난 <br>왜 먼 일을 저 먼 곳을 <br>나만 상상하고 있는 걸까 <br>혼자일 것 같아 같이 살아도 난 <br>같이 살아도 난 <br>]]></content><category term="Eny" label="Eny"/><category term="E.T (이.소.라)" label="E.T (이.소.라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/원라스트찬스/할렐루야_2017/</id><title>원라스트찬스 - 할렐루야 2017 - lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-09T00:11:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-09T00:11:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%90%EB%9D%BC%EC%8A%A4%ED%8A%B8%EC%B0%AC%EC%8A%A4/%ED%95%A0%EB%A0%90%EB%A3%A8%EC%95%BC_2017/" title="원라스트찬스 - 할렐루야 2017 - lyric"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>예수님 홀로 십자가 지셨네 <br>그러나 그 안에 <br>하나님 함께 하시었네 <br>예수님 홀로 기도 하시었네 <br>그러나 그 안에 <br>하나님 함께 하시었네 <br>너희는 내 안에서 평안을 누리라 <br>세상은 너희를 핍박하나 <br>너희는 강하고 담대할지어다 <br>내가 세상을 이겼노라 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>우리는 홀로 세상을 살아가네 <br>그러나 내 안에 <br>예수님 함께 하시었네 <br>우리는 홀로 내 아픔 감추었네 <br>그러나 내 안에 <br>예수님 함께 하시었네 <br>너희는 내 안에서 평안을 누리라 <br>세상은 너희를 핍박하나 <br>너희는 강하고 담대할지어다 <br>내가 세상을 이겼노라 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>할렐루 할렐루 할렐루 할렐루야 <br>]]></content><category term="원라스트찬스" label="원라스트찬스"/><category term="할렐루야 2017" label="할렐루야 2017"/></entry></feed>