<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:48:27+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다비치/그런_적_있나요/</id><title>다비치 - 그런 적 있나요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:24:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:24:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%B9%84%EC%B9%98/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B0_%EC%A0%81_%EC%9E%88%EB%82%98%EC%9A%94/" title="다비치 - 그런 적 있나요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잠이 드는 일이 마치 <br>깨어나는 일이 마치 <br>처음처럼 낯선 기분 <br>그대도 그런 적 있나요 <br>괜찮냐는 친구 전화에 그만 <br>선 채로 울음이 터져서 <br>하염없이 밉다가 <br>못 견디게 보고파 <br>하루에도 몇 번씩 그댈 <br>또 밀어내고 다시 끌어안죠 <br>이별이 원래 이런가요 <br>숨을 쉬는 일이 문득 <br>물을 마시는 게 문득 <br>아무 의미 없는 기분 <br>그대도 그런 적 있나요 <br>사랑했던 모든 순간이 정말 <br>다 있었던 일 맞나 싶어서 <br>미워 하는 마음 반 <br>보고 싶은 마음 반 <br>잊고싶은 마음 반 어쩜 <br>다 잊혀질까 두려운 마음 반 <br>이별이 원래 이런가요 <br>이렇게 하염없이 밉다가 <br>못 견디게 보고파 <br>하루에도 몇 번씩 그대를 <br>또 밀어내고 다시 끌어안죠 <br>이별이 원래 이런가요 <br>그대도 그런 적 있나요 <br>]]></content><category term="다비치" label="다비치"/><category term="그런 적 있나요" label="그런 적 있나요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다비치/PET/</id><title>다비치 - PET - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:24:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:24:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%B9%84%EC%B9%98/PET/" title="다비치 - PET - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘됐지 뭐 <br>그저 너만 바라보기엔 <br>사랑할 게 너무 많아서 <br>바람은 따뜻한 걸 <br>너의 입김보다 더 <br>뭐 허전한 맘쯤 <br>가득 담은 한잔 커피면 <br>괜찮아 조금 쓰지만 <br>미운 네 모습보다 <br>충분히 달콤하니까 <br>I'm fine 이런 느낌 <br>사과할게 <br>미안 너 없이도 <br>행복해서 <br>잘됐지 뭐 <br>외롭기 싫어 널 만난 나 <br>똑같이 외롭다면 난 <br>왜 널 기다리면서 <br>애를 태워 내가 왜 <br>뭐가 모자라서 <br>그저 기다리는 사랑을 <br>더는 할 수 없어 떠나 난 <br>그래도 기억해줘 <br>난 너뿐이었단 걸 <br>너만 기다리던 나는 없어 <br>기분 좋은 오늘 이후로 <br>난 나와 사랑을 나눌게 <br>너와 걷던 이곳에서 <br>어쩌면 날 닮은 <br>사랑이 날 찾아올지도 <br>모른다는 예감을 만나 <br>함께 걷고 싶은 걸 <br>I'm fine 이런 느낌 <br>사과할게 <br>미안 너 없이도 <br>행복해서 <br>잘됐지 뭐 <br>외롭기 싫어 널 만난 나 <br>똑같이 외롭다면 난 <br>왜 널 기다리면서 <br>애를 태워 내가 왜 <br>뭐가 모자라서 <br>그저 기다리는 사랑을 <br>더는 할 수 없어 떠나 난 <br>그래도 기억해줘 <br>난 너뿐이었단 걸 <br>네가 돌아오기만 <br>기다리던 PET 같은 <br>그런 나는 더 이상 <br>거기 없어 미안해 <br>네가 돌아오기만 <br>기다리던 PET 같은 <br>그런 나는 더 이상 <br>거기 없어 미안해 <br>네가 돌아오기만 <br>기다리던 PET 같은 <br>그런 나는 더 이상 <br>거기 없어 미안해 <br>]]></content><category term="다비치" label="다비치"/><category term="PET" label="PET"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다비치/내_옆에_그대인_걸/</id><title>다비치 - 내 옆에 그대인 걸 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:24:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:24:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%B9%84%EC%B9%98/%EB%82%B4_%EC%98%86%EC%97%90_%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%9D%B8_%EA%B1%B8/" title="다비치 - 내 옆에 그대인 걸 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뒤척이면서 아등바등 <br>별 세우며 잠을 청해도 <br>반짝반짝 그대가 눈부셔 <br>밥을 먹든 커피 마시든 <br>TV 보든 웃다가 울든 <br>곁에 있듯 내 옆에 너인 걸 <br>울었어 너 떠나던 날 <br>남몰래 울었어 <br>눈물이 앞을 가려와 <br>비처럼 쏟아지던 바보야 <br>잊지마 잊지마 언제까지나 <br>사랑해 사랑해 언제까지나 <br>혼자든 둘이든 상관없어 <br>내 옆에 그대인 걸 <br>전부인 듯 마지막인 듯 <br>두 팔 벌려 내게 안기던 <br>정말 그댄 나를 잊었나요 <br>그래 나야 널 사랑한 <br>네가 사랑한 나였단 걸 <br>잊지 마요 나를 기억해줘 <br>울었어 너 떠나던 날 <br>남몰래 울었어 <br>눈물이 앞을 가려와 <br>비처럼 쏟아지던 바보야 <br>잊지마 잊지마 언제까지나 <br>사랑해 사랑해 언제까지나 <br>혼자든 둘이든 상관없어 <br>내 옆에 그대인 걸 <br>길다란 내 미련의 끝은 <br>꿈이었다고 누가 <br>내게 말해줘요 <br>널 만나러 간다 괜찮아 <br>아픈 추억으로 날 가득 채울게 <br>울었어 또 울었어 <br>더 크게 울었어 <br>눈물이 앞을 가려와 <br>휘청이며 헤메이는 바보야 <br>잊지마 잊지마 언제까지나 <br>사랑해 사랑해 언제까지나 <br>혼자든 둘이든 상관없어 <br>내 옆에 그대인 걸 <br>잊지마 잊지마 언제까지나 <br>사랑해 사랑해 언제까지나 <br>혼자든 둘이든 상관없어 <br>내 옆에 그대인 걸 <br>잊지마 잊지마 언제까지나 <br>사랑해 사랑해 언제까지나 <br>혼자든 둘이든 상관없어 <br>내 옆에 그대인 걸 <br>내 옆에 그대인 걸 <br>내 옆에 그대인 걸 <br>]]></content><category term="다비치" label="다비치"/><category term="내 옆에 그대인 걸" label="내 옆에 그대인 걸"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다비치/받는_사랑이_주는_사랑에게/</id><title>다비치 - 받는 사랑이 주는 사랑에게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:24:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:24:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%B9%84%EC%B9%98/%EB%B0%9B%EB%8A%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4_%EC%A3%BC%EB%8A%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C/" title="다비치 - 받는 사랑이 주는 사랑에게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바람 불면 힘들 텐데 <br>왜 괜찮은 척 버티죠 <br>흔들리면 어때서 <br>가지 같은 두 손 뻗어 <br>낙엽들을 빼앗길까 <br>움켜쥐고 애썼죠 <br>비도 날카로운 햇살도 <br>그대 우거진 사랑 아래 피했죠 <br>꼿꼿이 선 채로 <br>언제나 날 지켜주죠 미안하게 <br>괜찮으니까 이젠 좀 <br>흔들려요 흔들려도 돼요 <br>무거운 잎들을 그냥 뭐 그냥 뭐 <br>바람에게 줘버리면 돼 <br>비가 내리면 함께 맞으면 돼 <br>나로 인해 힘들면서 <br>내 덕에 힘 난다는 듯 <br>웃어주지 말아요 <br>앙상해도 괜찮아요 <br>무언가를 원해 곁에서 <br>있었던 건 아니죠 <br>비도 날카로운 햇살도 <br>그대 우거진 사랑 아래 피했죠 <br>정말 괜찮아요 <br>그 마음만 영원하면 그럼 돼요 <br>괜찮으니까 이젠 좀 <br>흔들려요 흔들려도 돼요 <br>무거운 잎들을 그냥 뭐 그냥 뭐 <br>바람에게 줘버리면 돼 <br>비가 내리면 함께 맞으면 돼 <br>내려놓아요 그 무거운 잎들 <br>그냥 그냥 놓아요 그 무거운 짐들 <br>힘들었죠 아니긴요 <br>힘들겠죠 이제 내게 기대요 <br>이제 받는 법도 배워요 <br>괜찮으니까 이젠 좀 <br>흔들려요 흔들려도 돼요 <br>무거운 잎들을 그냥 뭐 그냥 뭐 <br>바람에게 줘버리면 돼 <br>비가 내리면 함께 맞으면 돼 <br>]]></content><category term="다비치" label="다비치"/><category term="받는 사랑이 주는 사랑에게" label="받는 사랑이 주는 사랑에게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/다비치/가을의_밤/</id><title>다비치 - 가을의 밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:24:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:24:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A4%EB%B9%84%EC%B9%98/%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%84%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%A4/" title="다비치 - 가을의 밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이별하는 가을의 밤은 무릇 아파 <br>정말 많이 사랑했단 그 말에 <br>다시 눈물만 <br>그랬듯이 슬픔은 결국 <br>익숙하지 않아 <br>바랐지만 그댄 내게 <br>머물러주지 않아 <br>사랑하는 그대여 거기 멈춰 서요 <br>내 걸음이 따라가긴 너무 느려서 <br>바라만 보네요 <br>두 눈은 또 따라 흐려져요 <br>나의 눈물 때문에 <br>울지 않아 애써 견뎌도 <br>눈썹이 젖어와 <br>잊겠다고 말을 해도 <br>다시 너를 생각해 <br>사랑하는 그대여 거기 멈춰서요 <br>내 걸음이 따라가긴 너무 느려서 <br>바라만 보네요 <br>두 눈은 또 따라 흐려져요 <br>나의 눈물 때문에 <br>얼마나 지나야 이 제자리 걸음을 <br>멈출 수 있을까요 <br>떠나가는 그대여 내게 약속해요 <br>돌아오는 길은 부디 잊지 말아요 <br>그 마음 떠나도 <br>내가 이곳에서 기다려요 <br>계절이 바뀐대도 <br>나를 생각해줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="다비치" label="다비치"/><category term="가을의 밤" label="가을의 밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Feldt/Runaways_Feat_Teemu/</id><title>Sam_Feldt - Runaways (Feat. Teemu) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:25:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:25:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sam_Feldt/Runaways_Feat_Teemu/" title="Sam_Feldt - Runaways (Feat. Teemu) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey little darling <br>I'm gonna take you outta the darkness <br>I wanna walk with you in theh ligh <br>and hold your head hihg <br><br>Hey little darling <br>We better go before it is too late <br>Sneak out the window and down the fire escape <br>Hold my hand tight <br><br>'Cause we're just run run runaways <br>Run run renegades <br>Run run to get away <br><br>And we just run run because we ain't <br>Givin'it up now to get away <br>Always a haunted place <br><br>Oh and you and I are the ghosts <br>Now I wanna take you home <br>But we're just run run runaways <br>Run run renegades <br>Nowhere I could't stay <br><br>Hey little darling <br>No we're not welcome here in this party <br>They're lookin' through us like uninvited <br>Hold your head high <br><br>'Cause we're just run run runaways <br>Run Run renegades <br>Run run to get awya <br><br>And we just run run beacause we ain't <br>Givin'it up now to get away <br>Always a hauncted place <br><br>Oh and you and I are the ghosts <br>Now I wanna take you home <br>But we're just run run runaways <br>Run run renegades <br>Nowhere I couldn't stay <br><br>Oh and you and I are the ghosts <br>Now I wanna take you home <br>But we're just run run runaways <br>Run run renegades <br>Nowhere I couldn't stay]]></content><category term="Sam Feldt" label="Sam Feldt"/><category term="Runaways (Feat. Teemu)" label="Runaways (Feat. Teemu)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백퍼센트/지독하게_Inst/</id><title>백퍼센트 - 지독하게 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:25:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:25:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%ED%8D%BC%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8/%EC%A7%80%EB%8F%85%ED%95%98%EA%B2%8C_Inst/" title="백퍼센트 - 지독하게 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무엇보다 지독하다고 <br>겨우 헤어져 다행이라고 <br>독이라도 네가 없는 <br>여기는 아니야 <br>돌아갈래 <br>그 입술을 묻히며 <br>달콤하게 날 녹여버리고 <br>너만 본다 맹세하게 하던 날 <br>설령 지독하게 아파도 <br>난 네게 돌아 갈 거야 <br>미친 짓이란 걸 알아도 <br>난 너를 찾아 갈 거야 <br>너에게 중독 돼버렸어 <br>깊이 퍼져버린 치명적인 독 <br>너의 존재가 내가 살아가는 <br>유일한 이유라고 생각해 <br>미쳐가나 봐 거울 속에 비친 <br>내 모습이 거지 같애 <br>다시 네 옆에 눕고 싶어 <br>돌아갈래 <br>다시 아플 기횔 줘 <br>너란 상처를 내게 묻혀줘 <br>그래 내가 머물 곳은 너니까 <br>미친 짓이란 걸 알아도 <br>난 너를 찾아 갈 거야 <br>지나간 시간을 돌리고 싶어 <br>지금에서야 이미 떠난 <br>너의 그림자를 쫓아가네 <br>그리곤 너의 흔적들을 찾아가네 <br>술에 취해 비틀 비틀대도 <br>왜 결국 내 발걸음은 <br>너의 집 앞으로 걸어가 <br>돌아갈래 <br>뻔한 결론이어도 <br>같은 답들의 반복이어도 <br>너를 위해 존재하는 나니까 <br>세상 그 누구가 막아도 <br>난 어떻게든 갈 거야 <br>험한 가시 밭을 걸어도 <br>난 다시 네게 갈 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="백퍼센트" label="백퍼센트"/><category term="지독하게 (Inst.)" label="지독하게 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백퍼센트/내_마음이_참_못돼서/</id><title>백퍼센트 - 내 마음이 참 못돼서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:25:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:25:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%ED%8D%BC%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8/%EB%82%B4_%EB%A7%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%9D%B4_%EC%B0%B8_%EB%AA%BB%EB%8F%BC%EC%84%9C/" title="백퍼센트 - 내 마음이 참 못돼서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[참 많이 오래 걸렸죠 <br>그대를 잊지 못하고 <br>영원히 내 가슴 안에 <br>살게 하는 날까지 <br>아파하던 시간 <br>많이도 견뎠죠 <br>내 마음이 참 못돼서 <br>너무나도 바보 같아서 <br>설명하려고 해도 <br>이해하려 하지 않았죠 <br>내 마음이 참 모자라서 <br>절대 그대만을 원해서 <br>선명한 기억들을 <br>붙잡고 살고만 있네요 <br>참 많이 오래 견뎠죠 <br>눈물로 살아가면서 <br>이제야 그리움으로 <br>그댈 허락하네요 <br>힘들었던 시간 <br>겨우 버텨냈죠 <br>내 마음이 참 못돼서 <br>너무나도 바보 같아서 <br>설명하려고 해도 <br>이해하려 하지 않았죠 <br>내 마음이 참 모자라서 <br>절대 그대만을 원해서 <br>선명한 기억들을 <br>붙잡고 살고만 있네요 <br>다 거짓말이죠 <br>우리 기억은 <br>그 자리에 설 수 없네요 <br>투명한 기억들로 <br>너를 간직한 채 나 살게요 <br>내 맘엔 그대만이 <br>내 맘이 너무 아파서 <br>그댈 밀어내지 못해서 <br>참아내려 해봐도 <br>한숨처럼 터져 나오죠 <br>내 마음이 갈 곳 없어서 <br>절대 그대만을 원해서 <br>선명한 추억들을 <br>붙잡고 살고만 있네요 <br>]]></content><category term="백퍼센트" label="백퍼센트"/><category term="내 마음이 참 못돼서" label="내 마음이 참 못돼서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백퍼센트/오늘_같은_날/</id><title>백퍼센트 - 오늘 같은 날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:25:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:25:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%ED%8D%BC%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EB%82%A0/" title="백퍼센트 - 오늘 같은 날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그래 어젯 밤엔 내가 심했었어 <br>당황해서 그래 <br>그 얘긴 나중에 다시 해 <br>나 오늘 조금 괜찮지 않니 <br>네가 준 옷을 입고 <br>선물도 준비해 왔는데 <br>딱딱한 얘기만 하기엔 <br>너무나 아까운 하늘인걸 <br>우리 저까지 잠시만 걸을까 <br>날 위해 시간을 양보해 줘 <br>진짜 눈물 나게 너무 좋은 날 <br>제발 그 말만은 꺼내지 마라 <br>하지 마 아직은 <br>내 손을 놓치지 말아줘 <br>너만 있으면 돼 함께해온 <br>패러다임 지켜져야만 해 <br>네가 아님 안돼 꿈꿔왔던 <br>패러다임 stay in my life <br>뭐야 못 본 사이 머리 새로 했네 <br>언제 바꾼 거야 <br>짧은 것도 잘 어울리네 <br>애꿎은 시계만 보지 말고 <br>내 눈도 맞춰줄래 <br>처음 날 보던 그때처럼 <br>아무리 화제를 돌려도 <br>도통 넌 표정을 풀지 않아 <br>제발 오늘 하루만 잘 넘기자 <br>내일은 달라질지도 몰라 <br>진짜 눈물 나게 너무 좋은 날 <br>제발 그 말만은 꺼내지 마라 <br>하지 마 아직은 <br>내 손을 놓치지 말아줘 <br>너만 있으면 돼 함께해온 <br>패러다임 지켜져야만 해 <br>네가 아님 안돼 꿈꿔왔던 <br>패러다임 stay in my life <br>시간은 계속 가 <br>느리지도 않고 빠르지도 않게 <br>타 들어가고 있는 내속아 <br>어쩐지 오늘따라 <br>없더라니 재수가 <br>아무리 찾고 잡아봐도 <br>더 나을 건 없는데 <br>나만 여기 남아 <br>이미 넌 떠났는데 왜 <br>가지 마 가지 마 오늘은 가지 마 <br>내게도 시간을 줘 이렇겐 아냐 <br>왜 하필 이런 날을 골라 <br>더 아프게 해 <br>왜 하필 오늘 같은 날에 왜 <br>눈부시게 햇살 좋은 날 <br>왜 넌 나를 두고 떠나려고 해 <br>가지 마 오늘과 이별은 <br>어울리지 않아 부탁해 <br>너만 있으면 돼 함께해온 <br>패러다임 지켜져야만 해 <br>네가 아님 안돼 꿈꿔왔던 <br>패러다임 stay in my life <br>stay in my life stay in my life <br>]]></content><category term="백퍼센트" label="백퍼센트"/><category term="오늘 같은 날" label="오늘 같은 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백퍼센트/안녕이라는_말은_싫어/</id><title>백퍼센트 - 안녕이라는 말은 싫어 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:25:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:25:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%ED%8D%BC%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8/%EC%95%88%EB%85%95%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC%EB%8A%94_%EB%A7%90%EC%9D%80_%EC%8B%AB%EC%96%B4/" title="백퍼센트 - 안녕이라는 말은 싫어 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무 말 못 하고 <br>바닥에 떨군 네 눈이 <br>많은걸 말하지만 난 모를래 <br>손톱만 깨물며 꾹 다문 네 입술이 <br>서럽게 하지만 난 몰라 <br>고갤 들고 나를 좀 봐봐 <br>변한 건 하나 없어 그대로야 <br>아픈 건 같이 고쳐가자 <br>언제나 함께 했잖아 <br>안녕이라는 말은 싫어 <br>우리에겐 없는 말이야 <br>너를 위한 거래도 난 모를래 <br>넌 이대로 나와 가줘 <br>얼마든지 시간은 줄게 <br>일년을 하루처럼 참아볼게 <br>원하면 뭐든 고쳐갈게 <br>내게서 멀어지지 마 <br>안녕이라는 말은 싫어 <br>우리에겐 없는 말이야 <br>이기적이라 해도 난 모를래 <br>넌 내 곁에 함께 해줘 <br>난 모른 척 할거야 다 잊어버려 <br>우린 버릇처럼 말했잖아 <br>서로 목숨 걸어 <br>사랑하자고 이별 따윈 없다고 <br>그런데 지금 이게 뭐야 <br>now you let me go <br>I can't believe this 모른 척 할거야 <br>나는 변치 않아 그때처럼 <br>잘해나갈 거야 <br>우릴 망친 익숙함에 속아 <br>소중한걸 잃지 마 가지 마 <br>마지막까지 함께 till we die <br>사랑했다는 말은 싫어 <br>안녕이라는 말은 싫어 <br>우리에겐 없는 말이야 <br>나를 위한 배려가 <br>무거워진 거라면 <br>내가 더 힘 내볼게 <br>슬픈 표정은 내가 싫어 <br>너완 어울리지 않아 <br>이기적이라 해도 난 모를래 <br>넌 내 곁에 함께해줘 <br>]]></content><category term="백퍼센트" label="백퍼센트"/><category term="안녕이라는 말은 싫어" label="안녕이라는 말은 싫어"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백퍼센트/너라서/</id><title>백퍼센트 - 너라서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:25:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:25:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%ED%8D%BC%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8/%EB%84%88%EB%9D%BC%EC%84%9C/" title="백퍼센트 - 너라서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 대답은 너잖아 <br>몇 번이고 너잖아 <br>뻔한 결론인걸 왜 너만 몰라 <br>되돌려도 너잖아 <br>앞으로도 너잖아 <br>네가 아닌 사람은 안되잖아 <br>넌 아닌 것 같다 <br>딴 놈 찾아 봐라 <br>또 한 여잘 울려 보냈어 <br>귀찮게 왜 이래 쿨하게 떨어져 <br>어느새 나쁜 놈이 됐어 <br>너와 헤어진 후로 <br>네가 하지 말라던 <br>나쁜 것만 입에 대봐도 <br>안 사던 옷을 사 입고 <br>여행을 떠나봐도 <br>너만한 감동이 없어 <br>네가 생각나 다른 여잘 만나도 <br>너만 생각나 다른 사랑을 해도 <br>맨날 똑같아 다시 결론은 너야 <br>너여서 너라서 너니까 <br>내 대답은 너잖아 <br>몇 번이고 너잖아 <br>뻔한 결론인걸 왜 너만 몰라 <br>되돌려도 너잖아 <br>앞으로도 너잖아 <br>네가 아닌 사람은 안되잖아 <br>모두 힐끔댈 만큼 <br>예쁜 여잘 두고도 <br>너와 비교를 하게 되고 <br>금새 또 지루해지고 <br>피곤함이 밀려와 <br>너만한 전율이 없어 <br>네가 생각나 다른 여잘 만나도 <br>너만 생각나 다른 사랑을 해도 <br>맨날 똑같아 다시 결론은 너야 <br>너여서 너라서 너니까 <br>I Miss you <br>믿지 않을래 아직은 <br>실감이 나질 않아 <br>빈자리가 왜 이리 <br>허전한지 나 지금 <br>같이 걷던 그 길에서 <br>너를 찾고 그려봐도 <br>보이지가 않는걸 <br>못되게 굴었던 그때의 <br>내가 너무 잔인해 <br>빨리 내게로 다시 돌아와 <br>손잡고 걸어 다니게 <br>더 진해져 가는 추억들이 말해 <br>너뿐이라고 <br>한 달을 못 가 <br>네가 대체 뭐라고 <br>잠깐을 못 가 <br>나는 어떡하라고 <br>결국 똑같아 내게 <br>문제는 너야 <br>너여서 너라서 너니까 <br>내 대답은 너잖아 <br>몇 번이고 너잖아 <br>뻔한 결론인걸 왜 너만 몰라 <br>되돌려도 너잖아 <br>앞으로도 너잖아 <br>네가 아닌 사람은 안되잖아 <br>]]></content><category term="백퍼센트" label="백퍼센트"/><category term="너라서" label="너라서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/백퍼센트/지독하게/</id><title>백퍼센트 - 지독하게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:25:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:25:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%B1%ED%8D%BC%EC%84%BC%ED%8A%B8/%EC%A7%80%EB%8F%85%ED%95%98%EA%B2%8C/" title="백퍼센트 - 지독하게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무엇보다 지독하다고 <br>겨우 헤어져 다행이라고 <br>독이라도 네가 없는 <br>여기는 아니야 <br>돌아갈래 <br>그 입술을 묻히며 <br>달콤하게 날 녹여버리고 <br>너만 본다 맹세하게 하던 날 <br>설령 지독하게 아파도 <br>난 네게 돌아 갈 거야 <br>미친 짓이란 걸 알아도 <br>난 너를 찾아 갈 거야 <br>너에게 중독 돼버렸어 <br>깊이 퍼져버린 치명적인 독 <br>너의 존재가 내가 살아가는 <br>유일한 이유라고 생각해 <br>미쳐가나 봐 거울 속에 비친 <br>내 모습이 거지 같애 <br>다시 네 옆에 눕고 싶어 <br>돌아갈래 <br>다시 아플 기횔 줘 <br>너란 상처를 내게 묻혀줘 <br>그래 내가 머물 곳은 너니까 <br>미친 짓이란 걸 알아도 <br>난 너를 찾아 갈 거야 <br>지나간 시간을 돌리고 싶어 <br>지금에서야 이미 떠난 <br>너의 그림자를 쫓아가네 <br>그리곤 너의 흔적들을 찾아가네 <br>술에 취해 비틀 비틀대도 <br>왜 결국 내 발걸음은 <br>너의 집 앞으로 걸어가 <br>돌아갈래 <br>뻔한 결론이어도 <br>같은 답들의 반복이어도 <br>너를 위해 존재하는 나니까 <br>세상 그 누구가 막아도 <br>난 어떻게든 갈 거야 <br>험한 가시 밭을 걸어도 <br>난 다시 네게 갈 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="백퍼센트" label="백퍼센트"/><category term="지독하게" label="지독하게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/가현/오늘밤도_길어요/</id><title>가현 - 오늘밤도 길어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:27:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:27:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%80%ED%98%84/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EB%B0%A4%EB%8F%84_%EA%B8%B8%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="가현 - 오늘밤도 길어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘밤도 길어요 <br>다들 안자고 뭐해요 <br>한 손에 폰 들고 뭐 봐요 <br>뭐 재밌는 구경이라도 났나 봐 <br>여기 저기 타고 가다 보면 <br>나만 이러고 있나 싶죠 <br>남들 사는 건 왜 좋아 보일까요 <br>왜 다 잘 지내죠 <br>결혼은 아직 멀었는 줄 알았는데 <br>다들 짝지어가네요 <br>오 호오 <br>난 아직 썸남 썸녀도 신기한데 <br>다들 결혼 반지에 시계 드레스 <br>오늘밤도 또 길어요 <br>다들 잘 자고 있나요 <br>아님 한 손에 폰 들고 잠 못 자요 <br>무슨 일이라도 있나 봐 <br>실시간 검색어 연관 검색어 <br>나와는 1도 상관없는데 <br>남들 사는 건 왜 좋아 보일까요 <br>왜 다 잘 지내죠 <br>삼시세끼 잘 챙겨먹는 <br>것도 힘든데 <br>다들 잘 챙겨먹고 있네요 <br>난 매일 라면 끓이기도 귀찮은데 <br>다들 치킨 스테이크 <br>야식은 삼겹살 <br>나이를 먹는 것도 서러운데 <br>뭘 먹었는지 다들 예쁘죠 <br>난 매일 가리기에 지쳤는데 <br>다들 흰티 청바지에 <br>깔창 없는 운동화 <br>]]></content><category term="가현" label="가현"/><category term="오늘밤도 길어요" label="오늘밤도 길어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/S1_Feat_더블캐슬/</id><title>헤이노 - S1 (Feat. 더블캐슬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:29:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:29:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/S1_Feat_%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/" title="헤이노 - S1 (Feat. 더블캐슬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우린 니들 머리 위로 <br>흔드는 손들의 리더 <br>거부 못해 넌 hey <br>벌써 너는 노예 <br>우린 니들 머리 위로 <br>흔드는 손들의 리더 <br>거부 못해 넌 hey <br>벌써 너는 노예 <br>처참 하기만한 <br>내가 꾀나 많이 컸어 <br>너도 포기 말고 <br>갈 때까지 가봐 계속 <br>더블캐슬 하고 <br>쌓아 올린 나의 캐슬 <br>나야 말로 진짜로 <br>노력하는 케이스 <br>만족 못해 아직 <br>세 개뿐인 바지 <br>고작 만원 짜리 <br>나의 결혼 반지 <br>결과를 원해 언제까지 <br>이렇게 살지 <br>이젠 오직 랩 <br>하나만이 나를 상징 <br>뭐가 됐던 나는 한번 <br>하고 말아 반드시 <br>내 인생이 지금 어딜 <br>향해 흘러 가는지 <br>모르지만 계속 <br>두근거린다고 가슴이 <br>그러니 난 갈 수 밖에 없어 <br>몇 명은 나를 <br>느끼고 있겠지 <br>아직 까진 내가 <br>긴가민가 싶겠지 <br>그럼 계속 봐 난 <br>끝까지 갈 거야 <br>랩을 계속 할거야 <br>우린 니들 머리 위로 <br>흔드는 손들의 리더 <br>거부 못해 넌 hey <br>벌써 너는 노예 <br>우린 니들 머리 위로 <br>흔드는 손들의 리더 <br>거부 못해 넌 hey <br>벌써 너는 노예 <br>어 사람들이 전부 <br>내가 착한 줄 아는데 <br>어 사실 별로 안 착해 <br>어 근데 나쁜 놈은 아니고 <br>어 완전 나쁜 놈 악마 같아 <br>어 어 난 평소에 착한 놈 <br>코스프레 <br>어 어 집에 돌아오면 <br>악마로 돌변해 <br>어 샤이니도 아니면서 <br>루시퍼 빙의해 <br>어 그거 알아 지옥으로 <br>가는 문은 총 세개 <br>군자동 아저씨 <br>my surve nick name <br>이 동네가 날 미치게 해 <br>make me change <br>썩은 경찰이 출몰해 광진 <br>police office <br>끌려갔지 개돼지도 아닌데 <br>채워진 은팔찌 <br>성실하게 살면 안돼 <br>뭐든 찾아 편법 <br>법 보다 주먹이 앞서 <br>건들면 퍽퍽 <br>씨푸둥 쇠파이프 <br>감히 감히 쒸발 <br>날 건들면 앞뒤 없어 <br>연장부터 챙겨 <br>우린 니들 머리 위로 <br>흔드는 손들의 리더 <br>거부 못해 넌 hey <br>벌써 너는 노예 <br>우린 니들 머리 위로 <br>흔드는 손들의 리더 <br>거부 못해 넌 hey <br>벌써 너는 노예 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="S1 (Feat. 더블캐슬)" label="S1 (Feat. 더블캐슬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/계속해/</id><title>헤이노 - 계속해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:29:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:29:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EA%B3%84%EC%86%8D%ED%95%B4/" title="헤이노 - 계속해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[개소리들 <br>내가 뭘 <br>노력한적 없었다면 거짓말이고 <br>주변에는 취미라고 말을 해두고 <br>너무 슬퍼 보일까 봐 웃음을 지어 <br>그래 아주 새빨간 웃음을 지어 <br>내 가사는 다 똑같아 나도 안다고 <br>머리 속에 가득 찼네 무서운 고민 <br>내 꿈이 나를 살게 했듯 <br>그와 반대로 <br>이제는 나를 무너트리려고 하네 <br>그래서 어쩌라고 난 계속할 거야 <br>그냥 단순히 아주 조금 <br>애석할 뿐야 <br>변함없어 나는 벌써 <br>돌아갈 수 없어 <br>그리고 나도 절대 돌아갈 <br>생각 없어 <br>한탄 좀 그만 넌 그냥 한탕주의 <br>아무도 억지로 하라 안 해 <br>힘들면 너나 그만해 난 놀 거야 <br>어쩔 거야 멈출거야 계속 할 거야 <br>누가 뭐라 그래 go go 계속해 <br>내가 한다는데 뭐 뭐 어쩌게 <br>내가 별로라고 해도 어쩌라고요 <br>니가 뭐라 해도 계속 할거라고요 <br>누가 뭐라 그래 go go 계속해 <br>내가 한다는데 뭐 뭐 어쩌게 <br>내가 별로라고 해도 어쩌라고요 <br>니가 뭐라 해도 계속 할거라고요 <br>실은 나도 모르겠어 <br>이랬다가 저랬다가 <br>내가 뭐를 하고 싶은 건지 몰라 <br>강해지길 원했지만 무너졌을 뿐 <br>사라진 게 아냐 단지 숨겨졌을 뿐 <br>어렸을 적 꿈 난 간직하고 있어 <br>여전히 음악이 날 상징하고 있어 <br>10년 넘게 아무 성과도 없지만 <br>버텨온 내게 아주 감사하고 있어 <br>감사하고 있어 난 잘하고 있어 <br>비록 아무도 듣지 않을 노래라도 <br>그 누구도 주목하지 않을 <br>무대라도 <br>받아들여 그냥 그렇게 살더라도 <br>내가 못한 탓이야 내가 이렇다고 <br>별 볼 일 없이 살다 보니 이렇다고 <br>그래 내 노래는 싹 다 이렇다고 <br>내가 해온 결과가 이렇다고 <br>그래서 어쩌라고 난 계속할 거야 <br>그냥 단순히 아주 조금 <br>애석할 뿐야 <br>변함없어 나는 벌써 <br>돌아갈 수 없어 <br>그리고 나도 절대 돌아갈 <br>생각 없어 <br>한탄 좀 그만 넌 그냥 한탕주의 <br>아무도 억지로 하라 안 해 <br>힘들면 너나 그만해 난 놀 거야 <br>어쩔 거야 멈출거야 계속할 거야 <br>누가 뭐라 그래 go go 계속해 <br>내가 한다는데 뭐 뭐 어쩌게 <br>내가 별로라고 해도 어쩌라고요 <br>니가 뭐라 해도 계속 할거라고요 <br>누가 뭐라 그래 go go 계속해 <br>내가 한다는데 뭐 뭐 어쩌게 <br>내가 별로라고 해도 어쩌라고요 <br>니가 뭐라 해도 계속 할거라고요 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="계속해" label="계속해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/건반/</id><title>헤이노 - 건반 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:29:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:29:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EA%B1%B4%EB%B0%98/" title="헤이노 - 건반 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어서 이리 와서 나를 반겨봐 빨리 <br>이제 와서 나를 아는척해 <br>내가 말했잖아 난 더 클 거라고 <br>또 말할게 난 더 클 거라고 <br>어서 이리 와서 나를 반겨봐 빨리 <br>이제 와서 나를 아는척해 <br>내가 말했잖아 난 더 클 거라고 <br>또 말할게 난 더 클 거라고 <br>가만있어도 이젠 예전과는 <br>다르네요 <br>맨날 우울했던 예전과는 <br>다른 내용 <br>벌써 13년이 지났다니 <br>빠르네요 <br>결말은 안 봐도 뻔한 내용 <br>헤이노 누가 내 욕 해도 이제 <br>신경 안 써 <br>자식들이 모르면 좀 가만히 있어 <br>완전 인정받는다고 사람들한테 <br>멍청이들이 마녀 사냥을 하네 <br>내 파트너는 덥캐슬뿐 이제 와서 <br>지가 뭔데 나를 팔아먹어 어 <br>난 겁 없이 달려 거의 비트를 발로 <br>찍어 드디어 건반을 샀어 <br>음악한지 13년 만에 건반을 샀어 <br>여태 컴퓨터 키보드로 찍었다고 <br>놀려봐 넌 이 기분을 못 망쳐 <br>왜 냠 난 이제 잘 산다고요 <br>어서 이리 와서 나를 반겨봐 빨리 <br>이제 와서 나를 아는척해 <br>내가 말했잖아 난 더 클 거라고 <br>또 말할게 난 더 클 거라고 <br>어서 이리 와서 나를 반겨봐 빨리 <br>이제 와서 나를 아는척해 <br>내가 말했잖아 난 더 클 거라고 <br>또 말할게 난 더 클 거라고 <br>불 끄라고 난 더 클 거라고 <br>웬만하면 다 나를 모르고 <br>나를 모를수록 나는 그럴수록 <br>열 받아 악을 지르고 더 할거라고 <br>나 같은 놈은 못 봤네 유일무이해 <br>아무도 몰라주면 걍 우리 둘이 해 <br>점점 내 주변으로 <br>모여드는 무리들 <br>이젠 나랑 작업하고 <br>싶어 줄이 구린 <br>애들 걸러 가지고 골라서 작업해 <br>비트도 보내는데 내가 더 잘해 <br>혼자 다해 나는 내가 다 할 줄 알아 <br>너는 별로 필요 없어 저리 가요 <br>건반도 샀다고 이제 쳐버려 <br>부러운 놈 없어 쬐금씩 돈 벌어 <br>실력이 늘어 계속 안 멈추고 <br>이제 비켜줘 전부 다 옆으로 <br>어서 이리 와서 나를 반겨봐 빨리 <br>이제 와서 나를 아는척해 <br>내가 말했잖아 난 더 클 거라고 <br>또 말할게 난 더 클 거라고 <br>어서 이리 와서 나를 반겨봐 빨리 <br>이제 와서 나를 아는척해 <br>내가 말했잖아 난 더 클 거라고 <br>또 말할게 난 더 클 거라고 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="건반" label="건반"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/새벽_다섯시_Feat_더블캐슬/</id><title>헤이노 - 새벽 다섯시 (Feat. 더블캐슬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:29:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:29:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD_%EB%8B%A4%EC%84%AF%EC%8B%9C_Feat_%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/" title="헤이노 - 새벽 다섯시 (Feat. 더블캐슬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[쿠랑 더블캐슬 잠든 새벽 다섯시 <br>나는 이 시간이 좋아 밤새웠지 <br>이 틈에 내 솔로 곡을 하나 만들어 <br>사람들은 제정신엔 <br>내 노래를 안 들어 <br>온 세상이 뿌얘지고 <br>파래지는 시간 <br>불면증에 시달려요 어차피 난 <br>더블캐슬 비트 하나 <br>훔쳐 랩을 입혀 <br>이게 너무 재밌어서 <br>이걸 할 땐 미쳐 <br>나랑 한번 솔직히 얘길 해보자고 <br>좀만 기다려 이제 해 떠 해 보자고 <br>넌 뭐 땜에 잠들지 못하니 <br>난 뭐 땜에 사람들이 욕하지 <br>어딜 가도 내 욕 뿐야 대체 내가 뭘 <br>내 가사는 내가 사는 삶처럼 <br>꿈에 대한 내용 뿐야 <br>이게 내 욕구야 <br>딴 짓 안 해 근데 왜 그러나 몰라 <br>왜 그럴까 <br>쿠랑 더블캐슬 잠든 새벽 다섯시 <br>헛소리만 늘어놔 새벽 다섯시 <br>졸린데 잠이 안 와 새벽 다섯시 <br>왠지 기분 좋아 지금 새벽 다섯시 <br>쿠랑 더블캐슬 잠든 새벽 다섯시 <br>헛소리만 늘어놔 새벽 다섯시 <br>졸린데 잠이 안 와 새벽 다섯시 <br>왠지 기분 좋아 지금 새벽 다섯시 <br>쿠는 쿨쿨자 우리는 쿵쿵따 <br>어제 세명 새벽에 술을 마셔 놓고 <br>잠을 못 자 <br>아마 오늘 세명 새벽에 <br>잠을 못 자서 낮잠을 자겠지 <br>캐치 <br>비트를 골라 잡아 <br>이 비트는 비장한데 <br>사실 아무 의미 없이 <br>멍 때리며 찍어놓고 <br>내가 만든 건지 까먹었어 난 <br>이 노래는 새벽 <br>다섯시에 만드는데 <br>벌써 여섯시가 다가와 <br>첫 차가 떴는데 집에 안가 다 <br>푹 쉬고 싶어 난 <br>어제 일 하고 못 자서 피곤 하잖아 <br>다들 왜 안가 여긴 우리집이야 <br>나의 생활 공간 나의 생활 공간 <br>나의 생활 공간 나의 생활 공간 <br>나의 생활 공간 나의 생활 공간 <br>쿠랑 더블캐슬 잠든 새벽 다섯시 <br>헛소리만 늘어놔 새벽 다섯시 <br>졸린데 잠이 안 와 새벽 다섯시 <br>왠지 기분 좋아 지금 새벽 다섯시 <br>쿠랑 더블캐슬 잠든 새벽 다섯시 <br>헛소리만 늘어놔 새벽 다섯시 <br>졸린데 잠이 안 와 새벽 다섯시 <br>왠지 기분 좋아 지금 새벽 다섯시 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="새벽 다섯시 (Feat. 더블캐슬)" label="새벽 다섯시 (Feat. 더블캐슬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/Where_You_At/</id><title>헤이노 - Where You At - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:29:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:29:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/Where_You_At/" title="헤이노 - Where You At - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잠시 후에 오디션을 <br>보러 가야 하는데 <br>난 연습 대신 <br>새로운 곡을 만드네 아 <br>망했어 내 영감이 멈추질 않아 <br>정말 이게 나의 천직인가 봐 <br>담배 좀 끊어야지 <br>속이 너무 시커매 <br>내 사업은 잘 돼가 <br>친구들이 식겁해 <br>말했잖아 난 실력 <br>있는 놈이라니까 <br>그럴 수밖에 없지 <br>하루 종일 하니까 <br>벌써 올해만 앨범이 <br>다섯 개 6월인데 <br>나를 만난 사장들은 <br>날 보고 물건이래 <br>계속 이렇게 할 수 있겠냐고 <br>물론이지 <br>사실 난 훨씬 잘해 금방 보여줄게 <br>작년의 나와 오늘은 <br>나는 천지차이 <br>너희도 알아 <br>매일 성장하는 성취감 <br>못 할거 없어 누구나 다 할 수 있어 <br>난 그걸 느꼈어 이젠 어디로 <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>너는 어디까지 갈 수 있어 <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>날 보고 배워둬 너도 할 수 있어 <br>내가 보고 배운 것 <br>내가 직접 겪은 건 <br>살아남는 자가 진짜 강하다는 것 <br>다들 3 4년 하다 말아 <br>그냥 말을 말아 <br>그 마음 알아 진짜 막막 하단 거 <br>난 정말 못해도 계속 성장하지 <br>내 정신은 단단해 매우 건강하지 <br>너넨 조금 하다 안되면 절망하지 <br>난 안 멈춰 계속해 될 때까지 <br>아직 내 말엔 힘이 없단 걸 알아 <br>10년 지나서 다시 한번 들어봐 <br>지금 난 내 과정들을 <br>쌓고 있는 거야 <br>과정 없인 결과 없어 <br>부정 하는 거야 <br>여긴 날로 먹으려는 <br>드는 놈이 너무 많아 <br>자책할 그 시간에 한번 더 노력해 <br>원래 어려워 니가 못난 게 아냐 <br>내게 물어보지 말고 <br>직접 하란 말야 <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>너는 어디까지 갈 수 있어 <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>where you at where you at <br>where you at boy <br>날 보고 배워둬 너도 할 수 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="Where You At" label="Where You At"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/우리는_Feat_WooD/</id><title>헤이노 - 우리는 (Feat. Woo.D) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:29:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:29:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_Feat_WooD/" title="헤이노 - 우리는 (Feat. Woo.D) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너무 오래 쉰 거 같아 <br>지금부터 다시 감 잡아야지 나 참 <br>매일 밥 먹듯이 랩을 해온 세월이 <br>잘 세어보니까 엄청 오래 됐구만 <br>지금 내 위에 군림하는 건 빚더미 <br>부디 내가 이겨내기만을 빌었지 <br>이런 빌어먹을 내가 싫어 <br>내일은 반드시 <br>뛰어 벗어나 버릴 거야 <br>이젠 벌써 나도 <br>스물여섯 살 새로운 집을 사 <br>이번 달 이사 가 <br>방 3개짜리 월세방 이상하게도 <br>난 참 운이 좋아 <br>공연하지 항상 누군가는 <br>나를 불러주네 <br>뭐 언제나 준비됐으니 불러도 돼 <br>나를 찾아 나를 찾아 <br>그래 나를 찾아 모두 나를 찾아 <br>죽지 않아 우린 계속 이걸 해나가 <br>웃지 마봐 우린 금방 다시 올라가 <br>끝이 아냐 우린 아직 까진 살아가 <br>죽지 않아 우린 죽지 않아 우린 <br>죽지 않아 우린 계속 이걸 해나가 <br>웃지 마봐 우린 금방 다시 올라가 <br>끝이 아냐 우린 아직 까진 살아가 <br>죽지 않아 우린 죽지 않아 우린 <br>정신 없이 바쁜 삶에 지쳐 아주 <br>잠시 뿐이지만 정신 차리는 때는 <br>오직 가사 쓸 때 그때는 쓸 데 없는 <br>생각 따윈 안 해 그렇게 여태 <br>잘 지내왔는데 점점 <br>일거린 더 늘어나 <br>반대로 가사 쓸 시간은 <br>점점 줄어가 <br>내 열정은 그대론데 <br>전에 비해 늘지 않는 실력을 <br>듣다 보면 자신감은 <br>바닥으로 들어가 <br>어찌 보면 이건 기회 <br>처음 겪는 슬럼프 <br>이걸 이겨냈을 때 <br>내 실력은 슬램덩크 <br>강백호처럼 일취월장 하겠지 <br>헤이노가 준 이 비트는 <br>마치 스키장 상급 슬로프 <br>내가 내 의지로 올라왔어 <br>기왕 올라온 거 <br>즐기며 멋지게 내려오겠어 <br>기대해 요즘에 작업이 <br>좀 뜸해졌어도 죽지 않아 <br>내 열정만큼은 으뜸해 <br>죽지 않아 우린 계속 이걸 해나가 <br>웃지 마봐 우린 금방 다시 올라가 <br>끝이 아냐 우린 아직 까진 살아가 <br>죽지 않아 우린 죽지 않아 우린 <br>죽지 않아 우린 계속 이걸 해나가 <br>웃지 마봐 우린 금방 다시 올라가 <br>끝이 아냐 우린 아직 까진 살아가 <br>죽지 않아 우린 죽지 않아 우린 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="우리는 (Feat. Woo.D)" label="우리는 (Feat. Woo.D)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/어린애야_Feat_더블캐슬_2Poo/</id><title>헤이노 - 어린애야 (Feat. 더블캐슬, 2Poo) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:29:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:29:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EC%96%B4%EB%A6%B0%EC%95%A0%EC%95%BC_Feat_%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC_2Poo/" title="헤이노 - 어린애야 (Feat. 더블캐슬, 2Poo) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매달 늘어나지 나의 앨범 수익이 <br>한달 300원이 <br>언제적 이야긴지 <br>이젠 4천원이 됐어 <br>그만큼 나를 찾아 듣는 이가 <br>점점 늘어가고 있다니까 <br>더 진하게 내 색깔을 입혀야겠어 <br>오늘 밤엔 치킨을 시켜야겠어 <br>한 명 두 명에서 <br>이젠 수십 명이 들어 <br>청담동에 매장에선 <br>내 앨범을 틀어 <br>어 사실 고민이야 <br>내가 뭐가 잘났다고 <br>솔직히 곡이 말야 <br>좋은 게 없어 보이는데 <br>근데 난 안 멈출 거고 <br>다음달엔 1600명짜리 <br>종합운동장에서 <br>홀로 공연할거야 <br>너흰 아직 몰라 뭐가 중요한지 <br>시작도 안 했다고 나는 아직 <br>어린애야 내 맘대로 해 <br>더 클 거야 아직 어린애야 <br>니 젖 좀 줘 먹어야 해 <br>어린애야 아직 어린애야 <br>어린애야 내 맘대로 해 <br>더 클 거야 아직 어린애야 <br>니 젖 좀 줘 먹어야 해 <br>어린애야 아직 어린애야 <br>야 난 담배 살 때 <br>아직도 민증 검사해 <br>이러다 서른 돼도 <br>보여 달랄 거 같애 <br>지갑에서 돈 꺼내려다가 증꺼내 <br>대조하면 웃음밖에 안 나오지 <br>그때나 지금이나 <br>달라진 게 없으니 <br>어머니 왜 저를 이렇게 나으셨나 <br>벌써 마음이 늙은이 <br>근데 모습이 어린이 <br>사는 곳도 어린이 그랜드 파크 <br>그래서 난 <br>성인군자 될라고 <br>군자동으로 이사 <br>난 s마트에서 맨날 술사 <br>1년째 가는 단골집도 <br>내 민증 검사해 왜냐면 <br>내 얼굴이 so fresh fxxking fresh <br>young &amp; fresh so fxxking fresh <br>old man but I'm so fxxking fresh <br>어린애야 내 맘대로 해 <br>더 클 거야 아직 어린애야 <br>니 젖 좀 줘 먹어야 해 <br>어린애야 아직 어린애야 <br>어린애야 내 맘대로 해 <br>더 클 거야 아직 어린애야 <br>니 젖 좀 줘 먹어야 해 <br>어린애야 아직 어린애야 <br>키는 이미 대한민국 <br>평균 넘어섰고 <br>무게는 묵직한 것이 <br>가벼운 남잔 아니 였고 <br>접고 접던 음악 대신 <br>현실 넘다 넘어졌고 <br>어른 흉내 내도 아직 <br>찾는 거는 초코초코 <br>그래 난 초코초코 <br>아님 딸기 맛에 젖고 젖어 <br>내일 모레 서른인데 어린애 입맛 <br>나랑 놀 때는 술 담배 말고 <br>그냥 초코 더 줘 <br>어린 입맛도 테크닉은 <br>어른이야 임마 <br>딸기맛 바나나맛 섞지마 <br>난 본래 맛을 원해 내게 권하지마 <br>필요 없어 저지방 <br>칼로리에 속지마 <br>맛있는 건 0칼로리 <br>거기 너 임마 <br>닭가슴살과는 더는 놀지마 <br>아직 많이 배고파요 난 성장기 <br>씹어 먹을 거야 저 밑 <br>제주부터 서울까지 <br>어린애야 내 맘대로 해 <br>더 클 거야 아직 어린애야 <br>니 젖 좀 줘 먹어야 해 <br>어린애야 아직 어린애야 <br>어린애야 내 맘대로 해 <br>더 클 거야 아직 어린애야 <br>니 젖 좀 줘 먹어야 해 <br>어린애야 아직 어린애야 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="어린애야 (Feat. 더블캐슬, 2Poo)" label="어린애야 (Feat. 더블캐슬, 2Poo)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/VM/</id><title>헤이노 - VM - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:30:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:30:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/VM/" title="헤이노 - VM - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가사들을 썼다가 <br>지워 혼란스런 밤 <br>정말 나도 나를 <br>하나도 몰라 <br>너무 로맨틱하거나 <br>아님 고집이 너무 쌘 가봐 <br>옛날 같지 않아 <br>더는 순진 하지 못해 <br>쉽게 승질 나지 <br>맘은 딱딱한 고체 <br>오직 신념대로 <br>살아가는 돈키호테 <br>제발 관두고 싶어 <br>나의 직장 호텔 <br>내 cd가 <br>나왔지만 어쩌라고 <br>바로 다음 앨범 <br>작업하기 바빠 아마 <br>나는 잔뜩 맘이 <br>꼬여 버려 <br>나는 나를 내버려둬야 <br>할 거 같아 <br>나는 내게 어울리는 <br>것만 골라해 <br>돈이 궁하지만 <br>돈에 눈 멀진 않아 <br>아무리 내가 불리해도 <br>입 닫진 않아 <br>내가 틀릴 수도 <br>있다고 항상 생각해 <br>그래도 난 나의 길을 <br>만을 원하기에 <br>그냥 나쁜 짓 해버려 <br>내가 진짜 원하면 <br>싹 다 갖다 버려 <br>누가 뭐라던 <br>나는 내가 하고 <br>싶은 대로 살 거야 <br>한번 사는 건데 <br>그래 나는 할거야 <br>내 노랠 아무도 <br>듣기 싫어한대도 <br>난 계속 할거야 <br>내가 알바야 <br>텔레비젼 같은 거 <br>봐봐야 거짓말뿐 <br>거기 속아넘어간 바보보단 <br>그냥 내가 믿는 대로 <br>행동하고 말아 <br>어차피 차피 니들 역시 <br>답을 모르잖아 <br>내가 틀릴 수도 있어 <br>그럼 틀린 거지 <br>내가 망할 수도 있어 <br>그럼 망한 거지 <br>그럼 니가 장담 <br>할 수 있어 못하지 <br>적어도 난 내가 <br>나의 삶을 살고 있어 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="VM" label="VM"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/무한대에_가까워_Feat_더블캐슬/</id><title>헤이노 - 무한대에 가까워 (Feat. 더블캐슬) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:30:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:30:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EB%AC%B4%ED%95%9C%EB%8C%80%EC%97%90_%EA%B0%80%EA%B9%8C%EC%9B%8C_Feat_%EB%8D%94%EB%B8%94%EC%BA%90%EC%8A%AC/" title="헤이노 - 무한대에 가까워 (Feat. 더블캐슬) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[무한대에 가까워 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>난 어쩌면 천재 <br>안 떨어져 절대 <br>실력이 자꾸 <br>마구 솟아 나의 연대 <br>기는 풍성해져 <br>이젠 귀족 대접 <br>불안정한 삶답게 <br>불안정한 스타일 <br>원래 무한이란 <br>고정되지 않는 거지 <br>안 멈춰 자꾸 움직여 <br>너의 허리 <br>러닝맨 옛 암어 러닝맨 <br>언제라도 나는 <br>멋지게 서있네 <br>그래 무한해 <br>그게 뭐든 간에 <br>나는 무한해 <br>조금 불안해 <br>뻔한 모든 건 거부하네 <br>그 덕분에 나는 <br>특별하지 너랑 달리 <br>아무것도 없는 데서 <br>일으켜네 창조해 <br>혼신의 힘을 다해 <br>덤벼 난 그래 <br>니가 못한 건 <br>내가 해네 <br>이런 나이기에 uh <br>그런 삶이기에 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>내 플로우 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>나의 재능 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>끝이 없다고 <br>무한대에 가까워 난 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>내 플로우 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>나의 재능 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>끝이 없다고 <br>무한대에 가까워 난 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>너흰 까무러치지 <br>지 지금 이걸 듣고 있으니 <br>니 인생 니 미래 그 결과가 <br>날 최종단계라 치지 <br>G6 지겹다고 이젠 지미랄 <br>얼 데이 올 타임 인 마 <br>홈타운 강남 like 조강지처 <br>한강물 떠 팔아 봉이 김선달 <br>봐 내 수명 길다 못해 무한대로가 <br>모아 담배 갑이 <br>내 키만큼 쌓였지만 <br>폐암 not in ma list <br>버킷 와우 <br>내일터 강남 <br>해가지기도 전에 동이 터 <br>명문대 연봉8천 <br>명함도 못 내밀어 <br>그야말로 무한대 <br>무한도 블랙카드 가진 <br>어느 회사 회장 직함단 <br>할배들의 놀이터 <br>물고 뜯고 맛보고 <br>즐기진 못해 호텔 <br>팁 받아 먹어 모아 <br>맥북 받아봐 내 손에 get <br>고객님들 지갑이 <br>흡사 대서양 바닷물 뺨치네 <br>고객님 성깔이 진상 <br>요우커 중국인 판치네 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>내 플로우 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>나의 재능 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>끝이 없다고 <br>무한대에 가까워 난 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>내 플로우 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>나의 재능 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>끝이 없다고 <br>무한대에 가까워 난 <br>어딜 봐도 나 같은 건 <br>없지 유일해 <br>밀고 당기는 게 주특기네 <br>예전에 누가 <br>나보고는 래퍼랑은 <br>어울리지 않는 댔지만 <br>이제 완전하게 나 답네 <br>나 다운 게 뭔데 <br>나는 무한한대 <br>컨트롤이 힘들뿐 <br>한계가 없네 <br>한 놈씩 제껴 <br>이젠 얼마 안 남았어 <br>얼른 내게 앵겨 <br>다들 탐을 내는 내 옆 <br>매력 잠재력 <br>다 때려 메이 웨더 <br>외로운 곳에 홀로 <br>올라 가있지 <br>나는 완전 나만의 <br>삶을 살지 <br>마찬가지로 난 <br>나만의 랩핑 <br>가장 중요하게 <br>생각하는 건 재미 <br>넌 이런 삶을 <br>감당할 수 있어 <br>이게 나의 삶 uh <br>이게 나니까 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>내 플로우 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>나의 재능 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>끝이 없다고 <br>무한대에 가까워 난 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>내 플로우 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>나의 재능 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>끝이 없다고 <br>무한대에 가까워 난 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>무한대에 가까워 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="무한대에 가까워 (Feat. 더블캐슬)" label="무한대에 가까워 (Feat. 더블캐슬)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/그냥/</id><title>헤이노 - 그냥 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:30:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:30:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EA%B7%B8%EB%83%A5/" title="헤이노 - 그냥 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[더는 모르겠어 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>다 이기면 되는 거야 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>내가 하면 돼 <br>혼자 하면 돼 <br>전부 내 탓 <br>내가 짊어져야 했던 거야 <br>더는 모르겠어 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>다 이기면 되는 거야 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>내가 하면 돼 <br>혼자 하면 돼 <br>전부 내 탓 <br>내가 짊어져야 했던 거야 <br>결국 모든 원인들은 <br>나 자신에게 <br>그냥 내가 최고가 <br>돼 다짐했네 <br>뭐 땜에 누구 땜에 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>내가 잘하면 되는 거야 <br>그래 그냥 <br>더 분발해 몸을 <br>데워놔 언제라도 <br>재빠르게 준비되게 <br>다 해두라고 <br>방심하는 순간 <br>무너져 명심하고 <br>앞으론 절대 지지 <br>않기로 해 <br>성공과 실패 어차피 <br>계속 할거라면 <br>신경 끄고 그냥 <br>온 힘을 다하는 게 나 <br>믿지 말아 그냥 <br>내가 다하는 게 나아 <br>같이 망할 바엔 <br>혼자 잘하는 게 나아 <br>팀 따위 몰라 <br>그런 거 잘 못해 그냥 <br>내가 하나부터 열까지 <br>해버리면 되지 <br>혼자뿐인 길 <br>그래 그냥 혼자뿐이길 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>나만 있음 된다고 <br>더는 모르겠어 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>다 이기면 되는 거야 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>내가 하면 돼 <br>혼자 하면 돼 <br>전부 내 탓 <br>내가 짊어져야 했던 거야 <br>더는 모르겠어 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>다 이기면 되는 거야 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>내가 하면 돼 <br>혼자 하면 돼 <br>전부 내 탓 <br>내가 짊어져야 했던 거야 <br>니가 내가 별로라고 <br>말해도 난 몰라 <br>이 노래가 어떻던 간 <br>이건 내 꺼야 <br>저리 가버려 뭔가 <br>착각하고 있는데 <br>난 착한 사람이 아냐 <br>너를 위한 노래도 아니고 <br>내 맘대로 할래 <br>어쩌라는 거야 <br>사람들은 나를 <br>너무 귀찮게 해 <br>니가 원하는 건 <br>니가 만들면 돼 <br>딴 놈을 원하면은 <br>그냥 걔를 만나 <br>뭐야 나도 두 번째가 <br>되긴 싫어 안 해 <br>집어 쳐 굶어 죽고 말아 <br>구걸 안 해 <br>나는 오직 <br>내가 되길 원해 <br>열심히 살뿐이야 <br>어차피 금방 죽어 <br>아무리 힘들어도 <br>딱 한 번 뿐이잖아 <br>나는 내 맘대로 <br>살아볼래 간섭 마 <br>니네 도움 필요 없어 <br>다시 가져가 <br>모르겠어 다 귀찮아 <br>이제 난 정말 <br>더는 모르겠어 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>다 이기면 되는 거야 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>내가 하면 돼 <br>혼자 하면 돼 <br>전부 내 탓 <br>내가 짊어져야 했던 거야 <br>더는 모르겠어 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>다 이기면 되는 거야 <br>다 귀찮아 그냥 <br>내가 하면 돼 <br>혼자 하면 돼 <br>전부 내 탓 <br>내가 짊어져야 했던 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="그냥" label="그냥"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤이노/갖고놀아/</id><title>헤이노 - 갖고놀아 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:30:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:30:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%B4%EB%85%B8/%EA%B0%96%EA%B3%A0%EB%86%80%EC%95%84/" title="헤이노 - 갖고놀아 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>아예 지배하지 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>마치 아이 같이 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>아예 지배하지 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>마치 아이 같이 <br>너가 원하는 걸 <br>내가 가지고 있어 <br>난 독특한 분위기를 <br>가지고 있어 <br>너넨 갖지 못하는걸 <br>가지고 있어 <br>난 매일 좋은 관계를 <br>가지고 있어 <br>오늘 밤엔 내가 <br>너를 그냥 가질게 <br>너의 작은 세상이 <br>온통 망가지게 <br>색다른걸 원해 <br>다른 놈들 너무 뻔해 <br>재미없는 것들 빼버리고 <br>놀자고 어때 <br>맨날 술만 쳐먹는 거 <br>지겹다고 너넨 <br>헛소리만 늘어놔 <br>어딜 가도 뻔해 <br>너 자신을 보여주기 <br>겁나나 봐 <br>징징거릴 거면 <br>너네 엄마랑 가 <br>왜 자꾸 시간을 날려 <br>재미없다고 난 더 <br>흥미롭고 유익한걸 <br>원해 고난도 <br>거기 여자애는 <br>놔둬 내꺼니까 <br>난 무척 얌전해 <br>괜히 날뛰지마 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>아예 지배하지 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>마치 아이 같이 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>다들 나를 보지 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>밤이 나를 찾지 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>아예 지배하지 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>마치 아이 같이 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>다들 나를 보지 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>밤이 나를 찾지 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>어딜 가도 백퍼 <br>분위기는 내꺼 <br>절대 본 적 없을 만한 <br>랩퍼 난 헤이노 <br>절대 안 뺏겨 <br>유일한 내 flow <br>하나같이 다 똑같은 <br>래퍼들만 떼로 <br>모여서 덤벼봐야 <br>내가 갖고놀아 널 <br>지루하기만한 <br>놈들 자꾸 뭐라고 <br>떠들어봐야 시끄러 <br>입 다물어 줘 <br>이젠 나의 차례 일로 <br>싹 다 모여줘 <br>이제부턴 여긴 <br>내가 접수해 갖고 놀아대 <br>어렸을 때부터 <br>난 이걸 갖고 놀았네 <br>아무도 모를만한 걸 <br>난 가지고 있어 <br>내 삶의 저작권은 <br>내가 가지고 있어 <br>난 갖고 놀아 <br>난 나의 삶을 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 난 <br>오늘 밤을 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 난 <br>이순간을 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 막 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>아예 지배하지 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>마치 아이 같이 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>다들 나를 보지 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>밤이 나를 찾지 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>아예 지배하지 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>마치 아이 같이 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>다들 나를 보지 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>밤이 나를 찾지 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>갖고 놀아 갖고 놀아 <br>갖고 놀아 널 <br>]]></content><category term="헤이노" label="헤이노"/><category term="갖고놀아" label="갖고놀아"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Into_Decay/</id><title>Meshuggah - Into Decay - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Into_Decay/" title="Meshuggah - Into Decay - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The most eloquent confession, your silence <br>The most admitting trait, your turning away <br>Avert your eyes and hush your struggling thoughts <br>Detachment assumed as life mutates into decay <br><br>The most manifest sign, your disregard <br>The one apparent fault, your shunning of care <br>Contempt now bred, refed and well sustained <br>Division now groomed, nurtured and will maintained <br><br>Apathy, opprobrium <br>Virulence and animosity <br>This sums you up <br>Betrayal, disunion and fear, isolation <br><br>Caught in this endless spiral, locked equilibrium <br>A stasis founded in this atrophy of thought <br>Your eyes unflinching, unaffected by the misery <br>Gone is commiseration, gone is any sympathy <br><br>One last farewell to perspicacity <br>Final surrender to futility <br>Dissociation, severance <br>What have you done <br>What have you become]]></content><category term="Meshuggah" label="Meshuggah"/><category term="Into Decay" label="Into Decay"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Our_Rage_Wont_Die/</id><title>Meshuggah - Our Rage Won`t Die - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Our_Rage_Wont_Die/" title="Meshuggah - Our Rage Won`t Die - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cry if you need to, disguise, evade, hide <br>Run 'til you hit water, then swim <br>Murder in your wake, plan, commit, exact <br>You have earned our rage, now fly <br><br>Beg if you have to, trade away your pride <br>Run 'til you hit ground, then dig <br>Death in your wake, those fantasies enacted <br>You will learn that our rage won't die <br><br>You will surely pay the ultimate price <br>There is no way you will escape our retribution <br>It will not matter how long it takes <br>You took them from us so we will take you <br><br>Do you believe that luck will somehow stand you by <br>Do you really think our resolve will wane <br>Do you really think that it will dissipate <br><br>We will haunt you, we will come for you <br>To collect on what you owe to us <br>Eye for eye, life for life <br>Only payment in full can end this strife]]></content><category term="Meshuggah" label="Meshuggah"/><category term="Our Rage Won`t Die" label="Our Rage Won`t Die"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Nostrum/</id><title>Meshuggah - Nostrum - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Nostrum/" title="Meshuggah - Nostrum - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Jealous vengeful fabrication <br>Halo crowned invention <br>Sacred universal lie <br>Artificial divine <br>Great archaic obsoletum <br>A prevarication <br>Deceitfully contrived <br><br>Synthesized fictitious <br>Dreamed up by remote prototypes <br>Opiate for the yearning mass <br>Administered applied <br>Three letter word for monster <br><br>Empty promises of healing <br>Profit aptly buried in the lies <br>An industry rapt with avarice <br>Medicating blind <br>Its acolytes <br><br>Useless panacea <br>Imaginary cure all <br>To you we cry and supplicate <br>Into your hell we fall <br>Blind belief in their eyes <br>Forever atoning, credulously waiting <br>Gazing to the skies]]></content><category term="Meshuggah" label="Meshuggah"/><category term="Nostrum" label="Nostrum"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Stifled/</id><title>Meshuggah - Stifled - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Stifled/" title="Meshuggah - Stifled - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Impotent king beneath our feet <br>You can rule down where you belong <br>In dirt compacted, buried deep, you dwell with those you wronged <br><br>Down there you can whisper, yell, even blare your odious lies <br>To your silent audience of worms as they share with you, your eyes <br><br>Tyrant, oppressor <br>Your once resounding voice now just muted cries <br><br>You self avowed murderous god <br>Ranks of annelids now you delegate <br>Your commands unheard under ground <br>Where your voice will never resonate <br><br>Your time has come <br>Declare the majesty fallen <br>Your dominance, your hateful influence forever stifled <br><br>Your sleep no longer impermanent <br>Decaying matter now sums you up <br>Like all the lives you've taken <br>Now so are you retreating to dust]]></content><category term="Meshuggah" label="Meshuggah"/><category term="Stifled" label="Stifled"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Ivory_Tower/</id><title>Meshuggah - Ivory Tower - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Ivory_Tower/" title="Meshuggah - Ivory Tower - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Why mourn this travesty <br>Hide this slow degradation <br>Claw and compete mindlessly <br>All things undone too late <br><br>Craving our waking sleep <br>Is binding us to this ivory tower <br>Serves to complete the truth that we cling onto <br><br>So what are these things you hold true <br>The defensive wounds of the unknowing eye <br>Weeping thousands of wretched tears <br>To lubricate the end with our fear <br>The concussion from the crack of the whip <br>Nullifies, sensations die <br>Always numbing, always preaching <br>Never resting, never sleeping <br><br>The construction is our penance here <br>Tumorous growth chiseled in white <br>When the darkness comes to slay the day <br>Enters horrors that you'll be wishing away <br><br>Which is the way]]></content><category term="Meshuggah" label="Meshuggah"/><category term="Ivory Tower" label="Ivory Tower"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Violent_Sleep_Of_Reason/</id><title>Meshuggah - Violent Sleep Of Reason - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Violent_Sleep_Of_Reason/" title="Meshuggah - Violent Sleep Of Reason - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A systematically applied veil to heedless eyes <br>Focus deflected, ignore <br>This is not our war <br>Bury the abject shame in the same bile as our ideals <br>The potent lubricant to deceits grinding wheels <br><br>The menacing implications, the violent sleep of reason <br>Betrayal we all help sustain <br>Humanitarian treason <br>This deadly inclination, this forfeiture of innocence <br>The sacrifice of guiltless souls for our own deliverance <br><br>The pain you feel <br>Indifference thrust into your back <br>Forged from our ignorance from our immorality <br>A parody, this mockery <br>To no avail you kneel before this our insanity <br><br>Another life condemned <br>Your fate sealed the second you came to exist <br>Your suffering non essential for we care not if you subsist <br><br>We will all belie ang allusion, any crime <br>Cower and hide any culpability denied <br><br>All will imply it's an illusion, a fallacy <br>So when you die, remember we said it's not reality]]></content><category term="Meshuggah" label="Meshuggah"/><category term="Violent Sleep Of Reason" label="Violent Sleep Of Reason"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/By_The_Ton/</id><title>Meshuggah - By The Ton - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/By_The_Ton/" title="Meshuggah - By The Ton - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[To you a beast you think you comprehend <br>Not necessarily made all evil <br>In the reflective pool of your eyes <br>I see fear and intrigue co mingle <br><br>You hesitate to deem me all bad <br>Yet when my face is shown, your eyes avert <br>New thoughts sprout from that fearfilled soil <br>Your nerves and intuition back on full alert <br><br>You think that you've seen the truth, you think you know <br>Yet disbelief grinds, the doubt it claws <br>In your sleepless delirium I devour your thoughts <br><br>If you only knew how your way of life sustains me <br><br>Like electricity coursing through my soul <br>Your will to retaliate, your vengeful thoughts announced <br>I bring you me conflict and death <br>And the promise of spilling red by the ton <br><br>I just might be there in your final moment <br>I just might be the last thing your eyes take in]]></content><category term="Meshuggah" label="Meshuggah"/><category term="By The Ton" label="By The Ton"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/MonstroCity/</id><title>Meshuggah - MonstroCity - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/MonstroCity/" title="Meshuggah - MonstroCity - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Skyline draped in shimmering red <br>Irradiant and treacherous <br>Neon prophecies hail the end, the capital of piety <br><br>Totalitarianopolis, city of dread <br>The glorious streets of dystopia continuously running red <br><br>This is where self is relinquished <br>Autonomy sacrificed <br>The idolatry of tyrants compulsory <br><br>Welcome all to MonstroCity where norm is that of the insane <br>All is illusion in MonstroCity <br>Bow to it, it knows your name <br><br>Relishing the idea of damnation <br>The wailing and gnashing of teeth <br>They know for sure where judgment's due <br>What's above and what's beneath <br><br>This is where we fail, where the self righteous reign <br>The empire of imaginary ghosts <br>This is blind credulity's domain <br><br>MonstroCity <br><br>In here everyone knows the truth <br>Which unforgiving icon is real <br>Intolerance and prejudice saturates their zeal <br><br>This is where self is relinquished <br>Autonomy sacrificed <br>The idolatry of tyrants compulsory]]></content><category term="Meshuggah" label="Meshuggah"/><category term="MonstroCity" label="MonstroCity"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Born_In_Dissonance/</id><title>Meshuggah - Born In Dissonance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Born_In_Dissonance/" title="Meshuggah - Born In Dissonance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We are origin <br>We are increate <br>You will see our coming for a thousand years <br>Every violent element incarnate <br>Made flesh and fused to one <br>You may call us remnant, as we are all that will be left <br><br>Brought forth by ancient whisper <br>Deployed by inverse suns <br>To capture the essence of creation <br>And render it undone <br><br>We come to make all things collide <br>Those joules define what we are <br>An energy born in dissonance <br>Long before first ever star <br><br>Baptized in the river you call time <br>We know that we are sacred <br>In human tongue we're apocalypse <br>For we bring with us obliteration <br><br>Through spectacles tuned to infinity <br>You will see our coming for a thousand years <br>You will know us then for what we truly are <br>The realization of every fear]]></content><category term="Meshuggah" label="Meshuggah"/><category term="Born In Dissonance" label="Born In Dissonance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Clockworks/</id><title>Meshuggah - Clockworks - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Meshuggah/Clockworks/" title="Meshuggah - Clockworks - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Dismantling the clockwork that makes me the cynic <br>Pallet, wheel and click <br>The properties of my indifference <br>Reverse engineering what makes it tick <br>Dissecting the finetuned mechanism <br>Rack and barrel, spring and pin <br>Its synchronous characteristics <br>To kill what makes it spin <br><br>Disassemble this machinery <br>Re program these eyes, undo this design <br><br>Labelled and filed, each part indexed <br>Broken to pieces then thoroughly burned <br>Deconstruction of what I am <br>Buried to make sure he never returns <br>Taken apart, defused, blueprints turned to ashes <br>Eradicate the last remains, remnants of the insane <br><br>Disintegration, the destruction of me now imperative <br>To purge myself of this condition, complete this dissolution a necessity <br><br>Break this deceitful machine <br><br>A lie, what once I was, obsolete instrument <br>An outmoded contraption, a malfunctioning device <br><br>That callous self now extinguished, that malignant self now disused <br>That conceited invention to nothing now reduced <br><br>Complete disintegration, the destruction of me now imperative <br>To purge myself of this condition, complete this dissolution a necessity <br><br>Break this deceitful machine]]></content><category term="Meshuggah" label="Meshuggah"/><category term="Clockworks" label="Clockworks"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chris_Lane/Drinkin_Games/</id><title>Chris_Lane - Drinkin` Games - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:34:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:34:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Chris_Lane/Drinkin_Games/" title="Chris_Lane - Drinkin` Games - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can already see it coming <br>The way you're two drinks in <br>And you're spinning 'round on the floor <br>I ain't sure what you're sipping <br>But I'm sure you're sipping something <br>That'll get you rolling the dice <br>To see if I'm still yours <br><br>Cause when it starts rolling off your lips <br>Baby I'm all in <br><br>You say it all when you say that you miss me <br>Say my name when you lean into kiss me <br>You play it off and blame it on the whiskey <br>Cause you're feeling all tipsy <br>It's game over when you cross that line <br>I lose every time <br><br>When you start drinking <br>Thats when you get to thinking of <br>Swinging right back into my arms <br>Girl, I can't shake it, No I can't take it <br>When you start playing drinking games with my heart <br><br>You pull my shirt and you get a little closer <br>With the buzz in your eyes and the smell of lies on your breath <br>Girl you and I know you would never do it sober <br>But all it takes is one too many for you to forget <br><br>And even though I'll never win <br>Baby here we go again <br><br>You say it all when you say that you miss me <br>Say my name when you lean into kiss me <br>You play it off and blame it on the whiskey <br>Cause you're feeling all tipsy <br>It's game over when you cross that line <br>I lose every time <br><br>When you start drinking <br>Thats when you get to thinking of <br>Swinging right back into my arms <br>Girl, I can't shake it, No I can't take it <br>When you start playing drinking games with my heart <br>You say it all when you say that you miss me <br>Say my name when you lean into kiss me <br>You play it off and blame it on the whiskey <br>Cause you're feeling all tipsy <br>It's game over when you cross that line <br>I lose every time <br><br>When you start drinking <br>Thats when you get to thinking of <br>Swinging right back into my arms <br>Girl, I can't shake it, No I can't take it <br>When you start playing drinking games with my heart <br><br>You can tell when I'm a little bit lonely <br>I know myself and I'm giving in slowly <br>You pour it strong, sip it all night long <br>Then ya get what you want and you're gone in the morning]]></content><category term="Chris Lane" label="Chris Lane"/><category term="Drinkin` Games" label="Drinkin` Games"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coleman_Hell/Witching_Hour/</id><title>Coleman_Hell - Witching Hour - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:35:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:35:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coleman_Hell/Witching_Hour/" title="Coleman_Hell - Witching Hour - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Meet me in the witching hour <br>Make my sins all come undone <br>Lift my spirit with your power <br>Dance until the rising sun <br><br>Kiss me, we're falling from the cliff's peak <br>We're slipping into harm's reach <br>We're marching to the heartbeat of a thousand dreams <br><br>In the witching hour, the witching hour <br>So tell me, are you with me now <br>You with me now <br>You found me in the witching hour, the witching hour <br>So tell me, are you with me now <br>You with me now <br><br>Meet me in the witching hour <br>Make my sins all come undone <br>Lift my spirit with your power <br>Dance until the rising sun <br><br>Godspeed, you're running, trying to break free <br>I'm begging you to take me <br>We're marching to the heartbeat of a thousand loves <br><br>In the witching hour, the witching hour <br>So tell me, are you with me now <br>You with me now <br>You found me in the witching hour, the witching hour <br>So tell me, are you with me now <br>You with me now <br><br>Meet me, meet me <br>Why don't you meet me <br>Oh, why won't you meet me]]></content><category term="Coleman Hell" label="Coleman Hell"/><category term="Witching Hour" label="Witching Hour"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coleman_Hell/2_Heads/</id><title>Coleman_Hell - 2 Heads - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:35:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:35:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coleman_Hell/2_Heads/" title="Coleman_Hell - 2 Heads - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There must be something in the water <br>And there must be something about your daughter <br>She said our love ain't nothing but a monster <br>Our love ain't nothing but a monster <br>With 2 Heads <br><br>I turn to you, you're all I see <br>Our love's a monster with 2 Heads and one heartbeat <br>I turn to you, you're all I see <br>Our love's a monster with 2 Heads and one heartbeat <br>We just got caught up in the moment <br>Why don't you call me in the morning instead <br>Before we turn into a monster <br>Before we turn into a monster with 2 Heads <br><br>I hope to god I'll love you harder <br>I hope to god I'll love you longer <br>If only I could live forever <br>If only I could hold you longer <br><br>There must be something in the water <br>And there must be something about your daughter <br>She said our love ain't nothing but a monster <br>Our love ain't nothing but a monster <br>With 2 Heads <br><br>I turn to you, you're all I see <br>Our love's a monster with 2 Heads and one heartbeat <br>I turn to you, you're all I see <br>Our love's a monster with 2 Heads and one heartbeat <br>We just got caught up in the moment <br>Why don't you call me in the morning instead <br>Before we turn into a monster <br>Before we turn into a monster with 2 Heads <br><br>I hope to god I'll love you harder <br>I hope to god I'll love you longer <br>If only I could live forever <br>If only I could hold you longer <br><br>Well I hope to god I'll love you harder <br>I hope to god I'll love you longer <br>If only I could live forever <br>If only I could hold you longer]]></content><category term="Coleman Hell" label="Coleman Hell"/><category term="2 Heads" label="2 Heads"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coleman_Hell/Fireproof/</id><title>Coleman_Hell - Fireproof - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:35:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:35:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coleman_Hell/Fireproof/" title="Coleman_Hell - Fireproof - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know me and you <br>Must be fireproof with all the hell that we've been through <br>When all our lovin' lost its charm <br>Learned to make a shelter out in the storm Hey <br>Made it out of the cold <br>Climbed a mountain and I stepped on burning coals <br>When all our lovin' fell apart <br>Someone left the light on out in the dark <br><br>You and I <br>We've both been <br>Through hell and high water <br>I'll be yours, you'll be mine <br>We'll be fireproof tonight <br>There's a spark catching fire <br>Feel it getting hotter <br>I'll be yours, you'll be mine <br>We'll be fireproof <br>We'll be fireproof <br><br>Did you know you and me <br>Must be fireproof with all these flames between our sheets <br>When all our lovin' was almost gone <br>Made some in the moonlight before the dawn Hey <br>Made it out of the heat <br>Crossed the desert and we sailed the seven seas <br>When all our lovin' felt so wrong <br>Found out all the hard times just made us strong <br><br>You and I <br>We've both been <br>Through hell and high water <br>I'll be yours, you'll be mine <br>We'll be fireproof tonight <br>There's a spark catching fire <br>Feel it getting hotter <br>I'll be yours, you'll be mine <br>We'll be fireproof <br>Fireproof <br>We'll be fireproof <br>Fireproof <br><br>You and I <br>We've both been <br>Through hell and high water <br>I'll be yours, you'll be mine <br>We'll be fireproof tonight <br>There's a spark catching fire <br>Feel it getting hotter <br>I'll be yours, you'll be mine <br>We'll be fireproof]]></content><category term="Coleman Hell" label="Coleman Hell"/><category term="Fireproof" label="Fireproof"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coleman_Hell/Summerland/</id><title>Coleman_Hell - Summerland - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:35:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:35:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Coleman_Hell/Summerland/" title="Coleman_Hell - Summerland - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't want to die today <br>But if I do, send me up to Summerland <br>I don't got no time to waste <br>Heaven is a place called Summerland <br><br>I might come back as a wombat <br>In my other life, I was a butterfly <br>Can you hear the spirits calling <br>Oh we oh we oh ay, oh we oh we oh <br><br>In Summerland <br>In Summerland, in Summerland <br>In Summerland, in Summerland <br>In Summerland, in Summerland <br>In Summerland, in Summerland <br><br>I don't want to die today <br>I don't want to leave and never come back <br>I just gotta find my way <br>Looking for a place called Summerland <br><br>Triple goddess in the forest <br>Can you carry my soul up to paradise <br>Shh, I think I hear their voices <br>Oh we oh we oh ay, oh we oh we oh <br><br>In Summerland <br>In Summerland, in Summerland <br>In Summerland, in Summerland <br>In Summerland, in Summerland <br>In Summerland, in Summerland <br>In Summerland, in Summerland <br><br>The sinners and the saints <br>They all go to Summerland <br>A heaven full of second chances <br>A place where everyone can start again]]></content><category term="Coleman Hell" label="Coleman Hell"/><category term="Summerland" label="Summerland"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/벽시계_Inst/</id><title>신용재_포맨 - 벽시계 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:37:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:37:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EB%B2%BD%EC%8B%9C%EA%B3%84_Inst/" title="신용재_포맨 - 벽시계 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뒤척이다 눈을 뜬 밤 <br>텅 빈 방안 결국 날 일으켜 <br>마치 일년 같았던 <br>하루 속에 자꾸 바보처럼 <br>서툴기만 했던 나 <br>또 멍하니 시계만 보고 있어 <br>Oh You You You <br>너 없는 모든 게 멈춘 것 같은데 <br>Baby It's You You You <br>여전히 모든 게 널 떠올리게 해 <br>Baby <br>매일 널 바래다 주며 <br>입 맞추던 열두 시 <br>매일 밤 아쉬워 하며 <br>전화를 끊던 한 시 <br>진짜 잘 자라던 두 시 <br>그때로 흘러가 다시 <br>You You You <br>왜 갈수록 기억은 선명한지 <br>고장난 마음이 반대로 흐르나 봐 <br>습관처럼 시계만 보고 있어 <br>Oh You You You <br>너 없는 모든 게 멈춘 것 같은데 <br>Baby It's You You You <br>여전히 모든 게 널 떠올리게 해 <br>Baby It's You You You <br>여전히 모든 게 <br>Everything Is You <br>널 떠올리게 해 <br>Baby <br>마지막 인사를 한 채 <br>돌아서던 열두 시 <br>매일 밤 조금은 취해 <br>전화를 걸던 한 시 <br>끝내 울어버린 두 시 <br>애써 눈을감아 다시 <br>You You You <br>Oh You You <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="벽시계 (Inst.)" label="벽시계 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/지구와_달_Inst/</id><title>신용재_포맨 - 지구와 달 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:37:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:37:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EC%A7%80%EA%B5%AC%EC%99%80_%EB%8B%AC_Inst/" title="신용재_포맨 - 지구와 달 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[얼마나 오래 따라온 걸까 <br>멀고 험한 길도 어디든 다 <br>그대란 지구 뒷 편의 달 <br>그 밤들을 비추던 나 <br>날 기억도 못하겠지만 <br>날 짐작도 못했겠지만 <br>그대 곁을 맴도는 하나 <br>그중에 하나 <br>멀리 있지만 늘 함께였어 난 <br>몰랐겠지만 늘 함께였어 난 <br>아주 오랜 시간을 이렇게 <br>하나만을 바라며 oh <br>그대와 난 지구와 달 하늘과 땅 <br>아침과 밤 바다와 강 <br>조금은 떨어진 듯 가까운 곳에 <br>그곳에 내가 서있어 <br>단 하루만 단 한 번만 <br>이대로만 나 하나만 바라봐 줘 <br>하루를 일년처럼 <br>기다려온 날 위해 <br>같은 시간 속을 걷지만 <br>다른 세상에 있는 것 같아 <br>손으로 대본 적 없지만 <br>그대는 정말 따뜻할 것 같아 <br>큰 걸 바라지 않아 <br>혼자하는 사랑 <br>이것도 나쁘진 않아 <br>난 그냥 이대로만 그대의 뒤에서 <br>바라만 볼 수 있다면 좋아 <br>멀리 있지만 늘 함께였어 난 <br>몰랐겠지만 늘 함께였어 난 <br>평생 떼낼 수 없는 그림자로 <br>그대 뒤에 살게 나 <br>그대와 난 지구와 달하늘과 땅 <br>아침과 밤 바다와 강 <br>조금은 떨어진 듯 가까운 곳에 <br>그래 거기 내가 여기 있어 <br>단 하루만 단 한 번만 <br>이대로만 나 하나만 바라봐 줘 <br>하루를 일년처럼 <br>기다려온 날 위해 <br>Don't make me leave you so far <br>Don't make me loose all my light <br>Don't make me leave you so far <br>Don't make me loose all my light <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="지구와 달 (Inst.)" label="지구와 달 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/빌려줄게_Inst/</id><title>신용재_포맨 - 빌려줄게 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:37:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:37:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EB%B9%8C%EB%A0%A4%EC%A4%84%EA%B2%8C_Inst/" title="신용재_포맨 - 빌려줄게 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혼자 있기 힘들 때 <br>나를 빌려줄게 <br>힘이 들면 언제나 <br>내게 기대면 돼 <br>흘러내린 눈물을 <br>멈출 수 없다면 <br>내 어깰 빌려줄게 <br>내게 적시면 돼 <br>불을 다 켜봐도 <br>맘이 어둡다 느끼고 <br>몸을 뉘어봐도 <br>맘을 놓을 수 없다면 <br>잠시 날 빌려줄게 <br>기대도 돼 <br>주저 말고 내게 와 <br>길었던 그 하루가 <br>힘겨웠을 테니까 그대 <br>아무 말 안해도 돼 <br>it’s alright it’s alright <br>왜 나만 안되지 <br>생각은 무거워지고 <br>내일이 두려워 <br>잠이 들 수가 없다면 <br>잠시 날 빌려줄게 <br>기대도 돼 <br>주저 말고 내게 와 <br>길었던 그 하루가 <br>힘겨웠을 테니까 그대 <br>아무 말 안해도 돼 <br>it’s alright oh <br>아무도 그 하루에 <br>관심이 없대도 <br>더는 외롭지 않게 <br>내가 들어줄게 <br>소리내 울어도 돼 <br>그래도 돼 <br>원한다면 언제나 <br>혼자여도 괜찮아 <br>무너져도 괜찮아 <br>이제 내가 널 안아줄게 <br>it’s alright it’s alright <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="빌려줄게 (Inst.)" label="빌려줄게 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/벽시계/</id><title>신용재_포맨 - 벽시계 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:37:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:37:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EB%B2%BD%EC%8B%9C%EA%B3%84/" title="신용재_포맨 - 벽시계 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뒤척이다 눈을 뜬 밤 <br>텅 빈 방안 결국 날 일으켜 <br>마치 일년 같았던 <br>하루 속에 자꾸 바보처럼 <br>서툴기만 했던 나 <br>또 멍하니 시계만 보고 있어 <br>Oh You You You <br>너 없는 모든 게 멈춘 것 같은데 <br>Baby It's You You You <br>여전히 모든 게 널 떠올리게 해 <br>Baby <br>매일 널 바래다 주며 <br>입 맞추던 열두 시 <br>매일 밤 아쉬워 하며 <br>전화를 끊던 한 시 <br>진짜 잘 자라던 두 시 <br>그때로 흘러가 다시 <br>You You You <br>왜 갈수록 기억은 선명한지 <br>고장난 마음이 반대로 흐르나 봐 <br>습관처럼 시계만 보고 있어 <br>Oh You You You <br>너 없는 모든 게 멈춘 것 같은데 <br>Baby It's You You You <br>여전히 모든 게 널 떠올리게 해 <br>Baby It's You You You <br>여전히 모든 게 <br>Everything Is You <br>널 떠올리게 해 <br>Baby <br>마지막 인사를 한 채 <br>돌아서던 열두 시 <br>매일 밤 조금은 취해 <br>전화를 걸던 한 시 <br>끝내 울어버린 두 시 <br>애써 눈을감아 다시 <br>You You You <br>Oh You You <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="벽시계" label="벽시계"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/지구와_달/</id><title>신용재_포맨 - 지구와 달 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:37:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:37:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EC%A7%80%EA%B5%AC%EC%99%80_%EB%8B%AC/" title="신용재_포맨 - 지구와 달 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[얼마나 오래 따라온 걸까 <br>멀고 험한 길도 어디든 다 <br>그대란 지구 뒷 편의 달 <br>그 밤들을 비추던 나 <br>날 기억도 못하겠지만 <br>날 짐작도 못했겠지만 <br>그대 곁을 맴도는 하나 <br>그중에 하나 <br>멀리 있지만 늘 함께였어 난 <br>몰랐겠지만 늘 함께였어 난 <br>아주 오랜 시간을 이렇게 <br>하나만을 바라며 oh <br>그대와 난 지구와 달 하늘과 땅 <br>아침과 밤 바다와 강 <br>조금은 떨어진 듯 가까운 곳에 <br>그곳에 내가 서있어 <br>단 하루만 단 한 번만 <br>이대로만 나 하나만 바라봐 줘 <br>하루를 일년처럼 <br>기다려온 날 위해 <br>같은 시간 속을 걷지만 <br>다른 세상에 있는 것 같아 <br>손으로 대본 적 없지만 <br>그대는 정말 따뜻할 것 같아 <br>큰 걸 바라지 않아 <br>혼자하는 사랑 <br>이것도 나쁘진 않아 <br>난 그냥 이대로만 그대의 뒤에서 <br>바라만 볼 수 있다면 좋아 <br>멀리 있지만 늘 함께였어 난 <br>몰랐겠지만 늘 함께였어 난 <br>평생 떼낼 수 없는 그림자로 <br>그대 뒤에 살게 나 <br>그대와 난 지구와 달하늘과 땅 <br>아침과 밤 바다와 강 <br>조금은 떨어진 듯 가까운 곳에 <br>그래 거기 내가 여기 있어 <br>단 하루만 단 한 번만 <br>이대로만 나 하나만 바라봐 줘 <br>하루를 일년처럼 <br>기다려온 날 위해 <br>Don't make me leave you so far <br>Don't make me loose all my light <br>Don't make me leave you so far <br>Don't make me loose all my light <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="지구와 달" label="지구와 달"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/혼잣말/</id><title>신용재_포맨 - 혼잣말 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:37:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:37:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%ED%98%BC%EC%9E%A3%EB%A7%90/" title="신용재_포맨 - 혼잣말 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 삶에 가장 빛나던 그 순간에 <br>내 꿈에 온통 네가 <br>가득했었던 날에 <br>내 손에 너의 손을 <br>그렇게 꼭 쥐고 다니던 <br>날들이 이젠 일기처럼 <br>지나간 일이지만 <br>왜 보냈어 <br>네가 떠난 후의 혼잣말 <br>버릇처럼 잊을 수 없는 걸 <br>내겐 너였단 걸 알면서 <br>다 알면서 왜 그랬어 <br>너를 보내고 내 모든게 <br>빛을 잃었어 나 <br>돌아보면 전부 너였어 <br>미안해 내게 남은건 그 한마디 <br>행복해 넌 들을 수 없지만 <br>진심이야 난 <br>내 품에 안겨있던 <br>너를 잊을순 없겠지만 <br>이젠 난 너의 추억속에 <br>남겨진 사람인걸 <br>왜 보냈어 <br>네가 떠난 후의 혼잣말 <br>버릇처럼 후회만 남을 걸 <br>너만 기다릴 걸 알면서 <br>다 알면서 왜 그랬어 <br>너를 보내고 <br>내 가슴이 멈춰버렸어 <br>소리없이 나 혼자 하는 말 <br>내 전부였던 네가 그리워 <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="혼잣말" label="혼잣말"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/맥박/</id><title>신용재_포맨 - 맥박 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:37:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:37:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EB%A7%A5%EB%B0%95/" title="신용재_포맨 - 맥박 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 뛰고 있었지 사랑이기에 <br>절대 믿어 의심치 않았지 <br>너무 빠르게 뛰어 <br>지친 줄도 모르고 <br>우린 믿어 의심치 않았지 <br>돌아오긴 희박 하다는 거 알아 <br>헛된 기댄 도박이란 것도 알아 <br>나 미치도록 절박했던 내 맘 <br>너를 위해 뛰던 내 맘 <br>이젠 맥박조차 뛰지 않아 <br>소리없이 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 <br>소리없이 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 <br>난 뛰고 있었지 사랑하나로 <br>그땐 믿어 의심치 않았지 <br>너무 빠르게 뛰어 <br>지친줄도 모르고 <br>우린 믿어 의심치 않았지 <br>돌아오긴 희박 하다는 거 알아 <br>헛된 기댄 도박이란 것도 알아 <br>나 미치도록 절박했던 내 맘 <br>너를 위해 뛰던 내 맘 <br>이젠 맥박조차 뛰질 않아 <br>소리없이 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 <br>소리없이 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 <br>천둥처럼 다시 넌 <br>내게 울려 퍼져가 너 너 <br>돌아오긴 희박 하다는 거 알아도 <br>헛된 기댄 도박이란 걸 다 알아도 <br>여전히 나 절박했던 내 맘 <br>너를 위해 뛰던 내 맘 <br>아직 너를 향해 뛰고 있어 <br>소리없이 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 <br>소리없이 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 쿵 <br>소리없이 쿵 쿵 쿵 <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="맥박" label="맥박"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신용재_포맨/빌려줄게/</id><title>신용재_포맨 - 빌려줄게 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:37:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:37:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%9A%A9%EC%9E%AC_%ED%8F%AC%EB%A7%A8/%EB%B9%8C%EB%A0%A4%EC%A4%84%EA%B2%8C/" title="신용재_포맨 - 빌려줄게 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혼자 있기 힘들 때 <br>나를 빌려줄게 <br>힘이 들면 언제나 <br>내게 기대면 돼 <br>흘러내린 눈물을 <br>멈출 수 없다면 <br>내 어깰 빌려줄게 <br>내게 적시면 돼 <br>불을 다 켜봐도 <br>맘이 어둡다 느끼고 <br>몸을 뉘어봐도 <br>맘을 놓을 수 없다면 <br>잠시 날 빌려줄게 <br>기대도 돼 <br>주저 말고 내게 와 <br>길었던 그 하루가 <br>힘겨웠을 테니까 그대 <br>아무 말 안해도 돼 <br>it’s alright it’s alright <br>왜 나만 안되지 <br>생각은 무거워지고 <br>내일이 두려워 <br>잠이 들 수가 없다면 <br>잠시 날 빌려줄게 <br>기대도 돼 <br>주저 말고 내게 와 <br>길었던 그 하루가 <br>힘겨웠을 테니까 그대 <br>아무 말 안해도 돼 <br>it’s alright oh <br>아무도 그 하루에 <br>관심이 없대도 <br>더는 외롭지 않게 <br>내가 들어줄게 <br>소리내 울어도 돼 <br>그래도 돼 <br>원한다면 언제나 <br>혼자여도 괜찮아 <br>무너져도 괜찮아 <br>이제 내가 널 안아줄게 <br>it’s alright it’s alright <br>]]></content><category term="신용재 (포맨)" label="신용재 (포맨)"/><category term="빌려줄게" label="빌려줄게"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pavlic/Btob/</id><title>Pavlic - Btob - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:38:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:38:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pavlic/Btob/" title="Pavlic - Btob - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm solid, not apparition <br>Better check your vision, see what you're missing, boy <br>I don't need your permission <br>To go on existing with or without you, boy <br>I ain't gonna let it go, 'cause this been going on too long <br><br>I won't be another ghost <br>No, I won't be invisible <br>You see me everywhere you go <br>No, I won't be invisible, yeah <br><br>Invisible <br>Invisible <br><br>I had my suspicions, you kept me at a distance <br>I ain't disappearing, boy <br>I thought you were worth it <br>Pulling back the curtain <br>I see why I was hurting boy <br>And I ain't gonna let it go <br>Now you see me with the lights on <br><br>I won't be another ghost <br>No, I won't be invisible <br>You see me everywhere you go <br>No, I won't be invisible, yeah <br><br>Invisible <br>Invisible <br><br>I won't be diminished, eclipsed, or hidden <br>You're gonna see my light blaze black to life <br>Like the phoenix rise <br>I won't be diminished, eclipsed, or hidden <br>You're gonna see my light blaze black to life <br>Like the phoenix rise <br><br>Invisible <br>Invisible <br>Invisible, tonight]]></content><category term="Pavlic" label="Pavlic"/><category term="Btob" label="Btob"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Twenty_One_Pilots/Stressed_Out/</id><title>Twenty_One_Pilots - Stressed Out - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:39:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:39:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Twenty_One_Pilots/Stressed_Out/" title="Twenty_One_Pilots - Stressed Out - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wish I found some better sounds no one's ever heard <br>I wish I had a better voice that sang some better words <br>I wish I found some chords in an order that is new <br>I wish I didn't have to rhyme every time I sang <br><br>I was told when I get older all my fears would shrink <br>But now I'm insecure and I care what people think <br><br>My name's Blurryface and I care what you think <br>My name's Blurryface and I care what you think <br><br>Wish we could turn back time, to the good old days <br>When our momma sang us to sleep but now we're stressed out <br>Wish we could turn back time, to the good old days <br>When our momma sang us to sleep but now we're stressed out <br><br>We're stressed out <br><br>Sometimes a certain smell will take me back to when I was young <br>How come I'm never able to identify where it's coming from <br>I'd make a candle out of it if I ever found it <br>Try to sell it, never sell out of it, I'd probably only sell one <br><br>It'd be to my brother, 'cause we have the same nose <br>Same clothes homegrown a stone's throw from a creek we used to roam <br>But it would remind us of when nothing really mattered <br>Out of student loans and tree-house homes we all would take the latter <br><br>My name's Blurryface and I care what you think <br>My name's Blurryface and I care what you think <br><br>Wish we could turn back time, to the good old days <br>When our momma sang us to sleep but now we're stressed out <br>Wish we could turn back time, to the good old days <br>When our momma sang us to sleep but now we're stressed out <br><br>We used to play pretend, give each other different names <br>We would build a rocket ship and then we'd fly it far away <br>Used to dream of outer space but now they're laughing at our face <br>Saying, Wake up, you need to make money <br>Yeah <br><br>We used to play pretend, give each other different names <br>We would build a rocket ship and then we'd fly it far away <br>Used to dream of outer space but now they're laughing at our face <br>Saying, Wake up, you need to make money <br>Yeah <br><br>Wish we could turn back time, to the good old days <br>When our momma sang us to sleep but now we're stressed out <br>Wish we could turn back time, to the good old days <br>When our momma sang us to sleep but now we're stressed out <br><br>Used to play pretend, used to play pretend, bunny <br>We used to play pretend, wake up, you need the money <br>Used to play pretend, used to play pretend, bunny <br>We used to play pretend, wake up, you need the money <br>We used to play pretend, give each other different names <br>We would build a rocket ship and then we'd fly it far away <br>Used to dream of outer space but now they're laughing at our face <br>Saying, Wake up, you need to make money <br>Yeah]]></content><category term="Twenty One Pilots" label="Twenty One Pilots"/><category term="Stressed Out" label="Stressed Out"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lukas_Graham/7_Years/</id><title>Lukas_Graham - 7 Years - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:40:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:40:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lukas_Graham/7_Years/" title="Lukas_Graham - 7 Years - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Once I was seven years old my momma told me <br>Go make yourself some friends or you'll be lonely <br>Once I was seven years old <br><br>It was a big big world, but we thought we were bigger <br>Pushing each other to the limits, we were learning quicker <br>By eleven smoking herb and drinking burning liquor <br>Never rich so we were out to make that steady figure <br><br>Once I was eleven years old my daddy told me <br>Go get yourself a wife or you'll be lonely <br>Once I was eleven years old <br><br>I always had that dream like my daddy before me <br>So I started writing songs, I started writing stories <br>Something about that glory just always seemed to bore me <br>'Cause only those I really love will ever really know me <br><br>Once I was twenty years old, my story got told <br>Before the morning sun, when life was lonely <br>Once I was twenty years old <br><br>I only see my goals, I don't believe in failure <br>'Cause I know the smallest voices, they can make it major <br>I got my boys with me at least those in favor <br>And if we don't meet before I leave, I hope I'll see you later <br><br>Once I was twenty years old, my story got told <br>I was writing about everything, I saw before me <br>Once I was twenty years old <br>Soon we'll be thirty years old, our songs have been sold <br>We've traveled around the world and we're still roaming <br>Soon we'll be thirty years old <br><br>I'm still learning about life <br>My woman brought children for me <br>So I can sing them all my songs <br>And I can tell them stories <br>Most of my boys are with me <br>Some are still out seeking glory <br>And some I had to leave behind <br>My brother I'm still sorry <br><br>Soon I'll be sixty years old, my daddy got sixty-one <br>Remember life and then your life becomes a better one <br>I made a man so happy when I wrote a letter once <br>I hope my children come and visit, once or twice a month <br><br>Soon I'll be sixty years old, will I think the world is cold <br>Or will I have a lot of children who can warm me <br>Soon I'll be sixty years old <br>Soon I'll be sixty years old, will I think the world is cold <br>Or will I have a lot of children who can warm me <br>Soon I'll be sixty years old <br><br>Once I was seven years old, momma told me <br>Go make yourself some friends or you'll be lonely <br>Once I was seven years old <br><br>Once I was seven years old]]></content><category term="Lukas Graham" label="Lukas Graham"/><category term="7 Years" label="7 Years"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이성현/우리_이렇게_사랑해요/</id><title>이성현 - 우리 이렇게 사랑해요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:41:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:41:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%84%B1%ED%98%84/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="이성현 - 우리 이렇게 사랑해요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 어여쁜 그대를 만나서 <br>지금 여기 있어요 <br>그대 그대도 같은 마음이라면 <br>내게 힘을 주세요 <br>혼자선 할 수 없어요 <br>둘이라도 힘들 땐 있죠 <br>우릴 감싸는 그 분을 믿어요 <br>우리에게 원하시는 <br>그 길 따라 걸어가봐요 <br>어느새 아름다워질 거에요 <br>사랑해요 눈에 보이는 <br>그 너머까지 <br>사랑해요 흔해 보이는 <br>저 너머까지 <br>나 그댈 바라볼 때 <br>더불어 새 힘주시는 <br>그 분의 음성 <br>귀 기울이며 살아요 <br>혼자선 할 수 없어요 <br>둘이라도 힘들 땐 있죠 <br>우릴 감싸는 그 분을 믿어요 <br>우리에게 원하시는 <br>그 길 따라 걸어가봐요 <br>어느새 아름다워질 거에요 <br>사랑해요 눈에 보이는 <br>그 너머까지 <br>사랑해요 흔해 보이는 <br>저 너머까지 <br>나 그댈 바라볼 때 <br>더불어 새 힘주시는 <br>그 분의 음성 <br>귀 기울이며 살아요 <br>우리에게 펼쳐진 <br>그 어떤 일이라도 <br>지금 마음으로 <br>온전히 하나 하나 되어요 <br>음음음 <br>]]></content><category term="이성현" label="이성현"/><category term="우리 이렇게 사랑해요" label="우리 이렇게 사랑해요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/온리유/너와_헤어져야_하는_이유/</id><title>온리유 - 너와 헤어져야 하는 이유 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:41:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:41:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A8%EB%A6%AC%EC%9C%A0/%EB%84%88%EC%99%80_%ED%97%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%A0%B8%EC%95%BC_%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0/" title="온리유 - 너와 헤어져야 하는 이유 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매일 반복되는 둘 <br>뻔하기만 한 말투 <br>그러려니 하고 <br>넘긴 내가 바보였어 <br>내일이면 끝날까 <br>후회하진 않겠지 <br>그러려니 하고 <br>넘기지 마 말하잖아 <br>너와 헤어져야 하는 <br>이윤 하나야 <br>자꾸 내 앞에서 <br>거짓말 좀 하지 마 <br>너만 믿고 견뎌왔던 <br>나는 뭐가 돼 <br>더 이상 참을 수가 없어 <br>우리 그만해 <br>모든 게 끝난 거야 <br>눈물이 주룩주룩 <br>아픔이 지나고 나면 <br>아무렇지 않겠지 <br>너를 사랑하지 않은 <br>이윤 하나야 <br>자꾸 사랑했던 <br>순간들이 허무해 <br>너만 믿고 견뎌왔던 <br>나는 뭐가 돼 <br>더 이상 말하기도 싫어 <br>우리 헤어져 <br>너와 헤어져야 하는 <br>이윤 하나야 <br>자꾸 내 앞에서 <br>거짓말 좀 하지 마 <br>너만 믿고 견뎌왔던 <br>나는 뭐가 돼 <br>더 이상 참을 수가 없어 <br>우리 그만해 <br>너를 사랑하지 않은 <br>이윤 하나야 <br>자꾸 사랑했던 <br>순간들이 허무해 <br>너만 믿고 버텨왔던 <br>나는 뭐가 돼 <br>더 이상 말하기도 싫어 <br>우리 헤어져 <br>]]></content><category term="온리유" label="온리유"/><category term="너와 헤어져야 하는 이유" label="너와 헤어져야 하는 이유"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/체리팩토리/가을이라_그래/</id><title>체리팩토리 - 가을이라 그래 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:42:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:42:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B2%B4%EB%A6%AC%ED%8C%A9%ED%86%A0%EB%A6%AC/%EA%B0%80%EC%9D%84%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC_%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%98/" title="체리팩토리 - 가을이라 그래 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[두 볼을 스치는 바람이 <br>어느새 시원해 시원해 <br>이제 슬슬 긴 팔 옷 <br>꺼내 입어 볼까 <br>가을 가을 가을 <br>가을이 왔으니 <br>매일 걷던 길인데 <br>왜 오늘따라 쓸쓸한거지 <br>가을이라 그래 <br>밥먹은지 얼마 안됐는데 <br>왜 배고프지 <br>가을이라 그래 <br>쌀쌀해져서 그래 <br>낙엽 떨어져서 그래 <br>라디오에서 자꾸 <br>촉촉한 발라드만 <br>나와서 그래 <br>정말 괜찮아 <br>이건 내 탓 아니야 <br>가을 가을 가을 <br>가을이라 그래 <br>매일 보던 드라마 <br>왜 오늘따라 <br>괜히 슬프지 <br>가을이라 그래 <br>매일 오던 카페 <br>왜 오늘따라 나만 <br>혼자 온 것 같지 <br>가을이라 그래 <br>쌀쌀해져서 그래 <br>낙엽 떨어져서 그래 <br>라디오에서 자꾸 <br>촉촉한 발라드만 <br>나와서 그래 <br>정말 괜찮아 <br>이건 내 탓 아니야 <br>가을 가을 가을 <br>가을이라 그래 <br>가을이라서 그래 <br>가을이라서 그래 <br>쓸쓸한 것도 <br>배고픈 것도 <br>외로운 것도 <br>모두 모두 다 <br>괜찮아 절대 <br>내 탓 아니야 <br>가을 가을 가을 <br>가을이라 그래 <br>가을 가을 가을 <br>가을이라 그래 <br>]]></content><category term="체리팩토리" label="체리팩토리"/><category term="가을이라 그래" label="가을이라 그래"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neeka/More_Than_You/</id><title>Neeka - More Than You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:43:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:43:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Neeka/More_Than_You/" title="Neeka - More Than You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's no place like this <br>There's no place like this <br>There's nowhere I would rather be <br><br>You best wishes <br>and postcard kisses <br>My heart is warmed, my body calmed <br><br>I want it more than you <br>I'm insatiable, I'm to much too <br>I want it more than you <br>Baby I do <br><br>There are no chains like these <br>There are no chains like these <br>Stainless care, the comfort's here <br><br>No touch so painless <br>No eyes so aimless <br>Beyond repair, the damage in there <br><br>I want it more than you <br>I'm insatiable, I'm to much too <br>I want it more than you <br>Baby I do <br><br>There's no place like this <br>There's no place like this <br>There's nowhere I would rather be <br><br>I want it more than you <br>I'm insatiable, I'm to much too <br>I want it more than you <br>Baby I do]]></content><category term="Neeka" label="Neeka"/><category term="More Than You" label="More Than You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십/주의_임재_앞에_잠잠해/</id><title>New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십 - 주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:43:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:43:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Creation_Worship_%EB%89%B4_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%85%98_%EC%9B%8C%EC%8B%AD/%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%98_%EC%9E%84%EC%9E%AC_%EC%95%9E%EC%97%90_%EC%9E%A0%EC%9E%A0%ED%95%B4/" title="New_Creation_Worship_뉴_크리에이션_워십 - 주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 여기 계시네 <br>와서 모두 굽혀 경배해 <br>신령과 진리로 <br>순결하신 주님 <br>거룩한 존전에 <br>주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 여기 계시네 <br>주의 영광 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주의 빛 비치네 <br>거룩한 불 태우시며 <br>영광의 관 쓰네 <br>주 영광 찬란해 <br>빛 되신 우리 왕 <br>주의 영광 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주의 빛 비치네 <br>주 영광 찬란해 <br>빛 되신 우리 왕 <br>주의 영광 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주의 빛 비치네 <br>주 영광 찬란해 <br>빛 되신 우리왕 <br>주의 영광 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주의 빛 비치네 <br>주의 능력 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 역사 하시네 <br>죄 사하고 치유하시는 <br>놀라운 주 은혜 <br>주 믿는 자에게 <br>능치 못함 없네 <br>주의 능력 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 역사 하시네 <br>주 믿는 자에게 <br>능치 못함 없네 <br>주의 능력 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 역사 하시네 <br>주 믿는 자에게 <br>능치 못함 없네 <br>주의 능력 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 역사 하시네 <br>주 영광 찬란해 <br>빛 되신 우리 왕 <br>주의 영광 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주의 빛 비치네 <br>순결하신 주님 <br>거룩하신 존 전에 <br>주의 임재 앞에 잠잠에 <br>주 여기 계시네 <br>순결하신 주님 <br>거룩한 존 전에 <br>주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해 <br>주 여기 계시네]]></content><category term="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)" label="New Creation Worship (뉴 크리에이션 워십)"/><category term="주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해" label="주의 임재 앞에 잠잠해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/일리노J/Piano_Masquerade_Feat_윤빛나라/</id><title>일리노J - Piano Masquerade (Feat. 윤빛나라) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%BC%EB%A6%AC%EB%85%B8J/Piano_Masquerade_Feat_%EC%9C%A4%EB%B9%9B%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC/" title="일리노J - Piano Masquerade (Feat. 윤빛나라) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[촉촉한 잿빛 바람 새벽이 왔어 <br>내 속엔 고스란히 <br>너를 쥐고 밤새 울다가 <br>멋드러지게 차려입고 <br>거울에 한번 웃어보고 <br>거추장스런 인사를 나눈다 <br>귓가에 들리는 피아노 <br>그 위에 난 또 춤을 춘다 <br>창피하고 또 차가운 몸짓들 <br>난 나나 어지러워 <br>넌 내겐 없는 사람 <br>난 나나 들려온다 <br>날 부른 이 피아노 <br>한 사람은 널 사랑했고 <br>한 사람은 울어 <br>이 노래는 또 흘러와 <br>날 위로하려네 <br>멋드러지게 차려입고 <br>화장을 몇번 고쳐내고 <br>얼굴에 번진 눈물을 닦는다 <br>귓가에 들리는 피아노 <br>그 위에 난 또 춤을 춘다 <br>창피하고 또 차가운 몸짓들 <br>난 나나 어지러워 <br>넌 나를 스쳐가고 <br>난 나나 춤을 춘다 <br>My Piano Masquerade <br>]]></content><category term="일리노.J" label="일리노.J"/><category term="Piano Masquerade (Feat. 윤빛나라)" label="Piano Masquerade (Feat. 윤빛나라)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정희_Jung-hee_Cho/Waltz_for_SP/</id><title>조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - Waltz for S.P. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9D%AC_Jung-hee_Cho/Waltz_for_SP/" title="조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - Waltz for S.P. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[만약에 <br>아주 만약에 말야 <br>지금 너의 그 말 <br>사실이라면 <br>정말 그랬다면 <br>왜 이제야 말을 해 <br>왜 이제서야 <br>나 알게하니 <br>내 머리 위 <br>해가 밤으로 가고 <br>어둠 일렁일때마다 <br>널 보낸 시간 안에 <br>날 가두고 <br>시간을 멈춰두고 <br>한참을 울었지 <br>매일을 견뎠지 <br>어떻게 하나요 <br>그 말 사실인가요 <br>우리 헤어졌던 그 길 위에서 <br>매일 날 기다렸단 그 말 <br>그랬나요 <br>애써 버텨왔는데 <br>왜 이제서야 <br>그런 말 하나요 <br>어떻게 하나요 <br>무얼 할 수 있나요 <br>우리 헤어진 뒤 난 <br>빈 방처럼 <br>캄캄해져버렸는데 <br>그럴 수 있나요 <br>날 찾아줄 수 있나요 <br>언젠가 그날처럼 <br>그날의 우리처럼 <br>그럴 수 있겠죠 <br>간절히 바래왔던 <br>그날의 우리처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)" label="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)"/><category term="Waltz for S.P." label="Waltz for S.P."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정희_Jung-hee_Cho/라랄라라/</id><title>조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 라랄라라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9D%AC_Jung-hee_Cho/%EB%9D%BC%EB%9E%84%EB%9D%BC%EB%9D%BC/" title="조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 라랄라라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직까지도 니 눈빛은 <br>날 설레이게해 <br>그 미소도 그 향기도 모두 다 <br>날 흔들어 <br>아닌 척해도 <br>뒤돌아 모른척해도 <br>넌 내 맘 다 알지 <br>내 손 짓에 내 몸 짓에 <br>모두 네게 다 들켜버려 <br>라랄라라 라랄라라 <br>노래 부르네 <br>널 품에 안은 듯이 <br>널 안고 춤추듯이 <br>라랄라라 라랄라라 <br>오늘 밤 너를 부르네 <br>가슴이 터질 듯이 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>아직까지도 니 입술은 <br>날 설레이게해 <br>니가 날 부르면 <br>난 아무 말도 못하고 <br>그냥 웃지 <br>라랄라라 라랄라라 <br>노래 부르네 <br>널 품에 안은 듯이 <br>널 안고 춤추듯이 <br>라랄라라 라랄라라 <br>오늘 밤 너를 부르네 <br>가슴이 터질 듯이 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>아직까지도 니 입술은 <br>날 설레이게해 <br>니가 날 부르면 <br>난 아무 말도 못하고 <br>그냥 웃지 <br>]]></content><category term="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)" label="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)"/><category term="라랄라라" label="라랄라라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정희_Jung-hee_Cho/3일의_낮과_밤/</id><title>조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 3일의 낮과 밤 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9D%AC_Jung-hee_Cho/3%EC%9D%BC%EC%9D%98_%EB%82%AE%EA%B3%BC_%EB%B0%A4/" title="조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 3일의 낮과 밤 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[혼자 와 줄 수 있나요 <br>남겨진 길에 홀로 서 있어 <br>다시 노랠 해줘요 <br>비틀거리며 나 <br>춤추고 싶어 <br>우리 다시 <br>모두 알 순 없겠지만 <br>잊진 않을게 남겨둔 말들 <br>계절이 지나는 곳에 <br>날 데려가줘요 <br>그 여름처럼 <br>기억할 수 있을까 <br>우리 함께했던 음악과 밤들을 <br>다시 볼 수 있을까 <br>흐르는 눈물이 자꾸 앞을 가려와 <br>기억할 수 있을까 <br>우리 함께했던 음악과 밤들을 <br>다시 볼 수 있을까 <br>흐르는 눈물이 자꾸 앞을 가려 <br>혼자 와줄 수 있나요 <br>그 여름처럼 혼자 서 있어 <br>다시 꿈꾸게 해줘요 <br>아픈 오늘이 <br>멈출 수 있게 <br>내게 와줘요 <br>멈출 수 있게 <br>내게 와줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)" label="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)"/><category term="3일의 낮과 밤" label="3일의 낮과 밤"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정희_Jung-hee_Cho/길_잃은_새에게_말_건네기/</id><title>조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 길 잃은 새에게 말 건네기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9D%AC_Jung-hee_Cho/%EA%B8%B8_%EC%9E%83%EC%9D%80_%EC%83%88%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_%EB%A7%90_%EA%B1%B4%EB%84%A4%EA%B8%B0/" title="조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 길 잃은 새에게 말 건네기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길 잃은 새를 보거든 <br>말을 건네 보세요 <br>어디서 왔는지 <br>어디로 가는지 <br>겁내지 않게 조심히 <br>다가서서는 <br>그녀의 말로 <br>말 건네줘요 <br>비에 젖은 그녈 보거든 <br>말을 건네 주세요 <br>아프진 않니 <br>두려워 하지마 <br>다치지 않게 조심히 <br>다가가 안아주면서 <br>그녀의 말로 <br>말 건네줘요 <br>당신도 비에 젖은 채 <br>홀자 울고 있네요 <br>외로워하지마 <br>슬퍼하지 마요 <br>겁내지 말고 조금씩 <br>내게로 와서 <br>당신의 말로 <br>말 건네줘요 <br>내게로 와 그대 <br>조금씩 천천히 <br>내게로 와서 <br>당신의 얘길 <br>내게 해줘요 그대 <br>내게로 와줘요 <br>겁내지 말고 천천히 <br>내게로 다가와서 <br>당신의 얘길 <br>내게 해줘요 그대 <br>내게로 와줘요 <br>조금씩 천천히 <br>내게로 와서 <br>당신의 얘길 <br>내게 해줘요 <br>내게로 와 그대 <br>겁내지 말고 천천히 <br>내게로 다가와서 <br>당신의 말로 <br>얘기 해줘요 <br>]]></content><category term="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)" label="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)"/><category term="길 잃은 새에게 말 건네기" label="길 잃은 새에게 말 건네기"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정희_Jung-hee_Cho/이미_알고_있었던_얘기_Feat_규영/</id><title>조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 이미 알고 있었던 얘기 (Feat. 규영) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9D%AC_Jung-hee_Cho/%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%B8_%EC%95%8C%EA%B3%A0_%EC%9E%88%EC%97%88%EB%8D%98_%EC%96%98%EA%B8%B0_Feat_%EA%B7%9C%EC%98%81/" title="조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 이미 알고 있었던 얘기 (Feat. 규영) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ah I feel like uh <br>호흡이 가빠져 <br>어제 혹은 그 때가 <br>그리워 film 감았어 <br>활짝 열린 문 <br>바람 부는 창을 닫아도 <br>옷까지 겹겹이 입은 <br>맘은 아직 시린 걸 <br>이미 넌 내게 <br>그만하자 말했지 <br>사실 기억 되돌림 <br>내가 먼저 시작했지 <br>그래 이건 사실 <br>어쩌면 업보인가봐 <br>우리 관계 내일도 없이 <br>이 정도인가봐 딱 <br>난 이제 널 붙잡지도 못해 <br>또 안지도 못해 <br>서로 다친 게 쌓이네 <br>서로 아픈 걸 확인해 <br>그 때 내가 쉽게 <br>말 안 뱉었더라면 uh <br>이미 알고 있었던 얘기 <br>이미 울어버렸던 얘기 <br>간다고 해 <br>아무 말도 하지 말고 <br>간다고 해 <br>미련 따윈 필요없지 <br>간다고 해 <br>이미 나는 알고 <br>있었는데 뭘 <br>간다고 해 <br>돌아보지 말고 그냥 <br>간다고 해 <br>후회 따윈 필요없지 <br>간다고 해 <br>Good bye my love bye bye <br>이미 알고 있었던 얘기 <br>타임머신은 없어 <br>잊은 줄 알았던 <br>기억들은 잔에서 넘쳐 <br>이미 울어버렸단 얘기 <br>울어버렸단 얘기 <br>울어버렸단 얘기 <br>이미 멀어져 버린 우리 <br>상영기를 꺼야 해 <br>우린 더 이상 <br>쌓일 수 없어 무너져야 해 <br>이미 알고 있었던 얘기 <br>날 보진 마 바보처럼 <br>우는 나를 <br>바라보지 마 <br>미안해할 필욘없어 <br>간다고 해 <br>Good bye my love bye bye <br>그때 떠났던 내가 널 붙들며 <br>쏟아냈던 날카로운 말들이 <br>이젠 내게 되돌아와 <br>날 흔들며 너를 잊으라 하네 <br>그때 니가 날 붙들며 <br>터질듯이 쏟아냈던 눈물이 <br>이젠 내게 흘러 넘쳐와 <br>날 흔들며 네게 달려 가라해 <br>달려 가라해 <br>네게 달려 가라해 <br>더는 우리 사이에 <br>끌어당기는 과학은 없어 <br>우리에겐 밤과 새벽 뿐 <br>그 때 그 낮은 없어 <br>솔직히 사실 나에겐 <br>너가 없는 삶은 없어 <br>생각나도 참는 것뿐야 <br>담배 끊을 때처럼 <br>uh 표 끊는 게 어려워 <br>너와 반대편 행 <br>넌 뒤돌 필요도 없이 <br>쭉 걸어가면 돼 <br>미안해 하지말어 <br>부담도 갖지 말고 <br>내가 너의 두 배 할게 <br>넌 날 생각하면 안 돼 이제 <br>이미 알고 있었던 얘기 <br>떨어지고 있어 <br>우린 계절을 <br>지나쳐버린 낙엽 같어 <br>이미 울어버렸단 얘기 <br>멀어지고 있어 <br>진심으로 너가 <br>마지막이길 바랬어 <br>이미 <br>떨어지고 있어 <br>우린 계절을 <br>지나쳐버린 낙엽 같어 <br>멀어져 버린 우리 <br>멀어지고 있어 <br>진심으로 너가 <br>마지막이길 바랬어 <br>이미 <br>떨어지고 있어 <br>우린 계절을 <br>지나쳐버린 낙엽 같어 <br>알고 있었던 얘기 <br>멀어지고 있어 <br>진심으로 너가 <br>마지막이길 바랬어 <br>이미 <br>떨어지고 있어 <br>우린 계절을 <br>지나쳐버린 낙엽 같어 <br>알고 있었던 얘기 <br>멀어지고 있어 <br>진심으로 너가 <br>마지막이길 바랬어 <br>이미 <br>떨어지고 있어 <br>우린 계절을 <br>지나쳐버린 낙엽 같어 <br>울어버렸단 얘기 <br>멀어지고 있어 <br>진심으로 너가 <br>마지막이길 바랬어 <br>]]></content><category term="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)" label="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)"/><category term="이미 알고 있었던 얘기 (Feat. 규영)" label="이미 알고 있었던 얘기 (Feat. 규영)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정희_Jung-hee_Cho/다_잊기로_해/</id><title>조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 다 잊기로 해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9D%AC_Jung-hee_Cho/%EB%8B%A4_%EC%9E%8A%EA%B8%B0%EB%A1%9C_%ED%95%B4/" title="조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 다 잊기로 해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽃잎을 따 마셨지 <br>한 잎 두 잎 가녀린 <br>꽃잎마다 새겨둔 <br>꽃말들처럼 아스라히 <br>피어오르네 <br>그대 속삭임 <br>다 잊기로 해 잊기로 해 <br>모두 잊기로 해 <br>오늘이 아닌 모든 밤 <br>우린 숨에 겨웠지 <br>한 잎 두 잎 <br>꽃을 피웠지 <br>꽃을 피웠지 <br>다 잊기로 해 잊기로 해 <br>모두 잊기로 해 <br>오늘이 아닌 모든 밤 <br>다 잊기로 해 잊기로 해 <br>모두 잊기로 해 <br>내 말이 아닌 모든 말 <br>잊기로 해 <br>다 잊기로 해 <br>다 잊기로 해 잊기로 해 <br>모두 잊기로 해 <br>오늘이 아닌 모든 밤 <br>다 잊기로 해 잊기로 해 <br>모두 잊기로 해 <br>내 말이 아닌 모든 말 <br>다 잊기로 해 잊기로 해 <br>모두 잊기로 해 <br>오늘이 아닌 모든 밤 <br>다 잊기로 해 잊기로 해 <br>모두 잊기로 해 <br>내 말이 아닌 모든 말 <br>다 잊기로 해 <br>모두 잊기로 해 <br>다 잊기로 해 <br>]]></content><category term="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)" label="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)"/><category term="다 잊기로 해" label="다 잊기로 해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정희_Jung-hee_Cho/천_개의_달/</id><title>조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 천 개의 달 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9D%AC_Jung-hee_Cho/%EC%B2%9C_%EA%B0%9C%EC%9D%98_%EB%8B%AC/" title="조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 천 개의 달 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[첫 달이 뜨던 밤 달빛이 차올라 <br>잠든 날 깨우네 <br>깨지 않기를 바랬어 <br>움켜쥔 기억들이 사라질까봐 <br>기다려왔던 밤 천개의 달이 떠 <br>부서져 내리네 <br>오늘이 오기를 바랬어 <br>머물러줘 내가 너에게 갈게 <br>조심스럽게 창가로 가 <br>커튼을 젖혀 난 너를 찾네 <br>널 기다렸던 날 꼭 찾아줘 그때 너 <br>한 걸음씩 너 다가와 내게로 <br>날 끌어당겨 <br>Fly high 날아올라 우리 둘이서 <br>I feel your thousand eyes <br>기다렸던 my wonderland <br>Fly high 날아올라 <br>깨지않을 꿈 속으로 <br>I feel your thousand eyes <br>우리 오늘 밤 단 둘이서 날아올라 <br>조심스럽게 창가로 가 <br>커튼을 젖혀 난 너를 찾네 <br>널 기다렸던 날 꼭 안아줘 <br>그 때 우리 <br>Fly high 날아올라 우리 둘이서 <br>I feel your thousand eyes <br>기다렸던 my wonderland <br>Fly high 날아올라 <br>깨지않을 꿈 속으로 <br>I feel your thousand eyes <br>우리 오늘 밤 <br>Fly high 날아올라 우리 둘이서 <br>I feel your thousand eyes <br>기다렸던 my wonderland <br>Fly high 날아올라 <br>깨지않을 꿈 속으로 <br>I feel your thousand eyes <br>우리 오늘 밤 단 둘이서 <br>날아올라 <br>]]></content><category term="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)" label="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)"/><category term="천 개의 달" label="천 개의 달"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정희_Jung-hee_Cho/그렇게_우린_시작되네/</id><title>조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 그렇게 우린 시작되네 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9D%AC_Jung-hee_Cho/%EA%B7%B8%EB%A0%87%EA%B2%8C_%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%B0_%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%91%EB%90%98%EB%84%A4/" title="조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - 그렇게 우린 시작되네 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[말은 필요없지 지금 우린 <br>시간을 멈추고 Stay with me <br>손가락 사이로 쏟아지는 별빛들 <br>서두르진 않아 우린 천천히 <br>따라가 너의 손짓 <br>그렇게 우린 시작되네 <br>순간 꿈결처럼 <br>난 내 모든 말을 잃어가네 <br>순간 별빛처럼 <br>넌 내게만 Oh 반짝이네 <br>따라가 너의 손짓 <br>그렇게 우린 시작되네 <br>따라가 너의 눈빛 <br>그렇게 우린 짙어지네 <br>순간 꿈결처럼 <br>난 내 모든 말을 잃어가네 <br>순간 별빛처럼 <br>넌 내게만 Oh 반짝이네 <br>우리 둘이 시간을 멈추고 <br>우리 둘이 서두르진 않아 <br>우리 둘이 조금씩 천천히 <br>우리 둘이 시작되네 <br>]]></content><category term="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)" label="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)"/><category term="그렇게 우린 시작되네" label="그렇게 우린 시작되네"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조정희_Jung-hee_Cho/Hello_rain/</id><title>조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - Hello, rain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%EC%A0%95%ED%9D%AC_Jung-hee_Cho/Hello_rain/" title="조정희_Jung-hee_Cho - Hello, rain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[봄 비가 내리는 일요일 아침엔 <br>너에게 전화를 걸어 <br>뭐해 볼까 <br>스치는 상쾌한 봄 바람이 <br>내 볼을 간지럽히네 기분이 좋아 <br>Hello Rain 빗방울 방울들 <br>Like your lips 촉촉히 내려 <br>Kiss my lips 니 손을 잡으면 <br>터질 듯 두근대 금세 <br>들킬 것만 같아 <br>넌 알까 한 순간도 빠짐없이 <br>내 하룬 너로 가득해 매일 매일 <br>Hello Rain 빗방울 방울들 <br>Like your lips 촉촉히 내려 <br>Kiss my lips 니 손을 잡으면 <br>터질 듯 두근대 금세 <br>들킬 것만 같아 <br>내 귓가에 속삭여 <br>이 밤 함께 있어 <br>Hello Rain 빗방울 방울들 <br>Like your lips 촉촉히 내려 <br>Kiss my lips 니 손을 잡으면 <br>터질 듯 두근대 금세 <br>들킬 것만 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)" label="조정희 (Jung-hee Cho)"/><category term="Hello, rain" label="Hello, rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/웃고_싶다_Bonus/</id><title>리민 - 웃고 싶다 (Bonus) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EC%9B%83%EA%B3%A0_%EC%8B%B6%EB%8B%A4_Bonus/" title="리민 - 웃고 싶다 (Bonus) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이렇게 벚꽃이 필때면 <br>너를 생각해 <br>언제쯤 우리 손을 꼭 잡고 <br>같은 길을 걸을까 <br>오늘은 꼭 하고 싶은말 <br>하고 말거야 <br>넌 지금 어딨니 <br>어서 내 앞에 빨리 나타나줘 <br>지루했던 날도 너 때문에 나는 <br>행복한 오늘이 되는걸 <br>이런게 사랑이 아닐까 <br>너랑 웃고싶다 같이 웃고싶다 <br>넌 나를 어떻게 생각할까 <br>참으면 병날것 같은데 <br>언제쯤 너에게 말해볼까 <br>사랑한다고 처음본 그날부터 <br>너만 빼고 모두 내 맘을 다 알아 <br>왜이리 눈치가 없는지 <br>상상해본걸 말해볼까 <br>너랑 웃고싶다 같이 웃고싶다 <br>넌 나를 어떻게 생각할까 <br>참으면 병날것 같은데 <br>언제쯤 너에게 말해볼까 <br>사랑한다고 처음본 그날부터 <br>오늘부터 우리 사귀어볼까 <br>너무 잘 어울릴 것 같은데 <br>오늘부터 우리 설레어볼까 <br>웃게해줄게 너만을 <br>사랑해줄게 너만을 <br>내평생을 너와함께 웃고싶다 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="웃고 싶다 (Bonus)" label="웃고 싶다 (Bonus)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/너와_함께_Feat_구현모/</id><title>리민 - 너와 함께 (Feat. 구현모) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EB%84%88%EC%99%80_%ED%95%A8%EA%BB%98_Feat_%EA%B5%AC%ED%98%84%EB%AA%A8/" title="리민 - 너와 함께 (Feat. 구현모) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매일 반복되는 바쁜 하루하루 <br>멀어져가는 나의 모습에 <br>슬퍼하시네 <br>상처뿐이라고 이젠 필요없다고 <br>잊혀져가는 나의 모습에 <br>아파하시네 <br>이제 기대어 쉬고 싶은데 <br>누군가에게 말하고 싶은데 <br>두 눈을 감고서 귀를 기울여봐 <br>주님이 말씀하시네 <br>힘들고 지쳤을 때 <br>너의 주를 바라라 <br>그가 새힘으로 너와 함께 하리라 <br>낙망하고 넘어져 <br>눈물이 흐를 때에도 <br>그가 너의 슬픔 닦아주시리 <br>이제 기대어 쉬고 싶은데 <br>누군가에게 말하고 싶은데 <br>두 눈을 감고서 귀를 기울여봐 <br>주님이 말씀하시네 <br>힘들고 지쳤을 때 <br>너의 주를 바라라 <br>그가 새힘으로 너와 함께 하리라 <br>낙망하고 넘어져 <br>눈물이 흐를 때에도 <br>그가 너의 슬픔 닦아주시리 <br>힘들고 지쳤을 때 <br>너의 주를 바라라 <br>그가 새힘으로 <br>너와 함께 하시리라 <br>낙망하고 넘어져 <br>눈물이 흐를 때에도 <br>그가 너의 슬픔 닦아주시리 <br>그가 너의 아픔 씻어주시리 <br>그가 너를 품에 안아주시리 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="너와 함께 (Feat. 구현모)" label="너와 함께 (Feat. 구현모)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/괴로울_때_주님의_얼굴_보라/</id><title>리민 - 괴로울 때 주님의 얼굴 보라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EA%B4%B4%EB%A1%9C%EC%9A%B8_%EB%95%8C_%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%96%BC%EA%B5%B4_%EB%B3%B4%EB%9D%BC/" title="리민 - 괴로울 때 주님의 얼굴 보라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[괴로울 때 주님의 얼굴 보라 <br>평화의 주님 바라보아라 <br>세상에서 시달린 친구들아 <br>위로의 주님 바라보아라 <br>눈을 들어 주를 보라 <br>네 모든 염려 주께 맡겨라 <br>슬플 때에 주님의 얼굴보라 <br>사랑의 주님 안식주리라 <br>힘이 없고 네 마음 연약할 때 <br>능력의 주님 바라보아라 <br>주의 이름 부르는 모든 자는 <br>힘주시며 늘 지켜주시리 <br>눈을 들어 주를 보라 <br>네 모든 염려 주께 맡겨라 <br>슬플 때에 주님의 얼굴보라 <br>사랑의 주님 안식주리라 <br>괴로울 때 주님의 얼굴 보라 <br>평화의 주님 바라보아라 <br>세상에서 시달린 친구들아 <br>위로의 주님 바라보아라 <br>눈을 들어 주를 보라 <br>네 모든 염려 주께 맡겨라 <br>슬플 때에 주님의 얼굴보라 <br>사랑의 주님 안식주리라 <br>눈을 들어 주를 보라 <br>네 모든 염려 주께 맡겨라 <br>슬플 때에 주님의 얼굴보라 <br>사랑의 주님 안식주리라 <br>슬플 때에 주님의 얼굴보라 <br>사랑의 주님 안식주리라 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="괴로울 때 주님의 얼굴 보라" label="괴로울 때 주님의 얼굴 보라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/별이_되는_꿈/</id><title>리민 - 별이 되는 꿈 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EB%B3%84%EC%9D%B4_%EB%90%98%EB%8A%94_%EA%BF%88/" title="리민 - 별이 되는 꿈 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 어렸을 때부터 <br>작은 꿈이 있었죠 <br>저 하늘 올라가 날아가는 꿈 <br>나 누군가를 보며 <br>그 꿈을 키워갔죠 <br>저 하늘 별처럼 반짝이는 꿈 <br>그땐 몰랐었죠 내가 누군지 <br>The reason why I sing I know <br>그대를 알고서 그대를 믿고서 <br>더 달콤한 목소리로 <br>오늘 내 꿈을 노래해 <br>그대를 만나서 그대를 안고서 <br>더 사랑스런 목소리로 <br>난 꿈을 꾸네 <br>그땐 몰랐었죠 내가 누군지 <br>The reason why I sing I know <br>그대를 알고서 그대를 믿고서 <br>더 달콤한 목소리로 <br>오늘 내 꿈을 노래해 <br>그대를 만나서 그대를 안고서 <br>더 사랑스런 목소리로 난 <br>그대를 알고서 그대를 믿고서 <br>더 달콤한 목소리로 <br>오늘 내 꿈을 노래해 <br>그대를 만나서 그대를 안고서 <br>더 사랑스런 목소리로 <br>난 꿈을 꾸네 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="별이 되는 꿈" label="별이 되는 꿈"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/나의_주님을/</id><title>리민 - 나의 주님을 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EB%82%98%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC%EB%8B%98%EC%9D%84/" title="리민 - 나의 주님을 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[거울 속에 비친 연약한 내 모습 <br>그 약속과 나의 기도 <br>또 잊으며 살았는지 <br>그러나 주님 한번도 <br>나를 포기하지 않네 <br>놀라운 은혜와 사랑으로 <br>따뜻하게 날 감싸네 <br>영원히 나의 주님을 나의 주님을 <br>영원히 찬양 할렐루야 <br>나의 주님을 나의 주님을 <br>영원히 찬양 할렐루 <br>거울 속에 비친 초라한 내 모습 <br>그 진리와 나의 믿음 <br>또 지우며 살았는지 <br>그러나 주님 한번도 <br>나를 포기하지 않네 <br>놀라운 은혜와 사랑으로 <br>따뜻하게 날 감싸네 <br>영원히 나의 주님을 나의 주님을 <br>영원히 찬양 할렐루야 <br>나의 주님을 나의 주님을 <br>영원히 찬양 할렐루 <br>나의 주님을 나의 주님을 <br>영원히 찬양 할렐루야 <br>나의 주님을 나의 주님을 <br>영원히 찬양 할렐루 <br>나의 주님을 나의 주님을 <br>영원히 찬양 할렐루야 <br>나의 주님을 나의 주님을 <br>영원히 찬양 할렐루 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="나의 주님을" label="나의 주님을"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/주의_약속하신_말씀_위에_서/</id><title>리민 - 주의 약속하신 말씀 위에 서 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%98_%EC%95%BD%EC%86%8D%ED%95%98%EC%8B%A0_%EB%A7%90%EC%94%80_%EC%9C%84%EC%97%90_%EC%84%9C/" title="리민 - 주의 약속하신 말씀 위에 서 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[주의 약속하신 말씀 위에 서 <br>영원토록 주를 찬송하리라 <br>소리 높여 주께 영광 돌리며 <br>약속 믿고 굳게 서리라 <br>굳게 서리 <br>영원하신 말씀 위에 굳게 서리 <br>굳게 서리 <br>그 말씀 위에 굳게 서리라 <br>주의 약속하신 말씀 위에 서 <br>세상염려 내게 엄습할 때에 <br>말씀으로 힘써 싸워 이기며 <br>약속 믿고 굳게 서리라 <br>굳게 서리 <br>영원하신 말씀 위에 굳게 서리 <br>굳게 서리 <br>그 말씀 위에 굳게 서리라 <br>약속 믿고 굳게 서 <br>약속 믿고 굳게 서 <br>약속 믿고 굳게 서 <br>약속 믿고 굳게 서 <br>약속 믿고 굳게 서 <br>워 워 워 워 워 <br>굳게 서리 <br>영원하신 말씀 위에 굳게 서리 <br>굳게 서리 <br>그 말씀 위에 굳게 서리라 <br>굳게 서리 <br>영원하신 말씀 위에 굳게 서리 <br>굳게 서리 <br>그 말씀 위에 굳게 서리라 <br>그 말씀 위에 굳게 서리라 <br>그 말씀 위에 굳게 서리라 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="주의 약속하신 말씀 위에 서" label="주의 약속하신 말씀 위에 서"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/그런_나/</id><title>리민 - 그런 나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EA%B7%B8%EB%9F%B0_%EB%82%98/" title="리민 - 그런 나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[고갤 들어 바라본 하늘 <br>그 위에 펼쳐진 초록빛 추억 <br>그저 좋기만 하지 않아서 <br>늘 품었던 가슴 속 울음소리 <br>고마워요 그대 <br>지금껏 그렇게 <br>거기 있어준 것 <br>감사해요 그대 <br>내 아픈 상처 <br>추억으로 안아주어서 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="그런 나" label="그런 나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/영원히_내가/</id><title>리민 - 영원히 내가 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EC%98%81%EC%9B%90%ED%9E%88_%EB%82%B4%EA%B0%80/" title="리민 - 영원히 내가 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이 세상에 어떤 것도 <br>표현할 수 없고 <br>그 누구도 대신 못할 사랑 <br>죄 없으신 하나님의 <br>아들의 그 피로 <br>우린 구원받고 하나님의 <br>자녀가 되버린 사랑 <br>나를 위해서 아들 죽인 <br>하나님의 그 사랑 <br>날 위해서 날 위해서 <br>전부를 내어주신 그 사랑 <br>완전한 사랑 놀라운 그 사랑 <br>십자가 그 사랑 <br>영원히 내가 영원히 <br>그 사랑을 전하며 살리라 <br>죄 없으신 하나님의 <br>아들의 그 피로 <br>우린 구원받고 하나님의 <br>자녀가 되버린 사랑 <br>나를 위해서 아들 죽인 <br>하나님의 그 사랑 <br>날 위해서 날 위해서 <br>전부를 내어주신 그 사랑 <br>완전한 사랑 놀라운 그 사랑 <br>십자가 그 사랑 <br>영원히 내가 영원히 <br>그 사랑을 전하며 <br>나를 위해서 아들 죽인 <br>하나님의 그 사랑 <br>영원히 내가 영원히 <br>그 사랑을 전하며 살리라 <br>우 우 우 우 우우우 <br>그 사랑을 전하며 살리라 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="영원히 내가" label="영원히 내가"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/오직_주_예수/</id><title>리민 - 오직 주 예수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EC%98%A4%EC%A7%81_%EC%A3%BC_%EC%98%88%EC%88%98/" title="리민 - 오직 주 예수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 눈물 뒤에 <br>주님이 계시고 <br>내 마음 속에 <br>위로가 가득해 <br>더 가까이 좀 더 가까이 <br>주님의 따뜻한 <br>품 안에 들어가 <br>내 눈물 뒤에 <br>주님이 계시고 <br>내 마음 속에 <br>위로가 가득해 <br>더 가까이 좀 더 가까이 <br>주님의 따뜻한 <br>품 안에 들어가 <br>주님의 따뜻한 <br>품 안에 들어가 <br>내 눈물 뒤에 <br>주님이 계셔 <br>내 맘속에 위로가 <br>넘치는 은혜 <br>주님이 주셨네 <br>내 노래 안에 <br>주님이 계셔 <br>내 주가 나를 돌보시네 <br>영원히 함께할 예수 <br>내 눈물 뒤에 <br>주님이 계시고 <br>내 마음 속에 <br>위로가 가득해 <br>더 가까이 좀 더 가까이 <br>주님의 따뜻한 <br>품 안에 들어가 <br>주님의 따뜻한 <br>품 안에 들어가 <br>내 눈물 뒤에 <br>주님이 계셔 <br>내 맘속에 위로가 <br>넘치는 은혜 <br>주님이 주셨네 <br>내 노래 안에 <br>주님이 계셔 <br>내 주가 나를 돌보시네 <br>영원히 함께할 예수 <br>내가 믿는 분 오직 주 예수 <br>나를 도울 분 오직 주 예수 <br>내가 믿는 분 오직 주 예수 <br>나를 도울 분 오직 주 예수 <br>내가 믿는 분 오직 주 예수 <br>나를 도울 분 오직 주 예수 <br>내 눈물 뒤에 <br>주님이 계셔 <br>내 맘속에 위로가 <br>넘치는 은혜 <br>주님이 주셨네 <br>내 노래 안에 <br>주님이 계셔 <br>내 주가 나를 돌보시네 <br>영원히 함께할 <br>영원히 함께할 예수 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="오직 주 예수" label="오직 주 예수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/나는_웁니다/</id><title>리민 - 나는 웁니다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%9B%81%EB%8B%88%EB%8B%A4/" title="리민 - 나는 웁니다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기억하나요 십자가 사랑 <br>나를 위해 생명을 버리신 <br>하나님 본체 만물의 주인 <br>십자가 달리신 분 <br>눈물로 기도하신 분 <br>나를 사랑하신 분 <br>그 사랑이 내게 <br>생명주시었네 <br>오직 나를 위하여 <br>하늘 보좌 버리신 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>나는 웁니다 <br>내게 주신 그 사랑 <br>모든 물과 피 <br>나를 위해 흘리신 <br>영원한 생명 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>나 오늘도 웁니다 <br>눈물로 기도하신 분 <br>나를 사랑하신 분 <br>그 사랑이 내게 <br>생명주시었네 <br>오직 나를 위하여 <br>하늘 보좌 버리신 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>나는 웁니다 <br>내게 주신 그 사랑 <br>모든 물과 피 <br>나를 위해 흘리신 <br>영원한 생명 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>나 오늘도 웁니다 <br>나의 눈물의 의미 <br>오직 당신은 아시죠 <br>생각만해도 눈물이 워 <br>나는 웁니다 <br>내게 주신 그 사랑 <br>모든 물과 피 <br>나를 위해 흘리신 <br>영원한 생명 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>나 오늘도 웁니다 <br>영원한 생명 <br>그 사랑 때문에 <br>나 오늘도 웁니다 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="나는 웁니다" label="나는 웁니다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/그_이름/</id><title>리민 - 그 이름 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EA%B7%B8_%EC%9D%B4%EB%A6%84/" title="리민 - 그 이름 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그 이름 생각할 때마다 <br>나의 마음은 떨리네 <br>묶여 있는 나를 <br>자유케하신 <br>그 유일한 이름 <br>그 이름 노래할 때마다 <br>나의 마음은 설레네 <br>내 맘의 문을 열고 <br>내 안에 들어온 <br>그 축복의 이름 <br>오직 그 이름으로만 <br>구원을 얻을 수 있네 <br>세상에 그 어떤 이름도 <br>내겐 아무 의미 없네 <br>그 이름 안에 내가 있고 <br>내 안에 그 이름 있으니 <br>세상에 모든 것이 다 <br>사라져도 난 두려움 없네 <br>오직 그 이름으로만 <br>구원을 얻을 수 있네 <br>세상에 그 어떤 이름도 <br>내겐 아무 의미 없네 <br>그 이름 안에 내가 있고 <br>내 안에 그 이름 있으니 <br>세상에 모든 것이 다 <br>사라져도 난 두려움 없네 <br>그 이름 때문에 <br>내가 살죠 내가 오늘도 <br>영원히 내 맘 속에 <br>머물 그 이름 <br>단 하나의 이름 예수 <br>그 이름 안에 내가 있고 <br>내 안에 그 이름 있으니 <br>세상에 모든 것이 다 <br>사라져도 난 두려움 없네 <br>세상에 모든 것이 다 <br>사라져도 난 두려움 없네 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="그 이름" label="그 이름"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/리민/내_삶의_주인/</id><title>리민 - 내 삶의 주인 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:44:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:44:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A6%AC%EB%AF%BC/%EB%82%B4_%EC%82%B6%EC%9D%98_%EC%A3%BC%EC%9D%B8/" title="리민 - 내 삶의 주인 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔은 힘들 때도 있지만 <br>그럴 때마다 <br>이겨낼 수 있던 건 <br>나를 사랑하는 분 <br>그 사랑으로 <br>믿음 하나가지고 <br>힘을 내보죠 <br>한걸음씩 다가가 <br>더 가까이 다가가 <br>나 주님 앞에 내 모든 걸 <br>모두 말할래 <br>할렐루야 찬양해 <br>하늘에 울려 퍼질 이 노래 <br>온맘 다해 주께 고백해 <br>내 삶의 주인은 바로 <br>내 삶의 주인은 오직 예수 <br>한걸음씩 다가가 <br>더 가까이 다가가 <br>나 주님 앞에 내 모든 걸 <br>모두 말할래 <br>할렐루야 찬양해 <br>하늘에 울려 퍼질 이 노래 <br>온맘 다해 주께 고백해 <br>내 삶의 주인은 바로 <br>내 삶의 주인은 오직 예수 <br>생각대로 안되는 게 참 많죠 <br>주님이 하실 일 <br>믿고 기다려요 <br>할렐루야 찬양해 <br>할렐루야 찬양해 <br>하늘에 울려 퍼질 이 노래 <br>온맘 다해 주께 고백해 <br>내 삶의 주인은 바로 <br>내 삶의 주인은 오직 예수 <br>내 삶의 주인은 바로 <br>내 삶의 주인은 오직 예수 <br>할렐루야 찬양해 <br>]]></content><category term="리민" label="리민"/><category term="내 삶의 주인" label="내 삶의 주인"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박윤정/십년을_만나고/</id><title>박윤정 - 십년을 만나고 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:45:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:45:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%9C%A4%EC%A0%95/%EC%8B%AD%EB%85%84%EC%9D%84_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%98%EA%B3%A0/" title="박윤정 - 십년을 만나고 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[한참 동안 망설이다 <br>다시 또 뒤를 돌아보았네 <br>떠나는 그대에게서 난 얼마나 <br>기를 쓰며 멀어지려 했는지 <br>너무 아파 살아온 과거가 <br>사라져 버린 그런 느낌 <br>거부할 수 없었던 그 미소와 <br>모든 걸 믿어버린 바보 같은 나 <br>잠시 머물렀던 그런 사람처럼 <br>담담한 그 모습 뒤로 <br>제발 다시 내게 <br>돌아올 순 없는 거냐고 <br>묻고 싶지만 <br>자존심만 움켜쥔 채로 <br>내 좋았던 시절에게 <br>떨어지는 초라한 눈물아 <br>십 년을 만나고 공유했던 것들 <br>너의 어깨 안에서 <br>하나씩 쌓아올린 <br>내 조그마한 성들이 <br>무너져 내리고 <br>먼지를 뒤집어쓴 채로 <br>네 눈앞에 있는데도 <br>한 달도 안되는 그녀와의 만남 <br>너의 추억 안에서 <br>통곡을 하고 있는 <br>내 눈물 위로 어떻게 <br>그렇게 잔인하게 <br>집착이라 말할 수 있는지 <br>십 년을 만나고 공유했던 것들 <br>너의 어깨 안에서 <br>하나씩 쌓아올린 <br>내 조그마한 성들이 <br>무너져 내리고 <br>먼지를 뒤집어쓴 채로 <br>네 눈앞에 있는데도 <br>한 달도 안되는 그녀와의 만남 <br>너의 추억 안에서 <br>통곡을 하고 있는 <br>내 눈물 위로 어떻게 <br>그렇게 잔인하게 <br>집착이라 말할 수 있는지 <br>]]></content><category term="박윤정" label="박윤정"/><category term="십년을 만나고" label="십년을 만나고"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lvndscape/Sunkissed_Feat_Bright_Sparks/</id><title>Lvndscape - Sunkissed (Feat. Bright Sparks) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:45:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:45:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lvndscape/Sunkissed_Feat_Bright_Sparks/" title="Lvndscape - Sunkissed (Feat. Bright Sparks) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Open road, open mind <br>Hands up, open skies <br>Summer long, you and me <br>The wheel is yours, where you wanna be <br><br>I'll take you anywhere <br>Il'l take you anywhere, babe <br>I'll take you anywhere <br>Said I'm gon take you anywhere, babe <br><br>Hey take me where the love is, love is <br>Baby take me where I wanna go <br>Where everybody's sunkissed, sunkissed <br>Wanna see the skin glow <br><br>Hey take me where the love is, love is <br>Baby take me where I wanna go <br>Where everybody's sunkissed, sunkissed <br>Wanna see the skin glow <br><br>Open hearts, dancin feet <br>The MJ playin, on repeat <br>I see the kids on the west coast, the kids from the east <br>Nothin makes much sense, babe you're where I wanna be <br><br>I'll take you anywhere <br>I'll take you anywhere, babe <br>I'll take you anywhere <br>Said I'm gon take you anywhere oh oh <br><br>Hey take me where the love is, love is <br>Baby take me where I wanna go <br>Where everybody's sunkissed, sunkissed <br>Wanna see the skin glow <br><br>Hey take me where the love is, love is <br>Baby take me where I wanna go <br>Where everybody's sunkissed, sunkissed <br>Wanna see the skin glow <br><br>Wanna see the skin <br>Said I, Said I'll take you where <br>Wanna see the skin <br>Ooooh take you where the love is, babe <br>Wanna see the skin <br>Anywhere, anywhere <br>Wanna see the skin <br><br>Take me where the love is, love is <br>Baby take me where I wanna go <br>Where everybody's sunkissed, sunkissed <br>Wanna see the skin glow <br><br>Take me where the love is, love is <br>Baby take me where I wanna go <br>Where everybody's sunkissed, sunkissed <br>Wanna see the skin glow]]></content><category term="Lvndscape" label="Lvndscape"/><category term="Sunkissed (Feat. Bright Sparks)" label="Sunkissed (Feat. Bright Sparks)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lvndscape/Everyday_My_Life/</id><title>Lvndscape - Everyday My Life - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:45:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:45:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lvndscape/Everyday_My_Life/" title="Lvndscape - Everyday My Life - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br><br>I need ya, I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>Cause I need ya and I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>I need ya, I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>Cause I need ya and I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br><br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br><br>I need ya, I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>Cause I need ya and I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>I need ya, I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>Cause I need ya and I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br><br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br><br>I need ya, I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>Cause I need ya and I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>I need ya, I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>Cause I need ya and I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>I need ya, I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>Cause I need ya and I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>I need ya, I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br>Cause I need ya and I want ya <br>Everyday of my life <br><br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life <br>Everyday of my life]]></content><category term="Lvndscape" label="Lvndscape"/><category term="Everyday My Life" label="Everyday My Life"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Weezer/Wind_In_Our_Sail/</id><title>Weezer - Wind In Our Sail - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Weezer/Wind_In_Our_Sail/" title="Weezer - Wind In Our Sail - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A boy and a girl <br>Albatross around their necks <br>Hands burning from the rope <br>Ships stranded in the tropics <br>Acidification wiped out the tiger shark <br>Let's try to save their souls <br>And trust the man with the Torah <br><br>We got the wind in our sail <br>Like Darwin on the Beagle <br>Or Mendel experimenting with a pea <br>We got the wind in our sail <br>And we can do so many great things together, together <br><br>Breathe in the salt <br>Slicing waves at 40 knots <br>Cumulonimbus in the sky <br>This is what we've waited for <br>And now there's no more hyperventilating in wheelchairs <br>We're gonna save the last dog on Funk Island <br>We're had to do it wrong befor we could do it right <br><br>We got the wind in our sail <br>Like Darwin on the Beagle <br>Or Mendel experimenting with a pea <br>We got the wind in our sail <br>And we can do so many great things together, together <br><br>Pushing the stone up the hill and if it rolls back down <br>Whoa, Sisyphus it rolls back down <br>Pushing the stone up the hill and if it rolls back down <br>Whoa, Sisyphus it rolls back down <br><br>We got the wind in our sail <br>Like Darwin on the Beagle <br>Or Mendel experimenting with a pea <br>We got the wind in our sail <br>And we can do so many great things together, together]]></content><category term="Weezer" label="Weezer"/><category term="Wind In Our Sail" label="Wind In Our Sail"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Weezer/California_Kids/</id><title>Weezer - California Kids - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Weezer/California_Kids/" title="Weezer - California Kids - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When you wake up <br>Cobwebs on your eyelids <br>Stuck in rigor mortis <br>Woah-woah <br>Just get going <br>'Til you hit the ocean <br>And you turn Californian <br>Woah-woah <br>You don't have to have the answers <br>Don't you worry <br>Don't you worry <br><br>It's gonna be alright <br>If you're on a sinking ship <br>The California kids <br>Will throw you a lifeline <br>And if you're up all night <br>Thinking about something you did <br>The California kids <br>Will show you the sunshine <br><br>In your bare feet <br>In mid-January <br>Swimming in the mystery <br>Woah-woah <br>Second-guessing <br>Almost everything <br>Don't you worry <br>Don't you worry <br><br>It's gonna be alright <br>If you're on a sinking ship <br>The California kids <br>Will throw you a lifeline <br>And if you're up all night <br>Thinking about something you did <br>The California kids <br>Will show you the starlight <br><br>All your old friends <br>Chilling back in Boston <br>You never forgot them <br>Woah-woah <br><br>It's gonna be alright <br>If you're on a sinking ship <br>The California kids <br>Will throw you a lifeline <br>And if you're up all night <br>Thinking about something you did <br>The California kids <br>Will show you the sunshine <br>The California kids <br>Will show you the starlight]]></content><category term="Weezer" label="Weezer"/><category term="California Kids" label="California Kids"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이디스_코드/Jane_Doe/</id><title>레이디스_코드 - Jane Doe - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BD%94%EB%93%9C/Jane_Doe/" title="레이디스_코드 - Jane Doe - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈 감아줘 <br>늘 까만 밤처럼 <br>You count on <br>끝이 없는 수를 세 <br>난 숨을게 <br>니가 찾지 못하게 <br>I know I’m a weirdo <br>Love or Hate <br>다 의미 없는 듯해 <br>Kiss or Diss <br>똑같은 입술로 <br>Everything is Nothing <br>새 하얀 내가 보기엔 <br>세상은 위험해 <br>She’s a Jane Doe <br>아무도 모르게 <br>꼭 감춰뒀던 <br>달의 뒤편 어디로 <br>She’s a Jane Doe <br>이름도 없는 <br>나를 만나도 부디 <br>못 본 척 해 줄래 <br>삐뚤삐뚤하죠 <br>당신의 기준엔 <br>점선 같은 존재 <br>I’m nothing nothing <br>어디에도 누구와도 <br>어울릴 수 없는 그런거라면 <br>부디 못 본 척 해 줄래 <br>안개 속에 날개를 숨겼지 <br>난 계속 날아오를 꿈만 꿔 <br>언제쯤 날 보여줄 수 있을까 <br>I know I’m a weirdo <br>어두운 방 <br>구석진 곳 벽장 속에 <br>나를 놓아두고 좀 잊어줘 <br>발가벗기듯 밝은 불빛 속에 <br>던지곤 웃는 너 <br>She’s a Jane Doe <br>아무도 모르게 <br>꼭 감춰뒀던 <br>달의 뒤편 어디로 <br>She’s a Jane Doe <br>이름도 없는 <br>나를 만나도 부디 <br>못 본 척 해 줄래 <br>나는 어떤 사람 수많은 <br>밤을 설레였었는데 <br>나는 없던 사람 울어도 <br>그 누가 알아봐줄까 날 <br>She’s a Jane Doe <br>날 모르게 <br>꼭 감춰뒀던 달의 뒤편 <br>어딘가 Right now <br>I’m a Jane Doe <br>어떤 표정도 <br>넌 모르잖아 <br>I’m no one just jane doe <br>삐뚤삐뚤하죠 <br>당신의 기준엔 <br>점선 같은 존재 <br>I’m nothing nothing <br>어디에도 누구와도 <br>어울릴 수 없는 그런거라면 <br>부디 못 본 척 해 줄래 <br>]]></content><category term="레이디스 코드" label="레이디스 코드"/><category term="Jane Doe" label="Jane Doe"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이디스_코드/The_Rain/</id><title>레이디스_코드 - The Rain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BD%94%EB%93%9C/The_Rain/" title="레이디스_코드 - The Rain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비가 그친지 몇 날이 지났음에도 <br>나는 아직도 이렇게 젖어있어요 <br>추억이라는 얕은 시간 속에 <br>여전히 내리는 이별의 비는 <br>나를 다 집어 삼켜 <br>두 눈 위로 가득 맺혀 <br>끝없이 쏟아져 내려 <br>터지는 빗방울에 놀라 <br>그대는 비를 피하죠 <br>외면 하지마 You cause the rain <br>내 맘을 모른 척 그댄 <br>내 눈물을 차갑게 피하죠 <br>Don’t Break my heart oh <br>들어줘 My rain drops <br>해가 구름에 가려져 있었음에도 <br>아침이 오는 것처럼 <br>의미 없는 기대뿐인 거야 <br>단 하루도 버틸 수 없을 만큼 <br>턱 밑까지 가득 고인 이 비는 <br>더는 참을 수 없이 <br>입술 틈새를 비집고 <br>끝없이 쏟아져 내려 <br>터지는 빗방울에 놀라 <br>그대는 비를 피하죠 <br>외면 하지마 You cause the rain <br>내 맘을 모른 척 그댄 <br>내 눈물을 차갑게 피하죠 <br>Don’t Break my heart oh <br>들어줘 My rain drops <br>고장이 난 듯 한 하늘 <br>햇살은 아직 먼 것 같아 <br>오늘 이 비에 내 눈물 더해 <br>그댈 좀 더 붙잡고 싶어 <br>아직도 모른 척 고개를 <br>돌리는 그대의 시선 <br>다시 한 번 또 내리는 Rain <br>아파도 무심코 피어난 <br>내 맘을 자를 수가 없어 <br>Don’t Break my heart oh <br>내려줘 My rain drops <br>]]></content><category term="레이디스 코드" label="레이디스 코드"/><category term="The Rain" label="The Rain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레이디스_코드/Lorelei/</id><title>레이디스_코드 - Lorelei - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94%EC%8A%A4_%EC%BD%94%EB%93%9C/Lorelei/" title="레이디스_코드 - Lorelei - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 이 밤이 마지막이란 걸 <br>말하지 않아도 알아 <br>일 분 일초를 <br>하나도 놓치기 싫은데 <br>잠들고 싶지 않아요 <br>달라지는 세계 <br>그 안에서 우린 <br>물가 위로 번진 <br>불꽃처럼 <br>힘을 잃어가도 쉽게 꺼지지 않아 <br>Oh you're my the only one <br>지금이 지나면 <br>전부 물거품이 되어 사라지게 돼 <br>해가 뜨기 전에 날 안아줘 <br>겨우 허락되는 하루라도 좋아 <br>내 맘을 더는 멈출 수 없어 <br>일 분 일초를 <br>영원보다 길게 만들어 <br>잠들 수 없게 해줘요 <br>더욱 선명하게 <br>나를 비춰주는 <br>Oh you're my the only one <br>지금이 지나면 <br>전부 물거품이 되어 사라지게 돼 <br>해가 뜨기 전에 날 안아줘 <br>겨우 허락되는 하루라도 좋아 <br>내 맘을 더는 멈출 수 없어 <br>지금이 아니면 <br>아무 소용없다는걸 알고 있잖아 <br>태양보다 먼저 날 안아줘 <br>다시 허락 될 하루는 이젠 없어 <br>이 밤을 우린 계속 달려가 <br>지금이 지나면 <br>전부 물거품이 되어 사라지게 돼 <br>해가 뜨기 전에 날 안아줘 <br>겨우 허락되는 하루라도 좋아 <br>내 맘을 더는 멈출 수 없어 <br>Lorelei Lorelei Lorelei Lorelei <br>]]></content><category term="레이디스 코드" label="레이디스 코드"/><category term="Lorelei" label="Lorelei"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오세희/인생길/</id><title>오세희 - 인생길 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%84%B8%ED%9D%AC/%EC%9D%B8%EC%83%9D%EA%B8%B8/" title="오세희 - 인생길 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[큰 산을 굽이돌아 <br>저 하늘을 바라보니 <br>먹물 같은 이내몸은 <br>구름처럼 흘러가네 <br>가슴으로 비 뿌리고 <br>비 맞으며 눈물짓고 <br>마음으로 눈 뿌리고 <br>눈 맞으며 웃음짓네 <br>여기인가 저기인가 <br>저기인가 여기인가 <br>마음쉬어 갈 곳 없어 <br>하염없이 바라보다 <br>제 갈길로 가는구나 <br>제 갈길로 가는구나 <br>세상을 돌고 돌아 <br>서 있는 땅 바라보고 <br>여기인가 하였더니 <br>머문자리 떠나가네 <br>가슴으로 비 뿌리고 <br>비 맞으며 눈물짓고 <br>마음으로 눈 뿌리고 <br>눈 맞으며 웃음짓네 <br>여기인가 저기인가 <br>저기인가 여기인가 <br>마음쉬어 갈 곳 없어 <br>하염없이 바라보다 <br>제 갈길로 가는구나 <br>제 갈길로 가는구나 <br>]]></content><category term="오세희" label="오세희"/><category term="인생길" label="인생길"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오세희/자주자주/</id><title>오세희 - 자주자주 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%84%B8%ED%9D%AC/%EC%9E%90%EC%A3%BC%EC%9E%90%EC%A3%BC/" title="오세희 - 자주자주 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔말고 자주자주 <br>뜸뜸말고 자주자주 <br>물어보고 확인 해줘요 <br>누가누가 내 가슴에 <br>내 가슴에 살고 있는지 <br>사랑한단 말은 <br>너무 흔해 <br>쓰고 싶지 않아요 <br>같이 있고 싶은 마음 <br>창가에 걸리는 밤 <br>바람으로 오시나요 <br>달빛으로 오시나요 <br>얼굴한번 보여 주세요 <br>가끔말고 자주자주 <br>뜸뜸말고 자주자주 <br>물어보고 확인 해줘요 <br>누가누가 내 가슴에 <br>내 가슴에 살고 있는지 <br>사랑한단 말은 <br>너무 흔해 <br>쓰고 싶지 않아요 <br>같이 있고 싶은 마음 <br>창가에 걸리는 밤 <br>바람으로 오시나요 <br>달빛으로 오시나요 <br>얼굴한번 보여 주세요 <br>얼굴한번 보여 주세요 <br>]]></content><category term="오세희" label="오세희"/><category term="자주자주" label="자주자주"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오세희/전통시장_재래시장/</id><title>오세희 - 전통시장 (재래시장) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%84%B8%ED%9D%AC/%EC%A0%84%ED%86%B5%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%A5_%EC%9E%AC%EB%9E%98%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%A5/" title="오세희 - 전통시장 (재래시장) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[힘 내세요 힘 내세요 <br>힘 내세요 힘 내세요 <br>재래시장 아줌마 <br>아저씨 힘 내세요 <br>야채 파는 아줌마 <br>과일 파는 아저씨 <br>웃음으로 손님들을 <br>반겨주네 <br>가족들 뒷바라지에 <br>세월 가는 줄 모르고 <br>어느새 주름살만 늘었네 <br>서민들이 애용하는 <br>생활의 터전 <br>땀방울에 사는 인생 <br>재래시장 아줌마 <br>아저씨 힘을 내세요 <br>힘 내세요 힘 내세요 <br>전통시장 아줌마 <br>아저씨 힘 내세요 <br>순대 파는 아줌마 <br>생선 파는 아저씨 <br>손짓으로 손님들을 <br>반겨주네 <br>자식들 뒷바라지에 <br>세월 가는 줄 모르고 <br>어느새 반평생이 지났네 <br>서민들이 애용하는 <br>생활의 터전 <br>땀방울에 사는 인생 <br>전통시장 아줌마 <br>아저씨 힘을 내세요 <br>땀방울에 사는 인생 <br>전통시장 아줌마 <br>아저씨 힘을 내세요 <br>]]></content><category term="오세희" label="오세희"/><category term="전통시장 (재래시장)" label="전통시장 (재래시장)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/제스터/멀어지다_Feat_강별/</id><title>제스터 - 멀어지다 (Feat. 강별) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%9C%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0/%EB%A9%80%EC%96%B4%EC%A7%80%EB%8B%A4_Feat_%EA%B0%95%EB%B3%84/" title="제스터 - 멀어지다 (Feat. 강별) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아픈 만큼 사랑인 것을 <br>우린 진정 알고 있을까 <br>서로 알지 못했던 <br>이별이란 상처에 아파해 <br>잊혀짐에 두려운 것을 <br>너는 진정 알고 있을까 <br>너의 기억 안에서 <br>사라져갈 내 모습이 <br>슬퍼서 <br>이제는 멀어져 <br>내 곁에 사라져 <br>너에게 하지 못할 <br>이 말을 <br>멀어져간 너에게 <br>떠나버린 너에게 <br>불러 본다 돌아와줘 <br>사랑만큼 깊어진 것이 <br>후회와 미련 <br>그리고 상처라 <br>돌이킬 수 있다면 <br>되돌릴 수 있다면 <br>다시 너를 <br>이제는 멀어져 <br>내 곁에 사라져 <br>너에게 하지 못할 <br>이 말을 <br>멀어져간 너에게 <br>떠나버린 너에게 <br>불러 본다 돌아와줘 <br>내게로 돌아와 <br>내 곁에 머물러 <br>너에게 하고 싶던 <br>이 말을 <br>네가 필요 하다고 <br>다시 내게 오라고 <br>불러 본다 하지만 넌 <br>이제는 멀어져 <br>내 곁에 사라져 <br>너에게 하지 못할 <br>이 말을 <br>멀어져간 너에게 <br>떠나버린 너에게 <br>불러 본다 돌아와줘 <br>]]></content><category term="제스터" label="제스터"/><category term="멀어지다 (Feat. 강별)" label="멀어지다 (Feat. 강별)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/번개소리사/동그랑땡/</id><title>번개소리사 - 동그랑땡 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%88%EA%B0%9C%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%82%AC/%EB%8F%99%EA%B7%B8%EB%9E%91%EB%95%A1/" title="번개소리사 - 동그랑땡 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[동그랑땡을 먹어보자 <br>동그랑땡을 먹어보자 <br>고기를 다지고 두부 넣고 <br>동그랑 동그랑 부쳐보자 <br>에헤라 좋구나 맛이 좋아라 <br>우리 엄마 손맛이다 <br>동그랑 동그랑땡을 먹자 <br>빈대떡을 먹어보자 <br>빈대떡을 먹어보자 <br>녹두를 올리고 맷돌 돌려 <br>빈대떡 빈대떡 부쳐보자 <br>에헤라 좋구나 맛이 좋아라 <br>우리 할머니 손맛이다 <br>빈대떡 빈대떡 먹어보자 <br>달큰한 배추전 먹어보자 <br>고소한 배추전 먹어보자 <br>샛노란 고갱이 그냥 먹고 <br>중간 잎 배추전 부쳐보자 <br>에헤라 좋구나 맛이 좋아라 <br>손으로 찢어서 먹어보자 <br>깨소금 양념장 찍어먹자 <br>에헤라 좋구나 맛이 좋아라 <br>화롯 불가에 둘러앉아 <br>동태전 파전도 먹어보자 <br>동그랑 동그랑땡을 먹자 <br>]]></content><category term="번개소리사" label="번개소리사"/><category term="동그랑땡" label="동그랑땡"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/번개소리사/국수/</id><title>번개소리사 - 국수 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:47:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:47:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%88%EA%B0%9C%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%82%AC/%EA%B5%AD%EC%88%98/" title="번개소리사 - 국수 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하얀 면발의 잔치국수 <br>너무너무 먹고 싶어 <br>건 다시 멸치 팍팍 넣고 <br>냄비뚜껑 열고 끓여요 <br>후루룩 쩝쩝 후루룩 쩝쩝 <br>기가 막혀 어머니가 그리워진다 <br>후루룩 쩝쩝 후루룩 쩝쩝 <br>뜨거워요 호호 불며 먹어 봅시다 <br>시원 새콤한 열무국수 <br>너무너무 먹고 싶어 <br>아낌없이 열무 넣고 <br>얼음 동동 띄워 먹어요 <br>후루룩 쩝쩝 후루룩 쩝쩝 <br>기가 막혀 침이 꼴딱 넘어 갑니다 <br>아삭 와삭 와삭 아삭 이 맛이야 <br>트림하면 잘 먹은 거지 <br>아 좋아라 사는 맛이 이런 것이야 <br>아 좋은데 빈대떡은 왜 생각날까 <br>후루룩 쩝쩝 후루룩 쩝쩝 <br>후루룩 쩝쩝쩝 <br>아사삭 와삭 아사삭 와삭 <br>아사삭 와사삭 <br>면이 익으면 필수조건 <br>얼음물에 빡빡 씻어요 <br>탱글한 면발 보장해요 <br>퉁퉁 불려 먹지 말아요 <br>비린내 없는 멸치육수 당기시면 <br>마른멸치 살짝 볶아요 <br>열무국수 별미는 <br>바로 찐 계란 이죠 <br>깨소금도 잊지 말아요 <br>아 좋아라 사는 맛이 이런 것이야 <br>아 좋은데 빈대떡은 왜 생각날까 <br>아하 좋아라 <br>사는 맛이 이런 것이야 <br>아하 좋은데 <br>막걸리는 왜 생각날까 <br>후루룩 쩝쩝 후루룩 쩝쩝 <br>후루룩 쩝쩝쩝 <br>아사삭 와삭 아사삭 와삭 <br>아사삭 와사삭 <br>]]></content><category term="번개소리사" label="번개소리사"/><category term="국수" label="국수"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/번개소리사/치킨_Chicken/</id><title>번개소리사 - 치킨 (Chicken) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:48:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:48:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%88%EA%B0%9C%EC%86%8C%EB%A6%AC%EC%82%AC/%EC%B9%98%ED%82%A8_Chicken/" title="번개소리사 - 치킨 (Chicken) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[닭다리를 손에 쥐고 <br>입으로 넣어본다 맛있게 냠냠 <br>살코기는 너를 주고 <br>껍데기는 내가 먹을게 오 <br>오늘밤은 나도 몰래 <br>치킨이 생각나 <br>어느 집이 제일 좋을까 <br>바삭대는 소리에 <br>온몸이 떨려오네 <br>오늘 꼭 먹어보자 <br>치킨먹자 오 <br>그동안 어떻게 참았나 <br>너무나 행복해 <br>시간이 멈춰졌으면 <br>치킨도 맛있지만 <br>하얀 무는 필수조건 <br>맛있게 와삭 맛있게 와삭 <br>그래도 목마르면 <br>생맥주도 시켜 봐요 <br>한잔쯤은 괜찮아요 <br>치킨먹자 오 <br>오늘 하루는 내가 쏠게 <br>오 걱정을 마 오 <br>날개는 먹지 마 <br>바람 피면 곤란하잖니 안돼 안돼 <br>내가 너를 지키려면 <br>날개는 내가 먹을게 안돼 <br>치킨먹자 오 <br>그동안 어떻게 참았나 <br>너무나 행복해 <br>시간이 멈춰졌으면 <br>치킨먹자 오 <br>오늘 하루는 내가 쏠게 <br>오 걱정을 마 오 <br>라라라라 라라라라 <br>라라라라 라라라 <br>라라라라 라라라라 <br>라라라라 라라라 <br>]]></content><category term="번개소리사" label="번개소리사"/><category term="치킨 (Chicken)" label="치킨 (Chicken)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김진아/한잔_술에/</id><title>김진아 - 한잔 술에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:48:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:48:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%84%EC%95%84/%ED%95%9C%EC%9E%94_%EC%88%A0%EC%97%90/" title="김진아 - 한잔 술에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[흘러가 버린 <br>기나긴 세월을 지나 <br>오늘밤 우연히 <br>마주친 눈빛 <br>떠나가 버린 <br>덧없는 우리 <br>청춘을 지나 <br>오늘밤 운명은 다시 <br>우리를 이끄나요 <br>어떻게 살았냐고 <br>어디에 있었냐고 <br>떨리는 술잔에 <br>비친 그 얼굴 <br>아무말 하지마요 <br>아무말 묻지마요 <br>모르는 남처럼 <br>스쳐 가세요 <br>바람불면 부는대로 <br>비가오면 오는대로 <br>흐르는 눈물에 젖어 <br>흩어진 세월 <br>아무말도 하지 말아요 <br>아무것도 묻지 말아요 <br>힘들고 지칠때 가끔 <br>한잔 술에 쉬어가요 <br>사라져 버린 <br>머나 먼 시간을 지나 <br>이순간 우연히 <br>마주친 당신 <br>흩어져 버린 <br>빛바랜 우리 <br>추억을 지나 <br>이순간 운명은 다시 <br>우리를 이끄나요 <br>어떻게 살았냐고 <br>어디에 있었냐고 <br>희미한 불빛에 <br>젖은 그 눈빛 <br>아무말 하지마요 <br>아무말 묻지마요 <br>모르는 남처럼 <br>스쳐 가세요 <br>바람불면 부는대로 <br>비가오면 오는대로 <br>흐르는 눈물에 젖어 <br>흩어진 세월 <br>아무말도 하지 말아요 <br>아무것도 묻지 말아요 <br>힘들고 지칠때 가끔 <br>한잔 술에 쉬어가요 <br>]]></content><category term="김진아" label="김진아"/><category term="한잔 술에" label="한잔 술에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김진아/가거나_말거나/</id><title>김진아 - 가거나 말거나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:48:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:48:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%A7%84%EC%95%84/%EA%B0%80%EA%B1%B0%EB%82%98_%EB%A7%90%EA%B1%B0%EB%82%98/" title="김진아 - 가거나 말거나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[사랑 갖고 장난치면 혼난다 <br>마음 갖고 장난치면 죽는다 <br>갈테면 가라 줏대도 없냐 <br>그런 사랑 나도 싫다 <br>사랑한다고 너무 좋다고 <br>네가 먼저 말해 놓고 <br>이젠 싫다고 헤어지자고 <br>말만하면 그만이냐 <br>미안하다고 내 잘못이라고 <br>남자답게 말하면 어디가 덧나 <br>눈치만 보고 딴 핑계만 대고 <br>요리조리 피하며 <br>도망만 다녀 어이가 없네 <br>어이가 상실이네 <br>가거나 말거나 오거나 말거나 <br>맘대로 해라 <br>살거나 말거나 죽거나 말거나 <br>알아서 해라 <br>사랑 갖고 장난치면 혼난다 <br>마음 갖고 장난치면 죽는다 <br>갈테면 가라 줏대도 없냐 <br>그런 사랑 나도 싫다 <br>말만 하라고 다 해 준다고 <br>매달릴땐 언제인데 <br>맨날 바쁘대 피곤만 하대 <br>누가 그 맘 모를까봐 <br>미안하다고 내 잘못이라고 <br>남자답게 말하면 어디가 덧나 <br>눈치만 보고 딴 핑계만 대고 <br>요리조리 피하며 <br>도망만 다녀 어이가 없네 <br>어이가 상실이네 <br>가거나 말거나 오거나 말거나 <br>맘대로 해라 <br>살거나 말거나 죽거나 말거나 <br>알아서 해라 <br>사랑 갖고 장난치면 혼난다 <br>마음 갖고 장난치면 죽는다 <br>갈테면 가라 줏대도 없냐 <br>그런 사랑 나도 싫다 <br>사랑 갖고 장난치면 혼난다 <br>마음 갖고 장난치면 죽는다 <br>갈테면 가라 줏대도 없냐 <br>잘 먹고 잘 살아라 <br>]]></content><category term="김진아" label="김진아"/><category term="가거나 말거나" label="가거나 말거나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/After_You/</id><title>Britt_Nicole - After You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:48:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:48:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/After_You/" title="Britt_Nicole - After You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'll be honest with all that I've been through <br>I've been runnin' after everything but you <br>And I'll be honest <br>Nothing satisfies <br>Like the love I find inside your eyes <br><br>There's nothing sweeter than your love <br>It's all I want, it's all I need <br>There's nothing sweeter than your love <br>You gave it all, poured out for me <br><br>So I'm not after the world <br>I'm after you <br>So I'm not after the world <br>I'm after you <br><br>You were watching <br>Waiting all this time <br>While I was searching for something in this life <br>But there's nothing here that I could find <br>Like the love I find inside your eyes <br><br>Cause nothing's sweeter than your love <br>It's all I want, it's all I need <br>There's nothing sweeter than your love <br>You gave it all, poured out for me <br><br>So I'm not after the world <br>I'm after you <br>So I'm not after the world <br>I'm after you <br>I'm not runnin' after the world <br>I'm runnin' after you <br>So I'm not after the world <br>I'm only after you <br><br>Nothing's sweeter than your love <br>It's all I want, it's all I need <br>There's nothing sweeter than your love <br>You gave it all, poured out for me <br><br>Cause nothing's sweeter than your love <br>It's all I want, it's all I need <br>There's nothing sweeter than your love <br>You gave it all, poured out for me <br><br>So I'm not after the world <br>I'm not after the world <br>I'm after you <br>So I'm not after the world <br>I'm not after the world <br>I'm after you]]></content><category term="Britt Nicole" label="Britt Nicole"/><category term="After You" label="After You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/Girls_Night_Out/</id><title>Britt_Nicole - Girls Night Out - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:48:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:48:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/Girls_Night_Out/" title="Britt_Nicole - Girls Night Out - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We, like, really need a girls night out <br>We need a girl's night out <br>Yeah Yep Hey <br>Let's go <br><br>It's been a crazy week, yeah <br>Haven't been off my feet, no <br>I need a stress relief, yeah <br>Only my girls can bring, oh <br><br>No worries, no drama <br>And no broken hearts <br>Don't know where we're goin' <br>Just get in the car <br>We're perfectly perfect <br>The way that we are, we are <br><br>Cause we ain't got nothin to prove, ooh <br>We'll let our hair down <br>And do what we wanna do, ooh <br>There ain't no boys allowed <br><br>So ladies are you down, down <br>For a girls night out <br>Getting loud, show me how you move, ooh <br>We need a girls night <br>We need a girls night out <br><br>We're laughing all night long, yeah <br>Ain't doing nothin' wrong, no <br>We karaoke on our phone yeah <br>Singing' our favorite song, oh <br><br>No worries, no drama <br>And no broken hearts <br>Don't know where we're goin' <br>Just get in the car <br>We're perfectly perfect <br>The way that we are, we are <br><br>Cause we ain't got nothin to prove <br>Ooh, we'll let our hair down <br>And do what we wanna do, ooh <br>There ain't no boys allowed <br><br>So ladies are you down, down <br>For a girls night out <br>Getting loud, show me how you move, ooh <br>We need a girls night <br>We need a girls night out <br><br>Welcome to the burger shack, were we can make your burgers just like that <br>May I have your order <br>Can we get seven double cheeseburgers please <br>Uh, you got any patties on the grill <br>Patties on the grill now <br>Can I get an order of french fries like seven <br>Wait a minute, you said you wanted an order of fries <br>Can we get seven chocolate milkshakes to dip our fries in <br>You dip fries in your milkshake <br>Yeah <br>Somebody look at this <br><br>Ladies are you down, down <br>For a girls night out <br>Getting loud, show me how you move, ooh <br>We need a girls night <br>Girls night out <br><br>Down, down Do the robot <br>Dougie Sprinkler <br>Is that the Carlton <br>Let me hear ya, loud <br>Oh yeah <br><br>We need a girls night <br>Girls night out <br><br>GIRL <br>Girls night out <br>GIRL <br>Girls night out <br>GIRL <br>Girls night out <br>We need a girls night <br>Girls night out <br><br>Ok, where ya'll going tonight <br>We got a girls night out, no no boys allowed]]></content><category term="Britt Nicole" label="Britt Nicole"/><category term="Girls Night Out" label="Girls Night Out"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/No_Filter/</id><title>Britt_Nicole - No Filter - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:48:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:48:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/No_Filter/" title="Britt_Nicole - No Filter - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There it is, I think we got the perfect shot <br>You'd never know at dinner we didn't even talk <br>And we look so amazing, who wouldn't wanna be us <br>But the smile that we're faking fades when the camera's off <br><br>And we hold it just for the moment <br><br>And what we let the whole world see <br>Isn't really you and me <br>So tell me was a picture worth <br>If we can't say a single word <br>We always put a filter on <br>To try to cover up the flaws <br>And if we do it all for show <br>I think it's time we let it go <br><br>Cause I can picture us, picture us <br>I can picture us with no filter <br>I can picture us, picture us <br>I can picture us with no filter on <br><br>Remember when we didn't have to live a lie <br>And now we can't even look each other in the eye <br>Yeah, I'd like to believe we could go back to the start <br>And if we turn it off would you see me in the dark <br><br>Can you hold me <br>Just for a moment <br><br>And what we let the whole world see <br>Isn't really you and me <br>So tell me was a picture worth <br>If we can't say a single word <br>We always put a filter on <br>To try to cover up the flaws <br>And of we do it all for show <br>I think it's time we let it go <br>Time we let it go <br><br>Cause I can picture us, picture us <br>I can picture us with no filter <br>I can picture us, picture us <br>I can picture us with no filter on <br><br>And we look so amazing, who wouldn't wanna be us <br>But the smile that I'm faking <br>Fades when the camera's off <br>And we hold it <br>Just for the moment <br><br>And what we let the whole world see <br>Isn't really you and me <br>So tell me was a picture worth <br>If we can't say a single word <br>We always put a filter on <br>To try to cover up the flaws <br>And if we do it all for show <br>I think it's time we let it go <br><br>Cause I can picture us, picture us <br>I can picture us with no filter <br>I can picture us, picture us <br>I can picture us with no filter on <br>With no filter on]]></content><category term="Britt Nicole" label="Britt Nicole"/><category term="No Filter" label="No Filter"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/Pave/</id><title>Britt_Nicole - Pave - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:48:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:48:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/Pave/" title="Britt_Nicole - Pave - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I love when it's raining <br>The way it hits the pavement do do do do <br>And bounces onto your skin <br>Yeah I just wanna be it <br><br>Say you wanna get outta here <br>Somewhere where the skies are clear <br>I know just the place to go <br>If we never make it there <br>I don't care if you don't care <br>I just gotta let you know <br><br>If you wanna jump from the top of the waterfall <br>Climb up the mountain <br>Just to hear the call <br>Swinging through the jungle <br>Running for tomorrow <br>Anywhere you wanna go <br>I can pave the road <br><br>For you <br>For you <br>For you <br><br>So pack your bags, we're leaving Let's go <br>Close your eyes and breathe in <br>Tell me, can you see it I can see it now <br>The place that we've been dreaming of <br><br>Say you wanna get outta here <br>Somewhere where the skies are clear <br>I know just the place to go <br>If we never make it there <br>I don't care if you don't care <br>I just gotta let you know <br><br>If you wanna jump from the top of the waterfall <br>Climb up the mountain <br>Just to hear the call <br>Swinging through the jungle <br>Running for tomorrow <br>Anywhere you wanna go <br>I can pave the road <br><br>For you <br>For you <br>For you <br>Yeah, I'll pave the road <br><br>Me and you baby <br>We can go wherever <br>I can pave the road <br><br>Yeah <br>For you <br>Yeah <br>For you <br>For you Yeah, I'll pave the road <br>For you <br>For you <br>For you <br>Me and you, baby <br>We can go wherever you wanna]]></content><category term="Britt Nicole" label="Britt Nicole"/><category term="Pave" label="Pave"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/All_Day/</id><title>Britt_Nicole - All Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:48:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:48:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/All_Day/" title="Britt_Nicole - All Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Sometimes I gotta go to work <br>I be thinking 'bout you all day <br>I be thinking 'bout you in the studio <br>Be thinking 'bout you on the stage <br>I was wishing I was holdin' you <br>Wishing I was singing you to sleep <br>Thinking about you all the time, everyday, all night, all my life <br>I don't wanna miss nothin' <br>I don't wanna miss nothin', nothin' <br>I don't wanna miss one smile, one cry <br>I don't wanna miss one smile, one cry <br>I don't wanna miss nothin' <br>I don't wanna miss nothin', nothin' <br>I don't wanna miss one smile, one cry <br>I dont wanna miss nothin', nothin', no <br><br>When you look back I know you will remember <br>That I did it all for you <br>I'll give you all my love <br>I'll give you all my heart <br>All day, all night' <br>For life, forever, always <br>I'll give you all my love <br>Gonna give you all my heart <br>All day, all night' <br>For life, forever, always <br>Oh, oh, woah <br>All day, all night, forever, and always <br>Oh, oh, woah <br>All day, all night, forever, and always <br><br>Every single second life goes by <br>I just wanna be by your side <br>That's what I'm feelin' tonight <br>That's what I'm feelin' tonight <br>Sometimes I look into your eyes <br>You're a miracle, and you are mine <br>You're a beautiful life, you're a beautiful life <br>Yeah <br><br>I don't wanna miss nothin' <br>I don't wanna miss nothin', nothin' <br>I don't wanna miss one smile, one cry <br>I don't wanna miss one smile, one cry <br>I don't wanna miss nothin' <br>I don't wanna miss nothin', nothin' <br>I don't wanna miss one smile, one cry <br>I don't wanna miss nothin', nothin', no <br><br>With the strength, you give me to move mountains <br>And fight lions, I'll do it for you <br><br>I'll give you all my love <br>I'll give you all my heart <br>All day, all night' <br>For life, forever, always <br>I'll give you all my love <br>Gonna give you all my heart <br>All day, all night' <br>For life, forever, always <br>Oh, oh, woah <br>All day, all night, forever, and always <br>Oh, oh, woah <br>All day, all night, forever, and always <br>Always, yeah <br><br>Sometimes I look into your eyes <br>And I see mine, and it's a beautiful, beautiful, beautiful life <br><br>I'll give you all my love <br>I'll give you all my heart <br>All day, all night' <br>For life, forever, always <br>I'll give you all my love <br>Gonna give you all my heart <br>All day, all night' <br>For life, forever, always <br>Oh, oh, woah <br>All day, all night, forever, and always <br>Oh, oh, woah <br>All day, all night, forever, and always <br><br>I will be there for you <br>I will be there for you, you ain't gotta go anywhere <br>I will be there for you <br>When I can't I know that God will be holdin' you <br>All day all night, forever <br>And always <br>Always]]></content><category term="Britt Nicole" label="Britt Nicole"/><category term="All Day" label="All Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/Be_The_Change/</id><title>Britt_Nicole - Be The Change - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-23T15:48:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-23T15:48:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Britt_Nicole/Be_The_Change/" title="Britt_Nicole - Be The Change - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've been staring at the world, waiting <br>I've been looking for a change lately <br>All the trouble and all the pain we're facing <br>Someone gotta be the hope and someone gotta be the love <br><br>Too much light to be livin' in the dark <br>Where are we going We ain't getting very far <br>Why waste time We only got one life <br><br>And don't you know it starts today <br>And baby, no, it's not too late <br>It begins with you and I <br>Together we can be the change <br>So go and let your heart burn bright <br>And watch it catch like a wild fire <br>I believe in you and I <br>Together we can be the change <br>Whoah, whoah <br>Whoah, together we can be the change <br><br>So many hearts around the world, breaking <br>If I only got one chance, I'll take it <br>Let my voice be the trumpet that can say that <br>Someone gotta be the hope and someone gotta be the love <br><br>Too much light to be livin' in the dark <br>Where are we going We ain't getting very far <br>Why waste time We only got one life <br><br>And don't you know it starts today <br>And baby, no, it's not too late oh no, it's not too late <br>It begins with you and I you and I <br>Together we can be the change <br><br>So go and let your heart burn bright <br>And watch it catch like a wild fire <br>I believe in you and I you and I <br>Together we can be the change <br>Whoah, whoah <br>Whoah, together we can be the change <br><br>Face it <br>One chance, we gotta take it <br>Stand together and change it <br>We can make this world bright <br>Turn on all the lights <br><br>Face it <br>One chance, we gotta take it we gotta take it <br>Stand together and change it change it <br>We can make this world bright <br>Turn on all the lights <br><br>We can be the change <br><br>And don't you know it starts today <br>And baby, no, it's not too late oh no, it's not too late <br>It begins with you and I you and I <br>Together we can be the change I know, that we can be the change <br><br>So go and let your heart burn bright <br>And watch it catch like a wild fire <br>I believe in you and I you and I <br>Together we can be the change <br>Whoah, whoah <br>Whoah, together we can be the change we can be the change <br>Whoah, whoah <br>Whoah, together we can be the change]]></content><category term="Britt Nicole" label="Britt Nicole"/><category term="Be The Change" label="Be The Change"/></entry></feed>