<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:35+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/박치용/그대_떠나는_날/</id><title>박치용 - 그대 떠나는 날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:20:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:20:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B0%95%EC%B9%98%EC%9A%A9/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80_%EB%96%A0%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%82%A0/" title="박치용 - 그대 떠나는 날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대가 나를 <br>떠날 거란 걸 <br>이미 알고 있었죠 <br>내 마음엔 비가 오고 <br>가야할 길을 잃었죠 <br>어떻게 그대를 <br>보내야 할까요 <br>그대 빈 자리가 <br>낯설게만 느껴져요 <br>그대 떠나는 날 <br>울지 않으리 <br>언젠가 이 사랑 <br>꼭 다시 <br>만나리라 믿기에 <br>그대가 내게 <br>올거라는 걸 <br>나는 알 수 있죠 <br>보고싶어 불러봐도 <br>아무 대답 없죠 <br>어떻게 그대를 <br>찾아야 할까요 <br>잘가라는 말은 <br>하지 못할 것같아 <br>여전히 이사랑 <br>그대에게 멈췄어요 <br>그대 떠나는 날 <br>울지 않으리 <br>언젠가 이 사랑 <br>꼭 다시 만나리라 <br>믿기에 믿기에 <br>그대여 잊지 말아요 <br>여기 한사람 <br>그대만을 사랑한 <br>날 기억해요 <br>]]></content><category term="박치용" label="박치용"/><category term="그대 떠나는 날" label="그대 떠나는 날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sko_스코/떡볶이_TTEOKBOKKI_Feat_박단/</id><title>Sko (스코) - 떡볶이 (TTEOKBOKKI) (Feat. 박단) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:20:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:20:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sko_%EC%8A%A4%EC%BD%94/%EB%96%A1%EB%B3%B6%EC%9D%B4_TTEOKBOKKI_Feat_%EB%B0%95%EB%8B%A8/" title="Sko (스코) - 떡볶이 (TTEOKBOKKI) (Feat. 박단) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이가 대변하네 이 땅의 <br>흐르는 또 다른 내 안의 피 <br>내가 나를 대표해서 <br>이 자리에 왔고 <br>Everything a Represent about me <br>난 빈집에 매거진 하나 들고 <br>취미를 찾고 있지 배트맨 <br>내 아이폰에 빈지노의 <br>Being myself가 <br>들어온 이후로 난 허슬해 <br>떡볶이 매워요 언제나 매워요 <br>미국은 느려요 <br>한국은 빨라요 색깔은 찐해요 <br>난 그걸 물어요 한국다운 색깔을 <br>파레트에 묻혀요 뱅 갱갱갱 우린 <br>Chang Chang Chang Chang <br>스테이크 스시 탕수육은 먹어도 <br>색깔은 저게 찐해 <br>Color's Like that <br>이건 코리안 HALAL FOOD <br>먹기 전 감사의 기도는 생략 중 <br>멀 그리 고민 많아 <br>걔 네가 먹는 햄버거는 <br>Fat or Japan 와규 <br>미안 나도 좋아해서 <br>배가 나오지만 <br>여자랑 같은 느낌이야 존나 쎄해 <br>좋은 곳이 너무 많지만 <br>스타벅스 정돈 괜찮아서 <br>You You You Should Stay man <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>When I was 초등학생 <br>My Mom은 내게 <br>너가 갖고 싶은걸 갖을려면 <br>이 엄만 더 열심히 일을 해야 돼 <br>한번도 부끄러워 한적 없었지 <br>자랑스런 떡볶이가 왜 <br>이게 아니었다면 <br>힙합을 내가 할 수 있었을까 <br>지금 로뎅이 돼 <br>오 Mom 내게 돈맛을 <br>일찍 알려주셨던 우리 엄만 <br>또 모든 알바 사장들은 <br>다 월급이 늦긴 했어도 걱정 마 <br>라고 씨불어 댔지 <br>이제 그런 걱정에서 <br>탈피한지 난 오래 지난 <br>난 오리지날 보고 싶어 <br>don't have to solve it <br>잃어버린 아이폰처럼 <br>찾길 하지다 <br>타바스코 Want it <br>캡사이신 Want it <br>와사비도 Want it <br>고추장도 Want it <br>싫은 랩펀 burn it <br>릴보이는 on it <br>가짜 랩펄 보 니 <br>On and On &amp; Funny <br>이건 겟잇뷰티 아니야 <br>더 이상 날 치장하려 하지마 <br>이건 신나는 노래야 <br>매우신 나는 그 신을 <br>매울 신 이라고 표현한다 <br>야 임마 <br>Ni hao ma wo jiao pu dan <br>Nimen yi ding zhidao <br>Wo shi tang cu rou de nanzi <br>Wo de liaoli ting hao chi <br>예 Shou'er to 베이징 <br>Zai na'er de wo lai gei ni <br>ma bro Sko shit <br>매콤달콤 떡볶이 <br>So hot like 泡菜 <br>한중미 아우르는 우리 스타일 <br>어디를 가든지 간에 <br>풍기는 맛있는 냄새 <br>칭챙총 시크리또 <br>레시피 쏟아지는 개런티 <br>아낌없는 재료비 <br>lye lye <br>맛나는 떡볶이 혼자서 <br>3인분 뚝딱임 <br>혼또니 오이시 고치 <br>소사마 요로시쿠 <br>내일두 탕수육 말구 <br>say what <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>떡볶이 <br>매워요 매워요 매워요 매워요 <br>]]></content><category term="Sko (스코)" label="Sko (스코)"/><category term="떡볶이 (TTEOKBOKKI) (Feat. 박단)" label="떡볶이 (TTEOKBOKKI) (Feat. 박단)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한올_Han-All/잘자_좋은_꿈_꿔_Inst/</id><title>한올 (Han-All) - 잘자 좋은 꿈 꿔 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:20:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:20:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%98%AC_Han-All/%EC%9E%98%EC%9E%90_%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80_%EA%BF%88_%EA%BF%94_Inst/" title="한올 (Han-All) - 잘자 좋은 꿈 꿔 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루는 짧은데 <br>한 시간씩은 참 길어 <br>고생한 내 팔다리를 <br>주물러줄 사람도 없어 <br>급히 먹은 점심이 <br>얹혀 있는 듯 한 채로 <br>또 살아보겠다고 <br>저녁을 먹고 있어 <br>집에 가는 길 들여다본 <br>휴대폰 세상엔 <br>나만 빼고 다 <br>행복해 보이네 <br>편의점에 들러 <br>맥주 한 캔 사서 <br>무의미하게 티비를 <br>보며 마시다가 <br>이런저런 생각에 <br>뒤척이다가 <br>지친 내게 수고했단 <br>한마디도 못한 채 <br>잠드네 <br>새벽 중간쯤 <br>눈이 떠져 문득 <br>창문 밖을 바라보니 <br>코 끝이 시리다가 <br>청승맞게 <br>눈물이 흐르네 <br>어디 없을까 <br>내 얘기를 들어줄 한 사람 <br>어딘가 있다면 <br>얼른 나타나줘 <br>오늘도 편의점에서 <br>맥주 한 캔 사고 <br>무의미하게 티비를 <br>보며 마시겠지 <br>이런저런 생각에 <br>뒤척이다가 <br>지친 내게 수고했단 <br>한마디도 못한 채 <br>아니 오늘은 할 거야 <br>오늘 하루 힘들었지 <br>고생했어 수고했어 <br>잘자 좋은 꿈꿔 To me <br>]]></content><category term="한올 (Han-All)" label="한올 (Han-All)"/><category term="잘자 좋은 꿈 꿔 (Inst.)" label="잘자 좋은 꿈 꿔 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한올_Han-All/잘자_좋은_꿈_꿔/</id><title>한올 (Han-All) - 잘자 좋은 꿈 꿔 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:20:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:20:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%EC%98%AC_Han-All/%EC%9E%98%EC%9E%90_%EC%A2%8B%EC%9D%80_%EA%BF%88_%EA%BF%94/" title="한올 (Han-All) - 잘자 좋은 꿈 꿔 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루는 짧은데 <br>한 시간씩은 참 길어 <br>고생한 내 팔다리를 <br>주물러줄 사람도 없어 <br>급히 먹은 점심이 <br>얹혀 있는 듯 한 채로 <br>또 살아보겠다고 <br>저녁을 먹고 있어 <br>집에 가는 길 들여다본 <br>휴대폰 세상엔 <br>나만 빼고 다 <br>행복해 보이네 <br>편의점에 들러 <br>맥주 한 캔 사서 <br>무의미하게 티비를 <br>보며 마시다가 <br>이런저런 생각에 <br>뒤척이다가 <br>지친 내게 수고했단 <br>한마디도 못한 채 <br>잠드네 <br>새벽 중간쯤 <br>눈이 떠져 문득 <br>창문 밖을 바라보니 <br>코 끝이 시리다가 <br>청승맞게 <br>눈물이 흐르네 <br>어디 없을까 <br>내 얘기를 들어줄 한 사람 <br>어딘가 있다면 <br>얼른 나타나줘 <br>오늘도 편의점에서 <br>맥주 한 캔 사고 <br>무의미하게 티비를 <br>보며 마시겠지 <br>이런저런 생각에 <br>뒤척이다가 <br>지친 내게 수고했단 <br>한마디도 못한 채 <br>아니 오늘은 할 거야 <br>오늘 하루 힘들었지 <br>고생했어 수고했어 <br>잘자 좋은 꿈꿔 To me <br>]]></content><category term="한올 (Han-All)" label="한올 (Han-All)"/><category term="잘자 좋은 꿈 꿔" label="잘자 좋은 꿈 꿔"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/mooi_무이/Angel_Feat_Jino/</id><title>mooi (무이) - Angel (Feat. Jino) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:20:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:20:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/mooi_%EB%AC%B4%EC%9D%B4/Angel_Feat_Jino/" title="mooi (무이) - Angel (Feat. Jino) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어떻게 난 시작할까 <br>가르쳐줄 순 없겠니 <br>oh girl <br>난 아무것도 모르겠어 <br>가까이 니가 있어도 <br>잡을 수 없는 별처럼 <br>oh girl <br>날 좌절하게 해 <br>두근두근 떨려와 <br>벼랑 끝에 있는 것처럼 <br>서투른 내 모습 니 손을 잡아 <br>달려가고만 싶어 <br>어느 누구도 없는 우리 둘만 <br>세상 끝까지 가고 싶어 <br>wow beautiful girl <br>넌 아주 완벽한 <br>your my angel <br>wow 날 받아줘요 <br>내 천사가 되어주오 <br>니 곁에 늘 함께 있어줄게 <br>내 맘에 언제나 있어줘 <br>oh 늘 함께 늘 너와 있고 싶어 <br>매일 아침마다 일어나 <br>니 모습 보고 싶어 <br>가장 먼저 네 눈에 띄는 게 <br>나였으면 했어 <br>oh girl 널 보고 싶어 <br>미치겠네 내 맘은 마치 앰뷸런스 <br>갈 길은 복잡한데 <br>앞에 차는 꽉 막혀 <br>시간은 없는데 <br>날 어필하지 못했어 <br>이러다 내 사랑 <br>생각만하다 막히나 <br>oh no 지금이라도 달려가 <br>두근두근 떨려와 <br>나비를 쫓는 아이처럼 <br>서투른 내 모습 잡히질 않아 <br>놓칠 수 없어 나의 <br>한줄기 빛과 같은 <br>그댄 angel <br>이젠 내 맘을 받아줘요 <br>wow beautiful girl <br>넌 아주 완벽한 <br>your my angel <br>wow 날 받아줘요 <br>내 천사가 되어주오 <br>니 곁에 늘 함께 있어줄게 <br>내 맘에 언제나 있어줘 <br>wow 늘 함께 늘 너와 있고 싶어 <br>wow beautiful girl <br>넌 아주 완벽한 <br>your my angel <br>wow 날 받아줘요 <br>내 천사가 되어주오 <br>니 곁에 늘 함께 있어줄게 <br>내 맘에 언제나 있어줘 <br>wow 늘 함께 늘 너와 있고 싶어 <br>]]></content><category term="mooi (무이)" label="mooi (무이)"/><category term="Angel (Feat. Jino)" label="Angel (Feat. Jino)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HiHills/10_10/</id><title>HiHills - 10/10 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:21:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:21:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HiHills/10_10/" title="HiHills - 10/10 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가을비가 내리는 날에 <br>난 문득 생각이 나네 <br>우린 갈 곳 없이 비를 맞아도 <br>마주보고 웃을 수 있었네 <br>그리움은 더 쌓여만 가고 <br>난 여전히 먼 곳을 바라보고 서서 <br>또 어딘가로 흘러가겠지 <br>내리는 가을비 맞으며 <br>조금씩 서서히 조금씩 서서히 <br>차가워져 가네 점점 식어가네 <br>차가워져 가네 점점 식어가네 <br>차가워져 가네 점점 식어가네 <br>차가워져 가네 점점 식어가네 <br>차가워져 가네 점점 식어가네 <br>차가워져 가네 점점 식어가네 <br>]]></content><category term="HiHills" label="HiHills"/><category term="10/10" label="10/10"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HiHills/Ooh_Ooh/</id><title>HiHills - Ooh Ooh - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:21:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:21:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HiHills/Ooh_Ooh/" title="HiHills - Ooh Ooh - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언젠가 난 <br>아무도 모르는 그 곳으로 <br>언젠가 넌 내가 <br>만질 수 없는 곳으로 <br>Ooh Ooh <br>결국 너와 나 우린 <br>Ooh Ooh <br>결국 너와 나 우리는 <br>Ooh Ooh <br>결국 너와 나 우린 <br>영원 할 수는 없을 거야 <br>언젠가 난 작별을 고하고 <br>혼자 걷겠지 <br>언젠가 넌 내게 안녕하고 <br>혼자 걷겠지 혼자 걷겠지 <br>Ooh Ooh <br>결국 너와 나 우린 <br>Ooh Ooh <br>결국 너와 나 우리는 <br>Ooh Ooh <br>결국 너와 나 우린 <br>영원 할 수는 없을 거야 <br>Ooh Ooh <br>would you still love me <br>Ooh Ooh <br>would you still love me <br>Ooh Ooh <br>결국 너와 나 우린 <br>Would you still love me <br>결국 너와 나 우리는 <br>Ooh Ooh <br>결국 너와 나 우린 <br>Would you still love me <br>영원 할 수는 없을 거야 <br>]]></content><category term="HiHills" label="HiHills"/><category term="Ooh Ooh" label="Ooh Ooh"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HiHills/LXD/</id><title>HiHills - LXD - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:21:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:21:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HiHills/LXD/" title="HiHills - LXD - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[매일 밤 찾아오던 어둠이 <br>어느 날 문득 <br>낯설게 느껴 질 때면 <br>난 이미 잊혀진 <br>기억들을 꺼내고 <br>어둠 속을 찾아서 걸어 <br>Yeah 먼 길을 돌아서 난 <br>한참을 거닐며 <br>아무런 이유도 없이 <br>아무런 이유도 없이 <br>Yeah 먼 길을 돌아서 난 <br>한참을 거닐며 <br>아무런 이유도 없이 <br>아무런 이유도 없이 <br>아 아무런 이유 없이 <br>밤새워 울었네 난 <br>아 아무런 이유 없이 <br>밤새워 울었네 난 <br>매일 밤 찾아오던 <br>어둠이 내게 <br>어느 날 문득 <br>낯설게 느껴 질 때면 난 <br>소리치며 화를 내고 도망쳐 <br>어둠 속을 혼자서 걸어 <br>Yeah 먼 길을 돌아서 난 <br>한참을 거닐며 <br>아무런 이유도 없이 <br>아무런 이유도 없이 <br>아 아무런 이유 없이 <br>밤새워 울었네 난 <br>아 아무런 이유 없이 <br>밤새워 울었네 난 <br>아 아무런 이유 없이 <br>밤새워 울었네 난 <br>아 아무런 이유 없이 <br>밤새워 울었네 난 <br>]]></content><category term="HiHills" label="HiHills"/><category term="LXD" label="LXD"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HiHills/Blow_my_mind/</id><title>HiHills - Blow my mind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:21:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:21:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/HiHills/Blow_my_mind/" title="HiHills - Blow my mind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너와 나 우리 헤엄치자 <br>아주 기나긴 밤을 지나 <br>아침이 밝아 올 때까지 <br>검은 강 위를 걸어보자 <br>젖은 안개 숲 속을 지나 <br>모든 게 하얘질 때까지 <br>나와 닮은 표정으로 <br>날 위로해줘 <br>너를 닮은 그곳으로 <br>날 데려가 줘 <br>Blow my mind <br>Blow me away <br>Blow my mind <br>Blow me away <br>너와 나 우리 날아가보자 <br>아주 기나 긴 밤을 지나 <br>모든 게 다 보일 때까지 <br>나와 닮은 표정으로 <br>날 위로해줘 <br>너를 닮은 그곳으로 <br>날 데려가 줘 <br>Blow my mind <br>Blow me away <br>Blow my mind <br>Blow me away <br>Ooh blow my mind <br>Ooh blow my mind <br>Ooh blow my mind <br>Ooh blow my mind <br>Oh blow my mind <br>Blow me away <br>Blow my mind <br>Oh blow me away <br>Ooh blow my mind <br>Ooh blow my mind <br>Ooh blow my mind <br>Ooh blow my mind <br>]]></content><category term="HiHills" label="HiHills"/><category term="Blow my mind" label="Blow my mind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanilla_Mousse/Day_By_Day/</id><title>Vanilla Mousse - Day By Day - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:22:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:22:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Vanilla_Mousse/Day_By_Day/" title="Vanilla Mousse - Day By Day - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다시 돌아올 순 없어 <br>다시 또 되돌릴 순 없어 <br>내일은 오늘로 <br>오늘은 또 어제로 <br>내 마음 속에 차곡차곡 <br>쌓여만 가는 너와의 기억 <br>기억은 다시 추억으로 <br>Day By Day <br>하루하루 또 <br>의미 없는 하루하루 <br>어서 빨리 어른이 <br>되고 싶었던 하루하루 <br>기타를 치며 노래를 하며 <br>하얗게 지새우던 <br>내 어린 시절 <br>돌아 갈 수 없는 시절 <br>내 텅 빈 마음 <br>속을 채워보려고 <br>하면할수록 내 주위는 <br>텅 비어 버렸어 <br>너무나 커다란 <br>내 꿈 앞에서 <br>한없이 작아져만 <br>가야했던 내 어린 시절 <br>알 수 없는 미래가 <br>너무나 두려워 <br>하얗게 지새우던 <br>그 많은 밤들 <br>때론 흘러 내리는 눈물 <br>주윌 둘러보면 <br>모두 웃고 있는데 <br>나 혼자 똑 떨어진 <br>것만 같아서 <br>그럴때면 너무 <br>외로웠어 <br>다시 돌아올 순 없어 <br>다시 또 되돌릴 순 없어 <br>내일은 오늘로 <br>오늘은 또 어제로 <br>내 마음 속에 차곡차곡 <br>쌓여만 가는 너와의 기억 <br>기억은 다시 추억으로 <br>Day By Day <br>영원할 것만 같던 첫사랑 <br>함께 있으면 아무것도 <br>두렵지 않던 친구들 <br>할머니께서 불러주던 노래 <br>이젠 들을 수 없어 <br>그게 난 조금 슬퍼 <br>슬퍼도 울지 않으려고 <br>난 애써왔어 <br>눈물을 참은 만큼 <br>옅어져만 가는 미소 <br>너무나 약해빠진 <br>나를 감추고 싶어 <br>과장된 내 모습 뒤에 <br>숨어 지내왔어 <br>화려한 파티가 <br>끝나고 나면 <br>또 다시 시작되는 <br>혼자만의 시간 <br>보일 듯 말듯 희미하게 <br>밤하늘을 비추고 있는 <br>저 별과 오늘도 한 잔 <br>알 수 없는 미래가 <br>너무나 두려워 <br>하얗게 지새우던 <br>그 많은 밤들 <br>때론 흘러 내리는 눈물 <br>주윌 둘러보면 <br>모두 웃고 있는데 <br>나 혼자 똑 떨어진 <br>것만 같아서 <br>그럴때면 너무 <br>외로웠어 <br>다시 돌아올 순 없어 <br>다시 또 되돌릴 순 없어 <br>내일은 오늘로 <br>오늘은 또 어제로 <br>내 마음 속에 차곡차곡 <br>쌓여만 가는 너와의 기억 <br>기억은 다시 추억으로 <br>Day By Day <br>]]></content><category term="Vanilla Mousse" label="Vanilla Mousse"/><category term="Day By Day" label="Day By Day"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/쿤요/My_Own_Fantasy_Vocal_별빛/</id><title>쿤요 - My Own Fantasy (Vocal 별빛) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:22:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:22:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%BF%A4%EC%9A%94/My_Own_Fantasy_Vocal_%EB%B3%84%EB%B9%9B/" title="쿤요 - My Own Fantasy (Vocal 별빛) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[누군가를 사랑하는 일 <br>누군가와 이별하는 일 <br>익숙해져 버린 슬픔에 <br>눈물들은 또 낯설어져 <br>My Dream <br>My Fantasy <br>돌아갈 순 없겠지 <br>가장 나였던 그 시간으로 <br>아픈 기억 너머로 <br>꿈속을 헤메이던 <br>행복했던 그 시간으로 <br>가슴으로 살던 그 때로 <br>가고 싶어 <br>두려움만 커져버려서 <br>발걸음은 더 무거워져 <br>맘을 써야 할 일들이 <br>어색해져 버린 나일까 <br>My Dream <br>My Fantasy <br>돌아갈 순 없겠지 <br>가장 나였던 그 시간으로 <br>아픈 기억 너머로 <br>꿈속을 헤메이던 <br>행복했던 그 시간으로 <br>가슴으로 살던 그 때로 <br>가고 싶어 <br>흘린 눈물들이 <br>잊으라고 <br>잊어야 한다고 <br>다그쳤던 기억 <br>다신 <br>꺼내지 않으려 했던 <br>이제 와 그립다 <br>말하게 된 기억 <br>My Dream <br>My Fantasy <br>돌아갈 수 없대도 <br>시간을 타고 <br>무뎌지려 해도 <br>앞을 볼 수 없어도 <br>사랑을 내밀었던 <br>다음을 생각하지 않았던 <br>처음의 나와 <br>가까워지기를 <br>]]></content><category term="쿤요" label="쿤요"/><category term="My Own Fantasy (Vocal 별빛)" label="My Own Fantasy (Vocal 별빛)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kokoshca/Mi_Chica_Preferida/</id><title>Kokoshca - Mi Chica Preferida - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:23:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:23:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kokoshca/Mi_Chica_Preferida/" title="Kokoshca - Mi Chica Preferida - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Eres mi chica preferida <br>Por tus labios secos con estrias <br>Eres mi chica preferida <br>Por tus pecas que al sol se duplican <br>Eres mi chica, mi chica, mi chica <br>Por tus besos humedos y frios que <br>siempre son lentos que saben mejor <br>Porque nunca te quejas de nada y <br>aceptas propuestas que te hago sin fe. <br>Porque actuas como una chiquilla y <br>luego, mujer, pretendes volver <br>Porque a pesar de que hay muchas otras <br>te tengo delante y siento tu piel <br>Alisate el pelo <br>Alisatelo ya <br>Fuiste mi chica preferida]]></content><category term="Kokoshca" label="Kokoshca"/><category term="Mi Chica Preferida" label="Mi Chica Preferida"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kokoshca/La_Fuerza/</id><title>Kokoshca - La Fuerza - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:23:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:23:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Kokoshca/La_Fuerza/" title="Kokoshca - La Fuerza - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Siempre hay una extrana fuerza <br>Que hace que salga <br>Una noche mas <br>No lo puedo evitar <br>Somos como los mosquitos <br>Que acuden zumbando <br>A la luz del neon <br><br>Amigos como azucarillos <br>Que endulzan la noche <br>Se disuelven despues <br>No los vuelvo a ver <br>Y danzamos como hienas <br>En busca de eso <br>Que tu llamas amor <br><br>Hoy no te he vuelto a ver <br>Hoy no te he vuelto a ver <br>Hoy no te he vuelto a ver <br><br>Y morir como borrachos en cualquier lugar <br>Y nadie hablara de nosotros mas <br>Y acabar con mis amigos bebiendome a tragos <br>Toda mi juventud <br><br>Es la fuerza <br>Es la fuerza <br><br>Por que nos frena la lluvia <br>Mojados por dentro mojarse por fuera <br>Que mas da <br>Y aunque no siempre es divertido <br>Yo se, que lo haria otra vez <br>Y acabar con mis amigos bebiendome <br>A tragos toda mi senectud <br><br>Y morir como borrachos en cualquier rincon <br>Y nadie hablara de nosotros mas, ¡mas! <br>Y luego me diras <br>Que nada mas salir <br>Querias regresar <br>Esa fuerza te lleva]]></content><category term="Kokoshca" label="Kokoshca"/><category term="La Fuerza" label="La Fuerza"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/용빈/타나/</id><title>용빈 - 타나 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:24:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:24:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%A9%EB%B9%88/%ED%83%80%EB%82%98/" title="용빈 - 타나 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[향기 바람 <br>너의 미소 불어와 <br>너의 첫 느낌은 <br>몸을 녹이는 따뜻한 바람 <br>어두운 풀숲을 밝히는 달빛 <br>타나 타나 타나 얼마나 <br>너를 보다가 뜨거워진 마음 <br>어떡하나 <br>달처럼 빛나는 머릿결 <br>별빛 두 눈망울 <br>보다가 보다가 애타는 시간만 <br>흘러가 저 하늘에 <br>새하얀 두 손을 보고 있으면 <br>다 녹아내려 <br>무엇보다 밝은 따뜻한 이 밤 <br>허전한 내 안을 가득히 채운 <br>그대의 눈빛 <br>아팠던 내 맘을 치유한 사람 <br>타나 타나 타나 얼마나 <br>너를 보다가 뜨거워진 마음 <br>어떡하나 <br>달처럼 빛나는 머릿결 <br>별빛 두 눈망울 <br>보다가 보다가 애타는 시간만 <br>흘러가 저 하늘에 <br>타나 얼마나 <br>너를 보다가 뜨거워진 마음 <br>어떡하나 <br>달처럼 빛나는 머릿결 <br>별빛 두 눈망울 <br>보다가 보다가 애타는 시간만 <br>흘러가 저 하늘에 <br>]]></content><category term="용빈" label="용빈"/><category term="타나" label="타나"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/용빈/이번_크리스마스/</id><title>용빈 - 이번 크리스마스 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:26:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:26:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%A9%EB%B9%88/%EC%9D%B4%EB%B2%88_%ED%81%AC%EB%A6%AC%EC%8A%A4%EB%A7%88%EC%8A%A4/" title="용빈 - 이번 크리스마스 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 눈동자 속 <br>모두 내려 넘쳐 <br>창 밖은 눈이 내리고 <br>점점 뜨거워지는 우리 둘 <br>오 메리 크리스마스 <br>너와 나 크리스마스 <br>네 손을 잡고 <br>이번 크리스마스엔 <br>아쉽지 않게 <br>외롭지 않게 너와 함께 <br>오 해피 크리스마스 <br>너와 나 크리스마스 <br>내일도 너와 매일 크리스마스 <br>party for you and me <br>party for you and me <br>party for you and me <br>christmas party for you and me <br>우리 빨개진 두 손 <br>꼭 잡고 걸어 <br>환하게 비춰진 우리 <br>조명아래 흰 눈 사이 <br>오 메리 크리스마스 <br>너와나 크리스마스 <br>네 손을 잡고 <br>이번 크리스마스엔 <br>아쉽지 않게 <br>외롭지 않게 너와 함께 <br>오 해피 크리스마스 <br>너와 나 크리스마스 <br>내일도 너와 매일 크리스마스 <br>party for you and me <br>party for you and me <br>party for you and me <br>christmas party for you and me <br>christmas oh happy new year <br>오 메리 크리스마스 <br>너와나 크리스마스 <br>네 손을 잡고 <br>이번 크리스마스엔 <br>아쉽지 않게 <br>외롭지 않게 너와 함께 <br>오 해피 크리스마스 <br>너와 나 크리스마스 <br>내일도 너와 매일 크리스마스 <br>party for you and me <br>오늘밤 너와 너와 함께 <br>오 메리 크리스마스 <br>너와나 크리스마스 <br>네 손을 잡고 <br>이번 크리스마스엔 <br>아쉽지 않게 <br>외롭지 않게 너와 함께 <br>오 해피 크리스마스 <br>너와 나 크리스마스 <br>내일도 너와 매일 크리스마스 <br>party for you and me <br>party for you and me <br>party for you and me <br>christmas party for you and me <br>]]></content><category term="용빈" label="용빈"/><category term="이번 크리스마스" label="이번 크리스마스"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Le_Mans/Zerbina/</id><title>Le Mans - Zerbina - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:26:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:26:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Le_Mans/Zerbina/" title="Le Mans - Zerbina - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Vivo en una ciudad <br>Tengo pocos amigos <br>Solo soy una mas <br>Se que no voy a sorprender <br><br>Y no se que pensar <br>Cuando otros opinan <br><br>Solo se si algo me sienta bien o mal <br>Cosas faciles de entender, tambien <br><br>Una vez cada mes <br>Compro un periodico <br>Nunca voy mas alla <br>De la cartelera y <br><br>No avanzo mas <br>No merece el esfuerzo <br><br>A alguien le puede interesar, no a mi <br>Todos saben lo que anda mal, yo no <br><br>Todos saben lo que anda mal, yo no <br>No te disgustes si eso me da igual <br>Solo se si algo me sienta mal o bien]]></content><category term="Le Mans" label="Le Mans"/><category term="Zerbina" label="Zerbina"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Boxed_In/Melt_Radio_Edit/</id><title>Boxed In - Melt (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:27:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:27:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Boxed_In/Melt_Radio_Edit/" title="Boxed In - Melt (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I still believe in alchemy <br>Light before the darkness <br>melt away the shade <br>I still believe in you and me <br>But iron won't turn gold lately <br>I could reach the border <br>climb up to the top <br>Pick you through a million faces <br>Why you always run from <br>why you never stop <br>Never in the same two places <br>You lost touch <br>You've been taken <br>gone today <br>Hold your gaze <br>as I watch you fade away <br>Don't know what you want <br>from me anymore <br>Two can play these games and turn <br>at the door <br>I could reach the border <br>climb up to the top <br>Pick you through a million faces <br>Why you always run from <br>why you never stop <br>Never in the same two places <br>You lost touch <br>You've been taken <br>gone today <br>Hold your gaze <br>as I watch you fade away <br>You lost touch <br>You've been taken <br>gone today <br>Hold your gaze <br>as I watch you fade away <br>Hold your gaze <br>in the distance melt away <br>Hold your gaze <br>in the distance melt away <br>Hold your gaze <br>in the distance melt away <br>Hold your gaze <br>in the distance melt away <br>Hold your gaze <br>in the distance melt away <br>Hold your gaze <br>in the distance melt away <br>]]></content><category term="Boxed In" label="Boxed In"/><category term="Melt (Radio Edit)" label="Melt (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/법천/상처/</id><title>법천 - 상처 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:27:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:27:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B2%95%EC%B2%9C/%EC%83%81%EC%B2%98/" title="법천 - 상처 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>무슨 사연 많아서 그렇게 아파하나요 <br>무슨 미련 많아서 그렇게 울고있나요 <br>세상을 살면서 사랑 몇번 이별 몇번 <br>안해본 사람 있나요 <br>울지마요 내사랑 슬퍼말아요 <br>너의 눈물 아픈상처 내가 가져 갈게요 <br>사랑해 내사랑으로 당신눈물 닦아줄게요 <br><br>2절 <br>세상을 살면서 사랑 몇번 이별 몇번 <br>안해본 사람 있나요 <br>울지마요 내사랑 슬퍼 말아요 <br>너의 눈물 아픈상처 내가 가져갈게요 <br>사랑해 내사랑으로 당신눈물 닦아줄게요 <br>사랑해 내사랑으로 당신눈물 닦아줄게요]]></content><category term="법천" label="법천"/><category term="상처" label="상처"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/도민/Later_Feat_김환수__이유진/</id><title>도민 - Later (Feat. 김환수 &amp; 이유진) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:28:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:28:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%84%EB%AF%BC/Later_Feat_%EA%B9%80%ED%99%98%EC%88%98__%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A0%EC%A7%84/" title="도민 - Later (Feat. 김환수 &amp; 이유진) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대 잘 지내나요 <br>아픈 곳은 없는지 <br>하루에도 몇 번 <br>생각이 나네요 <br>그땐 안 했던 <br>그대 걱정이 <br>함께 듣던 음악도 <br>함께 걷던 거리도 <br>이제는 모든 게 <br>추억이 돼버린 우리 <br>그땐 참 행복했는데 <br>시간이 지나야 <br>그때야 알게 되는 <br>것들이 너무 많죠 <br>미안하단 이 짧은 <br>고백을 하기가 <br>왜이리 힘든 건지 <br>그대가 있었기에 <br>많은 걸 깨달았고 <br>한 없이 퍼주는 <br>사랑도 배웠고 <br>이젠 그대를 <br>볼 순 없지만 <br>내 손 꽉 잡아주고 <br>내가 팔짱낄때면 <br>나만을 바라보던 <br>그 예쁜 눈빛도 <br>이젠 누군갈 <br>바라보겠죠 <br>내가 아는 나도 <br>모를 때가 많은데 <br>그래서 더 두려웠던 <br>시간도 많았죠 <br>나도 나를 사랑할 수 <br>없었는데도 어떻게 <br>그렇게 나를 <br>사랑해 줬나요 <br>그대가 알려준 <br>모든걸 줬던 그 사랑 <br>나로썬 감당할 수 <br>없었던 그 사랑이 <br>이제는 내 맘에 추억이 <br>돼버린 지금 <br>많은걸 깨닫게 해준 <br>나의 그대여 <br>서로가 있었기에 <br>많은 걸 깨달았고 <br>한없이 퍼주는 <br>사랑도 배웠고 <br>이젠 다른 사랑이지만 <br>내 손 꽉 잡아주고 <br>내가 팔짱낄때면 <br>나만을 바라보던 <br>그 예쁜 눈빛도 <br>이젠 누군갈 바라보겠죠 <br>누군갈 바라보겠죠 <br>]]></content><category term="도민" label="도민"/><category term="Later (Feat. 김환수 &amp; 이유진)" label="Later (Feat. 김환수 &amp; 이유진)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/글루미시즌/거짓말_Part2/</id><title>글루미시즌 - 거짓말 Part.2 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:29:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:29:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%80%EB%A3%A8%EB%AF%B8%EC%8B%9C%EC%A6%8C/%EA%B1%B0%EC%A7%93%EB%A7%90_Part2/" title="글루미시즌 - 거짓말 Part.2 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘 하루도 그대 생각으로 <br>아침에 눈을 뜨죠 <br>달라진 게 없는 나인데 <br>왜 이렇게 슬픈 거죠 <br>오늘 하루도 거닐어요 <br>그대와 함께 걷던 길 <br>모든 게 다 그대로인데 <br>왜 우리만 변한 거죠 <br>보고 싶어요 보고 싶어요 <br>이렇게 하루가 지나가죠 <br>보고 싶어요 보고 싶어요 <br>그렇게 잊혀져 가네요 <br>영원하자던 네 말 거짓말 인가요 <br>함께하자던 그 말 거짓말 인가요 <br>보고 싶어요 보고 싶어요 <br>이렇게 하루가 지나가죠 <br>보고 싶어요 보고 싶어요 <br>그렇게 잊혀져 가네요 <br>아직도 믿기질 않아 <br>아직도 난 널 사랑해 <br>아직도 내 눈물만 주르륵 <br>가슴이 미어져 아파 <br>oh oh oh oh <br>널 보고 싶어요 널 보고 싶어요 <br>이렇게 널 <br>]]></content><category term="글루미시즌" label="글루미시즌"/><category term="거짓말 Part.2" label="거짓말 Part.2"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/글루미시즌/Intro/</id><title>글루미시즌 - Intro - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:29:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:29:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B8%80%EB%A3%A8%EB%AF%B8%EC%8B%9C%EC%A6%8C/Intro/" title="글루미시즌 - Intro - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떠나지말아요 oh <br>그러지말아요 oh <br>woo woo <br>woo woo <br>oh oh oh oh <br>]]></content><category term="글루미시즌" label="글루미시즌"/><category term="Intro" label="Intro"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이자은/사랑한다_말하세요_With_소풍/</id><title>이자은 - 사랑한다 말하세요 (With 소풍) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:30:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:30:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%9E%90%EC%9D%80/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%9C%EB%8B%A4_%EB%A7%90%ED%95%98%EC%84%B8%EC%9A%94_With_%EC%86%8C%ED%92%8D/" title="이자은 - 사랑한다 말하세요 (With 소풍) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[당신은 웃는 모습이 <br>참 아름다워요 <br>그렇게 항상 밝게 웃어주세요 <br>귀여운 보조개도 참 멋져요 <br>누구라도 탐내지 <br>않을 수가 없을 거예요 <br>사랑을 부르는 <br>입술을 가졌어요 <br>내게 말해주세요 조용히 <br>그냥 사랑한다 말하세요 <br>나도 당신을 사랑해요 <br>그냥 사랑한다 말할게요 <br>약속은 슬픈 거니까요 <br>나는 그런 당신께 <br>귀 기울일게요 <br>다만 사랑을 약속하진 말아요 <br>약속이란 언젠가 <br>깨어질지 모르니 <br>그냥 사랑한다 말하세요 <br>나도 당신을 사랑해요 <br>그냥 사랑한다 말할게요 <br>약속은 슬픈 거니까요 <br>그냥 사랑한다 말하세요 <br>나도 당신을 사랑해요 <br>그냥 사랑한다 말할게요 <br>약속은 슬픈 거니까요 <br>]]></content><category term="이자은" label="이자은"/><category term="사랑한다 말하세요 (With 소풍)" label="사랑한다 말하세요 (With 소풍)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Too_Late/</id><title>Molotov Jukebox - Too Late - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:31:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:31:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Too_Late/" title="Molotov Jukebox - Too Late - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A bullet dogged <br>Steel my resolve <br>I don't bite my words <br><br>Yes you heard <br>A weight I miss <br>A conclusion I've kissed <br>Goodbye <br>There's more to say <br>He has more to say <br>But no where near far enough <br>With a full stomach <br>And a heavy heart <br>The tales you told were tall <br>And the talk you sold was cheap <br>There it is now I see <br>You short-changed me <br>It's too late and <br>The Sun is coming up again <br>It's too late and <br>The magic's wearing thin <br>Leaving <br>Going, going, gone <br>It's too late, you know it's too late <br>We've stayed the same <br>But positions change <br>My good intentions stopped <br>By sudden rain <br>Of all the things <br>That I could have done <br>I'm struggling to think of one <br>I need a remedy <br>A remedy <br>For you not listening <br>And blaming me <br>Snatching defeat <br>From the jaws of victory <br>With this full house <br>And heavy eyes <br>The tales you told were tall <br>And the talk you sold was cheap <br>There it is now I see <br>You short-changed me <br>It's too late and <br>The Sun is coming up again <br>It's too late and <br>The magic's wearing thin <br>Leaving <br>Going, going, gone <br>It's too late, you know it's too late <br>It's too late and <br>The Sun is coming up again <br>It's too late and <br>The magic's wearing thin <br>Leaving <br>Going, going, gone <br>It's too late, you know it's <br>You had me putting water in the wine <br>Now I top myself up <br>Jump overboard <br>You'll fly <br>You know it's too late <br>It's too late, baby it's too late <br>You know it's too late <br>You know it's too late]]></content><category term="Molotov Jukebox" label="Molotov Jukebox"/><category term="Too Late" label="Too Late"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Outside_In/</id><title>Molotov Jukebox - Outside In - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:31:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:31:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Outside_In/" title="Molotov Jukebox - Outside In - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Bleeding from the outside in <br>I should never have let that sn <br>so close to my heart <br>way I was back then <br>I loved to destroy my favourite things <br><br>So I closed my doors <br>Inside of me <br>let no one in <br>swallowed the key <br><br>So I closed my eyes <br>Held my breath <br>counted to ten <br>and then I counted again <br><br>cause I wanted to pretend <br>love would never come again <br>but you broke in <br>I was destined to descend <br>was a fall without an end <br>but you broke in <br><br>You broke in <br><br>Bleeding from the inside out <br>into you <br>into the chambers of your heart <br>you take off my heels <br>and make me wait <br>but that's okay <br><br>and I closed my eyes <br>Held my breath <br>counted to ten <br>and then I counted again <br><br>cause I wanted to pretend <br>love would never come again <br>but you broke in <br>I was destined to descend <br>was a fall without an end <br>but you broke in <br><br>what made you pick this broken house <br>with the numbers upside down <br>and pain flowers on the wall <br>flowers, I'd never seen before <br><br>cause I wanted to pretend <br>love would never come again <br>but you broke in <br>I was destined to descend <br>was a fall without an end <br>but you broke in <br>cause I wanted to pretend <br>love would never come again <br>but you broke in <br>I was destined to descend <br>was a fall without an end <br>but you broke in <br><br>You broke in <br>oh you broke <br>you broke in <br>baby how did you get in? <br><br>Baby how did you get in? <br>how did you get in? <br>baby, how did you get in? <br>how did you get in]]></content><category term="Molotov Jukebox" label="Molotov Jukebox"/><category term="Outside In" label="Outside In"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Leave_Your_Light_On/</id><title>Molotov Jukebox - Leave Your Light On - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:31:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:31:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Leave_Your_Light_On/" title="Molotov Jukebox - Leave Your Light On - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Reached the limits of my lies <br>with you encouraging me <br>to push it all aside <br><br><br>for just one night <br>that I didn't want to <br>that I didn't want to end. <br>that I didn't want to <br>that I didn't want to end. <br>The best bad idea I did <br>that's kiss <br>and tell me <br>how did you know my lips <br>so well so quickly. <br>And I didn't want you <br>didn't want you to stop. <br>And I didn't want you <br>didn't want you to stop. <br>The next morning I'm still hooked <br>reading into your replies <br>selling stories to myself <br>repressing fires at the same time. <br>And I want to leave your <br>want to leave your light on. <br>And I want to leave your <br>want to leave your light on. <br>Like a ghost between my sheets <br>make you real in my bed <br>making empty threats of love <br>making my no sound like a yes. <br>And I want to leave your <br>want to leave your light on. <br>And I want to leave my <br>want to leave my light on. <br>I'm hoping for <br>a little bit more <br>a little bit more <br>you make me blush <br>a little to much and everyone can see. <br>And I didn't want you <br>didn't want you to stop. <br>And I didn't want you <br>didn't want you to stop. <br>And I want to leave your <br>want to leave your light on. <br>And I want to leave your <br>want to leave your light on. <br>(Want to leave your light on... <br>I want to leave your light on... <br>Want to leave your light on...) <br>I'm hoping for <br>a little bit more <br>a little bit more <br>you make me blush <br>a little to much, they can see. <br>I'm hoping for <br>a little bit more <br>a little bit more <br>you make me blush <br>a little to much and everyone can see]]></content><category term="Molotov Jukebox" label="Molotov Jukebox"/><category term="Leave Your Light On" label="Leave Your Light On"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Trail_Of_Crumbs/</id><title>Molotov Jukebox - Trail Of Crumbs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:31:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:31:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Trail_Of_Crumbs/" title="Molotov Jukebox - Trail Of Crumbs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I remember how to miss you <br>I even love your bones <br>The way you wear them really aiuta you <br>Bring them back home <br>Fried this love at both ends <br>Only the with lies help me sleep <br>Appease this rain <br>Oh cover Oh cover <br>The liar in me, begs the lover in you <br>Silhouettes stand out <br>Showing the shapes that were made in a past <br>They cast a shade <br>Oh daylight Oh daylight <br>The darkness in me, paints the lover you <br>For sanctuary <br>For dishonesty <br>Even just for me, open up wide <br>Let a voice cry out <br>Come back, come back <br>Follow-up the trail of crumbs <br>Turn back, turn back <br>Poor creature, you're hurt <br>You're here, you're home <br>Feel the warmth on your bones <br>All grown up at loose ends <br>These hands are tired but pretty pretence <br>Still wear the scars <br>Forever forever <br>The splinters in me, could build the lover in you <br>A sanctuary <br>A dishonesty <br>Even just for me, open up wide <br>Let a voice cry out <br>Come back, come back <br>Follow-up the trail of crumbs <br>Turn back, turn back <br>Poor creature, you're hurt <br>You're here, you're home <br>Feel the warmth on your bones <br>Come back, come back <br>Follow-up the trail of crumbs <br>Don't stop until <br>You're back where you came from <br>You're here, you're home <br>Feel the warmth on your bones <br>The words I tried <br>Held an olive branch inside <br>Hold our love above you pride <br>Open up wide let a voice cry out <br>Come back, come back <br>Follow-up the trail of crumbs <br>Turn back, turn back <br>Poor creature, you're hurt <br>You're here, you're home <br>Feel the warmth on your bones <br>Come back, come back <br>Follow-up the trail of crumbs <br>Don't stop until <br>You're back where you came from <br>You're here, you're home <br>Feel the warmth on your bones <br>I remember how to miss you <br>I even love your bones <br>The way you wear them really suits you <br>Bring them back home]]></content><category term="Molotov Jukebox" label="Molotov Jukebox"/><category term="Trail Of Crumbs" label="Trail Of Crumbs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/If_I_Knew/</id><title>Molotov Jukebox - If I Knew - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:31:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:31:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/If_I_Knew/" title="Molotov Jukebox - If I Knew - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Even fools get old <br>lend your youth for the day <br>she said, just one taste <br><br><br>because I threw mine away <br>like we all do <br><br>Even Love gets old <br>lend me your shoes for the day <br>not sit still for a second <br>and chase all the ones that got away <br><br>You know you want to <br>put that shyness to bed <br><br>If I, if I knew back then]]></content><category term="Molotov Jukebox" label="Molotov Jukebox"/><category term="If I Knew" label="If I Knew"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/I_Cry/</id><title>Molotov Jukebox - I Cry - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:31:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:31:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/I_Cry/" title="Molotov Jukebox - I Cry - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stabbing in the dark blind <br>Sorry if I hurt you <br>I didn't mean to <br><br>You knew, when you got into me <br>I'm tricky with fidelity <br>I didn't mean to <br>Yes I told you that I loved you <br>told you you're the only one <br>but distractions come in tall dark strangers <br>I'm just a woman <br>yes I told you that I loved you <br>told you the only one <br>but distractions come in tall dark strangers <br>I'm just a woman <br>Nothing to say to you <br>I cry <br>Nothing to say to you <br>I cry <br>Como la tramontana <br>No puedes pararlo <br>Es Lo que hay <br>Locura de mi corazon <br>Como la tramontana <br>No puedes pararlo <br>Es Lo que hay <br>Locura de mi corazon <br>Ay, locura de mi corazon <br>Ay, locura de mi corazon <br>This desire bites the loving hand <br>This desire <br>This desire bites the loving hand <br>This desire <br>Como la tramontana <br>Tienes que seguirlo <br>Es Lo que hay <br>Adios a mi corazon <br>Como la tramontana <br>Tienes que seguirlo <br>Es Lo que hay <br>Adios a mi corazon <br>Ay, locura de mi corazon <br>Ay, locura de mi corazon <br>This desire bites the loving hand <br>This desire <br>This desire bites the loving hand <br>This desire <br>This desire bites the loving hand <br>This desire <br>This desire bites the loving hand <br>This desire <br>Ay, locura de mi corazon <br>Ay, locura de mi corazon <br>Ay, locura de mi corazon <br>Ay, locura de mi corazon]]></content><category term="Molotov Jukebox" label="Molotov Jukebox"/><category term="I Cry" label="I Cry"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Halfway_There/</id><title>Molotov Jukebox - Halfway There - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:31:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:31:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Halfway_There/" title="Molotov Jukebox - Halfway There - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was the child of a light ice keeper (?) <br>I've been drifting for days <br>Preacher told me of a promise land <br><br><br>Just beyond the heat and the haze <br>Sold my compass for a profit <br>I'll sell my wet shoes when I hit land <br><br>So I look straight up <br>At the sky and rain <br>But nothing comes down except <br>Water on a rainy day <br>(Unknown) <br>But will the time to stay <br>I'd rather hope we'll never move away (?) <br><br>Halfway there <br>Won't turn around <br>I'm halfway there, I can hear the sound <br>Of the music playing <br><br>Halfway there <br>Won't turn around <br>I'm halfway there, I can hear the sound <br>Of the music playing <br><br>So distracted by the summer sunrise <br>In the fading light <br>I hear the voice of the one I love <br>In the dark of the night <br>Told myself not to rock the boat <br>Hold still and steady my hand <br><br>So I place it there <br>On my heart and pray <br>I'll be meeting up with you again someday <br>Like the old people say <br>We come from dust and we'll be ashes one day <br><br>Halfway there <br>Won't turn around <br>I'm halfway there, I can hear the sound <br>Of the music playing <br><br>Halfway there <br>Won't turn around <br>I'm halfway there, I can hear the sound <br>Of the music playing <br><br>So I follow blind <br>Lost for forty days <br>Cast this map aside and find my own way <br>Like a bird that's rolling out the gate (?) <br>Headed straight to where the other songbirds play <br><br>Halfway there <br>Won't turn around <br>I'm halfway there, I can hear the sound <br>Of the music playing <br><br>Halfway there <br>Won't turn around <br>I'm halfway there, I can hear the sound <br>Of the music playing]]></content><category term="Molotov Jukebox" label="Molotov Jukebox"/><category term="Halfway There" label="Halfway There"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Dancing_With_The_Dead/</id><title>Molotov Jukebox - Dancing With The Dead - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:31:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:31:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Dancing_With_The_Dead/" title="Molotov Jukebox - Dancing With The Dead - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hot one <br>The ceiling sweats like its raining <br>As the steam trickles and ain't clothes the lights in halos <br><br><br>The crowd goes <br>Wild, for every song <br>As if they're living this night for the last time <br><br>Dancing, I'm dancing with the dead <br>The moon is the mirror ball <br>Dancing, I'm dancing with the dead <br>I come alive in the dancehall <br><br>Top hat <br>A hungry smile he's an island in the crowd <br>I wash up by his side <br>A rum kiss on each cheek <br>Makes me wild for everyone <br>As if I'm living this night for the last time <br><br>Dancing, I'm dancing with the dead <br>The moon is the mirror ball <br>Dancing, I'm dancing with the dead <br>I come alive in the dancehall <br><br>Hold on <br>That's ray on the keys with Nina <br>The curtain keeps going up <br>Free drinks on lady Katrina <br>We all go <br>Wild for every song <br>As if we are living this night for the last time <br><br>Dancing, I'm dancing with the dead <br>The moon is the mirror ball <br>Dancing, I'm dancing with the dead <br>I come alive in the dancehall <br>Dancing, I'm dancing with the dead <br>The moon is the mirror ball <br>Dancing, I'm dancing with the dead <br>I come alive in the dancehall]]></content><category term="Molotov Jukebox" label="Molotov Jukebox"/><category term="Dancing With The Dead" label="Dancing With The Dead"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Just_The_Thrill/</id><title>Molotov Jukebox - Just The Thrill - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:31:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:31:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Just_The_Thrill/" title="Molotov Jukebox - Just The Thrill - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Want to take a chance on you <br>but I'll loose, but i'll loose, but I'll loose <br>so hard trying to stop <br><br>throwing myself at you <br>never thought of you that way <br>till i felt the way you move <br>Didn't want to kiss you <br>but I do, but I do, but I do <br><br>trouble brewing <br>but I wont give way <br>oh, no matter what my friends say <br><br>Is it just a thrill of something new <br>because i cant have you <br>is it just a thrill of something new <br>because I can't have you <br><br>It went from nothing to this <br>so quick, so quick, so quick <br>a sudden closeness to you <br>made me flick like a light switch <br>betraying him at midnight <br>with thought of you at my fingertips <br>wish i'd drown in these tears <br>but they touch the smile on my lips <br><br>trouble brewing <br>but I wont give way <br>oh, no matter what my friends say <br><br>Is it just a thrill of something new <br>because i cant have you <br>is it just a thrill of something new <br>because I can't have you <br>Is it just a thrill of something new <br>because i cant have you <br>is it just a thrill of something new <br>because I can't have you <br><br>Am I seeing things <br>or are you teasing me? <br>prey on my weakness <br>oh please, oh please, oh please <br>if you begin to undress me <br>I would not have the strength to leave <br>so you need to take the lead <br><br>trouble brewing <br>but I wont give way <br>trouble has a man's name <br><br>Is it just a thrill of something new <br>because i cant have you <br>is it just a thrill of something new <br>because I can't have you <br>Is it just a thrill of something new <br>because i cant have you <br>is it just a thrill of something new <br>because I can't have you <br><br>I've been that girl before <br>a fool, a fool <br>I've thrown it all away <br>I've been that girl before <br>a fool, a fool <br>I've thrown it all away]]></content><category term="Molotov Jukebox" label="Molotov Jukebox"/><category term="Just The Thrill" label="Just The Thrill"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Pineapple_Girl/</id><title>Molotov Jukebox - Pineapple Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:31:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:31:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Molotov_Jukebox/Pineapple_Girl/" title="Molotov Jukebox - Pineapple Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You do what you like hun <br>cos your smile is sunny side up <br>yes you're late with the mixers and the fun <br><br><br>pour that pinapple juice in your cup <br><br>we have chaos in the kitchen hun <br>lovers and hats in the hall <br>a bedroom dance is a bedroom dance <br>stay fresh and sharp through it all <br><br>Lockdown at the Wilson's house <br>uh oh uh oh <br>I think I'm going under <br>Lockdown at the Wilson's house <br>Give me give me that pinapple girl's number <br><br>Finally the night has begun <br>the clock is drunk but the DJ is sober <br>I grab a pew to talk to you <br>but the music is too loud to talk over <br><br>So we take off our heels, put down the rum <br>cos the nights not getting younger <br>She's captain straight-through number one <br>yes this pinapple girl is a wonder <br><br>Lockdown at the Wilson's house <br>uh oh uh oh <br>I think I'm going under <br>Lockdown at the Wilson's house <br>Give me give me that pinapple girl's number <br><br>The neighbours all came and went <br>The Wilsons retired to bed <br>yes it's late for this mischief, I've got to run <br>Lets finish this next time instead <br>As I left I noticed that <br>Your number's still not in my phone <br>Yes it's late or far to early <br>Oh Wilsons please dont let her go <br><br>Lockdown at the Wilson's house <br>uh oh uh oh <br>I think I'm going under <br>Lockdown at the Wilson's house <br>Give me give me that pinapple girl's number <br><br>Give me give me <br>that pinapple girl's number <br>Give me give me <br>that pinapple girl's number]]></content><category term="Molotov Jukebox" label="Molotov Jukebox"/><category term="Pineapple Girl" label="Pineapple Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Malin/Since_Youre_In_Love/</id><title>Jesse Malin - Since You`re In Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:32:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:32:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Malin/Since_Youre_In_Love/" title="Jesse Malin - Since You`re In Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the rain comes down <br>In this northern town <br>It was a banner year <br>In the world of fear <br>I though I'd drop you a line <br><br>When you comb your hair <br>And you're unaware <br>And your friends all say that you're looking great <br>Those black and white movies apply <br><br>Since you're in love <br>I'm still sad over you <br><br>Gonna sleep away <br>All my sunny days <br>And in another year well I won't be here <br>Hoping that you'll change your mind <br>Since you're in love <br>I'm still sad over you]]></content><category term="Jesse Malin" label="Jesse Malin"/><category term="Since You`re In Love" label="Since You`re In Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Malin/Arrested/</id><title>Jesse Malin - Arrested - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:32:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:32:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Malin/Arrested/" title="Jesse Malin - Arrested - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Calls him daddy, calls him man <br>Another girl that they call Britney <br>Johnny sits and mans the phones <br>From the corner, he'll come get you <br><br>She wakes in the cold gray dawn <br>Football games they make me yawn <br>Cellophane and stomach aches <br>Pillow talk and perfume breaks <br><br>A married man with an estate <br>A hairdresser that swears he's straight <br>Her alimony is once a month <br>She beats the kid, he plays the drums <br>And oh, oh, oh, life goes by <br><br>With your Mardi Gras high <br>And your tenderloin low <br>Second hand blues and money to blow <br>When you get tired and arrested <br>There's something you should know <br>At least he's going home <br><br>The undercover makes the bust <br>But not before he gets a touch <br>Good ones copy, great ones steal <br>The rest of us we almost feel <br>And oh, oh, oh, life goes by <br><br>With your Mardi Gras high <br>And your tenderloin low <br>Second hand blues and money to blow <br>When you get tired and arrested <br>There's somewhere you can go <br>Between the blue and gold <br><br>He's gonna get a pension <br>Eleven years go to <br>The world's oldest profession <br>Ain't never gonna fold <br>With fortunes being told <br><br>With your Mardi Gras high <br>And your tenderloin low <br>Second hand blues and money to blow <br>When you get tired and arrested <br>There's something you should know <br>You're always in my soul]]></content><category term="Jesse Malin" label="Jesse Malin"/><category term="Arrested" label="Arrested"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Malin/Mona_Lisa/</id><title>Jesse Malin - Mona Lisa - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:32:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:32:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Jesse_Malin/Mona_Lisa/" title="Jesse Malin - Mona Lisa - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Steven's selling Marijuana <br>Uptown to the primadonnas <br>Medicate the counterculture <br>9 11 baby boom <br><br>Paulie's waiting to retire <br>Smoking like a forest fire <br>Putting on the panties and the lipstick <br>In his mother's room <br>Nothing to do, nothing to lose <br><br>And if you work your life away <br>Well send you flowers every day <br>And you make your departure baby <br>And get high, high <br><br>Hanging with the local talent <br>Drinking like you're Shane McGowan <br>Going through your garbage <br>Try to turn into gold <br>Down on the dole, selling your soul <br><br>And if you work your life away <br>Theyll keep your picture in a frame <br>And you make your departure baby <br>When you die, high <br><br>Bobbie joined the military <br>Jenny went and lost her cherry <br>Hanging at the commissary <br>Wants to see the Mona Lisa <br>If they ever do release her <br>I don't want to talk too soon <br><br>There's nothing to lose <br>Swimming in booze, selling your shoes <br>Nothing to lose, nothing to lose, nothing to lose]]></content><category term="Jesse Malin" label="Jesse Malin"/><category term="Mona Lisa" label="Mona Lisa"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/권PD/넌_모르는척해_Feat_김누리_월리_Of_빅타임/</id><title>권PD - 넌 모르는척해 (Feat. 김누리, 월리 Of 빅타임) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:34:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:34:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B6%8CPD/%EB%84%8C_%EB%AA%A8%EB%A5%B4%EB%8A%94%EC%B2%99%ED%95%B4_Feat_%EA%B9%80%EB%88%84%EB%A6%AC_%EC%9B%94%EB%A6%AC_Of_%EB%B9%85%ED%83%80%EC%9E%84/" title="권PD - 넌 모르는척해 (Feat. 김누리, 월리 Of 빅타임) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 모르는 척 해 <br>제발 그런 눈으로 <br>쳐다보지마 <br>니가 누굴만나든 <br>전혀 관심조차 <br>두지를 않아 <br>오 난 아무렇지도 않아 <br>나를 보지마 나 보지마 <br>날 쳐다보지마 아아 <br>halo halo 눈이 마주쳐도 <br>모른척 해 걸어가 저기 <br>니 남자에게가 어차피 <br>너와 나 사이 <br>끝나버린 사이 <br>아무일도 아닌듯 <br>웃어 딴 사람들이 <br>봐도 모르게 <br>자꾸 미끌미끌 들어와 <br>못이긴 척 <br>먼저 살금살금 다가와 <br>모르는 척 <br>여러번 흔들리고 <br>이러다가 망설이고 <br>우리 사이 왔다갔다 <br>헷갈려 더 불안하고 <br>반쯤 뜬거 같아 너와 나 <br>get closer <br>살좀 찐거 같아 돌아 와 <br>get ready <br>하루에도 몇번씩 <br>오락가락 하는 나보고 <br>도대체 어떻게하라고 이젠 또 <br>우리 둘이 어쩌지 <br>뭣이 중한디 <br>okey dokey 할 순 없어 <br>소꿉 친구 같이 <br>사람들의 관심 밖인 <br>miss casting 맞지 <br>우리에게 관심없지 <br>dispatch 아니고 death match <br>너 아님 나 둘 중 하나가 <br>더 좋아해야 끝나버리는 <br>이상한 game no pain no gain <br>I don't know your fame <br>and name <br>그냥 똑같아 <br>우리 둘은 단지 <br>same same <br>사랑했었지 <br>그땐 사랑했었지 <br>이젠 남이 된 우리사이 <br>모르는척 지나가 <br>자꾸자꾸 불안해지는 <br>내 맘 어떡해 <br>Everybody wanna good bye <br>Everybody wanna good bye <br>Everybody wanna good bye <br>Everybody wanna good bye <br>]]></content><category term="권PD" label="권PD"/><category term="넌 모르는척해 (Feat. 김누리, 월리 Of 빅타임)" label="넌 모르는척해 (Feat. 김누리, 월리 Of 빅타임)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/데니스프로젝트/Black_List_Feat_노훈/</id><title>데니스프로젝트 - Black List (Feat. 노훈) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:34:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:34:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8D%B0%EB%8B%88%EC%8A%A4%ED%94%84%EB%A1%9C%EC%A0%9D%ED%8A%B8/Black_List_Feat_%EB%85%B8%ED%9B%88/" title="데니스프로젝트 - Black List (Feat. 노훈) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Black List What <br>Clap Clap Clap Clap Clap Clap Clap <br>Clap Clap Clap Clap Clap Clap <br>A Yo <br>관심이 필요해 <br>I wanna do ay ay <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 네가 필요해 <br>all I wanna do ay ay I want it <br>관심이 필요해 <br>I wanna do ay ay <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 네가 필요해 <br>all I wanna do Do do I want it <br>난 너만의 <br>BLACK LIST <br>일지도 몰라 <br>근데 그보다 슬픈 건 <br>넌 나를 잘 몰라 <br>보기보다 순진 하지 <br>않은 널 알지만 <br>누구 보다 착한 너여도 <br>날 만나줄린 없잖아 <br>내 사랑은 <br>상상 속에서만 이뤄지고 <br>난 스토커는 아니지만 <br>숨어서 널 보게 돼 <br>고백을 멋지게 해야지 <br>근데 좀 무서워 <br>전혀 멋있어 보이지 않아 <br>내가 좀 우스워 <br>나와는 다른 삶을 <br>살아가는 너의 세상 <br>네 옆에 있는 남자들 <br>얼마나 보여줄까 <br>돈 멋진 차 선물로 <br>가방을 주거나 <br>맛있는 음식을 먹으며 <br>웃음을 주거나 <br>난 아냐 <br>사치 있는 너의 사랑 <br>근데 밤이면 달처럼 <br>니가 항상 떠올라 <br>뭘 몰라 그 녀석들은 <br>너를 사랑하지 않아 <br>너를 사랑하는 사람 <br>바로 나뿐이잖아 <br>관심이 필요해 <br>I wanna do ay ay <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 네가 필요해 <br>all I wanna do ay ay I want it <br>관심이 필요해 <br>I wanna do ay ay <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 네가 필요해 <br>all I wanna do Do do I want it <br>관심이 필요해 <br>I wanna do ay ay <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 네가 필요해 <br>all I wanna do ay ay I want it <br>관심이 필요해 <br>I wanna do ay ay <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 네가 필요해 <br>all I wanna do Do do I want it <br>널 보려고 많이 찾아온 <br>집 앞의 남자들 <br>Bad girl is you <br>All I wanna do <br>근데 내게 전혀 없거든 <br>그런 기회는 <br>뭐 생각해 볼 수 있을 거야 <br>다음 생에는 <br>그래도 아직도 <br>내 눈앞에 아른거려 <br>넌 뭘 입어도 그냥 아름다워 <br>내 전부를 줄게 <br>빈털털이 돼도 ok <br>뭐 어때 너의 기쁨이 <br>내 기쁨이야 all day <br>낮이건 밤이건 <br>상관없이 ring my bell <br>네가 어디에 있다고 해도 <br>난 달려갈게 <br>그러니 이제 치워줄래 <br>너의 black list <br>난 되고 싶어 <br>너만의 wish list <br>엇 비슷한 놈들이 <br>주위에 득실거려도 <br>상관없어 그 다음에 나를 불러도 <br>너의 향기가 코 끝에 묻어있어 <br>조금이라도 <br>너의 옷깃에 스치고만 싶어 <br>관심이 필요해 <br>I wanna do ay ay <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 네가 필요해 <br>all I wanna do ay ay I want it <br>관심이 필요해 <br>I wanna do ay ay <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 네가 필요해 <br>all I wanna do Do do I want it <br>관심이 필요해 <br>I wanna do ay ay <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 네가 필요해 <br>all I wanna do ay ay I want it <br>관심이 필요해 <br>I wanna do ay ay <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 네가 필요해 <br>all I wanna do Do do I want it <br>]]></content><category term="데니스프로젝트" label="데니스프로젝트"/><category term="Black List (Feat. 노훈)" label="Black List (Feat. 노훈)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이윤상/우리엄마/</id><title>이윤상 - 우리엄마 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:35:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:35:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%9C%A4%EC%83%81/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC%EC%97%84%EB%A7%88/" title="이윤상 - 우리엄마 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1절 <br>검은 머리 백발 되신 <br>늙으신 우리 엄마 <br>잔주름에 쌓인 모습 <br>너무나도 애처로워 <br>자나 깨나 자식 걱정 보낸 한평생 <br>깊고 큰 그 은혜를 왜 모르니까 <br>우리엄마 우리엄마 <br>만수무강하옵소서 <br>2절 <br>섬섬옥수 곱던 손은 <br>논밭처럼 갈라지고 <br>백옥 같던 그 살결엔 <br>검버섯이 피었구나 <br>지팡이 의지하신 야윈 그 모습 <br>곁에만 계시어도 힘이 됩니다 <br>우리엄마 우리엄마 <br>만수무강하옵소서 <br>후렴: <br>우리엄마 우리엄마 <br>만수무강하옵소서]]></content><category term="이윤상" label="이윤상"/><category term="우리엄마" label="우리엄마"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Knickers/Darling/</id><title>Knickers - Darling - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:36:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:36:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Knickers/Darling/" title="Knickers - Darling - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Darling, I know you're thinking <br>Yes, no, have I been drinking <br>I get off on your sweet kisses darling <br><br>Darling, when you can't see me <br>I get sea sick oh baby <br>Nothing cures me like you do, oh darling <br><br>Oh what can I do <br>Cos I'm in heaven every time I'm with you <br>Which means that every other time I'm in Hell <br>With other people just like Jean Paul Satre said, he said so <br><br>Darling, I know I'm slurring <br>My words, but still I'm yearning <br>For your touch and one quick cwtch, oh darling <br><br>Believe what I'm fed <br>The sacred order of the easily lead <br>Whenever you're away that's when I go wrong <br>You are my Bernie, I'm your Elton John <br><br>Just one more kiss <br>Or just one more little soft flick of your wrist <br>Sorry but you here makes me into a letch <br>Turns all the alphabet to X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X X <br><br>Darling, je sais que tu penses <br>Oui, non, est ce que j'ai bu <br>Tu m'allumes avec tes baisers, darling <br>Tu m'allumes avec tes baisers, darling <br>Tu m'allumes avec tes baisers, darling]]></content><category term="Knickers" label="Knickers"/><category term="Darling" label="Darling"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Knickers/A_Thousand_Ways/</id><title>Knickers - A Thousand Ways - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:36:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:36:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Knickers/A_Thousand_Ways/" title="Knickers - A Thousand Ways - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a thousand ways, to get yourself alone <br>And there's a thousand ways, to live out on your own <br>There's a thousand ways, and many tracks <br>To get yourself from there to back <br>And there's a thousand ways back home <br><br>There's a thousand ways, to travel when you know <br>And there's a thousand ways, to find out when you don't <br>There's a thousand ways, to live your life <br>From yesterday to Sunday night <br>And there's a thousand ways back home <br><br>When I get back home, I'll get unbent <br>I don't understand just why you went <br><br>Another brightened corner, has turned to a flicker <br>Because your light was taken away <br>I'll see you tomorrow but that doesn't help no <br>When all I want is for you to stay <br><br>There's a thousand ways, to just give up and run <br>And there's a thousand ways, to forget all that's gone <br>There's a thousand ways to hate yourself <br>But nothing helps til someone else says <br>There's a thousand ways <br>There's a thousand ways <br>There's a thousand ways back home]]></content><category term="Knickers" label="Knickers"/><category term="A Thousand Ways" label="A Thousand Ways"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Knickers/Are_You_Ready_Girl_/</id><title>Knickers - Are You Ready Girl? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:36:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:36:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Knickers/Are_You_Ready_Girl_/" title="Knickers - Are You Ready Girl? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Well in this new life, that you've found <br>Are you positive Are you sure <br>And are you ready girl Are you ready <br>Though it's fun you talk about <br>It's the night life you explore <br>So are you ready girl Are you ready <br><br>Because you're living with a man <br>Who will find no understanding <br>Do you mind if I break down and cry <br>Will you ever know the way <br>That I feel for you each day <br>So are you ready girl Are you ready <br>Are you ready girl Are you ready <br>Are you ready girl Are you ready <br>Are you ready <br>Are you ready girl <br>Are you ready <br><br>He'll buy you diamonds, he'll buy you rings <br>He'll buy your time, he'll buy your sin <br>But are you ready girl Are you ready <br>He'll keep you laughing for a while <br>Then he'll leave you, with a smile <br>So are you ready girl Are you ready <br><br>Because you're living with a man <br>Who will find no understanding <br>Do you mind if I break down and cry <br>Will you ever know the way <br>That I feel for you each day <br>So are you ready girl Are you ready <br>Are you ready girl Are you ready <br>Are you ready girl Are you ready <br>Are you ready <br>Are you ready girl <br>Are you ready]]></content><category term="Knickers" label="Knickers"/><category term="Are You Ready Girl?" label="Are You Ready Girl?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Knickers/My_Babys_Just_A_Baby_But_I_Love_Him_So/</id><title>Knickers - My Baby`s Just A Baby (But I Love Him So) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:36:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:36:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Knickers/My_Babys_Just_A_Baby_But_I_Love_Him_So/" title="Knickers - My Baby`s Just A Baby (But I Love Him So) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My baby's just a baby My baby's just a baby <br><br>He gets beat up by every <br>Dog gone body on his block <br>He can't tell the time you know <br>He don't know his ticking from his tock <br><br>He's not too clever, he's kind of slow <br>My baby's just a baby But I love him so <br>My baby's just a baby My baby's just a baby <br><br>He don't know the fashions no <br>It looks like he's living in a cave <br>His face is always cut up <br>Cos his daddy didn't teach him how to shave <br><br>What he's on, I just don't know <br>My baby's just a baby But I love him so <br>My baby's just a baby, my baby's just a One two three go <br><br>My friend's they say that I have changed My baby's just a baby <br>My friend's they say that I'm insane My baby's just a baby <br>Who cares <br><br>My baby's just a baby My baby's just a baby <br><br>He gets beat up by every <br>Dog gone body on his block <br>He can't tell the time you know <br>He don't know his ticking from his tock <br><br>He's not too clever, he's kind of slow <br>My baby's just a baby But I love him so <br>My baby's just a baby My baby's just a baby <br><br>My baby's just a baby but I love him so <br>My baby's just a baby but I love him so <br>My baby's just a baby but I love him so]]></content><category term="Knickers" label="Knickers"/><category term="My Baby`s Just A Baby (But I Love Him So)" label="My Baby`s Just A Baby (But I Love Him So)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/La_Monja_Enana/Estoy_Solo/</id><title>La Monja Enana - Estoy Solo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:37:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:37:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/La_Monja_Enana/Estoy_Solo/" title="La Monja Enana - Estoy Solo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Llego tarde a casa, despues de trabajar <br>No hay gente por las calles <br>Hoy se puede pasear <br>Abro mi ventana y contemplo la ciudad <br>No hay luna ni estrellas <br>Solo hay oscuridad <br><br>Marco tu telefono y no obtengo senal <br>No hay nadie al otro lado <br>Nadie con quien pueda hablar <br><br>Y empiezo a pensar, menuda tonteria <br>Que soy la unica persona viva <br>Que todos los demas han muerto o peor <br>Ahora estoy solo, me gusta la situacion <br>Todo es mas sencillo sin gente alrededor bis <br><br>Ya no hay hora punta, ni motivos para correr <br>El primero en todas partes <br>Y jamas pido la vez <br>Nadie me presenta gente a la que conocer <br>He dejado la terapia <br>Supere mi timidez <br><br>Y empiezo a pensar, menuda alegria <br>Que soy la unica persona viva <br>Que todos los demas han muerto o peor <br><br>Ahora estoy solo]]></content><category term="La Monja Enana" label="La Monja Enana"/><category term="Estoy Solo" label="Estoy Solo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/La_Monja_Enana/Me_Enamore_De_Un_Robot/</id><title>La Monja Enana - Me Enamore De Un Robot - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:37:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:37:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/La_Monja_Enana/Me_Enamore_De_Un_Robot/" title="La Monja Enana - Me Enamore De Un Robot - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Te vi de refilon <br>Buscando entre los discos <br>Y entonces decidi que ibas a ser mio <br><br>He logrado atrapar <br>Al novio perfecto <br>Es educado y servicial <br>Un poco frio pero atento <br><br>Algo no consigo entender <br>De su comportamiento <br>Y he empezado a sospechar <br>Que me oculta algun secreto <br><br>Podria asumir que aun vivieras con tus padres <br>Que fueras un psicopata o un obseso por Blade runner <br>Pero esto creo que no, esto es mucho peor <br><br>Me enamore de un robot, ya entiendo sus rarezas <br>Me enamore de un robot, ahora encajan las piezas <br>Me enamore de un robot, me quedare soltera <br>Me enamore de un robot, yo nunca tuve suerte en el amor <br><br>Pero al fin he podido ver <br>Que no es algo tan malo <br>Si no me gusta tu forma de ser <br>Te transformo sin reparos <br><br>Abro tu panel frontal <br>Cambio un par de cables <br>Yo te vuelvo a programar <br>Y ya me gustas mas que antes <br>Y me he dado cuenta de que prefiero el metal <br>Asi me resultas aun mas facil de manipular <br><br>Me enamore de un robot, ya entiendo sus rarezas <br>Me enamore de un robot, ahora encajan las piezas <br>Me enamore de un robot, adios a las peleas <br>Me enamore de un robot, no me pudo pasar nada mejor <br>Me enamore de un robot, ya entiendo sus rarezas <br>Me enamore de un robot, ahora encajan las piezas <br>Me enamore de un robot, adios a las peleas <br>Me enamore de un robot, no me pudo pasar nada mejor]]></content><category term="La Monja Enana" label="La Monja Enana"/><category term="Me Enamore De Un Robot" label="Me Enamore De Un Robot"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/La_Monja_Enana/Los_Dias_De_Perky_Pat/</id><title>La Monja Enana - Los Dias De Perky Pat - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:37:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:37:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/La_Monja_Enana/Los_Dias_De_Perky_Pat/" title="La Monja Enana - Los Dias De Perky Pat - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No se que me hizo aceptar el traslado a Marte <br>Un salario superior, un destino emocionante <br>Era mi gran ocasion de alejarme de la Tierra <br>Quise volver a empezar, hacer borron y cuenta nueva <br>Y es que en la publicidad todo era tan bonito <br>Un paraiso natural, Como he sido tan pardillo <br>El aire no huele igual, el sol brilla sin fuerza <br>Ya no aguanto un dia mas, voy a perder la cabeza <br><br>De noche, en la colonia, ya nada de esto importa <br>Todo se soluciona tomando una dosis de soma <br>Y ya no puedo distinguir lo real de lo irreal <br>Me prefiero evadir, son los dias de Perky Pat bis <br><br>Ya no voy a trabajar, paso el dia encerrado <br>Al lado de Perky Pat, en un mundo mas humano <br>Pero empiezo a sospechar que nada es lo que parece <br>Todo a mi alrededor tiembla y se desvanece <br>Me da igual la hora, ya nada de esto importa <br>Todo se soluciona tomando un poco mas de soma <br><br>Y ya no puedo distinguir lo real de lo irreal <br>Me prefiero evadir, son los dias de Perky Pat bis <br><br>Y ya no quiero distinguir lo real de lo irreal <br>Es mucho mejor asi, viviendo con Perky Pat]]></content><category term="La Monja Enana" label="La Monja Enana"/><category term="Los Dias De Perky Pat" label="Los Dias De Perky Pat"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/La_Monja_Enana/Amor_Cuantico/</id><title>La Monja Enana - Amor Cuantico - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:37:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:37:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/La_Monja_Enana/Amor_Cuantico/" title="La Monja Enana - Amor Cuantico - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Cuanto mas te observo, mas pareces cambiar <br>Y si no te miro, no sabre donde estas <br>Demasiada incertidumbre en nuestra relacion <br>Hago conjeturas sobre tu situacion <br><br>Amor cuantico amor <br>Amor cuantico amor <br>Amor cuantico amor <br>Amor cuantico <br><br>No se que hacer, ni que medidas tomar <br>Cuando voy a verte que me puedo encontrar <br>Estas vivo o estas muerto, o ambas cosas a la vez <br>Al abrir tu puerta, yo lo descubrire <br><br>Amor cuantico amor <br><br>Amor cuantico amor]]></content><category term="La Monja Enana" label="La Monja Enana"/><category term="Amor Cuantico" label="Amor Cuantico"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/La_Monja_Enana/Numeros/</id><title>La Monja Enana - Numeros - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:38:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:38:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/La_Monja_Enana/Numeros/" title="La Monja Enana - Numeros - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[El encargado nos hace una senal <br>Las emisoras comienzan a zumbar <br>Mi trabajo consiste en leer <br>Miles de cifras escritas en papel <br>Desde la embajada transmiten mi voz <br>?Siguen instrucciones, anote por favor? <br>Paso el dia recitando numeros, numeros <br>Paso el dia recitando numeros, numeros <br>Paso el dia recitando numeros, numeros <br>Paso el dia recitando numeros <br>La guerra fria jamas se termino <br>Me han asignado una nueva mision <br>Sin novedades desde hace mas de un mes <br>Paso los dias sin nada que hacer <br>Desde un garaje escucho tu voz <br>?No hay instrucciones, espere por favor? <br>Paso el dia anotando numeros, numeros <br>Paso el dia anotando numeros, numeros <br>Paso el dia anotando numeros, numeros <br>Paso el dia anotando numeros <br>Paso el dia recitando numeros, numeros <br>Paso el dia anotando numeros, numeros <br>Paso el dia recitando numeros, numeros <br>Paso el dia anotando numeros]]></content><category term="La Monja Enana" label="La Monja Enana"/><category term="Numeros" label="Numeros"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/튠업뮤지션/원한다면/</id><title>튠업뮤지션 - 원한다면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%A0%EC%97%85%EB%AE%A4%EC%A7%80%EC%85%98/%EC%9B%90%ED%95%9C%EB%8B%A4%EB%A9%B4/" title="튠업뮤지션 - 원한다면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 청개구리처럼 <br>거꾸로 살아왔지 <br>먹구름처럼 어둡고 <br>찌푸린 얼굴로 <br>나는 변한 게 없다고 <br>열아홉이면 벌써 다 컸다 <br>인생이 끝난 듯 말했지 <br>폭풍 같은 시간에 <br>힘이 들어 울면 <br>나무처럼 넌 자라날 거야 <br>한 번 더 할 수 있게 <br>언제나 너 원한다면 <br>용기를 내 넌 <br>포기하면 안돼 넌 <br>꿈을 꾸면 이뤄질 거야 <br>힘들었던 어제는 날 더 <br>멋지게 만들어 <br>포기하면 안돼 넌 <br>당당하게 이겨나가자 <br>평범했던 나와 <br>오래된 미움도 <br>나를 떠나간다 <br>폭풍 같은 시간에 <br>힘이 들어 울면 <br>나무처럼 넌 자라날 거야 <br>한 번 더 할 수 있게 <br>언제나 너 원한다면 <br>용기를 내 넌 <br>포기하면 안돼 넌 <br>꿈을 꾸면 이뤄질 거야 <br>힘들었던 어제는 날 더 <br>멋지게 만들어 <br>포기하면 안돼 넌 <br>당당하게 이겨나가자 <br>평범했던 나와 <br>오래된 미움도 <br>나를 떠나간다 <br>눈앞에 펼쳐진 현실은 <br>보기와 다르게 막막해 <br>세상은 이렇게 <br>넓고 넓은데 <br>내가 설 곳은 어디에 <br>어릴 적 부모님이 하신 <br>말씀은 틀린 게 하나 없고 <br>후회 따윈 없을 것 같던 <br>내 삶이 지금 미련으로 <br>되돌아오네 <br>꿈을 이루고 싶지만 <br>맘처럼 쉽지는 않아 <br>이미 너무 지쳤어 <br>꿈은 큰데 <br>지난날의 내 자신이 <br>한심하게 느껴질 정도로 <br>오늘 처음으로 <br>진지한 날 대면했네 <br>이젠 내가 나를 <br>포기하진 않겠어 <br>소중한 꿈을 <br>포기할 순 없기에 <br>지금 이 순간을 <br>포기하진 않겠어 <br>]]></content><category term="튠업뮤지션" label="튠업뮤지션"/><category term="원한다면" label="원한다면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/튠업뮤지션/그때/</id><title>튠업뮤지션 - 그때 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%8A%A0%EC%97%85%EB%AE%A4%EC%A7%80%EC%85%98/%EA%B7%B8%EB%95%8C/" title="튠업뮤지션 - 그때 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어릴 적 너무나 <br>철없던 그 시절 <br>그때에 나는 상처투성이 <br>세상은 너무나 <br>쉽게만 보였고 <br>미움도 영원할 줄 <br>알았던 나야 <br>뒤돌아보니 <br>나는 혼자였고 <br>답답한 바람은 <br>아직 내 머리 위로 <br>이제 우리 같이 기도해 <br>용기를 달라고 <br>수많은 유혹에 <br>힘들겠지만 <br>이제 꿈을 꾸며 <br>일어나 끝없이 달려봐 <br>나는 노래하네 <br>아름다운 꿈 <br>어릴 적 언제나 <br>외롭던 그 시절 <br>그때를 떠올리기는 싫어 <br>별들도 내게는 <br>반짝이지 않아 <br>상처로 가득 찼던 <br>까만 하늘 <br>뒤돌아보니 <br>나는 혼자였고 <br>지루한 태양은 <br>아직 내 머리 위로 <br>이제 우리 같이 기도해 <br>용기를 달라고 <br>수많은 유혹에 <br>힘들겠지만 <br>이제 꿈을 꾸며 <br>일어나 끝없이 달려봐 <br>나는 노래하네 <br>아름다운 꿈 <br>아직도 많은 아픔을 <br>견뎌내야 하지만 <br>멈출 수 없어 <br>불타는 내 맘 <br>이제 우리 같이 기도해 <br>용기를 달라고 <br>수많은 유혹에 <br>힘들겠지만 <br>이제 꿈을 꾸며 <br>일어나 끝없이 달려봐 <br>나는 노래하네 <br>아름다운 꿈 <br>이제 너를 위한 <br>세상을 마음껏 펼쳐봐 <br>이제 넌 절대 <br>혼자가 아니야 <br>]]></content><category term="튠업뮤지션" label="튠업뮤지션"/><category term="그때" label="그때"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/조태준/P215_Blue_Blue_Night/</id><title>조태준 - P.215 Blue Blue Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A1%B0%ED%83%9C%EC%A4%80/P215_Blue_Blue_Night/" title="조태준 - P.215 Blue Blue Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[파도소리마저 니 생각에 잠겨 <br>백사장에 누워 널 그리는 푸른 밤 <br>잠도 오지 않아 밤은 길어지고 <br>눈을 감아봐도 너는 거기 없는데 <br>음 <br>손 뻗으면 잡힐 것 같은 <br>별들은 내게 안기고 <br>내 작은 어깨에 기대던 넌 어디에 <br>강물처럼 흐르고 흘러 <br>이 넓은 바다 끝까지 <br>텅 빈 내 마음을 채우던 넌 어디에 <br>너는 무얼 할까 이 길고 긴 밤에 <br>전활 걸어볼까 용기가 나질 않아 <br>손 뻗으면 닿을 것 같은 <br>달빛이 넘쳐흐르네 <br>내 삶의 빛으로 내리던 넌 어디에 <br>강물처럼 흐르고 흘러 <br>이 넓은 바다 끝까지 <br>외롭던 내 삶을 달래던 넌 어디에 <br>]]></content><category term="조태준" label="조태준"/><category term="P.215 Blue Blue Night" label="P.215 Blue Blue Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/우주히피/P198_Longgoodbye/</id><title>우주히피 - P.198 Longgoodbye - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9A%B0%EC%A3%BC%ED%9E%88%ED%94%BC/P198_Longgoodbye/" title="우주히피 - P.198 Longgoodbye - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[마주앉아 있지만 <br>말을 섞고 있지만 넌 어디 <br>습관처럼 여전히 <br>서롤 향해 있지만 우리는 <br>오 손을 잡고서 <br>함께 길을 걸었지 <br>그게 너무나 아파와 <br>책임감이 강한 난 <br>결정할 수 없나봐 정들어 <br>여린 너는 언제나 <br>모질지 못했었지 정들어 <br>오 밥 먹는 내내 <br>우린 말이 없었지 <br>그게 너무나 아파와 <br>우리 사랑은 끝이 나야 <br>모른 척 잡힐 것만 같고 <br>그 때가 되면 모르는 <br>그 또는 그녀가 되겠지 <br>내가 널 좋아하고 <br>네가 나를 원하고 그 사이 <br>우리 맘이 교차된 <br>사랑이라 부르던 그 사이 <br>오 아직도 우린 가끔 사랑을 하지 <br>그게 너무나 아파와 <br>우리 사랑은 끝이 나야 <br>모른 척 잡힐 것만 같고 <br>그 때가 되면 모르는 <br>그 또는 그녀가 되겠지 <br>우리 둘이만 모르게 <br>오래전 끝은 시작됐고 <br>시간이 되면 모르는 <br>그 또는 그녀가 되겠지 <br>]]></content><category term="우주히피" label="우주히피"/><category term="P.198 Longgoodbye" label="P.198 Longgoodbye"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/고고보이스/P191_서로_사랑했던_지난_시간만큼/</id><title>고고보이스 - P.191 서로 사랑했던 지난 시간만큼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B3%A0%EA%B3%A0%EB%B3%B4%EC%9D%B4%EC%8A%A4/P191_%EC%84%9C%EB%A1%9C_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%96%88%EB%8D%98_%EC%A7%80%EB%82%9C_%EC%8B%9C%EA%B0%84%EB%A7%8C%ED%81%BC/" title="고고보이스 - P.191 서로 사랑했던 지난 시간만큼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[서로 사랑했던 지난 시간만큼 <br>계절이 변하고 많은 밤이 가면 <br>가슴속에 남아있던 <br>흔적들이 사라져 버릴까 <br>불이 꺼진 텅 빈 방안 <br>나의 헝클어진 머리 <br>쓸어 넘겨 홀로 앉아 <br>내게 남은 외로움과 <br>아픔들을 끌어안고 <br>숨을 삼켜 울지 않게 <br>서로 사랑했던 지난 시간만큼 <br>계절이 변하고 많은 밤이 가면 <br>가슴속에 남아있던 흔적들이 <br>사라져 버릴까 <br>아직 남아있는 내 미안함을 <br>들어줄 순 없나요 다시 한번 <br>미처 하지 못 했던 그 말들을 <br>들어줄 순 없나요 다시 한번 <br>이 밤이 가기 전에 <br>서로 사랑했던 지난 시간만큼 <br>계절이 변하고 많은 밤이 가면 <br>가슴속에 남아있던 흔적들이 <br>사라져 버릴까 <br>너를 미워했던 지난 시간만큼 <br>마음이 변하고 많은 날이 가면 <br>서로에게 남긴 그때 그 말들을 <br>이해할 수 있을까 <br>서로 믿지 못한 우리를 위해 <br>서로 믿지 못한 우리를 위해 <br>서로 믿지 못한 우리를 위해 <br>]]></content><category term="고고보이스" label="고고보이스"/><category term="P.191 서로 사랑했던 지난 시간만큼" label="P.191 서로 사랑했던 지난 시간만큼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/애리/P168_Shake_On_You___Psycho_Ramblings_Composed_By_임은석/</id><title>애리 - P.168 Shake On You / Psycho Ramblings (Composed By 임은석) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%A0%EB%A6%AC/P168_Shake_On_You___Psycho_Ramblings_Composed_By_%EC%9E%84%EC%9D%80%EC%84%9D/" title="애리 - P.168 Shake On You / Psycho Ramblings (Composed By 임은석) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Shake on you <br>Love should come you <br>Rock you <br>Come it all <br>Shake on you <br>Love should come it all <br>Shake on you <br>Love should come you <br>Rock you <br>Come it all <br>Shake on you <br>Love should come it all <br>Shake on you <br>Love should come you <br>Rock you <br>Come it all <br>Shake on you <br>Love should come it all <br>Shake on you <br>Love should come you <br>Rock you <br>Come it all <br>Shake on you <br>Love should come it all <br>Who's the one <br>Who loves me hard <br>Enough to hug me <br>I don't mean to hurt somebody <br>Psycho ramblings to the man <br>To the last I'll remember <br>Let me go <br>Until the dawn is coming <br>To the last I'll remember <br>Who's the one <br>Who loves me hard <br>Enough to hug me <br>I don't mean to hurt somebody <br>Psycho ramblings to the man <br>To the last I'll remember <br>Let me go <br>Until the dawn is coming <br>To the last I'll remember <br>]]></content><category term="애리" label="애리"/><category term="P.168 Shake On You / Psycho Ramblings (Composed By 임은석)" label="P.168 Shake On You / Psycho Ramblings (Composed By 임은석)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전보라/P157_사랑은_이_기적_Prod_By_허첵/</id><title>전보라 - P.157 사랑은 이 기적 (Prod. By 허첵) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EB%B3%B4%EB%9D%BC/P157_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%80_%EC%9D%B4_%EA%B8%B0%EC%A0%81_Prod_By_%ED%97%88%EC%B2%B5/" title="전보라 - P.157 사랑은 이 기적 (Prod. By 허첵) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔은 교활하게 <br>사랑을 비껴가겠지 <br>나도 모르게 <br>사랑을 뱉어 놓고 <br>모른체할 거야 <br>그럴 거야 <br>이제 <br>니가 알아봐 줘 <br>먼저 다가와 줘 <br>날 안아줘 <br>모른 척 <br>널 받아줄게 <br>니 손을 잡을게 <br>눈감아줄게 <br>니가 다가올수록 <br>난 더욱 흔들리겠지 <br>아무런 말도 하지 못해 네게 <br>상처받기 싫어서 <br>널 보면 나도 모르게 <br>발을 빼버리곤 해 <br>이제 <br>니가 알아봐 줘 <br>먼저 다가와 줘 <br>날 안아줘 <br>모른 척 <br>널 받아줄게 <br>니 손을 잡을게 <br>눈감아줄게 <br>사랑은 이기적 <br>사랑은 이기적이야 <br>기적 같은 것 <br>사랑 받고 싶어서 <br>난 사랑을 했어 <br>사랑 받고 싶어 <br>이제 <br>니가 알아봐 줘 <br>먼저 다가와 줘 <br>날 안아줘 <br>모른 척 <br>널 받아줄게 <br>니 손을 잡을게 <br>눈감아줄게 <br>날 안아줘 <br>이젠 내가 다가갈게 <br>내가 손 내밀게 <br>손을 꼭 잡아줘 <br>날 안아줘 <br>널 받아줄게 <br>니 손을 잡은 채 <br>이대로 꿈꾸고 싶어 <br>사랑은 이기적 <br>사랑은 이기적이야 <br>]]></content><category term="전보라" label="전보라"/><category term="P.157 사랑은 이 기적 (Prod. By 허첵)" label="P.157 사랑은 이 기적 (Prod. By 허첵)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이원영_블루파프리카/P137_연애를_시작한다는_건_말이야/</id><title>이원영 (블루파프리카) - P.137 연애를 시작한다는 건 말이야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%9B%90%EC%98%81_%EB%B8%94%EB%A3%A8%ED%8C%8C%ED%94%84%EB%A6%AC%EC%B9%B4/P137_%EC%97%B0%EC%95%A0%EB%A5%BC_%EC%8B%9C%EC%9E%91%ED%95%9C%EB%8B%A4%EB%8A%94_%EA%B1%B4_%EB%A7%90%EC%9D%B4%EC%95%BC/" title="이원영 (블루파프리카) - P.137 연애를 시작한다는 건 말이야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 매번 <br>거절할 걸 알면서 고백해 <br>너는 매번 <br>아닌 척하면서도 웃었지 <br>그런 네가 나를 행복하게 해 <br>너는 매번 <br>들킬걸 알면서도 숨기고 <br>나는 매번 <br>모른 척하는데도 다가가 <br>이런 우리 사인 아직 어색해 <br>그런데도 너의 모든 것이 궁금해 <br>그래 연애를 <br>시작한다는 건 말이야 <br>집에 오는 길에 맥주처럼 <br>멈출 수가 없는 것 <br>사랑이 시작된다는 건 말이야 <br>밤하늘에 별들까지 <br>모든 것이 너를 향해가는 것 <br>나는 요즘엔 <br>나보다 너를 더 생각해 <br>너는 요즘 들어 <br>웃는 모습이 많아져 <br>그런 너의 미소가 날 웃게 해 <br>그런 너의 모든 것을 감싸 안을게 <br>그래 연애를 <br>시작한다는 건 말이야 <br>달콤한 초콜릿처럼 <br>멈출 수가 없는 것 <br>사랑이 시작된다는 건 말이야 <br>휴일을 앞둔 저녁처럼 <br>모든 것이 아름다워지는 것 <br>길어져만 가는 새벽에 전화 <br>뻔하지만 설레는 얘기들 <br>두려워 망설이는 널 놓지 않을게 <br>네가 다시 끓어오를 때까지 <br>연애를 시작한다는 건 말이야 <br>집에 오는 길에 맥주처럼 <br>멈출 수가 없는 것 <br>사랑이 시작된다는 건 말이야 <br>밤하늘에 별들까지 <br>너를 향해 가는 것 <br>연애를 시작한다는 건 말이야 <br>달콤한 초콜릿처럼 <br>멈출 수가 없는 것 <br>사랑이 시작된다는 건 말이야 <br>휴일을 앞둔 저녁처럼 <br>모든 것이 아름다워지는 것 <br>아름다워지는 것 <br>]]></content><category term="이원영 (블루파프리카)" label="이원영 (블루파프리카)"/><category term="P.137 연애를 시작한다는 건 말이야" label="P.137 연애를 시작한다는 건 말이야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/윤기타/P69_사랑후에_남는_것들/</id><title>윤기타 - P.69 사랑후에 남는 것들 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9C%A4%EA%B8%B0%ED%83%80/P69_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%9B%84%EC%97%90_%EB%82%A8%EB%8A%94_%EA%B2%83%EB%93%A4/" title="윤기타 - P.69 사랑후에 남는 것들 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그래 너와 내가 했던 <br>모든 일들을 없던 걸로 하자 <br>그래 너와 내가 나눈 <br>모든 말들을 다 잊고 살자 <br>우리 사랑했던 날들 <br>손을 잡고 바라보던 그때 <br>지금 이제 와서 보니 <br>마음만 더 저려오네 <br>그래 너와 내가 했던 <br>모든 일들을 없던 걸로 하자 <br>그래 너와 내가 나눈 <br>모든 말들을 다 잊고 살자 <br>우리 함께 했던 날들 <br>서로에게 전부였던 그때 <br>모든 날을 붙잡으려 <br>무던히도 애써왔는데 <br>우리 사랑했던 날들 <br>지친 나를 웃게 했던 그때 <br>함께 했던 너는 없고 <br>너의 기억만 남아있네 <br>너와 내가 사랑했던 <br>모든 날들을 없는 듯 <br>살 수 있을까 <br>사랑하고 사랑받던 <br>모든 기억을 언제쯤 <br>잊을 수 있을까 <br>]]></content><category term="윤기타" label="윤기타"/><category term="P.69 사랑후에 남는 것들" label="P.69 사랑후에 남는 것들"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이진호/P47_독백/</id><title>이진호 - P.47 독백 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A7%84%ED%98%B8/P47_%EB%8F%85%EB%B0%B1/" title="이진호 - P.47 독백 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우린 변한 게 아냐 <br>시간이 흐른 것 뿐 <br>의미없는 눈물과 <br>울림없는 말일지라도 <br>이해해줘 시간이 필요해 <br>사랑은 곁에 있으니 <br>조금만 기다려줘 <br>그 당연했던 사랑이 <br>왜 널 비참하게 <br>만든 건지 난 오 왜 <br>매일 같은 마음속에 <br>갇혀 지낸지 오랜 <br>난 오 왜 <br>나를 속인 내가 <br>그냥 나 인줄 알고 <br>사랑해 한마디로 <br>나를 받아줬던 너에게 <br>이해해줘 그 커다란 <br>말을 아무렇지 않은 듯이 <br>너에게 하고 말았지 <br>그 찬란했던 사랑이 <br>왜 우릴 멀어지게 <br>하는 건지 난 오 왜 <br>매일 같은 마음속에 <br>갇혀 지낸지 오랜 <br>난 오 왜 <br>라 라 라 라 라 라 라 라 <br>]]></content><category term="이진호" label="이진호"/><category term="P.47 독백" label="P.47 독백"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/블랑_BLANC/P18_헤어지는_중/</id><title>블랑 (BLANC) - P.18 헤어지는 중 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%94%EB%9E%91_BLANC/P18_%ED%97%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%A7%80%EB%8A%94_%EC%A4%91/" title="블랑 (BLANC) - P.18 헤어지는 중 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우린 헤어지는 중 <br>끝나가는 중 <br>매일 만났던 이곳에 <br>매번 먹었던 음식에 <br>전에 했던 이야기 <br>이미 알고 있었지 <br>언제부턴가 조금씩 <br>어색해져버린 공기 <br>어딜 바라보는지 <br>무슨 얘길 하는지 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>우린 끝나가는 중 <br>예측 가능한 클리셰 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>흔들리는 너의 눈빛 <br>한숨 내뱉던 입술 <br>이해할 수 없는 미소 <br>천천히 흐르는 시간 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>우린 끝나가는 중 <br>예측 가능한 클리셰 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>알면서도 모르는 척 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>우린 끝나가는 중 <br>예측 가능한 클리셰 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>우린 끝나가는 중 <br>어디서부터 잘못돼 <br>여기까지 왔을까 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>끝나가는 중 <br>우린 헤어지는 중 <br>]]></content><category term="블랑 (BLANC)" label="블랑 (BLANC)"/><category term="P.18 헤어지는 중" label="P.18 헤어지는 중"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/하트/주르륵/</id><title>하트 - 주르륵 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:46:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:46:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%98%ED%8A%B8/%EC%A3%BC%EB%A5%B4%EB%A5%B5/" title="하트 - 주르륵 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나는 이별하지 <br>않은 것처럼 <br>오늘도 네가 나를 <br>사랑해주는 것처럼 <br>전활하고 기다리고 <br>널 만나러 가고 <br>넌 내가 보이지 <br>않는 것처럼 <br>안들리는 것처럼 <br>다른 사람과 <br>행복하게 웃고 있어 <br>나를 봤어 <br>나는 울고 있어 <br>주르륵 주르륵 <br>자꾸 두뺨 위로 <br>눈물이 흘러내린다 <br>주르륵 나 이렇게 주르륵 <br>오늘도 어제처럼 <br>헤어진 순간처럼 <br>또 주르륵 <br>너를 사랑하지 <br>않는 것처럼 <br>전부 잊은 것처럼 <br>물 한잔 네 얼굴에 <br>뿌려주고 올걸 <br>웃어줄걸 그냥 돌아설걸 <br>주르륵 주르륵 <br>자꾸 두뺨 위로 <br>눈물이 흘러내린다 <br>주르륵 나 이렇게 주르륵 <br>오늘도 어제처럼 <br>헤어진 순간처럼 <br>또 주르륵 <br>너를 모두 잊었다 <br>말하고 싶어 <br>안되는 줄 알면서 <br>널 아직도 사랑하면서 <br>바보 같은 여자야 <br>너무 답답한 나야 <br>나 같은 여자 <br>넌 다 잊었는데 <br>주르륵 또 주르륵 <br>이 거리에는 <br>다시 또 비가 내린다 <br>주르륵 나 이렇게 주르륵 <br>오늘도 어제처럼 <br>헤어진 순간처럼 <br>또 주르륵 <br>]]></content><category term="하트" label="하트"/><category term="주르륵" label="주르륵"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Atlantis/</id><title>Postiljonen - Atlantis - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Atlantis/" title="Postiljonen - Atlantis - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Slow it down in the night <br>Vote against her, vote against her now <br>We dont talk in the dark <br>In the black thats where the hearts collide <br><br>I get lost in your mind <br>Overnight i saw the bluest skies <br>You dont want me around <br>I let my hunger and my heart run wild <br><br>Do you hear my heart <br>Trembling hard and lonely <br>You cloud my eyes <br>Like a wind you're here then gone <br><br>Slow it down in the night <br>Vote against her, vote against her now <br>Out of luck I rewind <br>To the time when i was young and blind to the time when i was young and blind <br>When I was young and blind, when I was young and blind <br><br>Do you hear my heart <br>Trembling hard and lonely <br>You cloud my eyes <br>Like a wind you're here then gone]]></content><category term="Postiljonen" label="Postiljonen"/><category term="Atlantis" label="Atlantis"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/All_That_We_Had_Is_Lost/</id><title>Postiljonen - All That We Had Is Lost - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/All_That_We_Had_Is_Lost/" title="Postiljonen - All That We Had Is Lost - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's a boy I know <br>He's the one I dream of <br>Looks into my eyes <br>Takes me to the clouds above <br>Oh, I lose control <br>Can't seem to get enough <br>When I wake from dreaming <br>Tell me, is it really love <br>You know, you're sweet, you really are <br><br>All that we had is lost <br>All that we were is gone <br><br>Oh, wake me <br>I'm shaking <br>Wish I had you near me now <br>Said, there's now mistaking <br>What I feel is really love <br><br>All that we had is lost <br>All that we were is gone <br><br>Oh, tell me <br>Oh, tell me <br>How will I know <br>Oh, tell me <br>Oh, tell me <br>How will I know <br>Oh, tell me <br>It's something I couldn't live without <br>I couldn't live in those dreams you made, though <br>In those dreams we had it all <br><br>All that we had is lost <br>How will I know <br>All that we were is gone <br>How will I know <br>All that we had is lost <br>How will I know <br>All that we were is gone <br>How will I know <br>Oh, tell me <br>Oh, tell me <br>Oh, tell me <br>Oh, tell me]]></content><category term="Postiljonen" label="Postiljonen"/><category term="All That We Had Is Lost" label="All That We Had Is Lost"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Skying_High/</id><title>Postiljonen - Skying High - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Skying_High/" title="Postiljonen - Skying High - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Feeling like we're on a high <br>Livin' ain't the easy part, dreaming was <br>All we ever did was ride <br>And we fucked it all <br><br>Ahhhh <br><br>We're living our crazy ways <br>We ain't got time for love and games <br>Heading for the summer skies <br>You told me stories <br>That made me wander in the dark <br>You came in the summer <br>All you did was jump and shake my heart <br><br>Ahhhh]]></content><category term="Postiljonen" label="Postiljonen"/><category term="Skying High" label="Skying High"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Rivers/</id><title>Postiljonen - Rivers - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Rivers/" title="Postiljonen - Rivers - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh the sun <br>Gave us something we who <br>And the moon <br>Shines on rivers we swam and crawled into <br><br>When we die, I'll walk with you <br>When we go, I'll lie with you <br><br>Oh the wind, brought us somewhere we could <br>Soar high above all <br>And the moon <br>Shines on rivers we swam and crawled into <br><br>When we die, I'll walk with you <br>When we go, I'll lie with you <br>When we die, I'll walk with you <br>When we go, I'll lie with you]]></content><category term="Postiljonen" label="Postiljonen"/><category term="Rivers" label="Rivers"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Supreme/</id><title>Postiljonen - Supreme - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Supreme/" title="Postiljonen - Supreme - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We are what we are <br>Hopelessly in love <br>The stars in our sky <br>Never to unfold <br>When time takes us back the ocean turns to gold and <br>I could take you under my wings <br>Wherever we go <br>Our love is wild <br>When all we had was found <br>In the only place we know <br>Thats when I took you under my wings <br>Wherever we go <br>Our love is wild <br>Wherever we go <br>Our love is wild]]></content><category term="Postiljonen" label="Postiljonen"/><category term="Supreme" label="Supreme"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Plastic_Panorama/</id><title>Postiljonen - Plastic Panorama - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Plastic_Panorama/" title="Postiljonen - Plastic Panorama - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Plastic panorama <br>View from the camera <br>Lost you in the film <br>Your blame in the sun <br>Plastic panorama <br>View from the camera <br>Lost you in the film <br>Your blame in the sun <br>The timely borrow <br>The sun sets tomorrow <br>I know we can run <br>We can follow the night <br>You knew you had a vision <br>When you had permission <br>To fly to the night <br>And colour the sky <br>Ooooooh <br>What are you waiting for <br>Well I want to know <br>If you felt it all around <br>Plastic panorama <br>View from the camera <br>Lost you in the film <br>You're blaming the sun <br>Plastic Panorama <br>Flew from the drama <br>You said <br>This is true love, think this happens everyday <br>Ooooooh <br>What are you waiting for <br>Well I want to know <br>If you felt it all around <br>See, you felt it all <br>See, you felt it all <br>See, you felt it all <br>See, you felt it all]]></content><category term="Postiljonen" label="Postiljonen"/><category term="Plastic Panorama" label="Plastic Panorama"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/On_The_Run/</id><title>Postiljonen - On The Run - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/On_The_Run/" title="Postiljonen - On The Run - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[In the night our lights go on <br>Hold my hand as we shine through town <br>If you knew me you know that <br>I'm always higher when you're around <br>Oh, oh <br>We're always On The Run <br>Oh, boy <br>We'll shine until we're gone <br>Lay us down in the grass, alone <br>Let the sky fall in our arms <br>Might be dreaming and if I'm dreaming <br>Let me sleep forever more <br>Oh, oh <br>We're always On The Run <br>Oh, boy <br>We'll shine until we're gone <br>In your dream, oh, oh <br>In your dream, oh, oh <br>Let me in <br>x2 <br>Let me in <br>We were the ones who, we were the ones who were, here <br>x4 <br>Let me in <br>x3]]></content><category term="Postiljonen" label="Postiljonen"/><category term="On The Run" label="On The Run"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/We_Raise_Our_Hearts/</id><title>Postiljonen - We Raise Our Hearts - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/We_Raise_Our_Hearts/" title="Postiljonen - We Raise Our Hearts - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Heavy hearts <br>Starry night <br>Summer highs <br>Under these starlights, but <br>I couldn't get much higher <br>When I asked and you said you might <br>Know that exactly on this little night <br>You gave me your heart and said we'll be fine <br>We'll be so high in the sky <br>We'll be so high in the sky <br>Walks with you <br>On barefoot nights <br>Dreaming on <br>As we fill the sky <br>Oh and I <br>I couldn't get much higher <br>When I asked and you said you might <br>Know that exactly on this little night <br>You gave me your heart and said we'll be fine <br>We'll be so high in the sky <br>We'll be so high in the sky <br>We'll be so high]]></content><category term="Postiljonen" label="Postiljonen"/><category term="We Raise Our Hearts" label="We Raise Our Hearts"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Help/</id><title>Postiljonen - Help - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Postiljonen/Help/" title="Postiljonen - Help - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tell me who lied <br>When we waited for something to show <br>I know we fought the night <br>You always had a storm in your eyes <br>I could be the one you want when we're all gone <br>Help me, live on <br>I could be the one you hold when we're out of time <br>Get me somewhere I can roam alone <br>Oh you won't know <br>How I feel you in all that I do <br>And you, you came close <br>As you walked in and out of our lies <br>Then I'd feel you fading out <br>I could be the one you want when we're all gone <br>Help me, live on <br>I could be the one you hold when we're out of time <br>Get me somewhere I can roam alone <br>I could be the one you want when we're all gone <br>Help me, live on <br>I could be the one you hold when we're out of time <br>Get me somewhere I can roam alone <br>I'll be leaving you <br>I could be the one <br>I'll be leaving you <br>I could be the one]]></content><category term="Postiljonen" label="Postiljonen"/><category term="Help" label="Help"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Radio_Dept/Let_Me_Have_This/</id><title>The Radio Dept. - Let Me Have This - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Radio_Dept/Let_Me_Have_This/" title="The Radio Dept. - Let Me Have This - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I've reached a point where <br>I think I have it all <br>No one knew this, so take me now <br><br>This could be the final song <br>'cause I think I have it all <br>Only time can tell <br>But take me now <br>'cause I don't wanna know <br>If everything must go <br>Please let me have this <br>Or take me now <br><br>Please let me have this]]></content><category term="The Radio Dept." label="The Radio Dept."/><category term="Let Me Have This" label="Let Me Have This"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Radio_Dept/I_Dont_Like_It_Like_This/</id><title>The Radio Dept. - I Don`t Like It Like This - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Radio_Dept/I_Dont_Like_It_Like_This/" title="The Radio Dept. - I Don`t Like It Like This - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Words fail me all the time <br>I don't even feel like talking <br>still I go on and on <br>I'm dying here and you keep walking <br><br>why are you asking me this <br>can't you see I'm trying <br>I don't like it like this <br>no I think I'm dying <br><br>I can't calm down at all <br>panic is what panic feels like <br>can't we just stay silent <br>speaking now seems far too violent <br><br>why are you asking me this <br>can't you see I'm trying <br>I don't like it like this <br>no I think I'm dying]]></content><category term="The Radio Dept." label="The Radio Dept."/><category term="I Don`t Like It Like This" label="I Don`t Like It Like This"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Radio_Dept/Deliverance/</id><title>The Radio Dept. - Deliverance - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Radio_Dept/Deliverance/" title="The Radio Dept. - Deliverance - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[They're out to get me <br>try to upset me <br>and interpret me <br>can't they just let me <br><br>I've got five <br>due tomorrow night <br>I'm alright when I'm not sober <br>blend the green and brown <br>before I leave this town <br>all night will be over <br><br>and they don't know you <br>not like I know you <br>try to outgrow you <br>what does that show you <br><br>I've got five <br>due tomorrow night <br>stay down and come over <br>blend the green and brown <br>before we leave this town <br>all night will be over]]></content><category term="The Radio Dept." label="The Radio Dept."/><category term="Deliverance" label="Deliverance"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Radio_Dept/This_Past_Week/</id><title>The Radio Dept. - This Past Week - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Radio_Dept/This_Past_Week/" title="The Radio Dept. - This Past Week - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[This past week has been a strange one <br>Lazy, new and good and bad <br>Feelings come and go and change and <br>AC DC, good and bad and sad <br><br>Move to a bigger city <br>Leave home and face the pity <br>I'd rather stay in bed <br>knowing that it won't be pretty <br><br>I've wasted a year or so <br>I lost my will some time ago <br>Frustration comes when friends succeed in doing things <br>but then again that's me <br><br>I want to be a good friend <br>I want to find my best friend <br>Someone who wants to stay <br>Someone who doesn't go away]]></content><category term="The Radio Dept." label="The Radio Dept."/><category term="This Past Week" label="This Past Week"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Unnamed/Dont_Lie_To_Me/</id><title>Unnamed - Don`t Lie To Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:47:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:47:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Unnamed/Dont_Lie_To_Me/" title="Unnamed - Don`t Lie To Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤이 오는 거리에 <br>조용히 내려 앉은 <br>따뜻한 달빛과 <br>차가운 침묵만이 <br>지금 이순간 <br>너는 어디에 <br>영원을 말하던 <br>진심인 줄 알았던 <br>너의 거짓말 <br>Don't lie to me <br>이제 내게 <br>더이상 영원이란 <br>말은 하지마 <br>Don't lie to me <br>바보 같이 <br>또다시 상처받고 <br>싶지않아 <br>혼자가 더 좋다는 <br>위로를 하면서 <br>혼자 걷지 않았던 <br>길을 다시 걸어봐 <br>사랑한다고 <br>변함없다고 말하던 <br>영원을 속삭이던 <br>너는 어디에 <br>Don't lie to me <br>이제 내게 <br>더이상 영원이란 <br>말은 하지마 <br>Don't lie to me <br>바보 같이 <br>또다시 상처받고 <br>싶지않아 <br>어딘가에서 <br>많이 본듯한 <br>저 멀리서 <br>걸어 오는 모습이 <br>아직도 내가 기억하는 <br>예전 너와 나의 모습이 <br>]]></content><category term="Unnamed" label="Unnamed"/><category term="Don`t Lie To Me" label="Don`t Lie To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asbjorn/Call_Me_By_My_Name/</id><title>Asbjorn - Call Me By My Name - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:48:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:48:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asbjorn/Call_Me_By_My_Name/" title="Asbjorn - Call Me By My Name - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Do me right, do me wrong <br>Do him right, do him wrong <br>Better sorrow, than hollow <br>Yeah, yeah <br><br>Do me fast, do me slow <br>Do him fast, do him slow <br>Better you do it, than don't <br>Yeah, yeah <br><br>But I'm still keeping you inside of my heart <br>Yeah, I'm still keeping you inside of my heart <br><br>Call me by my name when you let me go <br>Say it like if you were all alone <br>Call me by my name when you let me go <br><br>Let me go, let me go <br>Say, Asbjorn, I let you go <br>Say, Asbjorn, I let you go <br><br>Love has been no friend of mine <br>Love was never a friend of his <br>But I get so high on heartache <br>Yeah, yeah <br><br>So when it's gone, I will cry <br>When it's gone, he will cry <br>Cause I know you'll be out of my mind <br>Yeah, yeah <br><br>That's why I'm still keeping you inside of my heart <br>That's why I'm still keeping you inside of my heart <br><br>Let me go, just let me go, yeah <br><br>But I'm still keeping you inside my heart <br>You told me to let you go <br>Yeah, I still keep you here inside my heart <br>Because you couldn't say my name <br><br>Let me go, let me go, let me go, yeah <br><br>Call me by my name <br>Tell it to my heart <br>Tell it to me, heart <br><br>Call me by my name when you let me go <br>Let me go, let me go, just let me go <br>Yeah, let me go, let me go <br>Just let me go <br>Say, Asbjorn, I let you go]]></content><category term="Asbjorn" label="Asbjorn"/><category term="Call Me By My Name" label="Call Me By My Name"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asbjorn/Moonia/</id><title>Asbjorn - Moonia - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:48:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:48:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asbjorn/Moonia/" title="Asbjorn - Moonia - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[People of the night <br>Don't you wanna feel heartbeats, unite as one <br>Unite as one <br><br>The stars are all aligned <br>Got a feeling this is what they've been talking about <br>They got me talking about it <br><br>Some moons we won't recall, when we're old <br>But there's a special one before every dawn <br>You gotta see it <br>I'm going to take you there <br><br>We've been tripping and walking 20 blocks tonight <br>We better start this moon society soon <br><br>People of the night <br>Don't you wanna feel heartbeats, unite as one <br>Unite as one <br><br>The stars are all aligned <br>Got a feeling this is what they've been talking about <br>They got me talking about it <br><br>And they will call us <br>Moonia, moonia, moonia <br>In the dark we celebrate our hearts <br>Moonia, moonia, moonia <br>In the dark we celebrate our hearts <br><br>We've been tripping and walking 20 blocks tonight <br>We better start this moon society soon <br><br>People of the night <br>Don't you wanna feel heartbeats, unite as one <br>Unite as one <br><br>The stars are all aligned <br>Got a feeling this is what they've been talking about <br>They got me talking about it <br><br>And they will call us <br>Moonia, moonia, moonia <br>In the dark we celebrate our hearts <br>Moonia, moonia, moonia <br>In the dark we celebrate our hearts <br><br>Winter night so long we grow <br>And she'll be our religion <br>Summer days take her away <br>We still grow and she'll be our religion <br><br>But some moons we won't recall, when we're old <br>But there's a special one before every dawn]]></content><category term="Asbjorn" label="Asbjorn"/><category term="Moonia" label="Moonia"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asbjorn/Kiddo/</id><title>Asbjorn - Kiddo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:48:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:48:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asbjorn/Kiddo/" title="Asbjorn - Kiddo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Everybody seems to know about us <br>You call me names, talk to my veins <br>You talk to me <br><br>When I'm looking for trouble I follow you <br>Doing what you do <br>Throwing stones, feeling your bones <br>I'm feeling you <br><br>Tell me words, tell me words about <br>How we make the most of our youth <br>You have a crystal, I have a crystal <br>Remember what we promised each other <br><br>Seems like everything we touch <br>Will turn towards us <br>We break and bend, we shape what we want <br>And I want you <br><br>Can I mold you, like you mold me <br>Cause soon we will grow up <br>And we should make the most of our youth <br>You have a crystal, I have a crystal <br>Remember what we promised each other <br><br>Kiddo let me show you how to be free <br>It's just a little something to put your worries to sleep <br>I promise ya, The night will be lighter, prettier <br>And you will make the most of your youth <br><br>Ahaha, hush, hush, hush, hush <br><br>Kiddo let me show you how to be free <br>It's just a little something to put your worries to sleep <br>I promise ya, The night will be lighter, prettier <br>And you will make the most of your youth <br><br>You will make the most of your youth]]></content><category term="Asbjorn" label="Asbjorn"/><category term="Kiddo" label="Kiddo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asbjorn/The_Love_You_Have_In_You/</id><title>Asbjorn - The Love You Have In You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:48:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:48:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asbjorn/The_Love_You_Have_In_You/" title="Asbjorn - The Love You Have In You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Easy tiger <br>We started it and we will end it <br>Every man I've ever loved has lost his way for a woman <br><br>Pseudo visions <br>Disillusions of a young heart <br>Whether I want it or not I will lose my way for a man <br><br>Lose yourself to all the love you have in you <br>No one knows exactly what you do <br>Lose yourself to all the love you have in you <br>And I will know exactly what to do <br><br>My dear tiger <br>Use your power to unite us <br>'Cause everybody's going towards a separate goal <br>And every word you say could turn my world around <br>And the funny thing about it is no one else will know <br><br>Lose yourself to all the love you have in you <br>No one knows exactly what you do <br>Lose yourself to all the love you have in you <br>And I will know exactly what to do <br><br>I will love you I will love you I will love you <br>I will love you I will love you I will love you <br>I will love you I will love you I will love you <br>You, you, you You, you, you <br>You, you, you You, you, you <br><br>I will love you <br>You, you, you You, you, you <br>You, you, you You, you, you <br><br>I will love you I will love you I will love you <br>I will love you I will love you]]></content><category term="Asbjorn" label="Asbjorn"/><category term="The Love You Have In You" label="The Love You Have In You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sulk/Past_Paradise/</id><title>Sulk - Past Paradise - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:49:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:49:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Sulk/Past_Paradise/" title="Sulk - Past Paradise - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A change of view <br>Await the new <br>And break into the sea <br>The waits over <br>Out of nowhere <br>To go where you've never been <br><br>I'm making your heart swing <br>I'll make you believe <br>Everyday isnt holy <br>Just lose yourself to me <br>Endlessly <br><br>In your own time <br>In your own right <br>In your own bespoken dream <br><br>You'll never have me <br>You'll never leave me <br>I will fulfill your every need <br><br>I'm making your heart swing <br>I'll make you believe <br>Everyday isnt holy <br>Just lose yourself to me <br>Endlessly <br><br>The sky above you <br>No air beneath you <br>No space and time left inbetween <br><br>No image of you <br>No truth or virtue <br>The only things youll ever see <br><br>Im making your heart swing <br>Ill make you believe <br>Everyday isnt holy <br>Just lose yourself to me <br>Endlessly <br><br>Im making your heart swing <br>Ill make you believe <br>Everyday isnt holy <br>Just lose yourself to me <br>Endlessly <br><br>Im making your heart swing <br>Ill make you believe]]></content><category term="Sulk" label="Sulk"/><category term="Past Paradise" label="Past Paradise"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asbjorn/Scandinavian_Love/</id><title>Asbjorn - Scandinavian Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:50:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:50:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Asbjorn/Scandinavian_Love/" title="Asbjorn - Scandinavian Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Whatcha do when nobody's watching <br>Scandinavian kid making out with the mirror <br>Bet your heart has never beat louder <br>Cause nobody knows you kissed another <br><br>But none of them made you cry like I will <br>Scandinavian Love <br>None of the, broke your heart like I will <br>Scandinavian Love <br>No one loved you like I will love you <br>None of them broke your heart like I will <br>Scandinavian Love <br><br>Don't act all Berlin <br>I know your heart is in bad condition <br>But you really can't help yourself <br>When you're in love with someone, it's a pseudo vision <br><br>But none of them made you cry like I will <br>Scandinavian Love <br>None of the, broke your heart like I will <br>Scandinavian Love <br>No one loved you like I will love you <br>None of them broke your heart like I will <br>Scandinavian Love <br><br>I know nothing about pain <br>I know nothing about love <br>But love is supposed to hurt sometimes <br><br>Every night I've been watching you <br>Picturing all the things we'd do, pseudo visions <br>My mission is being the first that you're kissing <br><br>Hey, you wanna go to the park Full moon <br>Meet me there after dark <br>You don't know the amount of damage I'll cause your heart <br><br>But none of them made you cry like I will <br>None of the, broke your heart like I will <br>No one loved you like I will love you <br>None of them broke your heart like I will <br><br>Like I will]]></content><category term="Asbjorn" label="Asbjorn"/><category term="Scandinavian Love" label="Scandinavian Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pepito_Rella/Hellboy/</id><title>Pepito Rella - Hellboy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:50:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:50:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Pepito_Rella/Hellboy/" title="Pepito Rella - Hellboy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ci esco ingiallito come pollo al curry <br>Spengo il Blackberry <br>Muoio, resuscito, puntate quasi sempre Kenny <br>Everyday I can fly, R Kelly <br>Ah Ah, scappotto sti locali <br>Ti arieggio i capelli <br>La fast life della tua high school <br>Ti ha portato a far panini dentro un fast food <br>Io zero Schoolboy, studio Schoolboy Q <br>Sono tipo Hellboy, cresciuto a tunz tunz <br><br>Voulez vous coucher con il mio Kelmon <br>Ad ogni barra colpi in faccia, Cobain <br><br>Cosi mantengo i vizi del dj <br><br>Ho visto i soldi finti come nel Monopoli, commercio i nanerottoli <br>Quelli veri nel commercio dentro ai pianerottoli <br>Pepito e Vox Populi, con l'odio nei globuli <br>Dubito col rap ci copuli, al massimo coccoli <br>Preghero il dio se mi fa fare il lampo <br>Non mi compro una lambo, ne compro 5 mambo <br>Visto tutti fare tutto ma non fare tanto <br>Come chi dice che fa brutto e non sa dirti quando <br><br>Muoio sul set come Brandon <br>Sognando le spiagge di Naama Bay <br>E io ho tutto l'occorrente nel Kelto <br>Per fare sorridere il mio dj <br><br>Guarda il tuo corpo come fluttua <br>Sara colpa dei Flute <br>Nel back non ho i cestini con la frutta <br>Ci sono le boccie svuotate dalla mia crew <br>Guarda il tuo corpo come fluttua <br>Sara colpa dei Flute <br>Nel back non ho i cestini con la frutta <br>Ci sono le boccie svuotate dalla mia crew]]></content><category term="Pepito Rella" label="Pepito Rella"/><category term="Hellboy" label="Hellboy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Agnes_Circle/Under_Reason/</id><title>The Agnes Circle - Under Reason - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:51:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:51:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Agnes_Circle/Under_Reason/" title="The Agnes Circle - Under Reason - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I contemplate <br>In idols I once made <br>Beckoned faith <br>Questioning the motives of our way <br>Illusions speak with more life now <br>How can they be wrong <br>Logic gone, blinded faith <br>Morals can't be found <br><br>Under your reason <br>Under reason <br><br>I hesitate <br>To grasp ideals you make <br>Disbelief <br>Truth in pantomime <br>Eyeless now as the innate <br>Where does absence lay <br>With challenged sight <br>Does truth enlight Or only shift the mind <br><br>Under your reason, under reason]]></content><category term="The Agnes Circle" label="The Agnes Circle"/><category term="Under Reason" label="Under Reason"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Agnes_Circle/Martial_Love/</id><title>The Agnes Circle - Martial Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:51:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:51:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Agnes_Circle/Martial_Love/" title="The Agnes Circle - Martial Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[On the enclaves of your heart <br>Praying on the lilac in you <br>Blind chivalry devout blue <br>Enfolding caraway <br><br>Dancing in your heart <br>Tell me everything that I want to hear <br>Tell me everything that I want to hear <br>Hanging in the mind <br><br>In martial love's impart <br>Weighing dawn's first pattern in you <br>Primrose in bloom without hue <br>Engulfed in dopamine <br><br>Dancing in your heart <br>Tell me everything that I want to hear <br>Tell me everything that I want to hear <br>Hanging in the mind]]></content><category term="The Agnes Circle" label="The Agnes Circle"/><category term="Martial Love" label="Martial Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zoda/No／Way/</id><title>Zoda - No／Way - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:51:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:51:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Zoda/No%EF%BC%8FWay/" title="Zoda - No／Way - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Qui c'e il contratto, tutto quello che ho detto e il resto e qua <br>Lo leggero <br>A tuo comodo <br>Pertanto in quanto il primo contraente da al secondo contraente e ai suoi soci piena facolta di usarlo a loro piacere e altresi di spedirlo, ritirarlo <br>trasportare lui e cio che gli appartiene compresi corpo, anima, carne, sangue o peni <br>Che significa <br>Ah, quella e una clausola per i trasporti <br><br>Imparate a dire di no <br>Iscritto ricambi No <br>Spero che cambi No <br>E nel frattempo che provate coltivo il mio spazio indoor Yolown <br>Lotto per la liberta in casa <br>Contro finti dei <br>I vostri affari non sono piu fatti miei <br>Vorrei vederli e non sentirli <br>Spegnervi e smentirvi <br>Perche parlando di profitti ho capito che approfitti <br>Cosa fate Per sentito dire odiate <br>Ma se vi sentite odiare dite avete udito male <br>Continui a guardarmi come se fossi niente <br>Continui a camminare come se niente fosse <br>No con il viso per chi delusione mi ha inciso <br>Ho condiviso le mie ore con chi mi voleva ucciso <br>Ha fallito Non sono resuscitato <br>Come quelli che fanno polemica in pubblico per scusarsi in privato <br><br>Guarda un po' chi c'e stasera, cambia l'atmosfera, magia nera <br>Scrivo il futuro con la mia penna a sfera <br>Progetto la vendetta che questa musica spera <br>Ma alla tua stupida scena taglio gole, ultima cena <br>Se penso al passato resto incastrato <br>Lascio chi mi ha infangato fermo impalato <br>Cambio forma, opinione ma non cambio missione <br>Sono dimagrito per quanto ho corso dietro alle persone <br>Spero in una via d'uscita, se la vedi avvisa <br>Si ma fallo prima che la mia pazienza si uccida <br>Vi lascio alla vostra monotonia <br>Chiudo gli occhi e volo via <br>Richiamami quando non ci sara piu il razzismo e l'omofobia <br>e una malattia quella di giudicare e basta <br>Non e che se punti il dito tutto passa <br>Qui chi regna e solo l'ignoranza <br>Meno male che mi distinguo dalla massa <br>Ma che mi arrabbio a fare <br>La punizione migliore e starsene zitti e continuare a farli sbagliare <br><br>I feel closed in this cage <br>If I do not forget yesterday <br>I'm trying to throw it out of my mind <br><br>So closed in this cage <br>Cause I cannot forget yesterday <br>I'm trying to throw it out of my mind <br><br>Ho perso cio che volevo salvare ed e stata la vera salvezza <br>Non mi ha oppresso, ho espresso il meglio dalla mia tristezza <br>Sono sommerso dal dolore ma so che la via e questa <br>E non smetto <br>Da solo mi concentro fino a che non mi esplode la testa <br>Vogliono tutto e subito sopraffatti dall'orgoglio <br>Ma poi restano al buio, finisce tutto in un secondo <br>Rimangono pieni di forse, di dubbi, mezze risposte <br>Basta fare corse per persone non corrisposte <br>E se <br>E se fosse tutto un sogno <br>Non mi resta che inseguirlo <br>Ma questa e la realta e ne paghi il conto <br>Svegliati, come fai a non capirlo <br>Nascono tutti uguali con il timbro <br>Ora prova a smentirlo <br>Mi sento in equilibrio scomodo sopra uno spillo <br>E non mi abbatto perche ogni mio strillo <br>Non sara vano finche ci sara qualcuno a concepirlo <br><br>I feel closed in the cage <br>If I do not forget yesterday <br>I've tried to throw it out of my mind <br><br>I feel closed in the cage <br>If I do not forget yesterday <br>But I know this is my way <br><br>Ho dato troppo a chi non meritava niente <br>In mezzo a questa folla mi serve un salvagente <br>Guardano ogni mia cicatrice come se fossi un ladro <br>Ma non e la cornice a raccontare il quadro <br>Ogni mattina fare colazione con la tensione <br>Di chi mi guarda con attenzione e non usa la ragione <br>Chi mi dipinge come una persona cattiva perche <br>Non sa apprezzare il mio colore <br><br>Credo nel mio cammino e non dico che il tuo e sbagliato <br>Se vedi me come nemico non posso essere tuo alleato <br>Per quanto sono abituato ormai ho lo sguardo congelato <br>Per tutto l'odio che ho conservato prendo la corsa e vado <br>Ardo per ogni sguardo arrivato in ritardo <br>Volto a farmi pensare che sono cambiato <br>E invece ogni gradino e da scalare <br>Voglio soddisfare mia madre con tutto quello che mio padre non le ha saputo dare]]></content><category term="Zoda" label="Zoda"/><category term="No／Way" label="No／Way"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신나라/니가_안들었으면_좋겠는_노래_Feat_서바울/</id><title>신나라 - 니가 안들었으면 좋겠는 노래 (Feat. 서바울) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:51:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:51:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC/%EB%8B%88%EA%B0%80_%EC%95%88%EB%93%A4%EC%97%88%EC%9C%BC%EB%A9%B4_%EC%A2%8B%EA%B2%A0%EB%8A%94_%EB%85%B8%EB%9E%98_Feat_%EC%84%9C%EB%B0%94%EC%9A%B8/" title="신나라 - 니가 안들었으면 좋겠는 노래 (Feat. 서바울) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[차가운 이 공기 <br>어렴풋이 기억나 그때가 <br>뭐 혼자도 난 좋지 <br>가끔은 니 생각에 잠 못 들지만 <br>니가 내게 돌아온단 기대 <br>더는 없어 너 없는 <br>지금이 좋아 난 좋아 <br>가끔 추억들에 혼자 기대 <br>너를 꺼내 열어보기도 <br>하지만 낭비야 <br>I need something else <br>Whoo whoo whoo <br>Whoo whoo <br>혼자서도 잘 지내 <br>웃기도 해 난 이제 <br>없을 뿐 너만 내게 <br>I wanna love you <br>I wanna leave you <br>가득 차있는 밝은 달 <br>비추는 건 아래 서있는 내게만 <br>다른 누구도 될 수 없어 <br>외로운 주인공 <br>저 달도 알아 spot light <br>니가 나를 지켜봐 <br>줄 것 같아 truman <br>자주 걷던 길을 가다 가끔 한두 번 <br>만이라도 마주치고 싶은 그런 밤 <br>단순 바람일 뿐 <br>내 맘 부여잡고 잠을 자 <br>나도 알고 있어 끝이란 걸 <br>너를 지워보려 <br>노력해도 안돼 잘 안돼 <br>너 아닌 다른 누굴 만나는 <br>내 모습이 어색하겠지만 나는 <br>I need someone else <br>Whoo whoo whoo <br>Whoo whoo <br>혼자서도 잘 지내 <br>웃기도 해 난 이제 <br>없을 뿐 너만 내게 <br>I wanna love you <br>I wanna leave you <br>Whoo whoo whoo <br>Whoo whoo <br>]]></content><category term="신나라" label="신나라"/><category term="니가 안들었으면 좋겠는 노래 (Feat. 서바울)" label="니가 안들었으면 좋겠는 노래 (Feat. 서바울)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신나라/마비_Paralysis/</id><title>신나라 - 마비 (Paralysis) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:51:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:51:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EB%82%98%EB%9D%BC/%EB%A7%88%EB%B9%84_Paralysis/" title="신나라 - 마비 (Paralysis) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[기억나니 <br>내가 너를 처음 만났던 날 <br>생각해봐 <br>어디서부터 뭐가 잘못된 거니 <br>너와 내 눈에만 보이던 <br>모든 것이 운명 같던 <br>시간 속 너의 모습 <br>YOU YOU YOU <br>너에게 부르던 노래 <br>달콤한 속삭임 <br>그딴 거 다 집어쳐 <br>난 널 원하지 않아 <br>I leave you tonight <br>baby oh I leave you tonight <br>오늘밤 널 떠나고 나면 다신 <br>사랑 같은 건 필요 없어 가져가 <br>your love love oh your love love <br>and oh your love take your love away <br>your love love oh your love love <br>and oh your love take your love away <br>you say I love you <br>사랑은 아프기만 한거지 <br>생각해봐 <br>이보다 서롤 망칠 수도 있는지 <br>너무 진하기만 했던 <br>너의 그 탁한 사랑은 <br>나를 지독하게 만져 슬프게 해 <br>나를 마비시켜 난 널 원하지 않아 <br>I leave you tonight <br>baby oh I leave you tonight <br>오늘밤 널 떠나고 나면 다신 <br>사랑 같은 건 필요 없어 가져가 <br>your love love oh your love love <br>and oh your love take your love away <br>your love love oh your love love <br>and oh your love take your love away <br>니가 본 그 마지막 <br>눈물은 멈춰버렸으니까 <br>I leave you tonight <br>baby oh I leave you tonight <br>오늘밤 널 떠나고 나면 다신 <br>사랑 같은 건 필요 없어 가져가 <br>baby oh I leave you tonight <br>baby oh I leave you tonight <br>오늘밤 널 떠나고 나면 다신 <br>사랑 같은 건 필요 없어 가져가 <br>your love love oh your love love <br>and oh your love take your love away <br>your love love oh your love love <br>and oh your love take your love away <br>]]></content><category term="신나라" label="신나라"/><category term="마비 (Paralysis)" label="마비 (Paralysis)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김성호/O_Sole_Mio/</id><title>김성호 - O Sole Mio - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:52:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:52:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%84%B1%ED%98%B8/O_Sole_Mio/" title="김성호 - O Sole Mio - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Che bella cosa e na iurnata e sole <br>Laria serena doppo me tempesta <br>Pellaria fresca pare gia na festa <br>Che bella cosa e na iurnata e sole <br>Ma na tu sole chiu belo oi ne <br>O sole mio sta infronte a te <br>O sole, O sole mio sta infronte a te <br>Sta infronte a te <br>Quanno fa notte e o sole se ne scenne <br>Me vene quase una malicunia <br>Sotto a fenesta en me restarria <br>Quanno fa notte e o sole se ne sceene <br>Ma na tu sole chiu belo oi ne <br>O sole mio sta infronte a te <br>O sole, O sole mio sta infronte a te <br>Sta infronte a te]]></content><category term="김성호" label="김성호"/><category term="O Sole Mio" label="O Sole Mio"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/자몽_Jamong/사랑이란_말/</id><title>자몽 (Jamong) - 사랑이란 말 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%90%EB%AA%BD_Jamong/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%EC%9D%B4%EB%9E%80_%EB%A7%90/" title="자몽 (Jamong) - 사랑이란 말 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[바보라도 좋아 네 곁에 있다면 <br>너무나도 따뜻해 <br>너무나도 소중해 네가 <br>볼품없는 내게 할 일이 생겼어 <br>아름다운 일기로 쓰여지도록 <br>하루에 하나씩 배워갈게 널 <br>우리 생이 끝날 때쯤 <br>영원히 기억되도록 <br>사랑이란 말을 우린 몰라도 <br>지금 이런 게 사랑일 꺼야 <br>가슴 벅찬 오늘 끝이라 해도 <br>나는 후회 없이 너를 사랑해 <br>사랑해 <br>누군가 우리를 샘 낼지 몰라 <br>있지 않은 일과 다툼 오해도 <br>알아주면 돼 <br>사랑이란 말을 우린 몰라도 <br>지금 이런 게 사랑일 꺼야 <br>가슴 벅찬 오늘 끝이라 해도 <br>나는 후회 없이 너를 사랑해 <br>사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="자몽 (Jamong)" label="자몽 (Jamong)"/><category term="사랑이란 말" label="사랑이란 말"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/차태현/지난날/</id><title>차태현 - 지난날 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%B0%A8%ED%83%9C%ED%98%84/%EC%A7%80%EB%82%9C%EB%82%A0/" title="차태현 - 지난날 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지난 옛 일 모두 기쁨이라고 <br>하면서도 <br>아픈 기억 찾아 헤메이는 건 <br>왜 일까 <br>가슴 깊이 남은 건 <br>때 늦은 후회 <br>덧없는 듯 쓴 웃음으로 <br>지나온 날들을 돌아보네 <br>예전처럼 돌이킬 순 없다고 <br>하면서도 <br>문득 문득 흐뭇함에 젖는 건 <br>왜 일까 <br>그대로 그 나름대로 <br>의미가 있어 <br>세상사람 얘기하듯이 <br>옛 추억이란 아름다운 것 <br>다시 못 올 지난날을 <br>난 꾸밈없이 영원히 간직하리 <br>그리움을 가득 안은 체 <br>가버린 지난 날 <br>잊지 못할 그 추억 속에 <br>난 우리들의 미래를 비춰보리 <br>하루하루 더욱 새로웁게 <br>그대와 나의 지난날 <br>언제 어디 누가 이유라는 탓 <br>하면 뭐해 <br>잘했었건 못했었건 간에 <br>그대로 그 나름대로 <br>의미가 있어 <br>세상사람 얘기하듯이 <br>옛 추억이란 아름다운 것 <br>다시 못 올 지난날을 <br>난 꾸밈없이 영원히 간직하리 <br>아쉬움을 가득 안은 체 <br>가버린 지난 날 <br>잊지 못할 그 추억 속에 <br>난 우리들의 미래를 비춰보리 <br>하루하루 더욱 새로웁게 <br>그대와 나의 지난날 <br>생각 없이 헛되이 지난다고 <br>하지 말아요 <br>그렇다고 변하는 것은 <br>아닐 테니까 지난 날 <br>다시 못 올 지난날을 <br>난 꾸밈없이 영원히 간직하리 <br>그리움을 가득 안은 체 <br>가버린 지난 날 <br>잊지 못할 그 추억 속에 <br>난 우리들의 미래를 비춰보리 <br>하루하루 더욱 새로웁게 <br>그대와 나의 지난날 <br>]]></content><category term="차태현" label="차태현"/><category term="지난날" label="지난날"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/자몽_Jamong/사랑하기_때문에/</id><title>자몽 (Jamong) - 사랑하기 때문에 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%90%EB%AA%BD_Jamong/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%98%EA%B8%B0_%EB%95%8C%EB%AC%B8%EC%97%90/" title="자몽 (Jamong) - 사랑하기 때문에 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[처음 느낀 그대 눈빛은 <br>혼자만의 오해였던가요 <br>해맑은 미소로 나를 <br>바보로 만들었소 <br>어제는 떠난 그대를 <br>잊지 못하는 내가 미웠죠 <br>하지만 이제 깨달아요 <br>그대만의 나였음을 <br>다시 돌아온 그댈 위해 <br>내 모든 것 드릴 테요 <br>우리 이대로 영원히 <br>헤어지지 않으리 <br>나 오직 그대만을 <br>사랑하기 때문에 <br>커다란 그대를 향해 <br>작아져 만 가는 나이기에 <br>그 무슨 뜻이라 해도 <br>조용히 따르리오 <br>어제는 지난 추억을 <br>잊지 못하는 내가 미웠죠 <br>하지만 이제 깨달아요 <br>그대만의 나였음을 <br>다시 돌아온 그댈 위해 <br>내 모든 것 드릴 테요 <br>우리 이대로 영원히 <br>헤어지지 않으리 <br>나 오직 그대만을 <br>사랑하기 때문에 <br>사랑하기 때문에 <br>]]></content><category term="자몽 (Jamong)" label="자몽 (Jamong)"/><category term="사랑하기 때문에" label="사랑하기 때문에"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성민/저_우주로/</id><title>감성민 - 저 우주로 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EB%AF%BC/%EC%A0%80_%EC%9A%B0%EC%A3%BC%EB%A1%9C/" title="감성민 - 저 우주로 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[밤 하늘 우주 별을보며 <br>별을 골라 떠나보자 <br>화성 말고 모르는 별 <br>누구 아니 모르는 별 <br>한참여 찾아본다 <br>저 멀리 찾아 보고서 <br>정하고 얘기해보자 <br>엄마한테만 <br>떠날래 저기 먼 저 우주 <br>가볼래 다른 세상으로 <br>아무도 보지 못한 그 곳 <br>나만의 우주 <br>떠날래 여기 어디 지구 <br>가볼래 모르는 그 우주 <br>나만이 갈 수 있는 그 곳 <br>나만의 우주 <br>집떠나 인사하고 <br>짐싸서 가방 메고서 <br>우주선 의자 앉아서 <br>카운트다운 <br>십 구 팔 칠 육 <br>오 사 삼 이 일 <br>구름을 헤쳐서 나가자 <br>태양을 등에 짊어지고 <br>우주를 마주하며 인사 <br>지구야 빠이빠이 <br>붉은 별 나의 별을 찾아 <br>푸른 별 사이를 지나서 <br>나의 별 찾을 때까지나 <br>우주를 지나 <br>붉은 별 나의 별을 찾아 <br>우주를 헤매이는 이 곳 <br>붉은 별 찾을 때까지나 <br>지구야 빠이빠이 <br>우주를 헤쳐서 나가자 <br>붉은 별 찾을 때까지나 <br>끝까지 갔다오고 말래 <br>나의 그 우주 <br>]]></content><category term="감성민" label="감성민"/><category term="저 우주로" label="저 우주로"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성민/여기_다시/</id><title>감성민 - 여기 다시 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EB%AF%BC/%EC%97%AC%EA%B8%B0_%EB%8B%A4%EC%8B%9C/" title="감성민 - 여기 다시 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[걷다보니 횡단보도 앞 <br>둘러보니 너의 정류장 <br>걷다보니 지금 여기에 <br>한참 둘러보니 <br>항상 그 버스 <br>한참 동안 서서 있다가 <br>시계보니 어느덧 시간 <br>가야하고 돌아서서 <br>가야지 발을 옮겨 <br>걸어보려 발을 옮겨 <br>혹시나 우연히 마주칠까 <br>반갑다 마주칠까 <br>그냥 바라볼까 <br>멍하니 서서있어 <br>이 버스 멈춰설 때 <br>내 숨도 멈춰설 때 <br>내린 너의 모습 <br>나를 보며 잠시 한참보다 <br>너를 보고 한참 서 보다가 <br>또 나를 보며 <br>웃으며 반갑다고 <br>나에게 인사해 <br>너를 보고 반갑다 웃으며 <br>인사하고 멍하니 서 있어 <br>아무말 못하고 <br>서서 또 있어 <br>너도 말 없이 서서 <br>이렇게도 우연히 봤어 <br>그자리에 오늘도 있어 <br>입을 떼며 발을 옮겼어 <br>나도 너를 따라 <br>발을 옮겼어 <br>너의 동네 골목길 따라 <br>바래다 준 그 골목길로 <br>너의 집 앞 계단 앞에 <br>너를 보내려할 때 <br>너를 불러 얼굴을 봐 <br>너를보며 웃다 울다 웃다 <br>나를보고 웃다 울다 웃다 <br>또 돌아서며 <br>울다 웃다 울다가 <br>또 웃다가 울다 <br>널 보내고 웃다 울다 웃다 <br>걸어가며 울다 웃다 울어 <br>발걸음을 옮기고 걸어가며 <br>또 한참을 울어 <br>]]></content><category term="감성민" label="감성민"/><category term="여기 다시" label="여기 다시"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/감성민/혼자서_걷다/</id><title>감성민 - 혼자서 걷다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%90%EC%84%B1%EB%AF%BC/%ED%98%BC%EC%9E%90%EC%84%9C_%EA%B1%B7%EB%8B%A4/" title="감성민 - 혼자서 걷다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[저기 횡단보도 앞에서 <br>니가 손 흔들것 같아 <br>파란불 바뀌고서 <br>널 찾아 불러 <br>넌 여기 내 앞에 없어 <br>자꾸 널 찾아 불러봐도 <br>내 앞엔 하얀색 <br>횡단보도만이 <br>널 찾아 널 불러 <br>항상 여기서 <br>손 흔들잖아 <br>널 찾아 널 불러 <br>니가 없어 <br>니 생각 날 것 같아 <br>날 것 같아 날 것 같아서 <br>보고 싶어 보고 싶어 <br>니 얼굴 미소가 생각 <br>날 것 같아 날 것 같아 <br>날 것 같아서 <br>보고 싶어 보고 싶어 <br>니 목소리 <br>들릴 것 같아 들릴 것 같아 <br>들릴 것 같아서 <br>보고 싶어 보고 싶어 <br>걷다 멈춰 돌아보다 <br>본 것 같아 본 것 같아 <br>본 것 같아서 <br>뒤돌아서 널 찾아 <br>아직도 그 자리잖아 <br>걸어 걷다 걸어 <br>버스 정거장에 올때면 <br>꼭 너의 뒷모습보며 <br>잘가라 손 흔들어 <br>널 보냈었지 <br>나 항상 뒷모습보며 <br>나도 발걸음을 옮겼어 <br>이젠 뒷모습 못 봐 <br>나는 못 갔어 <br>걷고 싶어 걷고 싶어 <br>걷고 싶어서 <br>너 없어도 너 없어도 <br>갈 수 있을줄 알았어 <br>걷고 싶어 걷고 싶어 <br>걷고 싶어서 <br>너의 모습 너의 모습 <br>지워버리고 <br>생각날까 생각날까 <br>생각날까봐 <br>걷고 또 걷고 또 걸어 <br>널 앞지를 때까지도 <br>걷고 또 걷고 또 걸어 <br>걷고 또 걸어 <br>내 뒤에 널 둘 때까지 <br>걷고 또 걸어 <br>이제 그만 걸어 <br>]]></content><category term="감성민" label="감성민"/><category term="혼자서 걷다" label="혼자서 걷다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/전기장판/눈사람이나__만들어야지/</id><title>전기장판 - 눈사람이나 만들어야지 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%84%EA%B8%B0%EC%9E%A5%ED%8C%90/%EB%88%88%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C%EC%9D%B4%EB%82%98__%EB%A7%8C%EB%93%A4%EC%96%B4%EC%95%BC%EC%A7%80/" title="전기장판 - 눈사람이나 만들어야지 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랫동안 눈을 감고 있었는데 <br>잠이 오지 않네요 <br>사르르 사르르 <br>눈이 오는 소리 들려 <br>급히 옷을 입고 <br>문 앞 계단 앞에 앉았죠 <br>차가워진 벽 위로 나를 기대고 <br>잠시 이 새벽을 담아요 <br>스르르 스르르 <br>나도 몰래 잠들었다 <br>나를 깨운 건 <br>여전히 익숙한 너의 번호 <br>오랜만이네 그 동안 잘 지냈을까 <br>궁금해서 전활 받고 싶어지지만 <br>애써 이 마음 꾹꾹 눌러서 <br>눈사람이나 만들어야지 <br>아침이 오고 또 다시 밤이 와도 <br>너는 그대로구나 <br>파르르 파르르 눈물이 떨어져도 <br>굳어버리는 그런 날 이라서 <br>오랜만이야 그 동안 잘 지냈었니 <br>궁금해서 전활 걸고 싶어지지만 <br>애써 이 마음 꾹꾹 눌러서 <br>눈사람이나 만들어야지 <br>오랜만이네 그 동안 잘 지냈을까 <br>궁금해서 전활 걸고 <br>싶어지지만 <br>애써 이 마음 꾹꾹 눌러서 <br>눈사람이나 만들어야지 <br>애써 이 마음 꾹꾹 눌러서 <br>]]></content><category term="전기장판" label="전기장판"/><category term="눈사람이나 만들어야지" label="눈사람이나 만들어야지"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/브리튼_치즈/미련/</id><title>브리튼 치즈 - 미련 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%B8%8C%EB%A6%AC%ED%8A%BC_%EC%B9%98%EC%A6%88/%EB%AF%B8%EB%A0%A8/" title="브리튼 치즈 - 미련 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잊으려 노력하고 <br>일부러 널 더 욕해도 <br>잠시 또 니 생각에 잠겨 <br>아직도 모르겠어 <br>어디서 잘못됐는지 <br>참고 참던 눈물이 흘러 <br>그렇게 울다 보면 <br>나도 모르게 <br>어느새 잠들어 있고 <br>그렇게 하루하루가 <br>지나고 <br>같은 반복 끝에 <br>이젠 알겠더라 <br>너 때문에 잠도 뒤척이고 <br>너 땜에 입맛도 없던 것도 <br>그냥 미련이더라 <br>너 없인 못살 것 같던 것도 <br>너 말고 관심 없었던 것도 <br>아무 소용 없더라 <br>그때 잠시더라 <br>하루는 느닷없이 <br>니 생각이 나 <br>죽을 것만 같았는데 <br>이제는 니가 <br>생각이 날 때면 <br>힘들었던 지난 시간이 <br>후회가 돼 <br>너 때문에 잠도 뒤척이고 <br>너 땜에 입맛도 없던 것도 <br>그냥 미련이더라 <br>너 없인 못살 것 같던 것도 <br>너 말고 관심 없었던 것도 <br>아무 소용 없더라 <br>그때 잠시 더라 <br>네게 밟힌 상처와 <br>네게 흘린 눈물은 <br>아무도 알아주지못해 <br>네게 날린 시간과 <br>네게 남은 미련은 <br>아무 의미가 없어 <br>미련 없어 <br>]]></content><category term="브리튼 치즈" label="브리튼 치즈"/><category term="미련" label="미련"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/단야/마지막_남자_2/</id><title>단야 - 마지막 남자 2 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%A8%EC%95%BC/%EB%A7%88%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%89_%EB%82%A8%EC%9E%90_2/" title="단야 - 마지막 남자 2 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[첫 번째 남자 두 번째 남자 <br>모두가 야속한 남자 <br>첫 번째 남자는 철없던 시절 <br>옆집에 살았던 순이네 오빠 <br>웃는 모습이 너무 예뻤던 <br>한없이 순진한 오빠 <br>두 번째 남자는 사회 나와서 <br>소개팅 나가서 만났던 남자 <br>너만 사랑해 듬직한 말에 <br>더없이 멋졌던 남자 <br>사랑은 거짓말 약속도 없던 일 <br>변함없는 내 사랑에 <br>아픔만 두고 간 사랑 <br>첫 번째 남자 두 번째 남자 <br>모두가 야속한 남자 <br>첫 번째 남자 두 번째 남자 <br>모두가 야속한 남자 <br>세 번째 남자는 운명 같았던 <br>한눈에 반했던 이상형 남자 <br>좋아해놓고 마음 변해서 <br>바람 핀 얄미운 남자 <br>마지막 남자는 지금 이 순간 <br>가슴을 흔드는 내 곁의 남자 <br>아침밥을 같이 하고픈 <br>내 인생 운명의 남자 <br>사랑은 거짓말 약속도 없던 일 <br>변함없는 내 사랑을 <br>끝까지 지켜줄 사랑 <br>바로 이 남자 마지막 남자 <br>내 인생 최고의 남자 <br>사랑은 거짓말 알고도 속는 일 <br>마지막은 바로 당신 <br>너에게 속아줄게 <br>바로 이 남자 마지막 남자 <br>내 인생 최고의 남자 <br>바로 이 남자 마지막 남자 <br>내 인생 최고의 남자 <br>]]></content><category term="단야" label="단야"/><category term="마지막 남자 2" label="마지막 남자 2"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/정승환/옛사랑_지방방위대_디저트맨_기쁘다_트리_오셨네/</id><title>정승환 - 옛사랑 (지방방위대 디저트맨, 기쁘다 트리 오셨네) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A0%95%EC%8A%B9%ED%99%98/%EC%98%9B%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_%EC%A7%80%EB%B0%A9%EB%B0%A9%EC%9C%84%EB%8C%80_%EB%94%94%EC%A0%80%ED%8A%B8%EB%A7%A8_%EA%B8%B0%EC%81%98%EB%8B%A4_%ED%8A%B8%EB%A6%AC_%EC%98%A4%EC%85%A8%EB%84%A4/" title="정승환 - 옛사랑 (지방방위대 디저트맨, 기쁘다 트리 오셨네) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[남들도 모르게 서성이다 울었지 <br>지나온 일들이 가슴에 사무쳐 <br>텅빈 하늘 위 불빛들 켜져가며 <br>옛사랑 그 이름 아껴 불러보네 <br>찬바람 불어와 옷깃을 여미우다 <br>후회가 또 화가 난 눈물이 흐르네 <br>누가 물어도 아플것 같지 않던 <br>지나온 내 모습 모두 거짓인가 <br>이젠 그리운 것은 <br>그리운대로 내 맘에 둘꺼야 <br>그대 생각이 나면 <br>생각난대로 내버려 두듯이 <br>흰눈 내리면 들판에 서성이다 <br>옛사랑 생각에 그 길 찾아가지 <br>광화문 거리 흰 눈에 덮여가고 <br>하얀 눈 하늘 높이 자꾸 올라가네 <br>이젠 그리운 것은 <br>그리운대로 내 맘에 둘꺼야 <br>그대 생각이 나면 <br>생각난대로 내버려 두듯이 <br>사람이란게 지겨울 때가 있지 <br>내 맘에 고독이 너무 흘러 넘쳐 <br>눈 녹은 봄 날 푸르른 잎새 위에 <br>옛사랑 그대 모습 영원 속에 있네 <br>하얀 눈 하늘 높이 자꾸 올라가네 <br>하얀 눈 하늘 높이 자꾸 올라가네 <br>]]></content><category term="정승환" label="정승환"/><category term="옛사랑 (지방방위대 디저트맨, 기쁘다 트리 오셨네)" label="옛사랑 (지방방위대 디저트맨, 기쁘다 트리 오셨네)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동우_LEE_DONG_WOO/What_A_Wonderful_Cane_English_Ver/</id><title>이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - What A Wonderful Cane (English Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_LEE_DONG_WOO/What_A_Wonderful_Cane_English_Ver/" title="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - What A Wonderful Cane (English Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[A black and white man <br>in a rainbow color world <br>Who has the most fun of them all <br>I see them running wild <br>Baby lions and clowns <br>I run my circus all over the town <br>No limit just imagine <br>Pink cotton candy dolphins in the sky <br>Conductor is ready <br>Alligator get steady <br>Let’s go out and bring them around <br>It’s a wonderful day <br>what a wonderful cane <br>Skip and a step <br>It takes me and you <br>anywhere and everywhere <br>Hey just whistle along you’re invited <br>Let’s cheer for those in the busy race <br>Another good day <br>With the sky full of ray <br>Let’s take a minute feel it shine <br>We’ll take it slowly step by step <br>No reason to rush take a break <br>I’ve been around the world <br>And I’ve seen so many things <br>Silver butterflies and dancing chimps <br>My favorite place <br>You know where to be <br>Where the ducks do their turns and tricks <br>Oh yeah <br>No limit just imagine <br>Pink cotton candy dolphins in the sky <br>Conductor is ready <br>Alligator get steady <br>Let’s go out and bring them around <br>It’s a wonderful day <br>what a wonderful cane <br>Skip and a step <br>It takes me and you <br>anywhere and everywhere <br>Hey just whistle along you’re invited <br>Let’s cheer for those in the busy race <br>Another good day <br>With the sky full of ray <br>Let’s take a minute feel it shine <br>We’ll take it slowly step by step <br>No reason to rush is there <br>Close your eyes and let go <br>You’ve done it before dream on <br>It’s all in your mind <br>Can’t you see the colors <br>I painted for you yeah <br>It’s a wonderful day <br>what a wonderful cane <br>Skip and a step <br>It takes me and you anywhere <br>and everywhere <br>Hey Just whistle along you’re invited <br>Cheer cause you’re in the race yeah <br>Another good day <br>With the sky full of ray <br>Let’s take a minute before it rains <br>Save up the golden sunshine <br>And hit the dance floor <br>Let them all join in <br>With my happy snappy cane <br>It’s another wonderful day <br>]]></content><category term="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)" label="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)"/><category term="What A Wonderful Cane (English Ver.)" label="What A Wonderful Cane (English Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동우_LEE_DONG_WOO/Step_It_Up/</id><title>이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - Step It Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_LEE_DONG_WOO/Step_It_Up/" title="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - Step It Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don’t you lie I see you <br>Don’t look back run ahead <br>Your excuses they don’t make sense at all <br>It’s tough but hey here’s a hand <br>and a shoulder for you <br>You can’t just sit around <br>Run ‘til your heart is about to burst <br>You’re nearly there <br>Keep calm and step it up <br>And the sky <br>is your limit don’t slow yourself down <br>In the race you are all by yourself <br>Have faith cause no matter what <br>I’ll be there for you <br>Don’t be nobody other than yourself <br>you’re fine <br>You’ll make it there before you know it <br>oh Let your heart take the lead <br>it’s getting better with time <br>you’ll see <br>what I mean <br>Keep calm and step it up <br>I’m staring at the same blue sky as you <br>I feel your pain <br>Keep calm and step it up <br>Your life isn’t yours <br>Let it roll and just go with it <br>Why are you shy <br>Don’t be afraid to fly high <br>And the sky <br>is your limit don’t Slow it down <br>You’ll be fine get on up <br>Don’t be nobody other than <br>yourself you’re fine <br>You’ll make it there before you know it <br>oh Let your heart take the lead <br>it’s getting better with time you’ll see <br>what I mean <br>Keep calm and step it up <br>]]></content><category term="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)" label="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)"/><category term="Step It Up" label="Step It Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동우_LEE_DONG_WOO/Wanna_Be_Your_Guitar/</id><title>이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - Wanna Be Your Guitar - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_LEE_DONG_WOO/Wanna_Be_Your_Guitar/" title="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - Wanna Be Your Guitar - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잘려지고 긁히고 얻어맞고 <br>그렇게 태어난 예쁜 기타 <br>마음 울리는 소리 <br>행복을 주는 소리 <br>그대 품에 안기면 <br>더 맑고 사랑스러운 소리 <br>잘리고 다시 긁혀지고 <br>얻어맞고 또 넘어졌어 <br>기타가 되고 싶어 <br>그대 품에 안기고 싶어 <br>노래 부르며 살고 싶어 Oh yes <br>Oh very good shape <br>호리호리한 옆구리는 <br>비욘세 보다 Sexy 해 <br>바라만 봐도 찌릿 <br>손끝만 닿아도 와락 <br>기타가 될 거야 <br>그대의 품에 안길 거야 <br>슬플 때나 또 기쁠 때도 <br>우울하고 화가 날 때도 <br>그냥 기타처럼 울어 <br>눈물에 노래를 실어 <br>4분의 4박자 OK <br>그대 품에서 그렇게 <br>나는 노래하는 기타 <br>]]></content><category term="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)" label="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)"/><category term="Wanna Be Your Guitar" label="Wanna Be Your Guitar"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이동우_LEE_DONG_WOO/Cheers_To_Nothing/</id><title>이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - Cheers To Nothing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-18T18:53:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-18T18:53:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%B0_LEE_DONG_WOO/Cheers_To_Nothing/" title="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO) - Cheers To Nothing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아침에는 해 뜨고 저녁엔 달뜨고 <br>집도 차도 없어도 Cheers to nothing <br>여름엔 비 오고 겨울엔 눈이 오고 <br>돈도 벗도 없어도 Cheers to nothing <br>지루한 밤잠은 안 오고 <br>나는 또 한 잔 마시고 <br>술 취해 바라본 밤하늘은 깜깜 <br>개미들도 바쁘고 <br>새들도 하늘을 나네 <br>뛰고 날 수 없어도 Cheers to nothing <br>지루한 밤 또다시 오고 <br>술도 없어 물만 마시고 <br>배고파 바라본 밤하늘은 깜깜 <br>여자친구 내게 준 반지 달라 하네 <br>I say goodbye <br>Cool 하게 던지고 집에 와 울었네 <br>지루한 밤 지나고 <br>더 지루한 낮이 오네 <br>밥 없고 힘없어도 Cheers to nothing <br>할 일 없는 내일 위해 Cheers to nothing <br>]]></content><category term="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)" label="이동우 (LEE DONG WOO)"/><category term="Cheers To Nothing" label="Cheers To Nothing"/></entry></feed>