<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:45+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/You_Got_The_Silver/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - You Got The Silver - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/You_Got_The_Silver/" title="The Rolling Stones - You Got The Silver - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["You Got The Silver" <br><br>Hey babe, what's in your eyes? <br>I saw them flashing like airplane lights <br>You fill my cup, babe, that's for sure <br>I must come back for a little more <br>You got my heart you got my soul <br>You got the silver you got the gold <br>You got the diamonds from the mine <br>Well that's all right, it'll buy some time <br>Tell me, honey, what will I do <br>When I'm hungry and thirsty too <br>Feeling foolish (and that's for sure) <br>Just waiting here at your kitchen door? <br>Hey baby, what's in your eyes? <br>Is that the diamonds from the mine? <br>What's that laughing in your smile? <br>I don't care, no, I don't care <br>Oh babe, you got my soul <br>You got the silver you got the gold <br>If that's your love, just leave me blind <br>I don't care, no, that's no big surprise]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="You Got The Silver" label="You Got The Silver"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Midnight_Rambler/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Midnight Rambler - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Midnight_Rambler/" title="The Rolling Stones - Midnight Rambler - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Midnight Rambler" <br><br>Did you hear about the midnight rambler <br>Everybody got to go <br>Did you hear about the midnight rambler <br>The one that shut the kitchen door <br>He don't give a hoot of warning <br>Wrapped up in a black cat cloak <br>He don't go in the light of the morning <br>He split the time the cock'rel crows <br>Talkin' about the midnight gambler <br>The one you never seen before <br>Talkin' about the midnight gambler <br>Did you see him jump the garden wall <br>Sighin' down the wind so sad <br>Listen and you'll hear him moan <br>Talkin' about the midnight gambler <br>Everybody got to go <br>Did you hear about the midnight rambler <br>Well, honey, it's no rock 'n' roll show <br>Well, I'm talkin' about the midnight gambler <br>Yeah, the one you never seen before <br>[ad lib] <br>Well you heard about the Boston... <br>It's not one of those <br>Well, talkin' 'bout the midnight...sh... <br>The one that closed the bedroom door <br>I'm called the hit-and-run raper in anger <br>The knife-sharpened tippie-toe... <br>Or just the shoot 'em dead, brainbell jangler <br>You know, the one you never seen before <br>So if you ever meet the midnight rambler <br>Coming down your marble hall <br>Well he's pouncing like proud black panther <br>Well, you can say I, I told you so <br>Well, don't you listen for the midnight rambler <br>Play it easy, as you go <br>I'm gonna smash down all your plate glass windows <br>Put a fist, put a fist through your steel-plated door <br>Did you hear about the midnight rambler <br>He'll leave his footprints up and down your hall <br>And did you hear about the midnight gambler <br>And did you see me make my midnight call <br>And if you ever catch the midnight rambler <br>I'll steal your mistress from under your nose <br>I'll go easy with your cold fanged anger <br>I'll stick my knife right down your throat, baby <br>And it hurts!]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Midnight Rambler" label="Midnight Rambler"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Let_It_Bleed/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Let It Bleed - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Let_It_Bleed/" title="The Rolling Stones - Let It Bleed - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Let It Bleed" <br><br>Well, we all need someone we can lean on <br>And if you want it, you can lean on me <br>Yeah, we all need someone we can lean on <br>And if you want it, you can lean on me <br>She said, "My breasts, they will always be open <br>Baby, you can rest your weary head right on me <br>And there will always be a space in my parking lot <br>When you need a little coke and sympathy" <br>Yeah, we all need someone we can dream on <br>And if you want it, baby, well you can dream on me <br>Yeah, we all need someone we can cream on <br>And if you want to, well you can cream on me <br>I was dreaming of a steel guitar engagement <br>When you drunk my health in scented jasmine tea <br>But you knifed me in my dirty filthy basement <br>With that jaded, faded, junky nurse <br>Oh what pleasant company <br>We all need someone we can feed on <br>And if you want it, well you can feed on me <br>Take my arm, take my leg, oh baby don't you take my head <br>Yeah, we all need someone we can bleed on <br>Yeah, and if you want it, baby, well you can bleed on me <br>Yeah, we all need someone we can bleed on <br>Yeah, yeah, and if you want it, baby, why don'cha bleed on me <br>All over <br>Ahh, bleed it alright, bleed it alright, bleed it alright <br>You can bleed all over me <br>Bleed it alright, bleed it alright, you can be my rider <br>You can cum all over me <br>Bleed it alright, baby, bleed it alright, bleed it alright <br>You can cum all over me <br>Bleed it alright, baby cum all over me]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Let It Bleed" label="Let It Bleed"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Live_With_Me/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Live With Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Live_With_Me/" title="The Rolling Stones - Live With Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Live With Me" <br><br>I got nasty habits, I take tea at three <br>Yes, and the meat I eat for dinner <br>Must be hung up for a week <br>My best friend, he shoots water rats <br>And feeds them to his geese <br>Don'cha think there's a place for you <br>In between the sheets? <br>Come on now, honey <br>We can build a home for three <br>Come on now, honey <br>Don't you wanna live with me? <br>And there's a score of harebrained children <br>They're all locked in the nursery <br>They got earphone heads they got dirty necks <br>They're so 20th century <br>Well they queue up for the bathroom <br>Round about 7:35 <br>Don'cha think we need a woman's touch to make it come alive? <br>You'd look good pram pushing <br>Down the high street <br>Come on now, honey <br>Don't you wanna live with me? <br>Whoa, the servants they're so helpful, dear <br>The cook she is a whore <br>Yes, the butler has a place for her <br>Behind the pantry door <br>The maid, she's French, she's got no sense <br>She's wild for Crazy Horse <br>And when she strips, the chauffeur flips <br>The footman's eyes get crossed <br>Don'cha think there's a place for us <br>Right across the street <br>Don'cha think there's a place for you, <br>In between the sheets?]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Live With Me" label="Live With Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Country_Honk/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Country Honk - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Country_Honk/" title="The Rolling Stones - Country Honk - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Country Honk" <br><br>I'm sittin' in a bar nibblin' a jar in Jackson <br>And on the street the summer sun it shines <br>There's many a bar-room queen <br>I've had in Jackson <br>But I just can't seem to drink you off my mind <br>It's the honky tonk women <br>Gimme, gimme, gimme the honky tonk blues <br>I laid a divorcee in New York City <br>I had to put up some kind of a fight <br>The lady she all dressed me up in roses <br>She blew my nose and then she blew my mind <br>It's the honky tonk women <br>Gimme, gimme, gimme the honky tonk blues <br>It's the honky tonk women <br>Gimme, gimme, gimme the honky tonk blues <br>It's the honky tonk women <br>Gimme, gimme, gimme thse honky tonk blues]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Country Honk" label="Country Honk"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Love_In_Vain/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Love In Vain - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Love_In_Vain/" title="The Rolling Stones - Love In Vain - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Love In Vain" <br><br>Well I followed her to the station <br>With a suitcase in my hand <br>Yeah, I followed her to the station <br>With a suitcase in my hand <br>Whoa, it's hard to tell, it's hard to tell <br>When all your love's in vain <br>When the train come in the station <br>I looked her in the eye <br>Well the train come in the station <br>And I looked her in the eye <br>Whoa, I felt so sad so lonesome <br>That I could not help but cry <br>When the train left the station <br>It had two lights on behind <br>Yeah, when the train left the station <br>It had two lights on behind <br>Whoa, the blue light was my baby <br>And the red light was my mind <br>All my love was in vain <br>All my love's in vain]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Love In Vain" label="Love In Vain"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Gimme_Shelter/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Gimme Shelter - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Gimme_Shelter/" title="The Rolling Stones - Gimme Shelter - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Gimme Shelter" <br><br>Oh, a storm is threat'ning <br>My very life today <br>If I don't get some shelter <br>Oh yeah, I'm gonna fade away <br>War, children, it's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>War, children, it's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>Ooh, see the fire is sweepin' <br>Our very street today <br>Burns like a red coal carpet <br>Mad bull lost your way <br>War, children, it's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>War, children, it's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>Rape, murder! <br>It's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>Rape, murder! <br>It's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>Rape, murder! <br>It's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>The floods is threat'ning <br>My very life today <br>Gimme, gimme shelter <br>Or I'm gonna fade away <br>War, children, it's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>It's just a shot away <br>I tell you love, sister, it's just a kiss away <br>It's just a kiss away <br>It's just a kiss away <br>It's just a kiss away <br>It's just a kiss away <br>Kiss away, kiss away]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Gimme Shelter" label="Gimme Shelter"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Salt_Of_The_Earth/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Salt Of The Earth - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Salt_Of_The_Earth/" title="The Rolling Stones - Salt Of The Earth - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Salt Of The Earth" <br><br>Let's drink to the hard working people <br>Let's drink to the lowly of birth <br>Raise your glass to the good and the evil <br>Let's drink to the salt of the earth <br>Say a prayer for the common foot soldier <br>Spare a thought for his back breaking work <br>Say a prayer for his wife and his children <br>Who burn the fires and who still till the earth <br>And when I search a faceless crowd <br>A swirling mass of gray and <br>Black and white <br>They don't look real to me <br>In fact, they look so strange <br>Raise your glass to the hard working people <br>Let's drink to the uncounted heads <br>Let's think of the wavering millions <br>Who need leading but get gamblers instead <br>Spare a thought for the stay-at-home voter <br>Empty eyes gaze at strange beauty shows <br>And a parade of the gray suited grafters <br>A choice of cancer or polio <br>And when I look in the faceless crowd <br>A swirling mass of grays and <br>Black and white <br>They don't look real to me <br>Or don't they look so strange <br>Let's drink to the hard working people <br>Let's think of the lowly of birth <br>Spare a thought for the rag taggy people <br>Let's drink to the salt of the earth <br>Let's drink to the hard working people <br>Let's drink to the salt of the earth <br>Let's drink to the two thousand million <br>Let's think of the humble of birth]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Salt Of The Earth" label="Salt Of The Earth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Factory_Girl/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Factory Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Factory_Girl/" title="The Rolling Stones - Factory Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Factory Girl" <br><br>Waiting for a girl who's got curlers in her hair <br>Waiting for a girl she has no money anywhere <br>We get buses everywhere <br>Waiting for a factory girl <br>Waiting for a girl and her knees are much too fat <br>Waiting for a girl who wears scarves instead of hats <br>Her zipper's broken down the back <br>Waiting for a factory girl <br>Waiting for a girl and she gets me into fights <br>Waiting for a girl we get drunk on Friday night <br>She's a sight for sore eyes <br>Waiting for a factory girl <br>Waiting for a girl and she's got stains all down her dress <br>Waiting for a girl and my feet are getting wet <br>She ain't come out yet <br>Waiting for a factory girl]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Factory Girl" label="Factory Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Stray_Cat_Blues/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Stray Cat Blues - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Stray_Cat_Blues/" title="The Rolling Stones - Stray Cat Blues - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Stray Cat Blues" <br><br>I hear the click-clack of your feet on the stairs <br>I know you're no scare-eyed honey. <br>There'll be a feast if you just come upstairs <br>But it's no hanging matter <br>It's no capital crime <br>I can see that you're fifteen years old <br>No I don't want your I.D. <br>And I can see that you're so far from home <br>But it's no hanging matter <br>It's no capital crime <br>Oh yeah, you're a strange stray cat <br>Oh yeah, don'tcha scratch like that <br>Oh yeah, you're a strange stray cat <br>I bet, bet your mama don't know you scream like that <br>I bet your mother don't know you can spit like that. <br>You look so weird and you're so far from home <br>But you don't really miss your mother <br>Don't look so scared I'm no mad-brained bear <br>But it's no hanging matter <br>It's no capital crime <br>Oh, yeah <br>Woo! <br>I bet your mama don't know that you scatch like that <br>I bet she don't know you can bite like that. <br>You say you got a friend, that she's wilder than you <br>Why don't you bring her upstairs <br>If she's so wild then she can join in too <br>It's no hanging matter <br>It's no capital crime <br>Oh yeah, you're a strange stray cat <br>Oh yeah, don'tcha scratch like that <br>Oh yeah, you're a strange stray cat <br>I bet you mama don't know you can bite like that <br>I'll bet she never saw you scratch my back]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Stray Cat Blues" label="Stray Cat Blues"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Prodigal_Son/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Prodigal Son - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Prodigal_Son/" title="The Rolling Stones - Prodigal Son - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Prodigal Son" <br><br>Well a poor boy took his father's bread and started down the road <br>Started down the road <br>Took all he had and started down the road <br>Going out in this world, where God only knows <br>And that'll be the way to get along <br>Well poor boy spent all he had, famine come in the land <br>Famine come in the land <br>Spent all he had and famine come in the land <br>Said, "I believe I'll go and hire me to some man" <br>And that'll be the way I'll get along <br>Well, man said, "I'll give you a job for to feed my swine <br>For to feed my swine <br>I'll give you a job for to feed my swine" <br>Boy stood there and hung his head and cried <br>Cause that is no way to get along <br>Said, "I believe I'll ride, believe I'll go back home <br>Believe I'll go back home <br>Believe I'll ride, believe I'll go back home <br>Or down the road as far as I can go" <br>And that'll be the way to get along <br>Well, father said, "See my son coming home to me <br>Coming home to me" <br>Father ran and fell down on his knees <br>Said, "Sing and praise, Lord have mercy on me" <br>Mercy <br>Oh poor boy stood there, hung his head and cried <br>Hung his head and cried <br>Poor boy stood and hung his head and cried <br>Said, "Father will you look on me as a child?" <br>Yeah <br>Well father said, "Eldest son, kill the fatted calf, <br>Call the family round <br>Kill that calf and call the family round <br>My son was lost but now he is found <br>Cause that's the way for us to get along" <br>Hey]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Prodigal Son" label="Prodigal Son"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Street_Fighting_Man/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Street Fighting Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Street_Fighting_Man/" title="The Rolling Stones - Street Fighting Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Street Fighting Man" <br><br>Ev'rywhere I hear the sound of marching, charging feet, boy <br>Cause summer's here and the time is right for fighting in the street, boy <br>But what can a poor boy do <br>Except to sing for a rock 'n' roll band <br>Cause in sleepy London town <br>There's just no place for a street fighting man <br>No <br>Hey! Think the time is right for a palace revolution <br>But where I live the game to play is compromise solution <br>Well, then what can a poor boy do <br>Except to sing for a rock 'n' roll band <br>'Cause in sleepy London town <br>There's no place for a street fighting man <br>No <br>Hey! Said my name is called disturbance <br>I'll shout and scream, I'll kill the king, I'll rail at all his servants <br>Well, what can a poor boy do <br>Except to sing for a rock 'n' roll band <br>Cause in sleepy London town <br>There's no place for a street fighting man <br>No]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Street Fighting Man" label="Street Fighting Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Jigsaw_Puzzle/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Jigsaw Puzzle - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Jigsaw_Puzzle/" title="The Rolling Stones - Jigsaw Puzzle - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Jig-Saw Puzzle" <br><br>There's a tramp sittin' on my doorstep <br>Tryin' to waste his time <br>With his methylated sandwich <br>He's a walking clothesline <br>And here comes the bishop's daughter <br>On the other side <br>She looks a trifle jealous <br>She's been an outcast all her life <br>Me, I'm waiting so patiently <br>Lying on the floor <br>I'm just trying to do my jig-saw puzzle <br>Before it rains anymore <br>Oh the gangster looks so fright'ning <br>With his luger in his hand <br>When he gets home to his children <br>He's a family man <br>But when it comes to the nitty-gritty <br>He can shove in his knife <br>Yes he really looks quite religious <br>He's been an outlaw all his life <br>Me, I'm waiting so patiently <br>Lying on the floor <br>I'm just trying to do this jig-saw puzzle <br>Before it rains anymore <br>Me, I'm waiting so patiently <br>Lying on the floor <br>I'm just trying to do this jig-saw puzzle <br>Before it rains anymore <br>Oh the singer, he looks angry <br>At being thrown to the lions <br>And the bass player, he looks nervous <br>About the girls outside <br>And the drummer, he's so shattered <br>Trying to keep up time <br>And the guitar players look damaged <br>They've been outcasts all thier lives <br>Me, I'm waiting so patiently <br>Lying on the floor <br>I'm just trying to do this jig-saw puzzle <br>Before it rains anymore <br>Oh, there's twenty-thousand grandmas <br>Wave their hankies in the air <br>All burning up their pensions <br>And shouting, "It's not fair!" <br>There's a regiment of soldiers <br>Standing looking on <br>And the queen is bravely shouting, <br>"What the hell is going on?" <br>With a blood-curdling "tally-ho" <br>She charged into the ranks <br>And blessed all those grandmas who <br>With their dying breaths screamed, "Thanks!" <br>Me, I'm just waiting so patiently <br>With my woman on the floor <br>We're just trying to do this jig-saw puzzle <br>Before it rains anymore]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Jigsaw Puzzle" label="Jigsaw Puzzle"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Parachute_Woman/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Parachute Woman - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Parachute_Woman/" title="The Rolling Stones - Parachute Woman - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Parachute Woman" <br><br>Parachute woman, land on me tonight <br>Parachute woman, land on me tonight <br>I'll break big in New Orleans <br>And I'll overspill in Caroline <br>Parachute woman, join me for a ride <br>Parachute woman, join me for a ride <br>I'll make my play in Dallas <br>And get hot again in half the time <br>Parachute woman, will you blow me out? <br>Parachute woman, will you blow me out? <br>Well, my heavy throbbers itchin' <br>Just to lay a solid rhythm down]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Parachute Woman" label="Parachute Woman"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Dear_Doctor/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Dear Doctor - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Dear_Doctor/" title="The Rolling Stones - Dear Doctor - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Dear Doctor" <br><br>Oh help me, please doctor, I'm damaged <br>There's a pain where there once was a heart <br>It's sleepin, it's a beatin' <br>Can't ya please tear it out, and preserve it <br>Right there in that jar? <br>Oh help me, please mama, I'm sick'ning <br>It's today that's the day of the plunge <br>Oh the gal I'm to marry <br>Is a bow-legged sow <br>I've been soakin' up drink like a sponge <br>"Don't ya worry, get dressed," cried my mother <br>As she plied me with bourbon so sour <br>Pull your socks up, put your suit on <br>Comb your long hair down, <br>For you will be wed in the hour <br>So help me, please doctor, I'm damaged <br>There's a pain where there once was a heart <br>I'm sleepin, it's a beatin' <br>Can't ya please take it out, and preserve it <br>Right there in that jar? <br>Oh help me, please doctor, I'm damaged <br>There's a pain where there once was a heart <br>It's sleepin, it's a beatin' <br>Can't ya please tear it out, and preserve it <br>Right there in that jar? <br>I was tremblin', as I put on my jacket <br>It had creases as sharp as a knife <br>I put the ring in my pocket <br>But there was a note <br>And my heart it jumped into my mouth <br>It read, "Darlin', I'm sorry to hurt you. <br>But I have no courage to speak to your face. <br>But I'm down in Virginia with your cousin Lou <br>There be no wedding today." <br>So help me, please doctor, I'm damaged <br>You can put back my heart in its hole <br>Oh mama, I'm cryin' <br>Tears of relief <br>And my pulse is now under control]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Dear Doctor" label="Dear Doctor"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/No_Expectations/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - No Expectations - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/No_Expectations/" title="The Rolling Stones - No Expectations - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["No Expectations" <br><br>Take me to the station <br>And put me on a train <br>I've got no expectations <br>To pass through here again <br>Once I was a rich man <br>Now I am so poor <br>But never in my sweet short life <br>Have I felt like this before <br>You heart is like a diamond <br>You throw your pearls at swine <br>And as I watch you leaving me <br>You pack my peace of mind <br>Our love was like the water <br>That splashes on a stone <br>Our love is like our music <br>Its here, and then its gone <br>So take me to the airport <br>And put me on a plane <br>I got no expectations <br>To pass through here again]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="No Expectations" label="No Expectations"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Sympathy_For_The_Devil/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Sympathy For The Devil - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Sympathy_For_The_Devil/" title="The Rolling Stones - Sympathy For The Devil - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Sympathy For The Devil" <br><br>Please allow me to introduce myself <br>I'm a man of wealth and taste <br>I've been around for a long, long year <br>Stole many a man's soul and faith <br><br>And I was 'round when Jesus Christ <br>Had his moment of doubt and pain <br>Made damn sure that Pilate <br>Washed his hands and sealed his fate <br><br>Pleased to meet you <br>Hope you guess my name <br>But what's puzzling you <br>Is the nature of my game <br><br>I stuck around St. Petersburg <br>When I saw it was a time for a change <br>Killed the Tsar and his ministers <br>Anastasia screamed in vain <br><br>I rode a tank <br>Held a general's rank <br>When the blitzkrieg raged <br>And the bodies stank <br><br>Pleased to meet you <br>Hope you guess my name, oh yeah <br>Ah, what's puzzling you <br>Is the nature of my game, oh yeah <br><br>I watched with glee <br>While your kings and queens <br>Fought for ten decades <br>For the gods they made <br><br>I shouted out, <br>"Who killed the Kennedys?" <br>When after all <br>It was you and me <br><br>Let me please introduce myself <br>I'm a man of wealth and taste <br>And I laid traps for troubadours <br>Who get killed before they reached Bombay <br><br>Pleased to meet you <br>Hope you guessed my name, oh yeah <br>But what's puzzling you <br>Is the nature of my game, oh yeah, get down, baby <br><br>Pleased to meet you <br>Hope you guessed my name, oh yeah <br>But what's confusing you <br>Is just the nature of my game <br><br>Just as every cop is a criminal <br>And all the sinners saints <br>As heads is tails <br>Just call me Lucifer <br><br>Cause I'm in need of some restraint <br>So if you meet me <br>Have some courtesy <br>Have some sympathy, and some taste <br><br>Use all your well-learned politesse <br>Or I'll lay your soul to waste, um yeah <br>Pleased to meet you <br>Hope you guessed my name, um yeah <br><br>But what's puzzling you <br>Is the nature of my game, um mean it, get down <br>Woo, who <br>Oh yeah, get on down <br><br>Oh yeah <br>Oh yeah! <br>Tell me baby, what's my name <br>Tell me honey, can ya guess my name <br><br>Tell me baby, what's my name <br>I tell you one time, you're to blame <br>Ooo, who <br>Ooo, who <br><br>Ooo, who <br>Ooo, who, who <br>Ooo, who, who <br>Ooo, who, who <br><br>Ooo, who, who <br>Oh, yeah <br>What's my name <br>Tell me, baby, what's my name <br><br>Tell me, sweetie, what's my name <br>Ooo, who, who <br>Ooo, who, who <br>Ooo, who, who <br><br>Ooo, who, who <br>Ooo, who, who <br>Ooo, who, who <br>Ooo, who, who <br><br>Oh, yeah]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Sympathy For The Devil" label="Sympathy For The Devil"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/On_With_The_Show/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - On With The Show - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/On_With_The_Show/" title="The Rolling Stones - On With The Show - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["On With The Show" <br><br>Good evening one and all, we're all so glad to see you here <br>We'll play your favorite songs while you're all so happy atmosphere <br>We'll start with 'Old Man River', then maybe 'Stormy Weather', too <br>I'm sure you know just what to do <br>On with the show good health to you <br><br>Please pour another glass, it's time to watch the cabaret <br>Your wife will never know that you're not really working late <br>Your hostess here is Wendy, you'll find her very friendly, too <br>And we don't care just what you do <br>On with the show good health to you <br><br>Petina, start the show at 2 o'clock <br><br>Oh, if by chance you find that you can't make it anymore <br>We'll put you in a cab and get you safely to the door <br>But we've got all the answers and we've got lovely dancers, too <br>There's nothin' else you have to do <br>On with the show good health to you <br><br>You're all such lovely people dancing, eating 'round the floor <br>But if you have to fight, please take your trouble out the door <br>For now I say with sorrow until this time tomorrow <br>We'll bid you all a find adieu <br>On with the show good health to you]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="On With The Show" label="On With The Show"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/2000_Light_Years_From_Home/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - 2000 Light Years From Home - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/2000_Light_Years_From_Home/" title="The Rolling Stones - 2000 Light Years From Home - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["2000 Light Years From Home" <br><br>Sun turnin' 'round with graceful motion <br>We're setting off with soft explosion <br>Bound for a star with fiery oceans <br>It's so very lonely, you're a hundred light years from home <br>Freezing red deserts turn to dark <br>Energy here in every part <br>It's so very lonely, you're six hundred light years from home <br>It's so very lonely, you're a thousand light years from home <br>It's so very lonely, you're a thousand light years from home <br>Bell flight fourteen you now can land <br>Seen you on Aldebaran, safe on the green desert sand <br>It's so very lonely, you're two thousand light years from home <br>It's so very lonely, you're two thousand light years from home]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="2000 Light Years From Home" label="2000 Light Years From Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Gomper/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Gomper - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Gomper/" title="The Rolling Stones - Gomper - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Gomper" <br><br>By the lake with lilly flowers <br>Wallow away the evening hours <br>To and fro she's gently gliding <br>On the glassy lake she's riding <br>She swims to the side <br>The sun sees her dried <br>The birds hover high <br>I'd stifle a cry <br>The birds hover high <br>She moans with a sigh]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Gomper" label="Gomper"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/The_Lantern/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - The Lantern - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/The_Lantern/" title="The Rolling Stones - The Lantern - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["The Lantern" <br><br>We, on our present life, <br>Knew that the stars were right. <br>That if you are the first to go, <br>You'll leave a sign to let me know, <br>Tell me so. <br>Please, carry the Lantern lights. <br>You crossed the sea of night, <br>Free from the spell of fright <br>Your cloak it is a spirit shroud. <br>You'll wake me in my sleeping hours, <br>Like a cloud. <br>So, please, carry the Lantern high. <br>Me, in my sorry plight, <br>You waiting ev'ry night. <br>My face it turns a deathly pale, <br>You're talking to me, through your veil, <br>I hear you wail. <br>So, please carry the Lantern light. <br>The servants sleep, <br>The door's are barred. <br>You hear the stopping of my heart-we never part. <br>So, please carry the Lantern high.]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="The Lantern" label="The Lantern"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Shes_A_Rainbow/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - She`s A Rainbow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Shes_A_Rainbow/" title="The Rolling Stones - She`s A Rainbow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["She's A Rainbow" <br><br>She comes in colors ev'rywhere; <br>She combs her hair <br>She's like a rainbow <br>Coming, colors in the air <br>Oh, everywhere <br>She comes in colors <br>She comes in colors ev'rywhere; <br>She combs her hair <br>She's like a rainbow <br>Coming, colors in the air <br>Oh, everywhere <br>She comes in colors <br>Have you seen her dressed in blue? <br>See the sky in front of you <br>And her face is like a sail <br>Speck of white so fair and pale <br>Have you seen a lady fairer? <br>She comes in colors ev'rywhere; <br>She combs her hair <br>She's like a rainbow <br>Coming, colors in the air <br>Oh, everywhere <br>She comes in colors <br>Have you seen her all in gold? <br>Like a queen in days of old <br>She shoots her colors all around <br>Like a sunset going down <br>Have you seen a lady fairer? <br>She comes in colors ev'rywhere; <br>She combs her hair <br>She's like a rainbow <br>Coming, colors in the air <br>Oh, everywhere <br>She comes in colors <br>She's like a rainbow <br>Coming, colors in the air <br>Oh, everywhere <br>She comes in colors]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="She`s A Rainbow" label="She`s A Rainbow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Sing_This_All_Together_See_What_Happens/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Sing This All Together (See What Happens) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Sing_This_All_Together_See_What_Happens/" title="The Rolling Stones - Sing This All Together (See What Happens) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Sing This All Together (See What Happens)" <br><br>Why don't we sing this song all together <br>Open our minds let the pictures come <br>And if we close all our eyes together <br>Then we will see where we all come from <br>Pictures of us in the circling sun <br>Pictures of the show that we're all one]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Sing This All Together (See What Happens)" label="Sing This All Together (See What Happens)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/2000_Man/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - 2000 Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/2000_Man/" title="The Rolling Stones - 2000 Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["2000 Man" <br><br>Well, my name is a number <br>A piece of plastic film <br>And I'm growin' funny flowers <br>In my little window sill <br>Dont you know I'm a 2,000 man <br>And my kids, they just don't understand me at all <br>Well my wife still respects me <br>I really misused her <br>I am having an affair <br>With the Random computer <br>Don't you know I'm a 2,000 man <br>And my kids, they just don't understand me at all <br>Oh daddy, proud of your planet <br>Oh mummy, proud of your sun <br>Oh daddy, proud of your planet <br>Oh mummy. proud of your sun <br>Oh daddy, your brain's still flashin <br>Like it did when you were young <br>Or do you come down crashin' <br>Seeing all the things you'd done <br>All was a big put on <br>Oh daddy, proud of your planet <br>Oh mummy. proud of your sun <br>Oh daddy, proud of your planet <br>Oh mummy. proud of your sun <br>Oh daddy, proud of your planet <br>Oh mummy. proud of your sun <br>Oh daddy, proud of your planet <br>Oh mummy. proud of your sun <br>And you know who's the 2000 man <br>And your kids they just won't understand you at all]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="2000 Man" label="2000 Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/In_Another_Land/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - In Another Land - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/In_Another_Land/" title="The Rolling Stones - In Another Land - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["In Another Land" <br><br>In another land where the breeze and the <br>Trees and flowers were blue <br>I stood and held your hand. <br>And the grass grew high and the feathers floated by <br>I stood and held your hand. <br>And nobody else's hand will ever do <br>Nobody else will do <br>Then I awoke <br>Was this some kind of joke? <br>Much to my surprise <br>I opened my eyes. <br>We walked across the sand and the sea and <br>The sky and the castles were blue. <br>I stood and held your hand. <br>And the spray flew high and the feathers floated by <br>I stood and held your hand. <br>And nobody else's hand will ever do <br>Nobody else will do <br>Then I awoke <br>Was this some kind of joke? <br>Much to my surprise <br>When I opened my eyes. <br>We heard the trumpets blow and the sky <br>Turned red when I accidently said <br>That I didn't know how I came to be here <br>Not fast asleep in bed. <br>I stood and held your hand. <br>And nobody else's hand will ever do <br>Nobody else's hand <br>Then I awoke <br>Was this some kind of joke? <br>I opened my eyes. <br>Much to my surprise.]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="In Another Land" label="In Another Land"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Citadel/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Citadel - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:49:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:49:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Citadel/" title="The Rolling Stones - Citadel - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Citadel" <br><br>Men are armed shout who goes there <br>We have journeyed far from here <br>Armed with bibles make us swear <br>Candy and taffy, hope we both are well <br>Please come see me in the citadel <br>Flags are flying, dollar bills <br>Round the heights of concrete hills <br>You can see the pinnacles <br>Candy and taffy, hope we both are well <br>Please come see me in the citadel <br>In the streets are many walls <br>Hear the peasants come and crawl <br>You can hear their lovers call <br>Candy and taffy, hope we both are well <br>Please come see me in the citadel <br>Screaming people fly so fast <br>In their shiny metal cars <br>Throug the woods of steel and glass <br>Candy and taffy, hope we both are well <br>Please come see me in the citadel]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Citadel" label="Citadel"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Sing_This_All_Together/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Sing This All Together - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Sing_This_All_Together/" title="The Rolling Stones - Sing This All Together - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Sing This All Together" <br><br>Why don't we sing this song all together <br>Open our heads let the pictures come <br>And if we close all our eyes together <br>Then we will see where we all come from <br>Pictures of us through the steamy haze <br>Picture of us painted in our place <br>Why don't we sing this song all together <br>Open our heads let the pictures come <br>And if we close all our eyes together <br>Then we will see where we all come from <br>Why don't we sing this song all together <br>Open our heads let the pictures come <br>And if we close all our eyes together <br>Then we will see where we all come from <br>Pictures of us beating on our drum <br>Never stopping til the rain has come <br>Why don't we sing this song all together <br>Open our heads let the pictures come <br>And if we close all our eyes together <br>Then we will see where we all come from]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Sing This All Together" label="Sing This All Together"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Sittin_On_A_Fence_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Sittin` On A Fence (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Sittin_On_A_Fence_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Sittin` On A Fence (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Sittin' On A Fence" <br><br>Since i was young i've been very hard to please <br>And i don't know wrong from right <br>But there is one thing i could never understand <br>Some of the sick things that a girl does to a man, so <br>I'm just sittin' on a fence <br>You can say i got no sense <br>Trying to make up my mind <br>Really is too horrifying <br>So i'm sittin on a fence <br>All of my friends at school grew up and settled down <br>And they mortgaged up their lives <br>One things not said too much, but I think it's true <br>They just get married cause there's nothing else to do, so <br>I'm just sittin' on a fence <br>You can say i got no sense <br>Trying to make up my mind <br>Really is too horrifying <br>So i'm sittin on a fence <br>I'm just sittin' on a fence <br>You can say i got no sense <br>Trying to make up my mind <br>Really is too horrifying <br>So i'm sittin on a fence <br>The day can come when you get old and sick and tired of life <br>You just never realize <br>Maybe the choice you made wasn't really right <br>But you go out and you don't come back at night, so <br>i'm just sittin' on a fence <br>You can say i got no sense <br>Trying to make up my mind <br>Really is too horrifying <br>So i'm sittin on a fence]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Sittin` On A Fence (Remastered / Mono)" label="Sittin` On A Fence (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Ride_On_Baby_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Ride On, Baby (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Ride_On_Baby_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Ride On, Baby (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Ride On, Baby" <br><br>A smile on your face <br>But not in your eyes <br>You're looking through me <br>You don't feel it inside <br>Get out and ride on, baby, ride on, baby <br>Ride on, baby, ride on, baby <br>I could pick your face out in an FBI file <br>You may look pretty but I can't say the same for your mind <br>Ah ah ah <br>You walk up to me <br>And try to look shy <br>The red round your eyes <br>Says that you ain't a child <br>Get out and ride on, baby, ride on, baby <br>Ride on, baby, ride on, baby <br>Well i've seen your face in a trashy magazine <br>You know where you're going but I don't like the places you've been <br>Ah ah ah <br>Get out and ride on, baby, ride on, baby <br>Ride on, baby, ride on, baby <br>I can pick your face out from the front or behind <br>You may look pretty but I can't say the same for your mind <br>Ah ah ah <br>Laugh it a bit <br>Give it a try <br>If i'm not impressed <br>You can still cry <br>Get out and ride on, baby, ride on, baby <br>Ride on, baby, ride on, baby <br>By the time your thirty gonna look sixty-five <br>You won't look pretty and your friends will have kissed you goodbye <br>Ride on, baby <br>Ride on, baby...]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Ride On, Baby (Remastered / Mono)" label="Ride On, Baby (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Take_It_Or_Leave_It_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Take It Or Leave It (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Take_It_Or_Leave_It_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Take It Or Leave It (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Take It Or Leave It" <br><br>You can turn off and on more times <br>than a flashin' neon sign. <br>When you want you're bad <br>But you can be so kind <br>Just take it or leave it <br>Don't tell your friend <br>Just what you're gonna do now <br>You take it or leave it, it's just my life <br>There've been times when you tried <br>Makin' eyes at all my so called friends <br>Then you go, now you're back <br>But you can be so kind <br>Just take it or leave it <br>Don't tell your friend <br>Just what you're gonna do now <br>You take it or leave it, it's just my life <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la <br>I'm sick and tired of the smile that you give <br>When you don't come home at night <br>You said you'd call, that's a lie <br>But you could be so kind <br>Just take it or leave it <br>Don't tell your friend <br>Just what you're gonna do now <br>You take it or leave it, it's just my life <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Take It Or Leave It (Remastered / Mono)" label="Take It Or Leave It (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Mothers_Little_Helper_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Mother`s Little Helper (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Mothers_Little_Helper_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Mother`s Little Helper (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Mother's Little Helper" <br><br>What a drag it is getting old <br>"Kids are different today," <br>I hear ev'ry mother say <br>Mother needs something today to calm her down <br>And though she's not really ill <br>There's a little yellow pill <br>She goes running for the shelter of a mother's little helper <br>And it helps her on her way, gets her through her busy day <br>"Things are different today," <br>I hear ev'ry mother say <br>Cooking fresh food for a husband's just a drag <br>So she buys an instant cake and she burns her frozen steak <br>And goes running for the shelter of a mother's little helper <br>And two help her on her way, get her through her busy day <br>Doctor please, some more of these <br>Outside the door, she took four more <br>What a drag it is getting old <br>"Men just aren't the same today" <br>I hear ev'ry mother say <br>They just don't appreciate that you get tired <br>They're so hard to satisfy, You can tranquilize your mind <br>So go running for the shelter of a mother's little helper <br>And four help you through the night, help to minimize your plight <br>Doctor please, some more of these <br>Outside the door, she took four more <br>What a drag it is getting old <br>"Life's just much too hard today," <br>I hear ev'ry mother say <br>The pusuit of happiness just seems a bore <br>And if you take more of those, you will get an overdose <br>No more running for the shelter of a mother's little helper <br>They just helped you on your way, through your busy dying day]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Mother`s Little Helper (Remastered / Mono)" label="Mother`s Little Helper (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Please_Go_Home_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Please Go Home (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Please_Go_Home_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Please Go Home (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Please Go Home" <br><br>Please go home <br>Please go home <br>Well maybe I'm talkin to fast <br>But I won't be the first or the last <br>In the sea of the thousand you cast <br>C'mon please go home <br>I don't have to ask what you do <br>I just have to look to get you <br>Means nothing to me to get through <br>Please go home <br>I don't want to be on my own <br>Cause I can't talk much better alone <br>But I don't have to ring like a phone <br>Won't you please go home <br>Please go home <br>In some early part of your days <br>You were told of the devious ways <br>That you thought you could get without pay <br>Won't you please go home <br>You reach a state of your mind <br>Where it's madness to look and to find <br>Your false affections so kind <br>Please go home <br>Won't you please go home]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Please Go Home (Remastered / Mono)" label="Please Go Home (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Back_Street_Girl_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Back Street Girl (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Back_Street_Girl_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Back Street Girl (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Backstreet Girl" <br><br>I don't want you to be high <br>I don't want you to be down <br>Don't want to tell you no lie <br>Just want you to be around <br>Please come right up to my ears <br>You will be able to hear what I say <br>Don't want you out in my world <br>Just you be my backstreet girl <br>Please don't be part of my life <br>Please keep yourself to yourself <br>Please don't you bother my wife <br>That way you won't get no help <br>Don't try to ride on my horse <br>You're rather common and coarse anyway <br>Don't want you out in my world <br>Just you be my backstreet girl <br>Please don't you call me at home <br>Please don't come knocking at night <br>Please never ring on the phone <br>Your manners are never quite right <br>Please take the favors I grant <br>Curtsy and look nonchalant, just for me <br>Don't want you part of my world <br>Just you be my backstreet girl]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Back Street Girl (Remastered / Mono)" label="Back Street Girl (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/My_Girl_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - My Girl (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/My_Girl_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - My Girl (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["My Girl" <br><br>I got sunshine, on a cloudy day. <br>When it's cold outside, I got the month of May. <br>I guess, you'll say, <br>What can make me feel this way? <br>My girl (my girl) my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl. <br>I go so much honey, the bees envy me. <br>I've got a sweeter song, baby, than the birds in the trees. <br>I guess, you'll say, <br>What can make me feel this way? <br>My girl (my girl) my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl. <br>Oooh oooh oooh oooh oooh. <br>Hey, hey, hey, hey. <br>Hey, hey, hey, hey. (oooh) <br>I don't need no money, or count my pay. <br>I've got all the riches, baby, one man can take. <br>I guess, you'll say, <br>What can make me feel this way? <br>My girl (my girl) my girl <br>Talkin' 'bout my girl. <br>I got sunshine, on a cloudy day. <br>I even got the month of May. <br>(My girl) My girl. I'm talkin' 'bout my girl.]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="My Girl (Remastered / Mono)" label="My Girl (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Out_Of_Time_Alternative_Mix___Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Out Of Time (Alternative Mix / Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Out_Of_Time_Alternative_Mix___Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Out Of Time (Alternative Mix / Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Out Of Time" <br><br>You don't know what's going on <br>You've been away for far too long <br>You can't come back and think you are still mine <br>You're out of touch, my baby <br>My poor discarded baby <br>I said, baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>Well, baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>I said, baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>You are all left out <br>Out of there without a doubt <br>Cause baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>You thought you were a clever girl <br>Giving up your social whirl <br>But you can't come back and be the first in line, on no <br>You're obsolete my baby <br>My poor old-fashioned baby <br>I said baby, baby, baby you're out of time <br>Well, baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>I said, baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>Yes, you are left out <br>Out of there without a doubt]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Out Of Time (Alternative Mix / Remastered / Mono)" label="Out Of Time (Alternative Mix / Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Lady_Jane_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Lady_Jane_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Lady Jane" <br><br>My sweet Lady Jane <br>When I see you again <br>Your servant am I <br>And will humbly remain <br>Just heed this plea my love <br>On bended knees my love <br>I pledge myself to Lady Jane <br>My dear Lady Anne <br>I've done what I can <br>I must take my leave <br>For promised I am <br>This play is run my love <br>Your time has come my love <br>I've pledged my troth to Lady Jane <br>Oh my sweet Marie <br>I wait at your ease <br>The sands have run out <br>For your lady and me <br>Wedlock is nigh my love <br>Her station's right my love <br>Life is secure with Lady Jane]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono)" label="Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Lets_Spend_The_Night_Together_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Let`s Spend The Night Together (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Lets_Spend_The_Night_Together_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Let`s Spend The Night Together (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Let's Spend The Night Together" <br><br>My, My, My, My <br>Don't you worry 'bout what's on your mind (Oh my) <br>I'm in no hurry I can take my time (Oh my) <br>I'm going red and my tongue's getting tied (tongues's getting tied) <br>I'm off my head and my mouth's getting dry. <br>I'm high, But I try, try, try (Oh my) <br>Let's spend the night together <br>Now I need you more than ever <br>Let's spend the night together now <br>I feel so strong that I can't disguise (oh my) <br>Let's spend the night together <br>But I just can't apologize (oh no) <br>Let's spend the night together <br>Don't hang me up just to let me down (don't let me down) <br>We could have fun just groovin' around around and around <br>Let's spend the night together <br>Now I need you more than ever <br>Let's spend the night together <br>Let's spend the night together <br>Now I need you more than ever <br>You know I'm smiling baby <br>You need some guiding baby <br>Now I need you more than ever <br>Let's spend the night together <br>Let's spend the night together now <br>This doesn't happen to me ev'ryday (oh my) <br>Let's spend the night together <br>No excuses offered anyway (oh my) <br>Let's spend the night together <br>I'll satisfy your every need (every need) <br>And I now know you will satisfy me <br>Let's spend the night together <br>Now I need you more than ever <br>Let's spend the night together now]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Let`s Spend The Night Together (Remastered / Mono)" label="Let`s Spend The Night Together (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Have_You_Seen_Your_Mother_Baby_Standing_In_The_Shadow__Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Have You Seen Your Mother, Baby, Standing In The Shadow? (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Have_You_Seen_Your_Mother_Baby_Standing_In_The_Shadow__Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Have You Seen Your Mother, Baby, Standing In The Shadow? (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Have You Seen Your Mother Baby, Standing In The Shadow?" <br><br>Have you seen your mother, baby, standing in the shadow? <br>Have you had another, baby, standing in the shadow? <br>I'm glad I opened your eyes <br>The have-nots would have tried to freeze you in ice <br>Have you seen your brother, baby, standing in the shadow? <br>Have you had another baby, standing in the shadow? <br>I was just passing the time <br>I'm all alone, won't you give all your sympathy to mine? <br>Tell me a story about how you adore me <br>Live in the shadow, see through the shadow, <br>Live through the shadow, tear at the shadow <br>Hate in the shadow, and love in your shadowy life <br>Have you seen your lover, baby, standing in the shadow? <br>Has he had another baby, standing in the shadow? <br>Baby, where have you been all your life? <br>Talking about all the people who should try anything twice <br>Have you seen your mother, baby, standing in the shadow? <br>Have you had another baby, standing in the shadow? <br>You take your choice at this time <br>The brave old world or the slide to the depths of decline]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Have You Seen Your Mother, Baby, Standing In The Shadow? (Remastered / Mono)" label="Have You Seen Your Mother, Baby, Standing In The Shadow? (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Ruby_Tuesday_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Ruby Tuesday (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Ruby_Tuesday_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Ruby Tuesday (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Ruby Tuesday" <br><br>She would never say where she came from <br>Yesterday don't matter if it's gone <br>While the sun is bright <br>Or in the darkest night <br>No one knows <br>She comes and goes <br>Goodbye, Ruby Tuesday <br>Who could hang a name on you? <br>When you change with every new day <br>Still I'm gonna miss you... <br>Don't question why she needs to be so free <br>She'll tell you it's the only way to be <br>She just can't be chained <br>To a life where nothing's gained <br>And nothing's lost <br>At such a cost <br>Goodbye, Ruby Tuesday <br>Who could hang a name on you? <br>When you change with every new day <br>Still I'm gonna miss you... <br>There's no time to lose, I heard her say <br>Catch your dreams before they slip away <br>Dying all the time <br>Lose your dreams <br>And you will lose your mind. <br>Ain't life unkind? <br>Goodbye, Ruby Tuesday <br>Who could hang a name on you? <br>When you change with every new day <br>Still I'm gonna miss you... [x2]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Ruby Tuesday (Remastered / Mono)" label="Ruby Tuesday (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Something_Happened_To_Me_Yesterday_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Something Happened To Me Yesterday (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Something_Happened_To_Me_Yesterday_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Something Happened To Me Yesterday (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Something Happened To Me Yesterday" <br><br>Something happened to me yesterday <br>Something, I can't speak of right away <br>Something happened to me, something, oh, so groovy <br>Something happened to me yesterday <br><br>He don't know if it's right or wrong <br>Maybe he should tell someone <br>He's not sure just what it was <br>Or if it's against the law, something <br><br>Something very strange I hear you say <br>You're talking in a most peculiar way <br>But something really threw me, something, oh, so groovy <br>Something happened to me yesterday <br>(Yesterday) <br><br>He don't know just where it's gone <br>He don't really care at all <br>No one's sure just what it was <br>Or the meaning and the cause, something <br><br>What kinda joint is this? <br>Take your partners <br><br>He don't know if it's right or wrong <br>Maybe he should tell someone <br>He's not sure just what it was <br>Or if it's against the law, something <br><br>Someone says there's something more to pay <br>For sins that you committed yesterday <br>It's really rather drippy but something, oh, so trippy <br>Something happened to me yesterday <br><br>Right, he don't know just where it's gone <br>He don't really care at all <br>No one's sure just what it was <br>Or the meaning and the cause, something <br><br>Someone's singing loud across the bay <br>Sittin' on a mat about to pray <br>Isn't half as looney as something, oh, so groovy <br>Something happened to me yesterday <br><br>Right, he don't know if it's right or wrong <br>Maybe he should tell someone <br>He's not sure just what it was <br>Or if it's against the law, something <br><br>Well, thank you very much and now I think it's time for us all to go <br>So from all of us to all of you not forgetting the boys in the band <br>And our producer, Reg Thorpe, we'd like to say "God Bless" <br>So, if you're out tonight, don't forget, if you're on your bike, wear white <br>Amen]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Something Happened To Me Yesterday (Remastered / Mono)" label="Something Happened To Me Yesterday (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Miss_Amanda_Jones_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Miss Amanda Jones (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Miss_Amanda_Jones_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Miss Amanda Jones (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Miss Amanda Jones" <br><br>Down and down she goes, oh, Amanda Jones <br>I said down and down and down and down <br>She'd look really lovely at home <br>Till somebody gonna come up and ask her <br>To live happily ever after, Miss Amanda Jones <br><br>On and on she goes, little miss Amanda Jones <br>I said on and on and on and on <br>Just watch her as she grow <br>Don't wanna say it very obviously <br>But she's losing her nobility, miss Amanda Jones <br><br>Hey girl, don't you realize <br>The money invested in you? <br>Hey girl, you just got to find <br>Someone who'll really pull your family through <br><br>Up and up she goes, our Amanda Jones <br>I said up and up and up and up <br>She looks quite delightfully stoned <br>She's the darling of the discotheque crowd <br>Of her lineage, she's rightfully proud, miss Amanda Jones <br><br>Hey girl, with your nonsense nose <br>All pointing right down at the floor <br>Hey girl, your suspender shows <br>And the girl behind you looks a bit unsure <br><br>Round and round she goes, the world of Amanda Jones <br>I said round and round and round and round <br>The balls and the dinners and show <br>The little girl, she just wanders about <br>Till it's time for her coming out, miss Amanda Jones <br><br>Round and round and round <br>Round and round and round <br>Round and round and round <br>...]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Miss Amanda Jones (Remastered / Mono)" label="Miss Amanda Jones (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Complicated_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Complicated (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Complicated_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Complicated (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Complicated" <br><br>She looks so simple in her way <br>Does the same thing everyday <br>But she's dedicated <br>To having her own way <br>She's very complicated <br>Yeah <br>Women seem to fill her mind <br>And many men in so short time <br>But she's underrated <br>She treats me oh so kind <br>She's very complicated <br>Yeah <br>We talk together and discuss <br>What is really best for us <br>She's sophisticated <br>My head's fit to bust <br>Cause she's so complicated <br>She knows just how to please her man <br>Softer than a baby lamb <br>But she's educated <br>Doesn't give a damn <br>She's very complicated <br>She looks so simple in her way <br>Does the same thing everyday <br>But she's dedicated <br>To having her own way <br>She's very complicated]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Complicated (Remastered / Mono)" label="Complicated (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Whos_Been_Sleeping_Here__Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Who`s Been Sleeping Here? (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Whos_Been_Sleeping_Here__Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Who`s Been Sleeping Here? (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Who's Been Sleeping Here" <br><br>What you say girl, you see what is wrong <br>You, must be joking, you was led alone <br>But the butler the baker, the laughing cavalier <br>Will tell me now, who's been sleeping here <br>I want to know <br>Tell me baby, who's been sleeping here <br>What you say girl, who'd you see that night <br>I was doing, doing something right <br>Oh the soldier, the sailor then there's the three muskateers <br>Yes, they'll now tell me now, who's been sleeping here <br>Did i ever tell you i want to know <br>Hey baby, who's been sleeping here <br>Don't you look like, like a goldilocks <br>There must be somewhere, somewhere you can stop <br>Yes there's the noseless old newsboy the old british brigadier <br>But you'll tell me now, who's been sleeping here <br>Who's been eating, eating off my plate <br>Who will tell me, who'll investigate <br>There's the seargeants the soldiers the cruel old grenadiers <br>But they'll tell me, now, who's been sleeping here <br>Cause i want to know who's been sleeping right here <br>Was it your mummy, your daddy, who's been sleeping here <br>Was it your auntie, your uncle, who's been sleeping here <br>Was it your boyfriend, your girlfriend, who's been sleeping here]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Who`s Been Sleeping Here? (Remastered / Mono)" label="Who`s Been Sleeping Here? (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Please_Go_Home_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Please Go Home (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Please_Go_Home_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Please Go Home (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Please Go Home" <br><br>Please go home <br>Please go home <br>Well maybe I'm talkin to fast <br>But I won't be the first or the last <br>In the sea of the thousand you cast <br>C'mon please go home <br>I don't have to ask what you do <br>I just have to look to get you <br>Means nothing to me to get through <br>Please go home <br>I don't want to be on my own <br>Cause I can't talk much better alone <br>But I don't have to ring like a phone <br>Won't you please go home <br>Please go home <br>In some early part of your days <br>You were told of the devious ways <br>That you thought you could get without pay <br>Won't you please go home <br>You reach a state of your mind <br>Where it's madness to look and to find <br>Your false affections so kind <br>Please go home <br>Won't you please go home]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Please Go Home (Remastered / Mono)" label="Please Go Home (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/All_Sold_Out_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - All Sold Out (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/All_Sold_Out_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - All Sold Out (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["All Sold Out" <br><br>Why put this sadness inside of me <br>Why be so matter-of-fact <br>Why put this one bit of hope in me <br>You sold me out and that's that <br>I hope that you're having fun with me <br>There's not much left to attack <br>I hope that you're nearly done with me <br>You sold me out and that's that <br>All sold out i'd never seen <br>A mind so tangled, a girl so strangled <br>All sold out well i felt so green <br>It was just like that <br>I was put down flat <br>I was sold out just like that <br>Oh baby <br>All sold out i'd never seen <br>A mind so tangled, a girl so strangled <br>All sold out well i felt so green <br>It was just like that <br>I was put down flat <br>I was sold out just like that <br>I missed the point of you doing it <br>Your mind has just jumped the track <br>I took a bit different view of it <br>You sold me out and that's that <br>Hey hey, that's that]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="All Sold Out (Remastered / Mono)" label="All Sold Out (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Cool_Calm_And_Collected_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Cool, Calm And Collected (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Cool_Calm_And_Collected_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Cool, Calm And Collected (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Cool, Calm &amp; Collected" <br><br>Well she's very wealthy it's true <br>So in that she is one up one you <br>She's dressed all in red, white and blue <br>And she always knows more than you do <br>She's so affected <br>Cool, calm, collected <br>She knows who to smile to today <br>She has just been brought up in that way <br>She knows all the right games to play <br>And she always just knows what to say <br>She's well respected <br>Cool, calm, collected <br>She's so affected <br>Cool, calm, collected <br>In public the strain's heard to bear <br>She exudes such a confident air <br>But behind she is not without care <br>But she sweeps it right under her hair <br>She's well respected <br>Cool, calm, collected <br>She seems to glow brilliantly white <br>And her hair seems to shine in the night <br>With her feet unbelievably light <br>And her teeth ready, sharpened to bite <br>She's so respected <br>Cool, calm, collected]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Cool, Calm And Collected (Remastered / Mono)" label="Cool, Calm And Collected (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/She_Smiled_Sweetly_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - She Smiled Sweetly (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/She_Smiled_Sweetly_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - She Smiled Sweetly (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["She Smiled Sweetly" <br><br>Why do my thoughts loom so large on me? <br>They seem to stay, for day after day <br>And won't disappear, I've tried every way <br>But she smiled sweetly <br>She smiled sweetly <br>She smiled sweetly <br>And says don't worry <br>Oh, no no no <br>Where does she hide it inside of her? <br>That keeps her peace most every day <br>And won't disappear, my hair's turning grey <br>But she smiled sweetly <br>She smiled sweetly <br>She smiled sweetly <br>And says don't worry <br>Oh, no no no <br>"There's nothing in why or when <br>There's no use trying, you're here <br>Begging again, and ov'r again" <br>That's what she said so softly <br>I understood for once in my life <br>And feeling good most all of the time <br>But she smiled sweetly <br>She smiled sweetly <br>She smiled sweetly <br>And said don't worry <br>Oh, no no no <br>Oh, no no no <br>Oh, no no no]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="She Smiled Sweetly (Remastered / Mono)" label="She Smiled Sweetly (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Connection_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Connection (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Connection_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Connection (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Connection" <br><br>All i want to do is get back to you <br>Connection, I just can't make no connection. <br>But all I want to do is to get back to you. <br>Everything is going in the wrong direction. <br>The doctor wants to give me more injections. <br>Giving me shots for a thousand rare infections <br>And I don't know if he'll let me go <br>Connection, I just can't make no connection. <br>But all I want to do is to get back to you. <br>Connection, I just can't make it, connection <br>But all I want to do is to get back to you. <br>My bags they get a very close inspection. <br>I wonder why it is that they suspect 'em <br>They're dying to add me to their collection <br>And I don't know if they'll let me go <br>Connection, I just can't make no connection. <br>But all I want to do is to get back to you. <br>Connection, I just can't make no connection. <br>But all I want to do is to get back to you.]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Connection (Remastered / Mono)" label="Connection (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Back_Street_Girl_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Back Street Girl (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Back_Street_Girl_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Back Street Girl (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Backstreet Girl" <br><br>I don't want you to be high <br>I don't want you to be down <br>Don't want to tell you no lie <br>Just want you to be around <br>Please come right up to my ears <br>You will be able to hear what I say <br>Don't want you out in my world <br>Just you be my backstreet girl <br>Please don't be part of my life <br>Please keep yourself to yourself <br>Please don't you bother my wife <br>That way you won't get no help <br>Don't try to ride on my horse <br>You're rather common and coarse anyway <br>Don't want you out in my world <br>Just you be my backstreet girl <br>Please don't you call me at home <br>Please don't come knocking at night <br>Please never ring on the phone <br>Your manners are never quite right <br>Please take the favors I grant <br>Curtsy and look nonchalant, just for me <br>Don't want you part of my world <br>Just you be my backstreet girl]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Back Street Girl (Remastered / Mono)" label="Back Street Girl (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/My_Obsession_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - My Obsession (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/My_Obsession_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - My Obsession (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["My Obsession" <br><br>My obsessions are your possessions <br>Every piece that I can get <br>My obsessions are your possessions <br>Till my mouth is soaking wet <br>I think I blew it now, confession <br><br>You can't dodge it, it's simple logic <br>You'd be better off with me <br>And you'll know it when you lost it <br>Lonely <br><br>My obsessions are your possessions <br>Are you smiling on my way <br>My obsessions are your possessions <br>One that you should give away <br>Give it to me now I've no objection <br><br>I don't mind if it's unkind <br>And it's not my property <br>But I want it just to be mine <br>Exclusively <br><br>Ooh baby, ooh baby <br>Ooh baby, ooh baby <br>Ooh baby, ooh baby <br>Ooh baby, ooh baby, aah <br><br>You need teaching, you're a girl <br>There are things in this world <br>That need teaching with discretion <br>My profession <br><br>My obsessions are your possessions <br>Are you used to the idea? <br>My obsessions are your possessions <br>Do you feel at home right here? <br>You should relax, it's my impression <br><br>Didn't see you were so young <br>I could almost be your son <br>Please turn in my direction <br>No objection]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="My Obsession (Remastered / Mono)" label="My Obsession (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Yesterdays_Papers_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Yesterday`s Papers (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Yesterdays_Papers_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Yesterday`s Papers (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Yesterday's Papers" <br><br>Who wants yesterdays papers <br>Who wants yesterdays girl <br>Who wants yesterdays papers <br>Nobody in the world <br>After this time i finally learned <br>After the pain and hurt <br>After all this what have i achieved <br>I've realized it's time to leave <br>Cause <br>Who wants yesterdays papers <br>Who wants yesterdays girl <br>Who wants yesterdays papers <br>Nobody in the world <br>Living a life of constant change <br>Every day means the turn of a page <br>Yesterdays papers are such bad news <br>Same thing applies to me and you <br>Who wants yesterdays papers <br>Who wants yesterdays girl <br>Who wants yesterdays papers <br>Nobody in the world <br>Seems very hard to have just one girl <br>When there's a million in the world <br>All of these people just can't wait <br>To fall right into their big mistake <br>Who wants yesterdays papers <br>Who wants yesterdays girl <br>Who wants yesterdays papers <br>Nobody in the world]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Yesterday`s Papers (Remastered / Mono)" label="Yesterday`s Papers (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Going_Home_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Going Home (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Going_Home_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Going Home (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Going Home" <br><br>Spendin' too much time away <br>I can't stand another day <br>Maybe you think I've seen the world <br>But I'd rather see my girl <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, bome, bome, bome-bome-bome, <br>Home, bome, bome, bome, back home <br>Yes, I am <br>All those letters ev'ry day <br>Maybe alright in their way <br>But I'd love to see your face <br>When I get home in their place <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, bome, bome, bome-bome-bome, <br>Home, bome, bome, bome, back home <br>Yes, I am <br>Alright <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, bome, bome, bome-bome-bome, <br>Home, bome, bome, bome, back home <br>Yes, I will <br>When you're three thousand miles away <br>I just never sleep the same <br>If I packed my things right now <br>I could be home in seven hours <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, bome, bome, bome-bome-bome, <br>Home, bome, bome, bome, back home <br>Yes, I will <br>Yes, I will <br>See my baby, see my baby <br>I wanna see my girl <br>I just can't wait, I just can't wait <br>I just can't wait, I just can't wait <br>I just can't wait, I just can't wait <br>I just can't wait, I just can't wait <br>I just can't wait <br>I'll see my baby <br>She'll make me feel alright <br>Gotta see my baby <br>She'll make me feel so good <br>She'll make me feel allright <br>Yes she does <br>In the middle of the night <br>So good ti ti tight <br>Feel allright, come on baby <br>I'm gonna get home babe <br>I feel allright <br>I'm lookin' for my baby <br>I'm gonna go in the early morning <br>I'm gonna catch that plane <br>Now it won't be long, I say <br>Listen to me <br>Long time since I've seen my baby <br>Yes it is <br>It's such a long long time <br>Yes it is, I feel allright <br>I'm gonna see my baby, one more time <br>I get home, I gotta get home <br>I wanna see my darling <br>I wanna make sweet sweet love <br>In the middle of the night <br>Early in the morning <br>In the midnight hour <br>She'll make me feel so good <br>She'll make me feel allright <br>When she touch my hands <br>And that's all I gotta say <br>Cause I'm gonna pack my bags <br>I wanna see you baby <br>See your face <br>Your pretty little smile <br>Your pretty clothes <br>Hear you talk <br>Come on <br>I'm comin' home <br>I'll see my baby <br>I'm goin' home <br>I'm gettin' out <br>To see your face <br>Makin' love to you baby <br>Yes it makes me feel so good <br>Inside <br>I feel so good inside <br>Touch me one more time <br>Come on little girl <br>You may look sweet <br>But I know you ain't <br>I know you ain't]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Going Home (Remastered / Mono)" label="Going Home (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/I_Am_Waiting_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - I Am Waiting (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/I_Am_Waiting_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - I Am Waiting (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["I Am Waiting" <br><br>I am waiting, I am waiting (oh yeah, oh yeah) <br>I am waiting, I am waiting (oh yeah, oh yeah) <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>You can't hold out, you can't hold out <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>You can't hold out, you can't hold out <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>See it come along and <br>don't know where it's from <br>Oh, yes you will find out <br>Well, it happens all the time <br>It's censored from our minds <br>You'll find out <br>Slow or fast, slow or fast <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>End at last, end at last <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Stand up coming years <br>and escalation fears <br>Oh, yes we will find out <br>Well, like a withered stone <br>Fears will pierce your bones <br>You'll find out <br>Oh we're waiting, oh we're waiting <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>Oh we're waiting, oh we're waiting <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Oh we're waiting, oh we're waiting <br>Oh we're waiting, oh were waiting...]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="I Am Waiting (Remastered / Mono)" label="I Am Waiting (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Its_Not_Easy_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - It`s Not Easy (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:50:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:50:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Its_Not_Easy_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - It`s Not Easy (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["It's Not Easy" <br><br>It's not easy <br>It's not easy living on your own <br>It's not easy <br>It's not easy living on your own <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>And it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>It's not easy living on your own <br>All of the things that you used to do <br>If they're done now, well they're done by you <br>It seems a big failing in a man <br>To take his girl for granted if he can <br>And it's hard thing (it's not easy) <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>And it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>It's not easy livin' on your own <br>There's no place where you can call home <br>Got me running like a cat in a thunderstorm <br>Just a big bed and a telephone <br>Like the last remnants of a stately home <br>And it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>Well, it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>It's not easy livin' on your own <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>And it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>It's not easy living on your own <br>Sit here thinking with your head of fire <br>Go think the same thing and never tire <br>Imaginin' the glow of her long clean hair <br>As she goes to sit on her own high chair <br>And it's hard thing (it's not easy) <br>Well, it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>Well, it's hard babe (it's not easy) <br>It's not easy livin' on your own <br>It's not easy (a pretty tough thing) <br>It's not easy (well, life pretty rough) <br>It's not easy (it's a hard time baby) <br>It's not easy (it's a hard time baby) <br>It's not easy (it's a pretty hard life)]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="It`s Not Easy (Remastered / Mono)" label="It`s Not Easy (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/High_And_Dry_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - High And Dry (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/High_And_Dry_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - High And Dry (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["High And Dry" <br><br>High and dry well, I'm up here with no warning <br>High and dry well, I couldn't get a word in <br>High and dry oh, what a way to go <br>She left me standing here just high and dry <br>A minute I was up there standing by her side <br>The next I was down there, well, left out of the ride and <br>High and dry oh, what a way to go <br>She left me standing here just high and dry <br>Anythin' I wished for I only had to ask her (yep) <br>I think she found out it was money I was after <br>High and dry oh, what a weird letdown <br>She left me standing here just high and dry <br>Alright <br>It's lucky that I didn't have any love towards her <br>Next time I'll make sure that the girl'll be much poorer <br>High and dry oh, what a way to go <br>She left me standing here just high and dry <br>High and dry well, I'm up here with no warnin <br>Yep <br>High and dry well, I couldn't get a word in <br>High and dry oh, what a way to go <br>She left me standin' here just high and dry <br>Well, she left me standin' here just high and dry <br>Well, she left me standin' here just high and dry <br>Hey!]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="High And Dry (Remastered / Mono)" label="High And Dry (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Flight_505_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Flight 505 (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Flight_505_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Flight 505 (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Flight 505" <br><br>Well, I was happy here at home <br>I got everything I need. <br>Happy bein' on my own <br>Just living the life I lead. <br>Well, suddenly it dawned on me <br>That this was not my life. <br>So I just phoned the airline girl <br>And said, "Get me on flight number 505, <br>Get me on flight number 505." <br>Well, I confirmed my reservation. <br>Then I hopped a cab. <br>No idea of my destination <br>And feeling pretty bad. <br>With my suitcase in my hand. <br>In my head, my new life. <br>So then I told the airline girl <br>"Well, get me on flight number 505, <br>Get me on flight number 505." <br>Alright. <br>Well, I sat right there in my seat. <br>Well, feeling like a king. <br>With the whole world right at my feet. <br>"Of course I'll have a drink!" <br>Well, suddenly I saw <br>That we never ever would arrive. <br>He put the plane down in the sea. <br>The end of flight number 505. <br>The end of flight number 505. <br>Alright. <br>Whew, they put the plane down in the sea. <br>The end of flight number 505. <br>The end of flight number 505.]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Flight 505 (Remastered / Mono)" label="Flight 505 (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Think_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Think (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Think_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Think (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Think" <br><br>I'm givin' you a piece of my mind. <br>There no charge of any kind. <br>Try a very simple test. <br>You should just retrace your steps. <br>And think back, back a little bit baby. <br>Back, back alright. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Think, think back a bit girl. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>Think about a year ago. <br>How we lived I'll never know. <br>Connin' people for a dime. <br>Here's another piece of my mind. <br>And think back, back a little bit baby. <br>Back, back alright. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Think, think back a bit girl. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>Take a look inside yourself. <br>You're not really someone else. <br>Still, I am the same old me. <br>You say I lack maturity. <br>But think back, back a little bit baby. <br>Back, back, alright! <br>We're not children anymore. <br>We don't need to play with toys. <br>Take a look and you will find <br>You're gettin' old before your time. <br>But think back, back a little bit baby. <br>Back, back alright. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Think, think I said back a bit girl. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>I said think. <br>You'd better think back a little bit. <br>I said think. <br>What about last year and the year before? <br>I said think. <br>You promised me so much. <br>I said think. <br>Doncha 'member what you said?]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Think (Remastered / Mono)" label="Think (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Doncha_Bother_Me_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Doncha Bother Me (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Doncha_Bother_Me_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Doncha Bother Me (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Doncha Bother Me" <br><br>I said, "Oh no, doncha follow me no more." <br>I said, "Oh no, doncha follow me no more." <br>Well I'm looking for my face <br>And I got no place to go <br>I said, "Oh no, doncha follow me no more." <br>I said, "Oh no, doncha follow me no more." <br>Well, pick your own mind <br>And don't you touch mine no more <br>Still waiting here for a single idea <br>In your clothes and your hair <br>I wore it last year <br>Oh no, doncha follow me no more <br>I said, "Oh no, doncha copy me no more." <br>I said, "Oh no, doncha copy me no more." <br>Well, the lines around my eyes <br>are protected by a copyright law <br>Well, all the clubs and the bars <br>And the little red cars <br>Not knowing why, but trying to get high <br>Oh no, doncha follow me no more <br>Doncha follow <br>Doncha follow]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Doncha Bother Me (Remastered / Mono)" label="Doncha Bother Me (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Under_My_Thumb_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Under My Thumb (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Under_My_Thumb_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Under My Thumb (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Under My Thumb" <br><br>Under my thumb <br>The girl who once had me down <br>Under my thumb <br>The girl who once pushed me around <br>It's down to me <br>The difference in the clothes she wears <br>Down to me, the change has come, <br>She's under my thumb <br>Ain't it the truth babe? <br>Under my thumb <br>The squirmin' dog who's just had her day <br>Under my thumb <br>A girl who has just changed her ways <br>It's down to me, yes it is <br>The way she does just what she's told <br>Down to me, the change has come <br>She's under my thumb <br>Ah, ah, say it's alright <br>Under my thumb <br>A siamese cat of a girl <br>Under my thumb <br>She's the sweetest, hmmm, pet in the world <br>It's down to me <br>The way she talks when she's spoken to <br>Down to me, the change has come, <br>She's under my thumb <br>Ah, take it easy babe <br>Yeah <br>It's down to me, oh yeah <br>The way she talks when she's spoken to <br>Down to me, the change has come, <br>She's under my thumb <br>Yeah, it feels alright <br>Under my thumb <br>Her eyes are just kept to herself <br>Under my thumb, well I <br>I can still look at someone else <br>It's down to me, oh that's what I said <br>The way she talks when she's spoken to <br>Down to me, the change has come, <br>She's under my thumb <br>Say, it's alright. <br>Say it's all... <br>Say it's all... <br>Take it easy babe <br>Take it easy babe <br>Feels alright <br>Take it, take it easy babe.]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Under My Thumb (Remastered / Mono)" label="Under My Thumb (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Lady_Jane_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Lady_Jane_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My sweet lady Jane <br>When I see you again <br>Your servant am I <br>And will humbly remain <br>Just heed this plea, my love <br>On bended knees my love <br>I pledge myself to lady Jane <br><br>My dear lady Anne <br>I've done what I can <br>I must take my leave <br>For promised I am <br>This play is run, my love <br>Your time has come, my love <br>I pledge my troth to lady Jane <br><br>Oh, my sweet Marie <br>I wait at your ease <br>The sands have run out <br>For your lady and me <br>Wedlock is nigh my love <br>Her station's right my love <br>Life is secure with Lady Jane]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono)" label="Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Stupid_Girl_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Stupid Girl (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Stupid_Girl_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Stupid Girl (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Stupid Girl" <br><br>I'm not talking about the kind of clothes she wears <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>I'm not talking about the way she combs her hair <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>The way she powders her nose <br>Her vanity shows and it shows <br>She's the worst thing in this world <br>Well, look at that stupid girl <br>I'm not talking about the way she digs for gold <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>Well, I'm talking about the way she grabs and holds <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>The way she talks about someone else <br>That she don't even know herself <br>She's the sickest thing in this world <br>Well, look at that stupid girl <br>Well, I'm sick and tired <br>And I really have my doubts <br>I've tried and tried <br>But it never really works out <br>Like a lady in waiting to a virgin queen <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>She bitches 'bout things that she's never seen <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>It doesn't matter if she dyes her hair <br>Or the color of the shoes she wears <br>She's the worst thing in this world <br>Well, look at that stupid girl <br>Shut-up, shut-up, shut-up, shut-up, shut-up <br>Shut-up, shut-up, shut-up, shut-up, shut-up <br>Shut-up, shut-up, shut-up <br>Like a lady in waiting to a virgin queen <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>She bitches 'bout things that she's never seen <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>She purrs like a pussycat <br>Then she turns 'round and hisses back <br>She's the sickest thing in this world <br>Look at that stupid girl]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Stupid Girl (Remastered / Mono)" label="Stupid Girl (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Paint_It_Black_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Paint It, Black (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Paint_It_Black_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Paint It, Black (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I see a red door and <br>I want it painted black <br>No colors anymore <br>I want them to turn black <br>I see the girls walk by <br>dressed in their summer clothes <br>I have to turn my head <br>until my darkness goes <br>I see a line of cars and <br>they're all painted black <br>With flowers and my love <br>both never to come back <br>I see people turn their heads <br>and quickly look away <br>Like a newborn baby <br>it just happens ev'ryday <br>I look inside myself and <br>see my heart is black <br>I see my red door <br>and I must have it painted black <br>Maybe then I'll fade away <br>and not have to face the facts <br>It's not easy facing up <br>when your whole world is black <br>No more will my green sea go <br>turn a deeper blue <br>I could not foresee this thing <br>happening to you <br>If I look hard enough <br>into the setting sun <br>My love will laugh with me <br>before the morning comes <br>I see a red door <br>and I want it painted black <br>No colors anymore <br>I want them to turn black <br>I see the girls walk by dressed <br>in their summer clothes <br>I have to turn my head <br>until my darkness goes <br>I want to see your face <br>painted black <br>black as night black as coal <br>Don't want to see the sun <br>flying high in the sky <br>I want to see it painted <br>painted painted painted black yea <br>]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Paint It, Black (Remastered / Mono)" label="Paint It, Black (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/What_To_Do_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - What To Do (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/What_To_Do_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - What To Do (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What to do yeah <br>I really don't know <br>I really don't know what to do <br>What to do yeah <br>I really don't know <br>I really don't know <br><br>Maybe when the TV stops <br>Faded out on the epilogue <br>Watch the screen just fade away <br><br>Now, I really don't know <br>I really don't know <br>What to do yeah <br>Well, I really don't know <br>I really don't know what to do <br>What to do yeah <br>I really don't know <br>I really don't know <br><br>There's a place where you get bored <br>That's what you make your money for <br>Drink and dance 'til four o'clock <br><br>Now, you really don't know <br>You really don't know what to do yeah <br><br>Nothin' to do, nowhere to go <br>You're talkin' to people that you don't know <br>There's na-na-nothin', to do-do-do <br>There's na-na-nothin', (no) no <br>You (I) really don't what to do yeah <br><br>Well, I really don't know <br>I really don't know what to do <br>What to do yeah <br>I really don't know <br>I really don't know <br><br>Hurry people get on your train <br>Don't be late for work again <br>Take this time to go to bed <br>Now, I really don't know <br>I really don't know what to do yeah <br><br>Nothin' to do, nowhere to go <br>You're talkin' to people that you don't know <br>There's na-na-nothin', to do-do-do <br>You're sick n' tired of foolin' 'round <br>There's na-na-nothin', to do-do-do <br>To do-do-do, to do-do-do <br>There's na-na-nothin', na-na-nothin' <br>Na-na-nothin', na-na-nothin' <br>Na-na-nothin', na-na-nothin' <br>Na-na-nothin']]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="What To Do (Remastered / Mono)" label="What To Do (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Think_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Think (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Think_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Think (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Think" <br><br>I'm givin' you a piece of my mind. <br>There no charge of any kind. <br>Try a very simple test. <br>You should just retrace your steps. <br>And think back, back a little bit baby. <br>Back, back alright. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Think, think back a bit girl. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>Think about a year ago. <br>How we lived I'll never know. <br>Connin' people for a dime. <br>Here's another piece of my mind. <br>And think back, back a little bit baby. <br>Back, back alright. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Think, think back a bit girl. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>Take a look inside yourself. <br>You're not really someone else. <br>Still, I am the same old me. <br>You say I lack maturity. <br>But think back, back a little bit baby. <br>Back, back, alright! <br>We're not children anymore. <br>We don't need to play with toys. <br>Take a look and you will find <br>You're gettin' old before your time. <br>But think back, back a little bit baby. <br>Back, back alright. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Think, think I said back a bit girl. <br>Think, think, think back baby. <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>Tell me who's fault was that, babe? <br>I said think. <br>You'd better think back a little bit. <br>I said think. <br>What about last year and the year before? <br>I said think. <br>You promised me so much. <br>I said think. <br>Doncha 'member what you said?]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Think (Remastered / Mono)" label="Think (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Take_It_Or_Leave_It_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Take It Or Leave It (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Take_It_Or_Leave_It_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Take It Or Leave It (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Take It Or Leave It" <br><br>You can turn off and on more times <br>than a flashin' neon sign. <br>When you want you're bad <br>But you can be so kind <br>Just take it or leave it <br>Don't tell your friend <br>Just what you're gonna do now <br>You take it or leave it, it's just my life <br>There've been times when you tried <br>Makin' eyes at all my so called friends <br>Then you go, now you're back <br>But you can be so kind <br>Just take it or leave it <br>Don't tell your friend <br>Just what you're gonna do now <br>You take it or leave it, it's just my life <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la <br>I'm sick and tired of the smile that you give <br>When you don't come home at night <br>You said you'd call, that's a lie <br>But you could be so kind <br>Just take it or leave it <br>Don't tell your friend <br>Just what you're gonna do now <br>You take it or leave it, it's just my life <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la-la-la <br>Oh, la-la-la-ta-ta-ta-ta-la-la]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Take It Or Leave It (Remastered / Mono)" label="Take It Or Leave It (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/I_Am_Waiting_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - I Am Waiting (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/I_Am_Waiting_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - I Am Waiting (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["I Am Waiting" <br><br>I am waiting, I am waiting (oh yeah, oh yeah) <br>I am waiting, I am waiting (oh yeah, oh yeah) <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>You can't hold out, you can't hold out <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>You can't hold out, you can't hold out <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>See it come along and <br>don't know where it's from <br>Oh, yes you will find out <br>Well, it happens all the time <br>It's censored from our minds <br>You'll find out <br>Slow or fast, slow or fast <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>End at last, end at last <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Stand up coming years <br>and escalation fears <br>Oh, yes we will find out <br>Well, like a withered stone <br>Fears will pierce your bones <br>You'll find out <br>Oh we're waiting, oh we're waiting <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>Oh we're waiting, oh we're waiting <br>Oh yeah, oh yeah <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Waiting for someone to come out of somewhere <br>Oh we're waiting, oh we're waiting <br>Oh we're waiting, oh were waiting...]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="I Am Waiting (Remastered / Mono)" label="I Am Waiting (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Its_Not_Easy_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - It`s Not Easy (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Its_Not_Easy_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - It`s Not Easy (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["It's Not Easy" <br><br>It's not easy <br>It's not easy living on your own <br>It's not easy <br>It's not easy living on your own <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>And it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>It's not easy living on your own <br>All of the things that you used to do <br>If they're done now, well they're done by you <br>It seems a big failing in a man <br>To take his girl for granted if he can <br>And it's hard thing (it's not easy) <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>And it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>It's not easy livin' on your own <br>There's no place where you can call home <br>Got me running like a cat in a thunderstorm <br>Just a big bed and a telephone <br>Like the last remnants of a stately home <br>And it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>Well, it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>It's not easy livin' on your own <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>And it's hard (it's not easy) <br>And it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>It's not easy living on your own <br>Sit here thinking with your head of fire <br>Go think the same thing and never tire <br>Imaginin' the glow of her long clean hair <br>As she goes to sit on her own high chair <br>And it's hard thing (it's not easy) <br>Well, it's a pretty hard thing (it's not easy) <br>Well, it's hard babe (it's not easy) <br>It's not easy livin' on your own <br>It's not easy (a pretty tough thing) <br>It's not easy (well, life pretty rough) <br>It's not easy (it's a hard time baby) <br>It's not easy (it's a hard time baby) <br>It's not easy (it's a pretty hard life)]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="It`s Not Easy (Remastered / Mono)" label="It`s Not Easy (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Out_Of_Time_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Out Of Time (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Out_Of_Time_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Out Of Time (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Out Of Time" <br><br>You don't know what's going on <br>You've been away for far too long <br>You can't come back and think you are still mine <br>You're out of touch, my baby <br>My poor discarded baby <br>I said, baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>Well, baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>I said, baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>You are all left out <br>Out of there without a doubt <br>Cause baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>You thought you were a clever girl <br>Giving up your social whirl <br>But you can't come back and be the first in line, on no <br>You're obsolete my baby <br>My poor old-fashioned baby <br>I said baby, baby, baby you're out of time <br>Well, baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>I said, baby, baby, baby, you're out of time <br>Yes, you are left out <br>Out of there without a doubt <br>Cause baby, baby, baby, you're out of time]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Out Of Time (Remastered / Mono)" label="Out Of Time (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/High_And_Dry_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - High And Dry (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/High_And_Dry_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - High And Dry (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["High And Dry" <br><br>High and dry well, I'm up here with no warning <br>High and dry well, I couldn't get a word in <br>High and dry oh, what a way to go <br>She left me standing here just high and dry <br>A minute I was up there standing by her side <br>The next I was down there, well, left out of the ride and <br>High and dry oh, what a way to go <br>She left me standing here just high and dry <br>Anythin' I wished for I only had to ask her (yep) <br>I think she found out it was money I was after <br>High and dry oh, what a weird letdown <br>She left me standing here just high and dry <br>Alright <br>It's lucky that I didn't have any love towards her <br>Next time I'll make sure that the girl'll be much poorer <br>High and dry oh, what a way to go <br>She left me standing here just high and dry <br>High and dry well, I'm up here with no warnin <br>Yep <br>High and dry well, I couldn't get a word in <br>High and dry oh, what a way to go <br>She left me standin' here just high and dry <br>Well, she left me standin' here just high and dry <br>Well, she left me standin' here just high and dry <br>Hey!]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="High And Dry (Remastered / Mono)" label="High And Dry (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Flight_505_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Flight 505 (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Flight_505_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Flight 505 (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Flight 505" <br><br>Well, I was happy here at home <br>I got everything I need. <br>Happy bein' on my own <br>Just living the life I lead. <br>Well, suddenly it dawned on me <br>That this was not my life. <br>So I just phoned the airline girl <br>And said, "Get me on flight number 505, <br>Get me on flight number 505." <br>Well, I confirmed my reservation. <br>Then I hopped a cab. <br>No idea of my destination <br>And feeling pretty bad. <br>With my suitcase in my hand. <br>In my head, my new life. <br>So then I told the airline girl <br>"Well, get me on flight number 505, <br>Get me on flight number 505." <br>Alright. <br>Well, I sat right there in my seat. <br>Well, feeling like a king. <br>With the whole world right at my feet. <br>"Of course I'll have a drink!" <br>Well, suddenly I saw <br>That we never ever would arrive. <br>He put the plane down in the sea. <br>The end of flight number 505. <br>The end of flight number 505. <br>Alright. <br>Whew, they put the plane down in the sea. <br>The end of flight number 505. <br>The end of flight number 505.]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Flight 505 (Remastered / Mono)" label="Flight 505 (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Going_Home_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Going Home (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Going_Home_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Going Home (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Going Home" <br><br>Spendin' too much time away <br>I can't stand another day <br>Maybe you think I've seen the world <br>But I'd rather see my girl <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, bome, bome, bome-bome-bome, <br>Home, bome, bome, bome, back home <br>Yes, I am <br>All those letters ev'ry day <br>Maybe alright in their way <br>But I'd love to see your face <br>When I get home in their place <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, bome, bome, bome-bome-bome, <br>Home, bome, bome, bome, back home <br>Yes, I am <br>Alright <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, bome, bome, bome-bome-bome, <br>Home, bome, bome, bome, back home <br>Yes, I will <br>When you're three thousand miles away <br>I just never sleep the same <br>If I packed my things right now <br>I could be home in seven hours <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, I'm goin' home <br>I'm goin' home, bome, bome, bome-bome-bome, <br>Home, bome, bome, bome, back home <br>Yes, I will <br>Yes, I will <br>See my baby, see my baby <br>I wanna see my girl <br>I just can't wait, I just can't wait <br>I just can't wait, I just can't wait <br>I just can't wait, I just can't wait <br>I just can't wait, I just can't wait <br>I just can't wait <br>I'll see my baby <br>She'll make me feel alright <br>Gotta see my baby <br>She'll make me feel so good <br>She'll make me feel allright <br>Yes she does <br>In the middle of the night <br>So good ti ti tight <br>Feel allright, come on baby <br>I'm gonna get home babe <br>I feel allright <br>I'm lookin' for my baby <br>I'm gonna go in the early morning <br>I'm gonna catch that plane <br>Now it won't be long, I say <br>Listen to me <br>Long time since I've seen my baby <br>Yes it is <br>It's such a long long time <br>Yes it is, I feel allright <br>I'm gonna see my baby, one more time <br>I get home, I gotta get home <br>I wanna see my darling <br>I wanna make sweet sweet love <br>In the middle of the night <br>Early in the morning <br>In the midnight hour <br>She'll make me feel so good <br>She'll make me feel allright <br>When she touch my hands <br>And that's all I gotta say <br>Cause I'm gonna pack my bags <br>I wanna see you baby <br>See your face <br>Your pretty little smile <br>Your pretty clothes <br>Hear you talk <br>Come on <br>I'm comin' home <br>I'll see my baby <br>I'm goin' home <br>I'm gettin' out <br>To see your face <br>Makin' love to you baby <br>Yes it makes me feel so good <br>Inside <br>I feel so good inside <br>Touch me one more time <br>Come on little girl <br>You may look sweet <br>But I know you ain't <br>I know you ain't]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Going Home (Remastered / Mono)" label="Going Home (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Doncha_Bother_Me_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Doncha Bother Me (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Doncha_Bother_Me_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Doncha Bother Me (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Doncha Bother Me" <br><br>I said, "Oh no, doncha follow me no more." <br>I said, "Oh no, doncha follow me no more." <br>Well I'm looking for my face <br>And I got no place to go <br>I said, "Oh no, doncha follow me no more." <br>I said, "Oh no, doncha follow me no more." <br>Well, pick your own mind <br>And don't you touch mine no more <br>Still waiting here for a single idea <br>In your clothes and your hair <br>I wore it last year <br>Oh no, doncha follow me no more <br>I said, "Oh no, doncha copy me no more." <br>I said, "Oh no, doncha copy me no more." <br>Well, the lines around my eyes <br>are protected by a copyright law <br>Well, all the clubs and the bars <br>And the little red cars <br>Not knowing why, but trying to get high <br>Oh no, doncha follow me no more <br>Doncha follow <br>Doncha follow]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Doncha Bother Me (Remastered / Mono)" label="Doncha Bother Me (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Under_My_Thumb_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Under My Thumb (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Under_My_Thumb_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Under My Thumb (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Under My Thumb" <br><br>Under my thumb <br>The girl who once had me down <br>Under my thumb <br>The girl who once pushed me around <br>It's down to me <br>The difference in the clothes she wears <br>Down to me, the change has come, <br>She's under my thumb <br>Ain't it the truth babe? <br>Under my thumb <br>The squirmin' dog who's just had her day <br>Under my thumb <br>A girl who has just changed her ways <br>It's down to me, yes it is <br>The way she does just what she's told <br>Down to me, the change has come <br>She's under my thumb <br>Ah, ah, say it's alright <br>Under my thumb <br>A siamese cat of a girl <br>Under my thumb <br>She's the sweetest, hmmm, pet in the world <br>It's down to me <br>The way she talks when she's spoken to <br>Down to me, the change has come, <br>She's under my thumb <br>Ah, take it easy babe <br>Yeah <br>It's down to me, oh yeah <br>The way she talks when she's spoken to <br>Down to me, the change has come, <br>She's under my thumb <br>Yeah, it feels alright <br>Under my thumb <br>Her eyes are just kept to herself <br>Under my thumb, well I <br>I can still look at someone else <br>It's down to me, oh that's what I said <br>The way she talks when she's spoken to <br>Down to me, the change has come, <br>She's under my thumb <br>Say, it's alright. <br>Say it's all... <br>Say it's all... <br>Take it easy babe <br>Take it easy babe <br>Feels alright <br>Take it, take it easy babe.]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Under My Thumb (Remastered / Mono)" label="Under My Thumb (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Lady_Jane_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Lady_Jane_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Lady Jane" <br><br>My sweet Lady Jane <br>When I see you again <br>Your servant am I <br>And will humbly remain <br>Just heed this plea my love <br>On bended knees my love <br>I pledge myself to Lady Jane <br>My dear Lady Anne <br>I've done what I can <br>I must take my leave <br>For promised I am <br>This play is run my love <br>Your time has come my love <br>I've pledged my troth to Lady Jane <br>Oh my sweet Marie <br>I wait at your ease <br>The sands have run out <br>For your lady and me <br>Wedlock is nigh my love <br>Her station's right my love <br>Life is secure with Lady Jane]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono)" label="Lady Jane (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Stupid_Girl_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Stupid Girl (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Stupid_Girl_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Stupid Girl (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Stupid Girl" <br><br>I'm not talking about the kind of clothes she wears <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>I'm not talking about the way she combs her hair <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>The way she powders her nose <br>Her vanity shows and it shows <br>She's the worst thing in this world <br>Well, look at that stupid girl <br>I'm not talking about the way she digs for gold <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>Well, I'm talking about the way she grabs and holds <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>The way she talks about someone else <br>That she don't even know herself <br>She's the sickest thing in this world <br>Well, look at that stupid girl <br>Well, I'm sick and tired <br>And I really have my doubts <br>I've tried and tried <br>But it never really works out <br>Like a lady in waiting to a virgin queen <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>She bitches 'bout things that she's never seen <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>It doesn't matter if she dyes her hair <br>Or the color of the shoes she wears <br>She's the worst thing in this world <br>Well, look at that stupid girl <br>Shut-up, shut-up, shut-up, shut-up, shut-up <br>Shut-up, shut-up, shut-up, shut-up, shut-up <br>Shut-up, shut-up, shut-up <br>Like a lady in waiting to a virgin queen <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>She bitches 'bout things that she's never seen <br>Look at that stupid girl <br>She purrs like a pussycat <br>Then she turns 'round and hisses back <br>She's the sickest thing in this world <br>Look at that stupid girl]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Stupid Girl (Remastered / Mono)" label="Stupid Girl (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Mothers_Little_Helper_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Mother`s Little Helper (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Mothers_Little_Helper_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Mother`s Little Helper (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Mother's Little Helper" <br><br>What a drag it is getting old <br>"Kids are different today," <br>I hear ev'ry mother say <br>Mother needs something today to calm her down <br>And though she's not really ill <br>There's a little yellow pill <br>She goes running for the shelter of a mother's little helper <br>And it helps her on her way, gets her through her busy day <br>"Things are different today," <br>I hear ev'ry mother say <br>Cooking fresh food for a husband's just a drag <br>So she buys an instant cake and she burns her frozen steak <br>And goes running for the shelter of a mother's little helper <br>And two help her on her way, get her through her busy day <br>Doctor please, some more of these <br>Outside the door, she took four more <br>What a drag it is getting old <br>"Men just aren't the same today" <br>I hear ev'ry mother say <br>They just don't appreciate that you get tired <br>They're so hard to satisfy, You can tranquilize your mind <br>So go running for the shelter of a mother's little helper <br>And four help you through the night, help to minimize your plight <br>Doctor please, some more of these <br>Outside the door, she took four more <br>What a drag it is getting old <br>"Life's just much too hard today," <br>I hear ev'ry mother say <br>The pusuit of happiness just seems a bore <br>And if you take more of those, you will get an overdose <br>No more running for the shelter of a mother's little helper <br>They just helped you on your way, through your busy dying day]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Mother`s Little Helper (Remastered / Mono)" label="Mother`s Little Helper (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Blue_Turns_To_Grey_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Blue Turns To Grey (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Blue_Turns_To_Grey_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Blue Turns To Grey (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Blue Turns To Grey" <br><br>So now that she is gone <br>You won't be sad for long <br>For maybe just an hour or just a moment <br>Of the day <br>Then blue turns to grey <br>And try as you may <br>You just don't feel good <br>You don't feel alright <br>And you know that you must find her, find her, find her <br>You think you'll have a ball <br>And you won't care at all <br>You'll find another girl or maybe more <br>To pass the time away <br>Then blue turns to grey <br>And try as you may <br>You just don't feel good <br>You just don't feel alright <br>And you know that you must find her, find her, find her <br>She's not home when you call <br>So you can go to all <br>The places where she used to go <br>But she has gone away <br>Then blue turns to grey <br>And try as you may <br>You just don't feel good <br>You don't feel alright <br>And you know that you must find her, find her, find her <br>Blue turns to grey (blue turns to grey) <br>She has gone away (blue turns to grey) <br>I feel so bad (blue turns to grey) <br>I wish you'd come on home (blue turns to grey) <br>I feel, I feel so down...]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Blue Turns To Grey (Remastered / Mono)" label="Blue Turns To Grey (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Gotta_Get_Away_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Gotta Get Away (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:54+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:54+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Gotta_Get_Away_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Gotta Get Away (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Baby, the truth is out so don't deny <br>Baby to think I believed all your lies <br>Darlin' I can't stand to see your face <br>It's the truth, you understand <br>I got to get away, got to get away <br>Gotta, gotta, gotta get away <br>Got to get away <br><br>Baby, I don't want to live here no more <br>Baby, though I tore your pictures off my walls <br>Darlin' this old room's falling in on me <br>You understand the truth now <br>I got to get away, got to get away <br>Gotta, gotta, gotta get away <br>Got to get away <br><br>Baby, oh, how could you take away your clothes <br>Baby, don't screw up this old heart of gold <br>Darling, this will rule my social flare <br>You understand me now <br>I got to get away, got to get away <br>Gotta, gotta, gotta get away <br>Got to get away]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Gotta Get Away (Remastered / Mono)" label="Gotta Get Away (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/As_Tears_Go_By_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - As Tears Go By (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/As_Tears_Go_By_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - As Tears Go By (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["As Tears Go By" <br><br>It is the evening of the day <br>I sit and watch the children play <br>Smiling faces I can see <br>But not for me <br>I sit and watch <br>As tears go by <br>My riches can't buy everything <br>I want to hear the children sing <br>All I hear is the sound <br>Of rain falling on the ground <br>I sit and watch <br>As tears go by <br>It is the evening of the day <br>I sit and watch the children play <br>Doin' things I used to do <br>They think are new <br>I sit and watch <br>As tears go by]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="As Tears Go By (Remastered / Mono)" label="As Tears Go By (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Im_Free_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - I`m Free (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:51:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:51:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Im_Free_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - I`m Free (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["I'm Free" <br><br>I'm free to do what I want any old time <br>I'm free to do what I want any old time <br>So love me, hold me, love me, hold me <br>I'm free any old time to get what I want <br>I'm free to sing my song though it gets out of time <br>I'm free to sing my song though it gets out of time <br>So love me, hold me, love me, hold me <br>And I'm free any old time to get what I want <br>Love me, hold me, love me, hold me <br>But I'm free any old time to get what I want <br>I'm free to choose what I please any old time <br>I'm free to choose what I please any old time <br>So hold me, love me, love me, hold me]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="I`m Free (Remastered / Mono)" label="I`m Free (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Get_Off_Of_My_Cloud_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Get Off Of My Cloud (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Get_Off_Of_My_Cloud_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Get Off Of My Cloud (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Get Off Of My Cloud" <br><br>I live in an apartment on the ninety-ninth floor of my block <br>And I sit at home looking out the window <br>Imagining the world has stopped <br>Then in flies a guy who's all dressed up like a Union Jack <br>And says, I've won five pounds if I have his kind of detergent pack <br>I said, Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Don't hang around 'cause two's a crowd <br>On my cloud, baby <br>The telephone is ringing <br>I say, "Hi, it's me. Who is it there on the line?" <br>A voice says, "Hi, hello, how are you?" <br>Well, I guess I'm doin' fine <br>He says, "It's three a.m., there's too much noise <br>Don't you people ever wanna go to bed? <br>Just 'cause you feel so good, do you have <br>To drive me out of my head?" <br>I said, Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Don't hang around 'cause two's a crowd <br>On my cloud baby <br>I was sick and tired, fed up with this <br>And decided to take a drive downtown <br>It was so very quiet and peaceful <br>There was nobody, not a soul around <br>I laid myself out, I was so tired and I started to dream <br>In the morning the parking tickets were just like <br>A flag stuck on my window screen <br>I said, Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Don't hang around 'cause two's a crowd <br>On my cloud <br>Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Hey! You! Get off of my cloud <br>Don't hang around, baby, two's a crowd]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Get Off Of My Cloud (Remastered / Mono)" label="Get Off Of My Cloud (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/The_Singer_Not_The_Song_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - The Singer Not The Song (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/The_Singer_Not_The_Song_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - The Singer Not The Song (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["The Singer Not The Song" <br><br>Everywhere you want I always go <br>I always give in because, babe, you know <br>You just say so cause you give me that <br>Feeling inside that I know must be right <br>It's the singer not the song <br>It's not the way you give in willingly <br>Others do it without thrilling me <br>Giving me that same old feeling inside that I <br>Know I must be right <br>It's the singer not the song <br>The same old places and the same old songs <br>We've been going there for much too long <br>There's something wrong and it gives me that feeling <br>Inside that I know I must be right <br>It's the singer not the song <br>It's the singer not the song <br>It's the singer not the song]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="The Singer Not The Song (Remastered / Mono)" label="The Singer Not The Song (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Look_What_Youve_Done_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Look What You`ve Done (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Look_What_Youve_Done_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Look What You`ve Done (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Look What You've Done" <br><br>Now look what you've done <br>Now look what you've done <br>Look what you've done baby <br>Now look what you've done <br>You left me here <br>The lonely one <br>And all I can say <br>Is look what you've done <br>A broken heart <br>A worried mind <br>Because of you baby <br>Dying all the time <br>I once had a dream <br>But now I've none <br>Your taking your love <br>And see what it done <br>I saw you last night <br>Out moving round <br>With your new turf <br>You paint the town <br>That is OK <br>You're having your fun <br>Because some day <br>They call you done <br>And now your bird cries <br>The shadow falls <br>Gloomy memories <br>And I recall <br>Your love is my life <br>As warm as the sun <br>But now it is gone <br>And see what it done]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Look What You`ve Done (Remastered / Mono)" label="Look What You`ve Done (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/You_Better_Move_On_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - You Better Move On (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/You_Better_Move_On_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - You Better Move On (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You ask me to give up the hand of the girl I love <br>You tell me, I'm not the man she's worthy of <br>But who are you to tell her who to love? <br>That's up to her, yes, and the Lord above <br>You better move on <br><br>Well I know you can buy her fancy clothes <br>But I believe she's happy with me without those things <br>Still you beg me to set her free <br>But my friend, that will never be <br>You better move on <br><br>Now I don't blame you for loving her <br>But can't you understand, man, she's my girl <br>And I, never never ever gonna let her go <br>'Cuz I, yeah, I love her so <br><br>I think you better go now , I'm getting mighty mad <br>You ask me to give up the only love I've ever had <br>Maybe I would, oh, but I love her so <br>I'm never gonna let her go <br>You better move on <br><br><br><br>Read more: Rolling Stones - You Better Move On Lyrics | MetroLyrics]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="You Better Move On (Remastered / Mono)" label="You Better Move On (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Talkin_‘Bout_You_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Talkin` ‘Bout You (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Talkin_%E2%80%98Bout_You_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - Talkin` ‘Bout You (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Talkin' About You" <br><br>Let me tell you 'bout a girl I know <br>I met her walking down an uptown street <br>She's so fine I wish she was mine <br>I get shook up every time we meet <br>Talkin' bout you (nobody but you, baby) <br>Nobody but you (yes you all the time) <br>I do mean you (yeah my baby) <br>Just trying to get a message to you <br>Let me tell you 'bout a girl I know <br>Help me know she looks so good <br>Lovely skin, well she's soaked in gin <br>She oughta be somewhere in Hollywood <br>Talkin' 'bout you (I'm talkin' 'bout my baby) <br>Nobody but you (yes she's alright) <br>I do mean you (yeah my baby) <br>Just trying to get a message to you <br>Talkin' 'bout you (nobody but you baby) <br>Nobody but you (yes you all the time) <br>I do mean you (yeah yeah) <br>Just trying to get a message to you <br>Let me tell you 'bout a girl I know <br>Sitting right here by my side <br>Lovely indeed that why I ask if she <br>Promise someday she will be my bride <br>Talkin' 'bout you (yeah talk) <br>Nobody but you (yes my my baby) <br>I do mean you (yeah yeah) <br>I'm just trying to get a message through <br>Talkin' bout my baby...]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Talkin` ‘Bout You (Remastered / Mono)" label="Talkin` ‘Bout You (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/She_Said_Yeah_Remastered___Mono/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - She Said Yeah (Remastered / Mono) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/She_Said_Yeah_Remastered___Mono/" title="The Rolling Stones - She Said Yeah (Remastered / Mono) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["She Said Yeah" <br><br>Dam deedle dee dam dam <br>Little girl, where did you come from? <br>Try a little bit to make my mouth dribble <br>Come on baby, let's ride away in the rain <br>Baby you drive me crazy <br>Drive my poor heart hazy <br>Just a little bit <br>A little while with you <br>Come on baby, let's ride away in the rain <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, yeah yeah yeah <br>Come on baby I want to make love to you <br>Well you drive me crazy <br>Dam deedle dee dam dam <br>My love is lazy <br>Dam deedle dee dam dam <br>Little miss I want to kiss <br>Come on baby, won't you do what I wish <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, yeah yeah yeah <br>Come on baby I want to make love to you <br>Yeah, ow! <br>Well I got the feeling, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>In my soul, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>I'm gonna love you, you know <br>One night or another <br>Come on baby, let me hear you say you love me <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, yeah yeah yeah <br>Come on baby I want to make love to you]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="She Said Yeah (Remastered / Mono)" label="She Said Yeah (Remastered / Mono)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Im_Free/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - I`m Free - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Im_Free/" title="The Rolling Stones - I`m Free - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["I'm Free" <br><br>I'm free to do what I want any old time <br>I'm free to do what I want any old time <br>So love me, hold me, love me, hold me <br>I'm free any old time to get what I want <br>I'm free to sing my song though it gets out of time <br>I'm free to sing my song though it gets out of time <br>So love me, hold me, love me, hold me <br>And I'm free any old time to get what I want <br>Love me, hold me, love me, hold me <br>But I'm free any old time to get what I want <br>I'm free to choose what I please any old time <br>I'm free to choose what I please any old time <br>So hold me, love me, love me, hold me <br>I'm free any old time to get what I want, yes I am]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="I`m Free" label="I`m Free"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/The_Under_Assistant_West_Coast_Promotion_Man/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - The Under Assistant West Coast Promotion Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/The_Under_Assistant_West_Coast_Promotion_Man/" title="The Rolling Stones - The Under Assistant West Coast Promotion Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["The Under Assistant West Coast Promotion Man" <br><br>Well I'm waiting at the bus stop in downtown L.A. <br>Well I'm waiting at the bus stop in downtown L.A. <br>But I'd much rather be on a boardwalk on Broadway <br><br>Well I'm sitting here thinkin' just how sharp I am <br>Well I'm sitting here thinkin' just how sharp I am <br>I'm an under assistant west coast promo man, yeah, yeah <br><br>Well I promo groups when they come into town <br>Well I promo groups when they come into town <br>Well they laugh at my toupee, they're sure to put me down <br><br>Well I'm sitting here thinking just how sharp I am <br>Yeah I'm sitting here thinking just how sharp I am <br>I'm a necessary talent behind every rock and roll band <br><br>Yeah, I'm sharp, I'm really, really sharp <br>I sure do earn my pay, sitting on the beach every day <br>Yeah, I'm real real sharp, yes I am <br>I got a Corvette and a seersucker suit, yes I have <br><br>Here comes the bus, uh oh <br>I though I had a dime, where's my dime <br>I know I have a dime somewhere <br>I'm pretty sure]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="The Under Assistant West Coast Promotion Man" label="The Under Assistant West Coast Promotion Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Heart_Of_Stone/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Heart Of Stone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Heart_Of_Stone/" title="The Rolling Stones - Heart Of Stone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Heart Of Stone" <br><br>There've been so many girls that I've known <br>I've made so many cry and still I wonder why <br>Here comes the little girl <br>I see her walking down the street <br>She's all by herself <br>I try and knock her off her feet <br>But, she'll never break, never break, never break, never break <br>This heart of stone <br>Oh, no, no, this heart of stone <br>What's different about her? I don't really know <br>No matter how I try I just can't make her cry <br>Cause she'll never break, never break, never break, never break <br>This heart of stone <br>Oh, no, no, no, this heart of stone <br>Don't keep on looking that some old way <br>If you try acting sad, you'll only make me glad <br>Better listen little girl <br>You go on walking down the street <br>I ain't got no love, I ain't the kind to meet <br>'Cause you'll never break, never break, never break, never break <br>This heart of stone <br>Oh, no, no, you'll never break this heart of stone darlin <br>No, no, this heart of stone <br>You'll never break it darlin <br>You won't break this heart of stone <br>Oh no no no <br>You better go <br>You better go home <br>Cause you'll, you'll never break this heart of stone]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Heart Of Stone" label="Heart Of Stone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Oh_Baby_We_Got_A_Good_Thing_Goin/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Oh, Baby (We Got A Good Thing Goin`) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Oh_Baby_We_Got_A_Good_Thing_Goin/" title="The Rolling Stones - Oh, Baby (We Got A Good Thing Goin`) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Oh Baby (We Got A Good Thing Goin')" <br><br>No matter how she wants me <br>I'm not going nowhere <br>I'm gonna stick right here, babe <br>You know how much I care <br>So don't worry 'bout me baby <br>Cause I'm right here at home <br>Oh baby, oh baby, we got a good thing goin <br>You may talk all about me <br>And scandalize my name <br>But deep down inside me <br>I know I'm the only man <br>So don't worry 'bout me baby <br>Cause I'm right here at home <br>Oh baby, oh baby, we got a good thing goin <br>So maybe I knew her <br>Once upon a time <br>But that's all in the past babe <br>Baby let me know you're mine, all mine, all mine <br>No matter how she wants me <br>I'm not going nowhere <br>I'm gonna stick right here, babe <br>I know how much you care <br>So don't worry 'bout me baby <br>'Cause I'm right here at home <br>Oh baby, oh baby, we got a good thing goin <br>Got a good thing goin' babe <br>We got a good thing goin <br>That's what I said <br>We got a good thing goin <br>Got a ?? one for ourselves <br>Got a thing goin' for ourselves <br>We got a pretty good thing goin]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Oh, Baby (We Got A Good Thing Goin`)" label="Oh, Baby (We Got A Good Thing Goin`)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Cry_To_Me/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Cry To Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Cry_To_Me/" title="The Rolling Stones - Cry To Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Cry To Me" <br><br>When your baby leaves you all alone <br>And nobody call you on the phone <br>Doncha feel like crying <br>Doncha feel like crying like crying like crying <br>C'mon baby, cry to me <br>When you're all alone in your lonely room <br>And there's nothing but the smell of her perfume <br>Doncha feel like crying <br>Doncha feel like crying like crying like crying <br>C'mon baby, (c'mon) cry to me <br>Nothing could be sadder than a glass of wine alone <br>Loneliness loneliness, it just a waste of your time <br>But you don't ever you don't ever have to walk alone <br>You see, so c'mon take my hand <br>C'mon walk with me <br>When you're waiting for a voice to come <br>In the night there is no one <br>Doncha feel like crying <br>Doncha feel like crying like crying like crying <br>C'mon baby, cry to me <br>C'mon baby, that's right cry to me <br>Yes, I want you to come on baby <br>C'mon c'mon cry to me <br>I want you to c'mon baby <br>C'mon c'mon and cry to me <br>Yeah c'mon baby c'mon I want you to cry cry cry to me <br>Yeah I want you to cry cry cry cry cry cry cry <br>I want you to cry cry cry cry cry cry cry cry...]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Cry To Me" label="Cry To Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Talkin_‘Bout_You/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Talkin` ‘Bout You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Talkin_%E2%80%98Bout_You/" title="The Rolling Stones - Talkin` ‘Bout You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Talkin' About You" <br><br>Let me tell you 'bout a girl I know <br>I met her walking down an uptown street <br>She's so fine I wish she was mine <br>I get shook up every time we meet <br>Talkin' bout you (nobody but you, baby) <br>Nobody but you (yes you all the time) <br>I do mean you (yeah my baby) <br>Just trying to get a message to you <br>Let me tell you 'bout a girl I know <br>Help me know she looks so good <br>Lovely skin, well she's soaked in gin <br>She oughta be somewhere in Hollywood <br>Talkin' 'bout you (I'm talkin' 'bout my baby) <br>Nobody but you (yes she's alright) <br>I do mean you (yeah my baby) <br>Just trying to get a message to you <br>Talkin' 'bout you (nobody but you baby) <br>Nobody but you (yes you all the time) <br>I do mean you (yeah yeah) <br>Just trying to get a message to you <br>Let me tell you 'bout a girl I know <br>Sitting right here by my side <br>Lovely indeed that why I ask if she <br>Promise someday she will be my bride <br>Talkin' 'bout you (yeah talk) <br>Nobody but you (yes my my baby) <br>I do mean you (yeah yeah) <br>I'm just trying to get a message through <br>Talkin' bout my baby...]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Talkin` ‘Bout You" label="Talkin` ‘Bout You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Gotta_Get_Away/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Gotta Get Away - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Gotta_Get_Away/" title="The Rolling Stones - Gotta Get Away - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Gotta Get Away" <br><br>Baby, the truth is out so don't deny <br>Baby to think I believed all your lies <br>Darlin' I can't stand to see your face <br>It's the truth, you understand <br>I got to get away, got to get away <br>Gotta, gotta, gotta get away <br>Got to get away <br>Baby, I don't want to live here no more <br>Baby, though I tore your pictures off my walls <br>Darlin' this old room's falling in on me <br>You understand the truth now <br>I got to get away, got to get away <br>Gotta, gotta, gotta get away <br>Got to get away <br>Baby, oh, how could you take away your clothes <br>Baby, don't screw up this old heart of gold <br>Darling, this will rule my social flare <br>You understand me now <br>I got to get away, got to get away <br>Gotta, gotta, gotta get away <br>Got to get away]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Gotta Get Away" label="Gotta Get Away"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Good_Times/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Good Times - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Good_Times/" title="The Rolling Stones - Good Times - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Good Times" <br><br>Whoa la la ta ta <br>Whoa la la ta ta <br>La la la all night long <br>Wanna tell you <br>Whoa la la ta ta <br>Whoa la la ta ta <br>La la la all night long <br>C'mon let the good times roll <br>We're gonna stay here to soothe our soul <br>It could take all night long <br>The evening sun is sinking low <br>The clock on the wall says it's time to go <br>I've got my plans I don't know about you <br>I tell you exactly what I'm gonna do <br>Get in the groove and let the good times roll <br>We're gonna stay here to soothe our soul <br>It could take all night long <br>It might be one o'clock it might be three <br>Time don't mean that much to me <br>Ain't felt this good since I don't know when <br>I might not feel this good again <br>So c'mon let the good time roll <br>We're gonna stay here to soothe our soul <br>It could take all night long <br>All night, all night <br>All night, all night long <br>Somebody said it might take all night long <br>All night, all night whoa <br>C'mon let the good times roll <br>We're gonna stay here to soothe our soul <br>It could take all night long]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Good Times" label="Good Times"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Thats_How_Strong_My_Love_Is/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - That`s How Strong My Love Is - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Thats_How_Strong_My_Love_Is/" title="The Rolling Stones - That`s How Strong My Love Is - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["That's How Strong My Love Is" <br><br>If I was the sun way up there <br>I'd go with my love everywhere <br>I'll be the moon when the sun go down <br>To let you know I'm still around <br>That's how strong my love is, baby <br>That's how strong my love is <br>That's how strong my love is <br>That's how strong my love is <br>I'll be the weeping willow drowning in my tears <br>You can go swimming when you're here <br>I'll be the rainbow when the sun is gone <br>Wrap you in my colors and keep you warm <br>That's how strong my love is <br>That's how strong my love is <br>That's how strong my love is <br>That's how strong my love is <br>I'll be the ocean so deep and wide <br>I'll dry the tears when you cry <br>I'll be the breeze when the storm is gone <br>To dry your eyes and keep you warm <br>That's how strong my love is <br>That's how strong my love is <br>That's how strong my love is <br>Baby that's how strong my love is <br>That's how strong my love is <br>That's how strong my love is <br>That's how strong my love is, baby <br>That's how strong my love is, yeah <br>That's how strong my love is <br>So deep and so wide my love is <br>Yes it is so strong can't get over it <br>Is so wide you can't get around me <br>That's how strong my love is <br>Yeah it so strong, so strong, so strong <br>Yeah yeah yeah, that's how strong my love is, is so strong <br>I wanna tell you can't say how strong it is <br>That's how strong my love is]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="That`s How Strong My Love Is" label="That`s How Strong My Love Is"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Hitch_Hike/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Hitch Hike - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Hitch_Hike/" title="The Rolling Stones - Hitch Hike - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Hitch Hike" <br><br>I'm going to Chicago that's the last place my baby stayed <br>I'm packing up my bags I'm gonna leave this town right away <br>I'm gonna find that girl if I have to hitch hike around the world <br>"Chicago City" that's what the sign on the freeway read <br>I'm gonna keep on going 'til I get to that street's called 6th and Main <br>I've gotta find that girl if i have to hitch hike around the world <br>C'mon hitch hike <br>Hitch hike children <br>Hitch hike <br>Hitch hike baby <br>Hitch hike <br>Hitch hike baby <br>C'mon hitch hike <br>Hitch hike darling <br>I'm going to St. Louis but my next stop just might be L.A., that's what I say <br>I got no money in my pocket so i'm going to have to hitch hike all the way <br>I'm gonna find that girl if i have to hitch hike around the world <br>C'mon hitch hike <br>Hitch hike children <br>Hitch hike <br>Hitch hike baby <br>Hitch hike <br>Hitch hike baby <br>C'mon hitch hike <br>Hitch hike children <br>Now c'mon c'mon hitch hike <br>Hitch hike children <br>Hitch hike <br>Hitch hike darling <br>C'mon hitch hike <br>Hitch hike children <br>Hitch hike hitch hike <br>Hitch hike baby <br>Mmmmm...]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Hitch Hike" label="Hitch Hike"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Mercy_Mercy/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - Mercy Mercy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/Mercy_Mercy/" title="The Rolling Stones - Mercy Mercy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["Mercy Mercy" <br><br>Have mercy, have mercy, baby <br>Have mercy, have mercy on me <br>Well I went to see the gypsy <br>To have my fortune read <br>She said "Man, your baby gonna leave you <br>Her bags are packed up under the bed," <br>That's right <br>Have mercy, have mercy, baby <br>Have mercy, have mercy on me <br>But if you leave me baby <br>Girl if you put me down <br>I'm gonna make it to the nearest river child <br>And jump overboard and drown <br>That's right <br>Have mercy, have mercy, baby <br>Have mercy, have mercy on me <br>I said hey hey baby, hey hey now <br>What you trying to do <br>Hey hey baby, hey hey now <br>Please don't say we're through <br>Have mercy, have mercy, baby <br>Have mercy, have mercy on me <br>But if you stay baby <br>I tell you what I'm gonna do <br>I'm gonna work two jobs, seven days a week <br>And bring my money home to you <br>That's right <br>Have mercy, have mercy, baby <br>Have mercy, have mercy on me <br>Yeah <br>Have mercy, have mercy, baby <br>Have mercy, have mercy on me]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="Mercy Mercy" label="Mercy Mercy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/She_Said_Yeah/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - She Said Yeah - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/She_Said_Yeah/" title="The Rolling Stones - She Said Yeah - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["She Said Yeah" <br><br>Dam deedle dee dam dam <br>Little girl, where did you come from? <br>Try a little bit to make my mouth dribble <br>Come on baby, let's ride away in the rain <br>Baby you drive me crazy <br>Drive my poor heart hazy <br>Just a little bit <br>A little while with you <br>Come on baby, let's ride away in the rain <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, yeah yeah yeah <br>Come on baby I want to make love to you <br>Well you drive me crazy <br>Dam deedle dee dam dam <br>My love is lazy <br>Dam deedle dee dam dam <br>Little miss I want to kiss <br>Come on baby, won't you do what I wish <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, yeah yeah yeah <br>Come on baby I want to make love to you <br>Yeah, ow! <br>Well I got the feeling, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>In my soul, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>I'm gonna love you, you know <br>One night or another <br>Come on baby, let me hear you say you love me <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, dam deedle dee dam dam <br>She said yeah, yeah yeah yeah <br>Come on baby I want to make love to you]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="She Said Yeah" label="She Said Yeah"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/One_More_Try/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - One More Try - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/One_More_Try/" title="The Rolling Stones - One More Try - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["One More Try" <br><br>You need some money in a hurry <br>But things ain't right <br>You try to beg and borrow maybe start a fight <br>Your friends don't wanna know you they just pass you by <br>So they couldn't be your friends because they wouldn't lie <br>Sit down shut up don't dare to cry <br>Things will get better if you really try <br>So don't ya panic don't ya panic <br>Give it one more try <br>Don't ya panic don't ya panic <br>Give it one more try <br>You gotta girl that doesn't bring you all she cries <br>The day turns into night to try to satisfy <br>You buy her all the things she want she don't improve <br>You think you'd give her up if you could make that move <br>Sit down shut up don't dare to cry <br>Things will get better if you really try <br>So don't ya panic don't ya panic <br>Give it one more try <br>Don't ya panic don't ya panic <br>Give it one more try <br>The things that don't matter easy come and go <br>And the things that satisfy only come real slow <br>You gotta know and watch it all in your mind <br>Cause it's better when you get it if you really try <br>Sit down shut up don't dare to cry <br>Things will get better if you really try <br>So don't ya panic don't ya panic <br>Give it one more try <br>Don't ya panic don't ya panic <br>Give it one more try <br>Keep on trying <br>Keep on trying <br>Keep on trying <br>Keep on trying <br>Keep on trying <br>You gotta keep trying]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="One More Try" label="One More Try"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/The_Spider_And_The_Fly/</id><title>The Rolling Stones - The Spider And The Fly - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-24T10:52:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-24T10:52:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Rolling_Stones/The_Spider_And_The_Fly/" title="The Rolling Stones - The Spider And The Fly - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA["The Spider And The Fly" <br><br>Sittin' thinkin' sinkin' drinkin <br>Wondering what I'd do when I'm through tonight <br>Smoking moping, maybe just hopin <br>Some little girl will pass on by <br>Don't wanna be alone but I love my girl at home <br>I remember what she said <br>She said, "My, my, my don't tell lies, keep fidelity in your head <br>My my my, don't tell lies. When you're done you should go to bed <br>Don't say hi, like a spider to a fly <br>Jump right ahead and you're dead" <br>Sit up, fed up, low down go round <br>Down to the bar at the place I'm at <br>Sitting drinking, supereficially thinking <br>About the rinsed-out blonde on my left <br>Then I said, "hi" like a spider to a fly <br>Remebering what my little girl said <br>She was common, flirty, she looked about thirty <br>I would have run away but I was on my own <br>She told me later she's a machine operator <br>She said she liked the way I held the microphone <br>I said my, my, like the spider to the fly <br>Jump right ahead in my web]]></content><category term="The Rolling Stones" label="The Rolling Stones"/><category term="The Spider And The Fly" label="The Spider And The Fly"/></entry></feed>