<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:45:58+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Prince_Royce/Deja_Vu/</id><title>Prince Royce - Deja Vu - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:45:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:45:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Prince_Royce/Deja_Vu/" title="Prince Royce - Deja Vu - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[[Shakira] <br>Tu me abriste las heridas <br>Que ya daba por curados con limon, tequila y sal <br><br>[Prince Royce] <br>Una historia repetida <br>Solamente un deja vu que nunca llega a su final <br>Mejor me quedo solo <br>Y me olvido de tus cosas, de tus ojos <br><br>[Shakira] <br>Mejor esquivo el polvo <br>No quiero caer de nuevo en ese foto <br>De locura, de hipocresia total <br><br>[Shakira] <br>¿Quien puede hablar del amor y defenderlo? <br>¡Que levante la mano por favor! <br><br>[Prince Royce] <br>¿Quien puede hablar del dolor y pagar la fianza <br>¡Pa' que salga de mi corazon! <br><br>[Prince Royce &amp; Shakira] <br>Si alguien va a hablar del amor, te lo aseguro <br>Ese no voy a ser yo <br>No, ese no voy a ser yo <br><br>[Prince Royce] <br>Esta idea recurrente quiere jugar con mi mente <br>Pa' volverme a engatuzar <br><br>[Shakira] <br>Una historia repetida <br>Solamente un deja vu que nunca llega a su final <br>Mejor me quedo sola <br>Me olvido de tus cosas, de tus ojos <br><br>[Prince Royce] <br>Mejor esquivo el polvo <br>No quiero caer de nuevo en esa foto <br>De locura, de hipocresia total <br><br>[Shakira] <br>¿Quien puede hablar del amor y defenderlo? <br>¡Que levante la mano por favor! <br><br>[Prince Royce] <br>¿Quien puede hablar del dolor y pagar la fianza? <br>¡Pa' que salga de mi corazon! <br><br>[Prince Royce &amp; Shakira] <br>Si alguien va a hablar del amor, te lo aseguro <br>Ese no voy a ser yo <br><br>[Prince Royce] <br>¿Quien puede hablar del amor <br><br>[Shakira] <br>Y defenderlo? <br><br>[Prince Royce &amp; Shakira] <br>¡Que levante la mano por favor! <br><br>[Shakira] <br>¿Quien puede hablar del dolor y pagar la fianza? <br>¡Pa' que salga de mi corazon! <br><br>[Prince Royce &amp; Shakira] <br>Si alguien va a hablar del amor, te lo aseguro <br>Ese no voy a ser yo <br>Ese no voy a ser yo]]></content><category term="Prince Royce" label="Prince Royce"/><category term="Deja Vu" label="Deja Vu"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_바이챈스/난_또/</id><title>BiChance (바이챈스) - 난 또 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:46:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:46:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_%EB%B0%94%EC%9D%B4%EC%B1%88%EC%8A%A4/%EB%82%9C_%EB%98%90/" title="BiChance (바이챈스) - 난 또 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 또 누굴 또 만나게 될까 <br>만날 때 마다 평생 함께 할거라 <br>마지막인 것처럼 사랑했지만 <br>이젠 장담 못해 <br>그래도 다 쏟아 붇고 싶어 나 <br>어릴 땐 사랑에 대한 확신 <br>뭣도 없으면서 미친 듯이 <br>누군가를 사랑하기가 <br>어렵지 않았는데 <br>나이 들고 상황은 좋고 <br>여유가 생겼는데도 <br>어려워 더 두려워 <br>어려워 더 두려워 <br>아 하긴 쉴 때도 됐지 뭐 <br>8년을 곁에 누군가를 두고 <br>있느라 감정이 너무 지쳤어 <br>이젠 쉬고 있지 종점을 위해서 <br>아 근데 마지막이라니 <br>아쉽기도 하지만 <br>조카를 보자니 <br>또 마지막이고 싶지 <br>근데 그건 또 내 맘 같지 않지 <br>난 또 누굴 또 만나게 될까 <br>만날 때 마다 평생 함께 할거라 <br>마지막인 것처럼 사랑했지만 <br>이젠 장담 못해 <br>그래도 다 쏟아 붇고 싶어 나 <br>나오는 모든 영화를 <br>같이 보거나 <br>잠들 때마다 영화를 <br>보지 않아도 <br>내 취향의 말투로 <br>내가 잠들 때까지 <br>속삭이고 싶어 <br>숨소리든 목소리든 <br>팀과 메리 나 노아나 엘리 가 <br>되고 싶어 <br>우리 둘이 하는 모든 게 다 <br>영화가 되길 바래 <br>조금 늦어도 괜찮아 이대로 <br>자연스레 다가와줘 <br>모두가 흥분할 스토리로 <br>내게 다가와 <br>난 또 누굴 또 만나게 될까 <br>만날 때 마다 평생 함께 할거라 <br>마지막인 것처럼 사랑했지만 <br>이젠 장담 못해 <br>그래도 다 쏟아 붇고 싶어 나 <br>난 또 누굴 또 <br>난 또 누굴 또 <br>난 또 누굴 또 <br>난 또 누굴 또 <br>난 또 누굴 또 <br>난 또 누굴 또 <br>난 또 누굴 또 <br>난 또 누굴 또 <br>또 또 <br>]]></content><category term="BiChance (바이챈스)" label="BiChance (바이챈스)"/><category term="난 또" label="난 또"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_바이챈스/붕/</id><title>BiChance (바이챈스) - 붕 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:46:32+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:46:32+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_%EB%B0%94%EC%9D%B4%EC%B1%88%EC%8A%A4/%EB%B6%95/" title="BiChance (바이챈스) - 붕 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[해는 중천에 떠있어 <br>떠있어 Right <br>눈 떴는데도 아직 붕 떠 있어 <br>붕붕 <br>기분이 이상해 <br>아니 내 발도 붕 떠있어 <br>홀가분해 모든 게 훅 가있어 <br>해는 중천에 떠있어 <br>떠있어 Right <br>눈 떴는데도 아직 붕 떠 있어 <br>붕붕 <br>기분이 이상해 <br>아니 내 발도 붕 떠있어 <br>홀가분해 모든 게 훅 가있어 <br>아니 사실 차인 거에 가까운데 <br>난 왜 이리 기분이 좋은데 <br>끝났다는 사실보다 <br>새로운 시작을 <br>할 수 있단 게 난 기뻐 <br>이제 밤이나 아침마다 <br>천장은 하얀 스케치북 <br>이제 난 뭘 그릴까 <br>화가는 아니지만 <br>난 내 그림을 사랑해 <br>이제 그릴 수 있을 것 같아 <br>big pictures <br>너 없는 세상은 없어서 <br>다시 내 세상을 그리고 있어 <br>Ma World <br>너 없는 세상은 없어서 <br>다시 내 세상을 그리고 있어 <br>Ma World <br>유난히 밝은 아침 <br>요 근래 몇 년 간에 가장 <br>내가 바랬던 건 하나 <br>없지만 이상하리만큼 <br>행복한 건 건 <br>Fake my life <br>Fake my life <br>누가 날 속인 거야 <br>아 미안 그게 나야 <br>그 애가 곁에 있을 때도 <br>마음은 항상 어려웠고 <br>성공에 가까웠을 때도 <br>표정은 항상 굳어 있었어 <br>주머닌 비고 그 애도 없고 <br>성공은 저 멀리 갔고 <br>자살할 이유는 다 있는데도 <br>이상하리만큼 <br>내 기분은 붕 붕 붕 <br>떠있어 <br>떠있어 Right <br>눈 떴는데도 아직 붕 떠 있어 <br>붕붕 <br>기분이 이상해 <br>아니 내 발도 붕 떠있어 <br>홀가분해 모든 게 훅 가있어 <br>해는 중천에 떠있어 <br>떠있어 Right <br>눈 떴는데도 아직 붕 떠 있어 <br>붕붕 <br>기분이 이상해 <br>아니 내 발도 붕 떠있어 <br>홀가분해 모든 게 훅 가있어 <br>]]></content><category term="BiChance (바이챈스)" label="BiChance (바이챈스)"/><category term="붕" label="붕"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_바이챈스/Walking_On_the_Air_Feat_153/</id><title>BiChance (바이챈스) - Walking On the Air (Feat. 153) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:46:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:46:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_%EB%B0%94%EC%9D%B4%EC%B1%88%EC%8A%A4/Walking_On_the_Air_Feat_153/" title="BiChance (바이챈스) - Walking On the Air (Feat. 153) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Walking on the air <br>모두가 내게 말해 <br>man walking to the sky <br>날아갈 것만 같아 <br>Walking on the air <br>모두가 내게 말해 <br>man walking to the sky <br>날아갈 것만 같아 <br>모든걸 끝내고 집에 와 <br>씻고 난 뒤 커피 한잔과 <br>연애의 온도를 봐도 <br>그녀가 생각이 나질 않잖아 <br>뭔가 달라 진 것 같아 <br>이제서야 Orange를 이해할까 <br>방에 가득 소리로 채워놔 <br>안되겠어 오늘은 와인각 <br>2500원짜리가 내겐 딱 <br>한 잔 들고 음악 틀고 <br>춤추기 시작 <br>Walking on the air <br>모두가 내게 말해 <br>man walking to the sky <br>날아갈 것만 같아 <br>Walking on the air <br>모두가 내게 말해 <br>man walking to the sky <br>날아갈 것만 같아 <br>아무 생각 없이 <br>아무런 압박 없이 <br>난 즐기지 이 소릴 <br>마약 한 것 같이 <br>내 가사에는 의미 <br>가 많이 있지만 여긴 <br>아무 것도 없지 <br>이건 absolute Music <br>이젠 낭만을 원하지 <br>Romantic Music <br>형식이나 공식 <br>은 없지 내 음악은 마치 <br>Walking on the air <br>모두가 내게 말해 <br>man walking to the sky <br>날아갈 것만 같아 <br>Walking on the air <br>모두가 내게 말해 <br>man walking to the sky <br>날아갈 것만 같아 <br>Welcome to the Chillvana Hill <br>palm trees good music <br>서너 번씩 울려대는 카톡 소리는 <br>오늘 밤 우리의 관심 밖이야 <br>밖의 밖의 밖이야 <br>구름 위에 내 발자국을 scrapin' <br>하고 있는데 니 목소리 <br>절대로 들릴 일이 하나도 없지 <br>난 아마 내일의 모레의 <br>그 다음 날쯤 내려갈게 <br>맘마미아 맘마미아 <br>난 풀 냄새 싫어하는데 <br>이건 어쩐 일이야 <br>창문 열어봐 <br>공룡 지나가는지 확인해 <br>아니면 스피커에 <br>내 음악 나오는지 check <br>날 알아 두는 게 좋을 거야 <br>그래 너넨 날 알아 두는 게 <br>좋을 거야 일산에서 <br>유일한 초록머리 뚜벅초 <br>Starbucks green <br>Whatever I'm good <br>Walking on the air <br>모두가 내게 말해 <br>man walking to the sky <br>날아갈 것만 같아 <br>Walking on the air <br>모두가 내게 말해 <br>man walking to the sky <br>날아갈 것만 같아 <br>]]></content><category term="BiChance (바이챈스)" label="BiChance (바이챈스)"/><category term="Walking On the Air (Feat. 153)" label="Walking On the Air (Feat. 153)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_바이챈스/Ask_About_Love/</id><title>BiChance (바이챈스) - Ask About Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:46:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:46:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_%EB%B0%94%EC%9D%B4%EC%B1%88%EC%8A%A4/Ask_About_Love/" title="BiChance (바이챈스) - Ask About Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[첫 마디는 <br>사랑이 뭐야 <br>첫 대답은 <br>오빠가 하는 건 아니야 <br>미련이겠지 좋게 말해도 <br>웃으면서 둘러댔지 나도 <br>알지 나도 답을 알아도 <br>생각처럼 되질 않아 사실 말야 <br>눈감으면 보이던 상상에 넌 <br>지금 내 앞에 너와 많이 달라 <br>많이 달라 <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>우리 사이엔 <br>아메리카노와 바닐라라떼 <br>테이블 위 각자의 <br>지갑과 폰 그것뿐 <br>이상해 이건 아닌데 <br>내 손엔 익숙한 니 프사와 <br>몇 년째 고민하던 <br>연락 했는데 아무렇지 않네 <br>그저 반갑네 마치 오랜만에 <br>만난 친구처럼 <br>잘 지냈냐니 <br>나 땜에 힘들었을 텐데 <br>내가 하는 말들이 모두 한심해 <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>뭐가 다른 건가 <br>이건 아닌 건가 <br>내가 변한 건가 <br>이걸 바랬던가 <br>가만히 널 바라봐 <br>친구들과 했던 <br>말만하며 편히 앉아 <br>몇 년째 담아 뒀던 <br>보고 싶었다는 말과 <br>기다리겠다는 말을 하고 <br>쌓인 오해들과 <br>진심을 한참 얘기하고 <br>집에 가는 길 <br>오래된 숙제를 한 기분이야 <br>솔직히 설레진 않았지 <br>솔직히 설레진 않았지 <br>솔직히 설레진 않았지 <br>솔직히 설레진 않았지 <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>Ask about Love <br>]]></content><category term="BiChance (바이챈스)" label="BiChance (바이챈스)"/><category term="Ask About Love" label="Ask About Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_바이챈스/아직_널_Feat_153/</id><title>BiChance (바이챈스) - 아직 널 (Feat. 153) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:46:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:46:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_%EB%B0%94%EC%9D%B4%EC%B1%88%EC%8A%A4/%EC%95%84%EC%A7%81_%EB%84%90_Feat_153/" title="BiChance (바이챈스) - 아직 널 (Feat. 153) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꿈 속에서 입 맞추다 <br>잠깨니 내 곁에 넌 아닌데 <br>두근두근거리고 있어 <br>내 맘 <br>잠결이라 생각하고 <br>옆에 있는 그녀에 입 맞추고 <br>잠시 앉아 하고 있어 <br>니 생각 <br>맘이 날 모르는 건지 <br>내가 맘을 모르는 건지 <br>나도 날 잘 모르겠어 <br>이게 뭔지 <br>널 기다리는 건지 <br>잊기를 기다리는 건지 <br>난 그저 뭔가를 <br>기다리고 있어 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>기다려 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>기다려 <br>내가 밤하늘일 때 <br>넌 작은 빛 이였는데 <br>내 어둠이 덮었네 <br>밤하늘의 이 별을 <br>해가 뜬 저 하늘엔 <br>흔적은 하나 없는데 <br>하룰 마치고 꿈꾸네 <br>밤 하늘에 이 별을 <br>맘이 나를 모르는 건지 <br>내가 맘을 모르는 건지 <br>나도 날 잘 모르겠어 <br>이게 뭔지 <br>널 기다리는 건지 <br>잊기를 기다리는 건지 <br>난 그저 뭔가를 <br>기다리고 있어 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>기다려 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>기다려 <br>사실 널 기다렸어 <br>근데 오늘 밤은 못 기달려 <br>다시 너에게 전화를 해볼까 <br>친한 척 아님 만취한 척 <br>야 티났어 <br>지금 핸들 잡았으니까 <br>좀 기달려 <br>너의 마디마디 마다마다 <br>나의 흔적을 남겨놨던 <br>그 밤을 알아 <br>잊지 못했기에 <br>니 품으로 다시 돌아가 <br>지나가 버리려는 이 밤의 <br>멱살을 잡아 <br>다시 왔어 너의 집 앞에 <br>길을 잃지도 않았지 <br>난 여기가 젤 <br>내 맘을 편하게 해 <br>문 잠궈 아무도 못나가게 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>기다려 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>기다려 <br>아직 널 아직 널 <br>아직 널 <br>]]></content><category term="BiChance (바이챈스)" label="BiChance (바이챈스)"/><category term="아직 널 (Feat. 153)" label="아직 널 (Feat. 153)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_바이챈스/Justwo/</id><title>BiChance (바이챈스) - Justwo - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:46:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:46:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/BiChance_%EB%B0%94%EC%9D%B4%EC%B1%88%EC%8A%A4/Justwo/" title="BiChance (바이챈스) - Justwo - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나의 숨결이 네 살결에 닿아 <br>나의 숨결이 너의 숨결이 <br>너의 숨결이 내 살결에 닿아 <br>나의 숨결이 너의 숨결이 <br>울리는 우리 목소리 <br>간혹 열고 닫히는 문소리 <br>차가운 벽과 공기 <br>불 꺼지고 어둠이 <br>오면 소리만 남아 가만히 <br>너가 보일때 너의 표정이 <br>뭘 바라는 건지 난 잘알지 <br>눈 감지마 <br>너를 보는 내 눈을 봐 <br>숨 참지마 <br>니 숨은 이미 들리니까 <br>못 참자나 <br>내 모든건 네게 닿아 <br>잠 못들자나 잠 못들자나 <br>나의 숨결이 네 살결에 닿아 <br>나의 숨결이 너의 숨결이 <br>너의 숨결이 내 살결에 닿아 <br>나의 숨결이 너의 숨결이 <br>내 시선은 널 훓고 <br>넌 그런 내 시선을 훓어 <br>작은 움직임조차 느낄수 있어 <br>내가 니 소리를 만들고 <br>또 내 소리를 만들어 <br>우리의 소리가 <br>또 다른 소리를 만들고 있어 <br>눈 감지마 <br>너를 보는 내 눈을 봐 <br>숨 참지마 <br>네 숨은 이미 들리니까 <br>못 참자나 <br>내 모든건 네게 닿아 <br>잠 못들자나 잠 못들자나 <br>나의 숨결이 네 살결에 닿아 <br>나의 숨결이 너의 숨결이 <br>너의 숨결이 내 살결에 닿아 <br>나의 숨결이 너의 숨결이 <br>]]></content><category term="BiChance (바이챈스)" label="BiChance (바이챈스)"/><category term="Justwo" label="Justwo"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태사비애/사랑한_죄_잊지_못하는_벌/</id><title>태사비애 - 사랑한 죄 잊지 못하는 벌 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:46:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:46:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%82%AC%EB%B9%84%EC%95%A0/%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91%ED%95%9C_%EC%A3%84_%EC%9E%8A%EC%A7%80_%EB%AA%BB%ED%95%98%EB%8A%94_%EB%B2%8C/" title="태사비애 - 사랑한 죄 잊지 못하는 벌 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[꽃잎이 떨어지고 <br>그 꽃잎이 또 지고 <br>시간이 흐르고 또 세월이 가도 <br>그 사람 생각나서 <br>너 하나 때문에 <br>그 눈물 때문에 <br>다른 사랑을 믿지 못해 <br>널 사랑한 죄로 <br>나 벌을 받고서 <br>하루 하루를 살아가 <br>지워질 수가 없어 <br>사라지지가 않아 <br>사그라지지 않는 깊은 그 곳은 <br>시간은 거꾸로 가 <br>너 하나 때문에 <br>그 눈물 때문에 <br>다른 사람은 믿지 못해 <br>널 사랑한 죄로 <br>나 벌을 받고서 <br>하루 하루를 살아가 <br>세상 사람이 모두 다 나를 떠나도 <br>나는 당신만 있어주면 돼 <br>말야 그때 순간조차 눈물이 나 <br>이렇게 너에게 미친 내 사랑아 <br>사랑이 뭐라고 <br>당신이 뭐라고 <br>다른 사람은 믿지 못해 <br>너무 사랑해서 <br>가슴이 아파도 <br>나는 그 사람 사랑해 <br>]]></content><category term="태사비애" label="태사비애"/><category term="사랑한 죄 잊지 못하는 벌" label="사랑한 죄 잊지 못하는 벌"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/J_Hus/Did_You_See/</id><title>J Hus - Did You See - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:46:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:46:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/J_Hus/Did_You_See/" title="J Hus - Did You See - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Did you see what <br>Did you see what I done yeah yeah <br>Did you see what I done yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah <br><br>Did you see what I done <br>Came in a black Benz, left in a white one <br>I'm just a hoodlum I came with my bonsam when niggas wanna try some <br>Did you see what I done <br>Came in a black Benz, left in a white one <br>I'm just a hoodlum I came with bonsam when niggas wanna try some <br><br>Came looking like a ganja farmer <br>Your daddy betta hide his daughter <br>Shake her bonda just like I taught her <br>Splashed her bonda with holy water <br>Lickle spice for the winter season <br>Your chicken needs a lickle season yeah <br>Did you see what he did <br>The black benz turn white and they can't believe it <br>Make 'em repeat it <br>Das some new shit <br>They've never seen it <br>You should feel it <br>Meet and greet it <br>I'd be a genius if I didn't think with my penis <br>Gyaldem thinking I'm awesome <br>Mandem approach with caution <br>True say we came with the bonsam <br>But true say we came for the bonda <br>Some round ting that I can put my paws on <br><br>Did you see what I done <br>Came in a black Benz, left in a white one <br>I'm just a hoodlum I came with my bonsam when niggas wanna try some <br>Did you see what I done <br>Came in a black Benz, left in a white one <br>I'm just a hoodlum I came with the bonsam when niggas wanna try some <br><br>Came smelling like I've robbed a 9 bar <br>Looking for the baddest diva <br>Hol' up let me analyse her <br>Batty looking like a hypnotiser <br>Come let me try some <br>Suttin' you can climb on <br>Oh you're a shy one <br>Who you tryna hide from <br>Baby jump in the black ride <br>And put your friend in the white one <br>I'm a benzo addict <br>Pulled up in traffic <br>Me and my friends switched cars and it looked like magic <br>They never seen such a skinny man in a big puffer jacket <br>That's unfamiliar, I came looking like a bodybuilder <br>Out here's windy yana <br>You're the one that I'm into yana <br>Don't you wanna see the interior <br><br>Did you see what I done <br>Came in a black Benz, left in a white one <br>I'm just a hoodlum I came with my bonsam when niggas wanna try some <br>Did you see what I done <br>Came in a black Benz, left in a white one <br>I'm just a hoodlum I came with the bonsam when niggas wanna try some <br><br>Did you see what I done <br>Came in a black Benz, left in a white one <br>I'm just a hoodlum I came with my bonsam when niggas wanna try some <br>Did you see what I done <br>Came in a black Benz, left in a white one <br>I'm just a hoodlum I came with the bonsam when niggas wanna try some]]></content><category term="J Hus" label="J Hus"/><category term="Did You See" label="Did You See"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/달동네왈츠/우리_희망은_여기야/</id><title>달동네왈츠 - 우리 희망은 여기야 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:47:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:47:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8B%AC%EB%8F%99%EB%84%A4%EC%99%88%EC%B8%A0/%EC%9A%B0%EB%A6%AC_%ED%9D%AC%EB%A7%9D%EC%9D%80_%EC%97%AC%EA%B8%B0%EC%95%BC/" title="달동네왈츠 - 우리 희망은 여기야 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[시끄러운 소음 사이로 <br>너의 웃음 들리길 <br>빈틈없는 하룰 넘기며 <br>너의 꿈이 스미길 <br>밀린 아픔을 <br>쏟아내도 무색해지길 <br>둔한 이길이 <br>가벼워지기를 <br>좋은기억 없다 하지만 <br>살아갈만 하기를 <br>숨소리도 힘이 들 만큼 <br>힘든 날도 있지만 <br>달근하게 부는 바람에 <br>너의 한숨 날리길 <br>굳은 두손이 <br>포기가 아니길 <br>어쩌면 남은 현실이 <br>더 진부하겠지 <br>이렇게 오는 그길이 <br>수고스러웠지 <br>익숙한 사람 마저 <br>낯설어진 이길도 <br>함께 간다면 우리 <br>희망은 여기야 <br>좋은기억 없다 하지만 <br>살아갈만 하기를 <br>숨소리도 힘이 들 만큼 <br>힘든 날도 있지만 <br>달근하게 부는 바람에 <br>너의 한숨 날리길 <br>굳은 두손이 <br>포기가 아니길 <br>어쩌면 남은 현실이 <br>더 진부하겠지 <br>이렇게 오는 그길이 <br>수고스러웠지 <br>익숙한 사람 마저 <br>낯설어진 이길도 <br>함께 간다면 우리 <br>희망은 여기야 <br>어쩌면 남은 현실이 <br>더 진부하겠지 <br>이렇게 오는 그길이 <br>수고스러웠지 <br>익숙한 사람 마저 <br>낯설어진 이길도 <br>함께 간다면 우리 <br>희망은 여기야 <br>함께 간다면 우리 <br>희망은 여기야 <br>]]></content><category term="달동네왈츠" label="달동네왈츠"/><category term="우리 희망은 여기야" label="우리 희망은 여기야"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Teachers_PIC_aka_엄선생/과거형_With_랑쑈_Of_버블시스터즈_Prod_ANDRO/</id><title>Teacher`s PIC a.k.a. 엄선생 - 과거형 (With 랑쑈 Of 버블시스터즈) (Prod. ANDRO) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:48:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:48:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Teachers_PIC_aka_%EC%97%84%EC%84%A0%EC%83%9D/%EA%B3%BC%EA%B1%B0%ED%98%95_With_%EB%9E%91%EC%91%88_Of_%EB%B2%84%EB%B8%94%EC%8B%9C%EC%8A%A4%ED%84%B0%EC%A6%88_Prod_ANDRO/" title="Teacher`s PIC a.k.a. 엄선생 - 과거형 (With 랑쑈 Of 버블시스터즈) (Prod. ANDRO) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[잠 못 이루는 밤이 계속 돼 <br>부모님께는 죄송해서 <br>손 벌린 적 없지만 해드린 것 없네 <br>재수없게 되는 건 없고 나이 먹네 <br>곧 마흔이 코앞 <br>어쩌라고 so what <br>안 취하면 못 자 <br>쓸데없는 문자 <br>SNS에 똥싸 질러 한번 웃자 <br>어차피 잠들면 다 잊어 <br>내 꿈에선 이룰까 <br>꿔준 돈처럼 깨면 또 잃을까 <br>꺼진 불처럼 다시 보면 붙을까 <br>열정을 식히는 건 <br>내가 아닌 당신의 결정 <br>돌아보면 까만색 <br>얼룩진 도화지엔 대체 <br>뭘 그린 걸까 <br>삶에 찌든 모습 <br>일그러진 일상 같아 보여 <br>결국 내 얼굴인 건가 <br>내가 하고 싶은 일은 <br>하고 싶던 일로 과거형 <br>꿈과 목표는 바뀌었어 <br>모든 게 일로 닥쳤어 <br>돈 벌면 돼 <br>뭐든지 해서 먹고 살면 돼 <br>모나지 않게 그렇게 <br>뭘 해도 중간인 성격 <br>그만하면 됐어 <br>모자라진 않지만 <br>과하지도 않게 <br>쓸데없는 걱정 <br>잘못된 건 아닌지 <br>혹시 잘못 온 건 아닌 건지 <br>작정 하고 팠던 <br>우물에는 물이 안 나와 <br>아니 찔끔씩 나오는 게 <br>날선 나를 만들어 <br>이런 시련들이 날 더 <br>단단하게 할지 단념하게 할지 <br>발버둥을 치며 <br>하루 벌어 하루 먹어 <br>편의점이 편해진 건 이미 오래 전 <br>또래 친구들은 <br>이미 자릴 잡고 살어 <br>애들 보기 민망한 건 <br>나도 나일 먹어서 일거야 <br>돌아보면 까만색 <br>얼룩진 도화지엔 대체 <br>뭘 그린 걸까 <br>삶에 찌든 모습 <br>일그러진 일상 같아 보여 <br>결국 내 얼굴인 건가 <br>내가 하고 싶은 일은 <br>하고 싶던 일로 과거형 <br>꿈과 목표는 바뀌었어 <br>모든 게 일로 닥쳤어 <br>돈 벌면 돼 <br>뭐든지 해서 먹고 살면 돼 <br>모나지 않게 그렇게 <br>오늘따라 술 생각이 <br>안 나는 건 왜 <br>먹고 마시고 놀 때가 아니라는 <br>생각이 드는 게 더 외로워 <br>오늘따라 술 생각이 <br>안 나는 건 왜 <br>먹고 마시고 놀 때가 아니라는 <br>생각이 드는 게 더 외로워 <br>내가 하고 싶은 일은 <br>하고 싶던 일로 과거형 <br>꿈과 목표는 바뀌었어 <br>모든 게 일로 닥쳤어 <br>돈 벌면 돼 <br>뭐든지 해서 먹고 살면 돼 <br>모나지 않게 그렇게 <br>내가 하고 싶은 일은 <br>하고 싶던 일로 과거형 <br>꿈과 목표는 바뀌었어 <br>모든 게 일로 닥쳤어 <br>돈 벌면 돼 <br>뭐든지 해서 먹고 살면 돼 <br>모나지 않게 그렇게 <br>내가 하고 싶은 일은 <br>하고 싶던 일로 과거형 <br>꿈과 목표는 바뀌었어 <br>모든 게 일로 닥쳤어 <br>돈 벌면 돼 <br>뭐든지 해서 먹고 살면 돼 <br>모나지 않게 그렇게 <br>]]></content><category term="Teacher`s PIC a.k.a. 엄선생" label="Teacher`s PIC a.k.a. 엄선생"/><category term="과거형 (With 랑쑈 Of 버블시스터즈) (Prod. ANDRO)" label="과거형 (With 랑쑈 Of 버블시스터즈) (Prod. ANDRO)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/동요세상/불장난/</id><title>동요세상 - 불장난 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:48:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:48:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%8F%99%EC%9A%94%EC%84%B8%EC%83%81/%EB%B6%88%EC%9E%A5%EB%82%9C/" title="동요세상 - 불장난 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[불장난 하지 말아요 <br>불장난 하면 안돼요 <br>절대 안돼요 큰일 나 <br>불장난 절대로 하지 마세요 <br><br>불장난 하지 말아요 <br>불장난 하면 안돼요 <br>조그만 불씨 커지면 <br>눈 깜짝할 사이 큰 불이 돼요 <br><br>불장난 하지 말아요 <br>불장난 하면 안돼요 <br>착한 어린이 됩시다 <br>성냥을 가지고 놀지 말아요]]></content><category term="동요세상" label="동요세상"/><category term="불장난" label="불장난"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김연은/나보다_더_나를_잘_아는_분/</id><title>김연은 - 나보다 더 나를 잘 아는 분 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:49:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:49:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%97%B0%EC%9D%80/%EB%82%98%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4_%EB%8D%94_%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EC%9E%98_%EC%95%84%EB%8A%94_%EB%B6%84/" title="김연은 - 나보다 더 나를 잘 아는 분 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[길게 여운을 남기던 <br>저녁 황혼이 어둠을 몰고 와 <br>창문 밖으로 <br>나의 모습만이 비치고 <br>어디로 가는지도 모르고 <br>마냥 흘러가는 가슴은 <br>이내 기억 속에 채워지네 <br>오고 가던 그 길거리가 <br>오늘따라 다르게만 보이고 <br>가로등 아래 기대 서 있는 <br>내 모습이 왠지 작게만 느껴져 <br>가만히 모든 걸 내려놓을 때 <br>그분이 대신하시죠 <br>나보다 더 나를 잘 아는 주님께 <br>이젠 맡겨드려요 <br>때론 느낄 수 있었던 <br>행복이라는 그 삶의 의미를 <br>찾아 다니다 홀로 <br>방황하던 나날들 <br>어디에 있는지도 모르고 <br>그냥 스쳐 가는 세상은 <br>이내 시간 속에 변해가네 <br>오고 가던 그 길거리가 <br>오늘따라 다르게만 보이고 <br>가로등 아래 기대 서 있는 <br>내 모습이 왠지 작게만 느껴져 <br>가만히 모든 걸 내려놓을 때 <br>그분이 대신하시죠 <br>나보다 더 나를 잘 아는 주님께 <br>이젠 맡겨드려요 <br>모두 맡겨드려요 <br>]]></content><category term="김연은" label="김연은"/><category term="나보다 더 나를 잘 아는 분" label="나보다 더 나를 잘 아는 분"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/주설옥/평소처럼/</id><title>주설옥 - 평소처럼 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:49:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:49:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A3%BC%EC%84%A4%EC%98%A5/%ED%8F%89%EC%86%8C%EC%B2%98%EB%9F%BC/" title="주설옥 - 평소처럼 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[내 눈물 속 세상은 그대로 <br>어제와 다르지 않을 텐데 <br>왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 <br>너 하나 내게서 떠난다고 <br>어제와 다르지 않을 텐데 <br>왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 <br>근데 왜 이렇게 <br>원하고 원하는지 <br>평소처럼 평소처럼 <br>널 사랑할 수만 있다면 <br>아프면 아프다고 또 슬프다고 <br>말 할 수만 있다면 <br>평소처럼 평소처럼 너 <br>내 옆에 있어준다면 <br>가슴이 답답하고 열이 <br>난다고 날 좀 안아달라고 <br>어두워진 캄캄한 방에서 <br>니가 좋아하던 노래를 하네 <br>예 예 예 예 예 <br>아직도 이해가 안 되는 건 <br>어제와 다르지 않을 텐데 <br>왜 왜 왜 왜 왜 <br>근데 왜 대체 왜 이렇게 <br>아픈 건지 <br>평소처럼 평소처럼 <br>널 사랑할 수만 있다면 <br>아프면 아프다고 또 슬프다고 <br>말 할 수만 있다면 <br>평소처럼 평소처럼 너 <br>내 옆에 있어준다면 <br>가슴이 답답하고 열이 <br>난다고 날 좀 안아달라고 <br>다시 한 번 아무 일 없단 듯이 <br>내게 말 걸어주면 <br>가슴이 터질 듯이 <br>다시 사랑할 텐데 <br>평소처럼 평소처럼 <br>널 사랑할 수만 있다면 <br>아프면 아프다고 또 슬프다고 <br>말 할 수만 있다면 <br>평소처럼 평소처럼 너 <br>내 옆에 있어준다면 <br>가슴이 답답하고 열이 <br>난다고 날 좀 안아달라고 <br>평소처럼 <br>]]></content><category term="주설옥" label="주설옥"/><category term="평소처럼" label="평소처럼"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/에이미/찰떡궁합/</id><title>에이미 - 찰떡궁합 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:49:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:49:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%97%90%EC%9D%B4%EB%AF%B8/%EC%B0%B0%EB%96%A1%EA%B6%81%ED%95%A9/" title="에이미 - 찰떡궁합 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그동안 사귄 적 많았었지만 <br>짜릿한 뭔가가 전혀 없었어 <br>사랑의 감정 못 느껴본 거야 <br>사랑을 많이 한 줄 알았어 <br>널 보게 되면서 느꼈던 거야 <br>예전과는 다른 뭔가 있었어 <br>짜릿한 기분 너의 시선 속에 <br>난 몰래 두근두근 거렸지 <br>너와 나 사이 화학작용에 <br>세상이 전부 꽃 향기야 <br>이런 기분 사랑인가봐 <br>드디어 알게 된 거야 <br>이런 케미돋는 사랑이 너무 좋아 <br>야릇한 느낌이 전해지는 <br>오늘 밤 너와 둘이 있고 싶어 <br>밤새워 사랑하고파 <br>이런 케미돋는 사랑이 너무 좋아 <br>사랑을 드디어 알게 됐어 <br>너 때문에 내 삶이 <br>너무 행복해졌어 고마워 <br>사랑해 사랑해 말을 안 해도 <br>마음으로 전부 느낄 수 있어 <br>너의 눈길이 내 몸을 흔들어 <br>너 역시 나 때문에 흥분해 <br>이런 케미가 너무 짜릿해 <br>우리는 천생연분이야 <br>너와 나는 운명의 상대 <br>드디어 만나게 됐어 <br>이런 케미돋는 사랑이 너무 좋아 <br>야릇한 느낌이 전해지는 <br>오늘 밤 너와 둘이 있고 싶어 <br>밤새워 사랑하고파 <br>이런 케미돋는 사랑이 너무 좋아 <br>사랑을 드디어 알게 됐어 <br>너 때문에 내 삶이 <br>너무 행복해졌어 고마워 <br>케미돋는 사랑이 너무 좋아 <br>야릇한 느낌이 전해지는 <br>오늘 밤 너와 둘이 있고 싶어 <br>밤새워 사랑하고파 <br>이런 케미돋는 사랑이 너무 좋아 <br>사랑을 드디어 알게 됐어 <br>너 때문에 내 삶이 <br>너무 행복해졌어 고마워 <br>]]></content><category term="에이미" label="에이미"/><category term="찰떡궁합" label="찰떡궁합"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/스테디셀러/너에게_Feat_하이디/</id><title>스테디셀러 - 너에게 (Feat. 하이디) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:49:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:49:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8A%A4%ED%85%8C%EB%94%94%EC%85%80%EB%9F%AC/%EB%84%88%EC%97%90%EA%B2%8C_Feat_%ED%95%98%EC%9D%B4%EB%94%94/" title="스테디셀러 - 너에게 (Feat. 하이디) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너에게 주고 싶어 <br>나의 모든 것을 다 <br>너에게 달려가고 있어 <br>나 이렇게 <br>설레는 날씨와 <br>널 닮은 저 햇살이 <br>바람에 날리는 <br>널 담은 향기가 <br>나의 작은 순간들을 <br>가득 채워주는걸 <br>너 없는 시간까지도 <br>온통 너로 가득해 <br>너에게 주고 싶어 <br>나의 모든 것을 다 <br>너에게 달려가고 있어 <br>나 이렇게 <br>너로 가득한 마음이 <br>하늘을 날 수 있도록 <br>그때처럼 웃어줄래 <br>너에게 닿을 수 있게 <br>너에게 주고 싶어 <br>나의 모든 것을 다 <br>너에게 달려가고 있어 <br>나 이렇게 <br>내가 숨 쉴 수 있는 <br>세상이 되어준 <br>너에게 말할게 <br>너만을 사랑한다고 <br>숨결보다 더 따뜻한 <br>너의 하늘 속에서 영원히 <br>너에게 주고 싶어 <br>나의 모든 것을 다 <br>너에게 주고 싶어 <br>나의 모든 것을 다 <br>너에게 달려가고 있어 <br>나 이렇게 <br>]]></content><category term="스테디셀러" label="스테디셀러"/><category term="너에게 (Feat. 하이디)" label="너에게 (Feat. 하이디)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desriot/Alive/</id><title>Desriot - Alive - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:50:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:50:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desriot/Alive/" title="Desriot - Alive - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Close your eyes and think about it <br>When we come here <br>where we are and who I am <br>Calm down and take it easy <br>If you afraid you can't remember <br>The world doesn't change <br>even if I die <br>Yeah Will never change it no more <br>If you wonder what I mean <br>Do not ask Do not ask me <br>Life doesn't give you the answers <br>지금도 시간은 흘러 <br>Just Alive Just Alive Just Alive <br>Yeah You're just alive <br>보이는 게 전부인 너에겐 <br>looks like crazy <br>서로 다른 길을 걸어 <br>But the goal is one 삶이란 <br>길을 따르든 만들든 <br>그건 네 선택일 텐데 <br>The world doesn't change <br>even if I die <br>Yeah Will never change it no more <br>If you wonder what I mean <br>Do not ask Do not ask me <br>Life doesn't give you the answers <br>지금도 시간은 흘러 <br>Just Alive Just Alive Just Alive <br>Yeah You're just alive <br>보이는 게 전부인 너에겐 <br>looks like crazy <br>If you wonder what I mean <br>Do not ask Do not ask me <br>Life doesn't give you the answers <br>아직도 시간은 흘러 <br>Just Alive Just Alive Just Alive <br>Yeah You're just alive <br>보이는 게 전부인 너에겐 <br>looks like crazy <br>]]></content><category term="Desriot" label="Desriot"/><category term="Alive" label="Alive"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desriot/Drawing/</id><title>Desriot - Drawing - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:50:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:50:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desriot/Drawing/" title="Desriot - Drawing - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Always hard <br>무언가 알아간다는 건 <br>Another step <br>저 멀리 널 향해 <br>Always repeat <br>무언가 결정하는 건 <br>Another step <br>서 있는 널 향해 <br>The sun sank below <br>the horizon but <br>We keep going <br>바람을 타고서 <br>어느날 사라진 <br>너를 찾아서 <br>헤매다 잠이들어 <br>Please don't forget <br>our memory <br>해가 뜨면 약속대로 <br>하루가 지나고 <br>눈을 감고 내일을 <br>기다리는 나 <br>Do you remember <br>흐르지 않던 시간 <br>같은 길 <br>다른 발걸음에 맞춰 난 <br>어디론가 바쁘게 <br>가는 사람들 속 <br>그 사이 널 만났을때 <br>그때의 나 <br>그리운 저 너머 <br>I can't wait anymore <br>Fall asleep <br>가끔 난 창가에서 <br>노을을 보며 <br>새벽을 기다려 <br>꿈에서 사라진 <br>너를 만나서 <br>망설이다 눈을 떠 <br>Please don't forget <br>our memory <br>해가 뜨면 약속대로 <br>하루가 지나고 <br>눈을 감고 내일을 <br>기다리는 나 <br>Do you remember <br>흐르지 않던 시간 <br>같은 길 <br>다른 발걸음에 맞춰 난 <br>어디론가 바쁘게 <br>가는 사람들 속 <br>그 사이 널 만났을때 <br>그때의 나 <br>그리운 저 너머 <br>I can't wait anymore <br>Oh <br>]]></content><category term="Desriot" label="Desriot"/><category term="Drawing" label="Drawing"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desriot/Crowd/</id><title>Desriot - Crowd - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:50:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:50:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desriot/Crowd/" title="Desriot - Crowd - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Just not me <br>Everyone think so <br>You don't know <br>Everyone think so <br>This is wrong wrong <br>Why don't you tell me <br>그대로 둔다고 <br>달라질건 없어 <br>Don't count on it <br>I want to live <br>I want to change world <br>at this moment <br>I want to break <br>I want to change you <br>at this moment <br>Think well over <br>what's wrong with it <br>And when you Find out it <br>Don't avoid it <br>That is because the answer <br>is around you <br>crowd and crowd cry <br>Think well over <br>what's wrong with it <br>And when you Find out it <br>Don't avoid it <br>That is because the answer <br>is around you <br>crowd and crowd cry <br>If you don't say anything <br>I don't know who you are <br>말해주면 뭐해 <br>들어주질 않는데 <br>So Did you try <br>수많은 군중들 그 속에 너 <br>앉아서 울고 있는 척 <br>그 모습이 너무 싫어 <br>I want to live <br>I want to change world <br>at this moment <br>I want to break <br>I want to change you <br>at this moment <br>Think well over <br>what's wrong with it <br>And when you Find out it <br>Don't avoid it <br>That is because the answer <br>is around you <br>crowd and crowd cry <br>Think well over <br>what's wrong with it <br>And when you Find out it <br>Don't avoid it <br>That is because the answer <br>is around you <br>crowd and crowd cry <br>Think well over <br>what's wrong with it <br>And when you Find out it <br>Don't avoid it <br>That is because the answer <br>is around you <br>crowd and crowd cry <br>Think well over <br>what's wrong with it <br>And when you Find out it <br>Don't avoid it <br>That is because the answer <br>is around you <br>crowd and crowd cry <br>]]></content><category term="Desriot" label="Desriot"/><category term="Crowd" label="Crowd"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desriot/Warning/</id><title>Desriot - Warning - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:50:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:50:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desriot/Warning/" title="Desriot - Warning - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Warning <br>Get out of my head <br>Too many think <br>I'm gonna burst head <br>Life isn't fair <br>you know that <br>Start <br>It is different for everyone <br>I can not see my way anywhere <br>Nobody around <br>I'm alone <br>Alive <br>it's all the same in the game <br>I can not down my anger <br>Never lose the chain <br>under the deep river <br>they will find you <br>as soon as you give up <br>they will follow you <br>even madly run away <br>Don't try to win <br>cause it will disappear <br>Everybody standing with a knife <br>If you see avoid <br>They will Laughing Out Loud <br>It will over if you look back <br>Crazy <br>If you see avoid <br>They will Laughing Out Loud <br>Please <br>Please Let me go <br>In the kingdom of the blind <br>the one-eyed is king <br>I'm going mad <br>Everybody standing with a knife <br>If you see avoid <br>They will Laughing Out Loud <br>It will over if you look back <br>Crazy <br>If you see avoid <br>They will Laughing Out Loud <br>Everybody standing with a knife <br>If you see avoid <br>They will Laughing Out Loud <br>It will over if you look back <br>Crazy <br>If you see avoid <br>They will Laughing Out Loud <br>]]></content><category term="Desriot" label="Desriot"/><category term="Warning" label="Warning"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desriot/A_Rainy_Night/</id><title>Desriot - A Rainy Night - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:51:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:51:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Desriot/A_Rainy_Night/" title="Desriot - A Rainy Night - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비를 맞으며 걷다 <br>하늘을 보고선 <br>나도 모르는 무언가를 <br>한참 고민해 <br>두 팔을 벌려 <br>차가운 밤공길 <br>끌어안고 하염없이 <br>질문을 던져 <br>Wake up wake up wake up <br>Look at the sky for you <br>Stand up stand up stand up <br>Time is running out <br>침대에서 눈을 떠 <br>어제보다 더 <br>어두워진 밖 <br>폭풍우를 뚫고 달려 <br>Wake up in the night <br>Ready for another fight <br>I really want to cry <br>But searching for a light <br>Wake up in the night <br>Ready for another fight <br>I really want to cry <br>But searching for a light <br>Sometimes I want to stop <br>반복의 굴레 더는 지겨워 <br>모두 내려놓고 싶지만 <br>놓치는 게 슬퍼서 <br>A rainy night <br>난 하늘에 <br>떠올라 비를 맞으며 <br>긴 숨을 내쉬어 <br>땅에 닿았을 때 다시 <br>Wake up in the night <br>Ready for another fight <br>I really want to cry <br>But searching for a light <br>Wake up in the night <br>Ready for another fight <br>I really want to cry <br>But searching for a light <br>Wake up in the night <br>Ready for another fight <br>I really want to cry <br>But searching for a light <br>Wake up in the night <br>Ready for another fight <br>I really want to cry <br>But searching for a light <br>]]></content><category term="Desriot" label="Desriot"/><category term="A Rainy Night" label="A Rainy Night"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Deux_Yvestres/Ego/</id><title>Deux Yvestres - Ego - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:51:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:51:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Deux_Yvestres/Ego/" title="Deux Yvestres - Ego - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't know where I start to say <br>about the time thrown away <br>the book to put down all I felt <br>I never forget what you did <br>I don't know how I’m supposed to tell <br>beautiful moments we shared <br>with good-bye-letters in my hand <br>Something's coming down <br>The mass is coming down <br>Blackout is coming down <br>That fucker's coming down <br>This is falling <br>but no one's gonna find remains <br>It's not the end <br>It goes round and round <br>down to down <br>I don't know why I define myself <br>I don't know why I define myself <br>I don't know why I define myself <br>Something's coming down <br>The mass is coming down <br>Blackout is coming down <br>That fucker's coming down <br>This is falling <br>but no one's gonna find remains <br>It's not the end <br>It goes round and round <br>The mass is coming down <br>Blackout is coming down <br>That fucker's coming down <br>This is falling <br>but doesn't mean anything <br>'cause it's not the end <br>It goes round and round <br>down to down <br>]]></content><category term="Deux Yvestres" label="Deux Yvestres"/><category term="Ego" label="Ego"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Mary/</id><title>Phil Smith - Mary - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:53:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:53:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Mary/" title="Phil Smith - Mary - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Mary left town a long long time ago <br>Where she went to I never did know <br>Now I don't get nothin' but cold driving rain <br>When I take a walk down memory lane <br><br>And the wind it blows hard down the street these days <br>Ain't nothin' but curtains and locks on the gates <br>And I miss her hands at the wheel on the way <br>Down the road to her place at the end of the day <br><br>You wanna stay for a while have a drink <br>With eyes that said more than her mouth ever did <br>And I miss her hands at the wheel on the way <br>Down the road to her place at the end of the day <br><br>And the wind it blows hard down the street these days <br>Ain't nothin' but curtains and locks on the gates <br>See Mary left town a long time ago <br>Where she went to I never did know <br>The day that she left I got drunk fought and swore <br>Felt my heart sink and go right through the floor <br>Kicked a hole clear through the publican's door <br>And busted a window at the company store <br>Walked 15 miles through the cold drivin rain <br>And slept on her porch <br><br>See Mary left town a long long time ago <br>Where she went to I never did know]]></content><category term="Phil Smith" label="Phil Smith"/><category term="Mary" label="Mary"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/One_More_For_The_Road/</id><title>Phil Smith - One More For The Road - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/One_More_For_The_Road/" title="Phil Smith - One More For The Road - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I came down to see you <br>Just the other day <br>I met your ma and she drove the knife <br>A little farther home I'd say <br>Well I can't see to clearly now <br>Through the bottom of this empty cup <br>And even though <br>I know this night won't <br>Lighten up my load <br>You'd better give me <br>One more for the road <br><br>'cause honey I'm a drinker now <br>That's the way it's gonna stay <br>Your streets don't hold much hope for me <br>But I drive 'em all the same <br>And I can't see too clearly now <br>Through the bottom of this empty cup <br>And even though I know this night won't <br>Lighten up my load <br>You'd better give me <br>One more for the road <br><br>I left my heart at the borderline <br>Where the river winds it's way <br>I think of you when I pass through <br>All those fields of blowin' cane <br>Well they all shout your name <br>And I can't see too clearly now <br>Through the bottom of this empty cup <br>Even though I know this night won't <br>Lighten up my load <br>You'd better give me <br>One more for the road]]></content><category term="Phil Smith" label="Phil Smith"/><category term="One More For The Road" label="One More For The Road"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/The_Grave_Of_Margaritis/</id><title>Phil Smith - The Grave Of Margaritis - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/The_Grave_Of_Margaritis/" title="Phil Smith - The Grave Of Margaritis - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Angel lies face down in the graveyard <br>Just flappin' her wings in the cool Autumn breeze <br>And Margaritis died in 1953 <br>A husband and a father <br>Oh Lord there was grief <br>Like you've never seen <br><br>And all around the clouds <br>Were promising rain <br>But what did they bring to the scene <br>Nothing but shadows <br>And a too early grave <br>A too early grave for thee <br><br>Do the headstones confound you <br>The epitaphs they read <br>They found their way home one year at a go <br>Do you float like a drifter <br>Or stop at the scene <br>Aware of the load <br>They would make you carry <br>All the way to the end of the line <br><br>And all around the clouds <br>Were promising rain <br>But what did they bring to the scene <br>Nothing but shadows <br>And a too early grave <br>A too early grave for thee <br><br>And the pine trees that point the way home <br>They offer you no peace at all <br>And the headstones just sink on their owners <br>Like they're tired of standing here too]]></content><category term="Phil Smith" label="Phil Smith"/><category term="The Grave Of Margaritis" label="The Grave Of Margaritis"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Where_Does_It_Go_/</id><title>Phil Smith - Where Does It Go? - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Where_Does_It_Go_/" title="Phil Smith - Where Does It Go? - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I pack a change of clothes <br>In case she asks me to stay <br>At the end of the day <br><br>But we've been down that road <br>Too many times <br>And some things they don't ever change <br>No matter how you try <br><br>Dropped you off as the sun <br>Bid us goodnight <br>And I remember someone once told me <br>Love never dies <br><br>So where does it go <br><br>And I hold her tight <br>But she don't love me like you did <br>Oh darling I'm sorry <br>I acted just like I did <br>And oh Lord we tried <br>The best that we knew <br>I don't know how this love left us <br>Feeling so blue <br><br>So where does it go <br><br>Just like lovers do <br>Oh we had our fights <br>At the end of the day <br>It ain't about who's wrong <br>And it ain't about who's right <br>And I guess we loved <br>But sometimes that's not enough <br>To keep two people together <br>And we fell apart <br><br>Where does it go]]></content><category term="Phil Smith" label="Phil Smith"/><category term="Where Does It Go?" label="Where Does It Go?"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Everybodys_Going_Somewhere/</id><title>Phil Smith - Everybody`s Going Somewhere - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Everybodys_Going_Somewhere/" title="Phil Smith - Everybody`s Going Somewhere - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Head out the drive <br>Turn left, then right, then right again <br>Hit the freeway hard <br>And slip alone through the night <br>Slip alone through the night <br><br>Head into the night <br>Just like a shooting star <br>But don't tell no one <br>And don't believe all ya hear <br><br>Cause everybody's going somewhere <br>Yeah everybody's going somewhere <br>Oh everybody's going somewhere <br><br>Head into the night <br>Just like a shooting star <br>But don't believe all you see <br>And don't tell no one <br>Cause it's a secret <br>Oh oh it's a secret <br><br>Everybody's going somewhere x 3]]></content><category term="Phil Smith" label="Phil Smith"/><category term="Everybody`s Going Somewhere" label="Everybody`s Going Somewhere"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Baby_Doll/</id><title>Phil Smith - Baby Doll - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Baby_Doll/" title="Phil Smith - Baby Doll - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Maybe I should just stop running <br>Make a stand and fold this hand <br>I'm holding on too tight <br>The joker's wearing kind of thin <br>The queen of hearts she tells me <br>Boy you'd better make a choice, you're wearing out your welcome here <br><br>La de da, just like a boy <br>But you know I wanna be a man <br>And girl I know you're not a toy <br><br>Can you help me understand <br>Can you help me understand <br><br>Night she sets out on the city <br>I wanna come in from the cold <br>But maybe I'm too old to ever change my weary ways <br>Baby doll, baby doll, do I disappoint you <br>Looking for the answers <br>Losing sight of what I got in my two hands <br><br>La de da, just like a boy <br>But you know I wanna be a man <br><br>Oh girl I know you're not a toy <br>Can you help me understand <br>Can you help me understand <br>Can you help me understand <br><br>Bounced around for all these years <br>Just like a pinball in the back room <br>Of some bar you're never been <br>Waiting for someone to play <br>But it's closing time and everybody's holding hands or <br>Drunk or both, oh God am I too late <br><br>La de da, just like a boy <br>But you know I wanna be a man <br>Oh girl I know you're not a toy <br><br>Can you help me understand <br>Can you help me understand <br>Can you help me understand]]></content><category term="Phil Smith" label="Phil Smith"/><category term="Baby Doll" label="Baby Doll"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Ill_Walk_The_Line_One_More_Time/</id><title>Phil Smith - (I`ll Walk The Line) One More Time - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Ill_Walk_The_Line_One_More_Time/" title="Phil Smith - (I`ll Walk The Line) One More Time - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Turn off the fan and lie in the cool morning air <br>And hold my love tight <br>To the sound of the freeway I'd die if I go nowhere <br>But she holds back the night <br><br>And I'll walk the line one more time <br>Oh I'll walk the line one more time <br><br>If you find love is nothing but flowers and a crying despair You know love ain't there <br>In the evening she comes and she tries <br>To make peace all our own <br>Oh why do I fight it would I die alone <br><br>And I'll walk the line one more time <br>Oh I'll walk the line one more time <br><br>And I mean every word that I say, nothing more nothing less <br>And you know that I long, I long to be near <br>To love you and hold you and feel your soft caress <br>And I mean what I say, nothing more, nothing less <br><br>Oh I'll walk the line one more time <br>Yes I'll walk the line one more time <br>Oh I'll walk the line one more time <br>Yes I'll walk the line one more time]]></content><category term="Phil Smith" label="Phil Smith"/><category term="(I`ll Walk The Line) One More Time" label="(I`ll Walk The Line) One More Time"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Blackbird/</id><title>Phil Smith - Blackbird - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Blackbird/" title="Phil Smith - Blackbird - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When the rain falls down <br>Will you drive straight home <br>To be with him, in his time of need <br>In his time of need <br><br>When the blackbird sings <br>Will you spread you wings and fly <br>Straight in to the sky, with no regrets <br>With no regrets <br><br>And it sure feels good to be back home again <br>It sure feels good to be standing again, at your side <br>Oh we worked hard, but we worked out all right <br><br>Will you pack yr bags, will you drive straight home <br>To see him girl when he calls yr name <br><br>When the blackbird sings <br>Will you spread you wings and fly <br>Straight in to the sky, with no regrets <br>With no regrets <br><br>And it sure feels good to be back home again, that's right <br>It sure feels good to be standing again, at your side <br>Oh we worked hard, but we worked out all right <br><br>When the rain falls down <br>Will you drive straight home <br>To be with him <br>When the blackbird sings <br>Will you spread you wings and fly <br>Straight in to the sky, with no regrets <br>With no regrets]]></content><category term="Phil Smith" label="Phil Smith"/><category term="Blackbird" label="Blackbird"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Annie/</id><title>Phil Smith - Annie - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Annie/" title="Phil Smith - Annie - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Down on the esplanade we'd walk at night <br>Watch the flames as someone else played with fire <br>The Western Pier just like a satellite <br>That someone set on fire and pushed into the night <br><br>We crossed the road and you kissed me hard enough <br>To knock me down, down, down <br>One smile from you was usually all it took <br>To knock me out <br><br>And outside all the leaves are falling down <br>But I loved you Annie <br>Riding through these streets just like the wind <br>Oh I loved you Annie straight as I could be <br><br>You were the shining light I'd never be <br>You had to save yourself for someone else to glow <br>You lit the night up like a shooting star <br>I was caught up in the blazing tail <br><br>You looked at me then kissed me hard enough <br>To knock me down <br>One smile from you was usually all it took <br>To knock me out <br><br>And outside all the leaves are falling down <br>But I loved you Annie <br>Riding through these streets just like the wind <br>Oh I loved you Annie <br>Straight as I could be <br><br>I never really held you long enough to really make a change <br>And all the stars that stand above us now for a while we burned as bright <br>And all the stars that stand above us now for a while we burned as bright X2 <br><br>I loved you Annie straight as I could be <br>I loved you Annie how did you love me <br>I loved you Annie straight as I could be <br>I loved you Annie how did you love me]]></content><category term="Phil Smith" label="Phil Smith"/><category term="Annie" label="Annie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Goldmine/</id><title>Phil Smith - Goldmine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Phil_Smith/Goldmine/" title="Phil Smith - Goldmine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I got a smell of death <br>From the house on the hill <br>I learnt it at an early age <br>I learnt it well <br><br>And the goldmine's still burning <br>At the back of my mind and it's fierce <br>And the long road's still calling <br>Like a star on the hill <br>Late at night all alone <br><br>When the phone rings in the dead of the night <br>I still feel that fear <br>When the car left the road, and no sound followed <br>Oh Lord I said a prayer <br><br>And the goldmine's still burning <br>At the back of my mind and it's fierce <br>And the long road still haunts me <br>Like a star on the hill <br>Late at night all alone <br><br>I got a smell of death <br>From the house on the hill <br>I learnt it at an early age <br>I learnt it well, I learnt it well]]></content><category term="Phil Smith" label="Phil Smith"/><category term="Goldmine" label="Goldmine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VICTON_빅톤/SUNRISE/</id><title>VICTON (빅톤) - SUNRISE - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VICTON_%EB%B9%85%ED%86%A4/SUNRISE/" title="VICTON (빅톤) - SUNRISE - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다 지나갈 거라고 속삭였지 <br>다 괜찮을 거라고 생각했지 Uh <br>달려온 길들을 돌아보면 <br>곳곳엔 상처들이 가득 남아 <br>불안했었던 시간 <br>우린 이제 빛을 볼 거야 <br>너와 보고 싶었던 <br>Sunrise <br>매일 우릴 위해 빛날 거야 <br>너와 간직하고 싶던 <br>Sunrise <br>더 이상 놓치지는 않을 거야 <br>마냥 즐거웠던 좋은 기억들만 <br>되새기며 힘들 땐 내게 기대 <br>오늘은 더 밝아질 <br>Sunrise <br>Brighter sunrise <br>Woo sunrise <br>또 돌아올 거라고 <br>기다리던 Uh <br>더 늘어갈 거라고 <br>늘 반복했지 Uh <br>달려온 길들을 돌아보면 <br>조그만 이 추억에 <br>목이 메어와 <br>불안했었던 시간 <br>우린 이제 빛을 볼 거야 <br>너와 보고 싶었던 <br>Sunrise <br>매일 우릴 위해 빛날 거야 <br>너와 간직하고 싶던 <br>Sunrise <br>더 이상 놓치지는 않을 거야 <br>마냥 즐거웠던 좋은 기억들만 <br>되새기며 힘들 땐 내게 기대 <br>오늘은 더 밝아질 <br>Sunrise <br>Brighter sunrise <br>Woo sunrise <br>Yeah We gonna shine <br>bright like a sunrise <br>You just hold me tight babe <br>it's gonna be a alright <br>여기가 어디일까 겁이 나 <br>머리가 조인다만 뒤돌지 마 <br>넌 충분히 잘해왔고 잘하고 있어 <br>keep going <br>진짜 내 말 믿어 넌 잘하고 있어 <br>keep going <br>Like the sunrise <br>기다렸던 <br>Sunrise uh <br>Sunrise Sunrise <br>저 멀리서 더 빛나게 기다려 <br>다가갈 테니 <br>너와 보고 싶었던 <br>Sunrise <br>매일 우릴 위해 빛날 거야 <br>너와 간직하고 싶던 <br>Sunrise <br>더 이상 놓치지는 않을 거야 <br>마냥 즐거웠던 좋은 기억들만 <br>되새기며 힘들 땐 내게 기대 <br>오늘은 더 밝아질 <br>Sunrise <br>Brighter sunrise <br>Woo sunrise <br>Oh Sunrise Sunrise <br>]]></content><category term="VICTON (빅톤)" label="VICTON (빅톤)"/><category term="SUNRISE" label="SUNRISE"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VICTON_빅톤/이_나쁜/</id><title>VICTON (빅톤) - 이 나쁜.. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VICTON_%EB%B9%85%ED%86%A4/%EC%9D%B4_%EB%82%98%EC%81%9C/" title="VICTON (빅톤) - 이 나쁜.. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hey girl <br>What's going on <br>what's going on huh <br>You the one and only <br>Bae I'm sorry please <br>오늘따라 차가운 분위기 <br>말이라도 해줘 <br>하루 종일 눈칫밥만 먹어 <br>네 옆에서 <br>뭐가 그리 문젠지 <br>왜 이리 꿍한 건지 <br>풀래야 풀 수가 없는 <br>어려운 너지 <br>무슨 말이라도 욕이라도 해 <br>그게 널 풀리게 하지는 <br>않겠지만 <br>미안 미안 미안 미안해 <br>Oh my girl <br>이미 늦었겠지만 <br>이 나쁜 손이 Ah <br>널 멀리하게 했어 <br>이 못된 말이 <br>Sorry baby <br>널 잃게 만들어 <br>잡지 못해 <br>I'll be Waiting <br>잡지 못하는 나 <br>있을 때 잘해주지 못한 나 <br>Oh Yeah <br>Get on Get on Get on <br>Get on Get on <br>나쁜 이 남자를 용서해줘 <br>Get on Get on Get on <br>Get on Get on <br>더 잘할게 <br>Still tick tockin' <br>우린 잠시 멈추고 <br>사랑만 하기에도 <br>모자란 시간만 흘러 <br>바닥에 내 무릎이 <br>하늘에 내 두 손이 <br>널 바라보는 내 눈빛이 <br>말하고 있는 걸 <br>잘못했단 말도 용서하라고 <br>어떤 말도 풀리는 말은 <br>없겠지만 <br>딱 한 번만 나를 봐줄래 <br>Oh my girl <br>이미 늦었겠지만 <br>이 나쁜 손이 <br>Ah <br>널 멀리하게 했어 <br>이 못된 말이 <br>Sorry baby <br>널 잃게 만들어 <br>잡지 못해 <br>I'll be Waiting <br>잡지 못하는 나 <br>있을 때 잘해주지 못한 나 <br>Oh Yeah <br>Get on Get on Get on <br>Get on Get on <br>나쁜 이 남자를 용서해줘 <br>Get on Get on Get on <br>Get on Get on <br>더 잘할게 <br>이렇게 나 매달리잖아 <br>Oh 내가 착해 주지 못해서 <br>그게 미안해 <br>그래 이런 나 받아줄 <br>여잔 없어 너밖에 <br>너 없이 나 버틸 자신 <br>없는 거 잘 알잖아 <br>지금 당장에 네 앞에 <br>날 바라보고 말해 <br>내가 더 잘할게 <br>이제 진짜 더 이상은 안돼 <br>이 나쁜 손이 <br>Ah <br>널 멀리 하게했어 <br>이 못된 말이 <br>Sorry baby <br>널 잃게 만들어 <br>잡지 못해 <br>I'll be Waiting <br>잡지 못하는 나 <br>있을 때 잘해주지 못한 나 <br>Oh Yeah <br>Get on Get on Get on <br>Get on Get on <br>나쁜 이 남자를 용서해줘 <br>Get on Get on Get on <br>Get on Get on <br>더 잘할게 <br>Get on Get on Get on <br>Get on Get on <br>나쁜 이 남자를 용서해줘 <br>Get on Get on Get on <br>Get on Get on <br>더 잘할게 <br>]]></content><category term="VICTON (빅톤)" label="VICTON (빅톤)"/><category term="이 나쁜.." label="이 나쁜.."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VICTON_빅톤/얼타/</id><title>VICTON (빅톤) - 얼타 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VICTON_%EB%B9%85%ED%86%A4/%EC%96%BC%ED%83%80/" title="VICTON (빅톤) - 얼타 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[왜 또 얼타 얼타 얼타 <br>왜 이래 왜 이래 왜 이래 Uh <br>나 자꾸만 얼타 왜 이런 걸까 <br>오늘따라 내가 왜 이런 걸까 <br>이유는 네가 너무 예뻐서 <br>이유는 네가 너무 예뻐서 <br>왜 그렇게 얼타냐고 물어봐도 <br>답을 못하는 이유는 뭘까 <br>왜냐면 네가 너무 쩔어서 <br>왜냐면 네가 너무 쩔어 쩔어서 Baby <br>오늘의 문제 <br>네가 딱 붙는 거 입고 <br>등장하는 순간 심장 두근 <br>눈을 어디다 둘까 <br>고민하는 그 순간 <br>너의 미소 한방에 <br>난 죽음 죽음 <br>한발 빼려고 하면 <br>두발 들어오는 걸 <br>이런 널 어떻게 해 <br>자꾸 숨 가쁘게 두드리는데 <br>오늘 넌 오늘 넌 오늘 넌 <br>과감하니까 <br>나 자꾸만 얼타 왜 이런 걸까 <br>오늘따라 내가 왜 이런 걸까 <br>이유는 네가 너무 예뻐서 <br>이유는 네가 너무 예뻐서 <br>왜 그렇게 얼타냐고 물어봐도 <br>답을 못하는 이유는 뭘까 <br>왜냐면 네가 너무 쩔어서 <br>왜냐면 네가 너무 쩔어 쩔어서 Baby <br>멍 때려 멍 때려 왜 내가 <br>멍 때려 멍 때려 널 보면 <br>벙 찌고 벙 찌고만 있어 <br>오늘의 문제 <br>너 때문에 내가 <br>매일 밤 매일 밤마다 <br>아무렇지 않은 척 <br>아무것도 아닌 척 해봐도 <br>잠은 오지를 않고 <br>자꾸 너만 오는데 <br>이런 널 어떻게 해 <br>숨 막히게 들어오는데 <br>오늘도 오늘도 오늘도 <br>얼 타는데 <br>나 자꾸만 얼타 왜 이런 걸까 <br>오늘따라 내가 왜 이런 걸까 <br>이유는 네가 너무 예뻐서 <br>이유는 네가 너무 예뻐서 <br>왜 그렇게 얼타냐고 물어봐도 <br>답을 못하는 이유는 뭘까 <br>왜냐면 네가 너무 쩔어서 <br>왜냐면 네가 너무 쩔어 쩔어서 Baby <br>Yeah right <br>이렇게 너무 쩔어주게 예쁘면 <br>내가 막 얼타 얼타 <br>근데 내가 너무 얼빠지게 <br>얼타는 사이 <br>딴 늑대들은 뭘 봐 뭘 봐 <br>EY Bay I wanna <br>너와 나의 콜라보 <br>난 너의 순애보 <br>대체 왜 내 맘을 몰라줘 <br>자꾸 다가오면서 왜 또 <br>한발 두발 세발 네가 <br>왜 또 멍 때려 멍 때려 왜 내가 <br>멍 때려 멍 때려 널 보면 <br>벙 찌고 벙 찌고만 있어 <br>난 어이 어이없어 <br>멍 때려 멍 때려 왜 내가 <br>정신 없어 정신 없어서 나 <br>얼타고 얼타고만 있어 <br>왜 그렇게 얼타냐고 물어봐도 <br>답을 못하는 이유는 뭘까 <br>왜냐면 네가 너무 쩔어서 <br>왜냐면 네가 너무 쩔어 쩔어서 Baby <br>나 또 얼타 얼타 얼타 <br>난 어이 어이없어 <br>]]></content><category term="VICTON (빅톤)" label="VICTON (빅톤)"/><category term="얼타" label="얼타"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VICTON_빅톤/IN_THE_AIR/</id><title>VICTON (빅톤) - IN THE AIR - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VICTON_%EB%B9%85%ED%86%A4/IN_THE_AIR/" title="VICTON (빅톤) - IN THE AIR - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Yeah <br>Already know what it is ya <br>Ay bae hands up in the air <br>매일 밀리언 <br>Songs on the floor <br>여길 지켜봐 우린 넘 달라 <br>내가 살짝 Groove 타면 <br>모두 숨죽여 비추지 Spotlight <br>전부 나만 쳐다보는 걸 <br>머리 손 발끝까지 <br>Looks good <br>방심하고 쳐다보다 <br>Uh 출구는 없을걸 No way <br>Yeah 볼륨을 높여줘 Game on <br>Yeah girl I know 뭐 원하는지 <br>낮은 조명 아래도 <br>터지는 Potential <br>알고 있어 벌써 <br>느끼고 있는 걸 <br>보여줄게 이쯤에서 <br>Welcome to my world <br>이제 두 손 높이 들어 <br>Hands in the air <br>우릴 따라 <br>Let’s do it let’s go <br>Wave it in the air 마치 <br>just don’t care what <br>Wave it in the air 같이 <br>just don’t just don’t <br>Wave it in the air 마치 <br>just don’t care <br>느껴지니 감 오니 <br>U got it u got it <br>Oh 나 원해 더 높이 <br>손을 In the air <br>I want that 더 크게 외쳐 <br>In the air <br>야 야 내가 다 뻘쭘해 <br>어디서 본 건 있어 <br>갖고 죄다 흉내 <br>I don’t really care <br>about what you say <br>오늘은 뭐든지 Okay Yeah <br>Twenty four seven <br>three sixty five <br>We livin one life <br>and one try Yeah <br>지금 이 순간에도 <br>시간은 계속 가 <br>Key는 내 손에 있어 <br>baby let’s ride <br>좀 더 늦기 전에 <br>진짤 알아봐 Right now <br>날 봐 돌아서서 <br>더 즐겨봐 Good life <br>보여줄게 상상도 못했던 <br>Brand nu world <br>이제 두 손 높이 들어 <br>Hands in the air <br>우릴 따라 <br>Let’s do it let’s go <br>Wave it in the air <br>마치 just don’t care what <br>Wave it in the air <br>같이 just don’t just don’t <br>Wave it in the air <br>마치 just don’t care <br>느껴지니 감 오니 <br>U got it u got it <br>Oh 나 원해 더 높이 <br>손을 In the air <br>I want that 더 크게 외쳐 <br>In the air <br>멈추지 말아줘 My fantasy <br>I wanna make you mine yeah <br>점점 이끌려와 To my galaxy <br>점점 끌려와 Uh <br>준비됐어 이젠 다 보여줄게 <br>So beautiful 지금 이 순간 <br>Don’t let it go <br>Wave it in the air <br>마치 just don’t care what <br>Wave it in the air <br>같이 just don’t just don’t <br>Wave it in the air <br>마치 just don’t care <br>느껴지니 감 오니 <br>U got it u got it <br>Oh 나 원해 더 높이 <br>손을 In the air <br>I want that 더 크게 외쳐 <br>In the air <br>나 원해 더 높이 <br>손을 In the air <br>I want that 더 크게 외쳐 <br>In the air <br>Wave it in the air <br>마치 just don’t care what <br>Wave it in the air <br>같이 just don’t just don’t <br>Wave it in the air <br>마치 just don’t care <br>Wave it in the air <br>마치 just don’t care <br>Wave it in the air <br>같이 just don’t just don’t <br>Wave it in the air <br>마치 just don’t care <br>더 높이 손을 In the air <br>]]></content><category term="VICTON (빅톤)" label="VICTON (빅톤)"/><category term="IN THE AIR" label="IN THE AIR"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VICTON_빅톤/EYEZ_EYEZ/</id><title>VICTON (빅톤) - EYEZ EYEZ - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:54:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:54:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VICTON_%EB%B9%85%ED%86%A4/EYEZ_EYEZ/" title="VICTON (빅톤) - EYEZ EYEZ - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[E Y E Z <br>Woo 우리 오랜만에 봤잖아 <br>내가 많이 서운했잖아 <br>조금만 더 네가 늦었다면 <br>뒤끝 작렬했을 거야 Bebe <br>Woo 넌 또 핸드폰만 보네 매번 <br>그런 건 That’s no no 해 <br>이건 에바야 에바에바야 <br>뭐라 해봐야 진짜 에바야 <br>날 두고 네가 네가 네가 왜 <br>어딜 어딜 어딜 봐 <br>너까지 나한테 이러지 말고 <br>나만 봐줘 Eyez Eyez Bebe Woo <br>꿀 떨어지게 <br>매일매일 Eyez Eyez Bebe <br>저 별처럼 Okay <br>반짝이는 Ice Ice My Bebe Woo <br>너만 담을게 영원히 <br>Shinin You Shinin You <br>Eyez Eyez Eyez Eyez <br>Look at my eyez <br>EYEZ EYEZ EYEZ <br>EYEZ EYEZ <br>내 사랑은 One way One way <br>뻥 터져버릴 Pompeii Pompeii <br>이제는 내가 하는 <br>모든 말들은 네 귀엔 <br>Bow wow wow wow <br>Yippy Yo Yippy Yeah <br>넌 폰만 쳐다보며 웃어 <br>예쁘게 Babe <br>날 잠금 화면처럼 밀어 <br>Lay Back Yeah <br>I want it 그저 따스한 눈빛 <br>한 번이면 풀리지 <br>아 진짜 이건 이건 아닌데 <br>지적한 거 아닌데 <br>무섭게 인상 좀 쓰지 말고 <br>나만 봐줘 Eyez Eyez Bebe Woo <br>꿀 떨어지게 <br>매일매일 Eyez Eyez Bebe <br>저 별처럼 Alright <br>반짝이는 Ice Ice My Bebe Woo <br>너만 담을게 영원히 <br>Shinin You Shinin You <br>Eyez Eyez Eyez Eyez <br>Look at my eyez <br>여긴 어디 나는 누구 <br>할 정도로 나에게 <br>빠져버렸으면 좋겠는데 <br>날 가지고 놀면서 <br>밀고 또 당길 때면 <br>어쩔 수 없어 또 끌려 다녀도 <br>자꾸 져주고 싶어 <br>나만 봐줘 Eyez Eyez Bebe Woo <br>꿀 떨어지게 <br>매일매일 Eyez Eyez Bebe 저 별처럼 <br>반짝이는 Ice Ice My Bebe Woo <br>너만 담을게 영원히 <br>Shinin You Shinin You <br>Eyez Eyez Eyez Eyez <br>Look at my eyez <br>EYEZ EYEZ EYEZ EYEZ EYEZ <br>E 내 눈 안에 너 <br>Y 네 눈 안에 나 <br>E 내 맘 안에 너 너 <br>Z <br>E Y E Z <br>]]></content><category term="VICTON (빅톤)" label="VICTON (빅톤)"/><category term="EYEZ EYEZ" label="EYEZ EYEZ"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fukjo/Nord/</id><title>Fukjo - Nord - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:57:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:57:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fukjo/Nord/" title="Fukjo - Nord - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Invecchierai in posti freddi sai io resto qui <br>mi fermo ancora un po' <br>In una mera illusione <br>in cui potro perdermi ancora un altro po' <br>Siamo il gelo ormai <br><br>Neve io saro e non mi perderai lo sai il gusto lo conosci gia？？ <br>E se perderai, spariro <br>Ormai siamo il gelo ormai]]></content><category term="Fukjo" label="Fukjo"/><category term="Nord" label="Nord"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fukjo/Quello_Che_Mi_Do/</id><title>Fukjo - Quello Che Mi Do - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:57:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:57:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fukjo/Quello_Che_Mi_Do/" title="Fukjo - Quello Che Mi Do - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lasciami un istante a ricordare la mia vile sensazione <br>quella che non riesco piu a provare nel doverti digerire <br>Piuttosto che pensare tutto il giorno ad una vera <br>soluzione t'affanni con vedute insulse oggettivamente <br>troppo acute <br><br>Quello che mi do, quello che mi do <br>quello che mi do non fa piu <br>Fatti spazio amore <br>nel mio inferno c'e un bel sole <br>Quello che mi do, quello che mi do <br>quello che mi do non fa piu male]]></content><category term="Fukjo" label="Fukjo"/><category term="Quello Che Mi Do" label="Quello Che Mi Do"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fukjo/Saturno_Contro/</id><title>Fukjo - Saturno Contro - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:57:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:57:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fukjo/Saturno_Contro/" title="Fukjo - Saturno Contro - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lasciami capire dove andare e lo farei senza di te <br>ogni mia rivoluzione ha bisogno di parole che non dirai <br>Abbiamo saturno contro amore <br>mi dici non ci pensare <br>nei tuoi viaggi stellari, nelle cene fuori <br>nelle offerte speciali <br>io trovero un pezzo di noi Un pezzo di noi <br>Aria non mi vantero Aria non mi vantero <br>Aria non mi vantero Aria non mi vantero <br>Nei tuoi viaggi stellari, nelle cene fuori <br>nelle offerte speciali io trovero un pezzo di noi]]></content><category term="Fukjo" label="Fukjo"/><category term="Saturno Contro" label="Saturno Contro"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fukjo/Winchester/</id><title>Fukjo - Winchester - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:57:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:57:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fukjo/Winchester/" title="Fukjo - Winchester - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Come un imprevisto eccoci <br>immobili <br>Non mentirmi <br>non dirmi cose che potrei usarti contro <br>E non basta eludermi <br>dovrei ucciderti <br>Ma tu sei ovunque e in ogni errore <br>Vorrei sparire e poi sfiorarti un altro po' <br>Potrei ma non lo vuoi annientarti in un attimo <br>Non sei quello che ho da perdere <br>Non sei quello che ho da perdere <br>Non sei quello che ho da perdere <br>Non sei quello che ho da perdere]]></content><category term="Fukjo" label="Fukjo"/><category term="Winchester" label="Winchester"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fukjo/Amorevolmente/</id><title>Fukjo - Amorevolmente - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T19:57:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T19:57:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Fukjo/Amorevolmente/" title="Fukjo - Amorevolmente - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Amorevolmente tossico, svuotami l'animo <br>Siamo ancora vergini <br>ma e dentro che poi scalpiti <br><br>Piccole lucciole <br>addestrate alla psichedelia <br>Piccole lucciole <br>addestrate alla psichedelia <br><br>Amorevolmente comico, svuotami l'animo <br>Siamo fiori sterili <br>su prati di alibi <br><br>Piccole lucciole <br>addestrate alla psichedelia Piccole lucciole <br>addestrate alla psichedelia]]></content><category term="Fukjo" label="Fukjo"/><category term="Amorevolmente" label="Amorevolmente"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NEON/저녁보다_아침이_더_예뻐/</id><title>NEON - 저녁보다 아침이 더 예뻐 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:09:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:09:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/NEON/%EC%A0%80%EB%85%81%EB%B3%B4%EB%8B%A4_%EC%95%84%EC%B9%A8%EC%9D%B4_%EB%8D%94_%EC%98%88%EB%BB%90/" title="NEON - 저녁보다 아침이 더 예뻐 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[High heel 보단 편한 Loafer <br>Skinny jeans ponytail style까지 <br>하늘 하게 입은 모습에도 <br>훤히 보이는 High waist fit <br>살포시 찡긋하는 눈썹과 <br>살짝은 삐쭉하는 입술이 <br>애기같이 귀여워서 <br>계속 바라보게 돼 <br>you are so beautiful <br>매번 들어서 너는 질리겠지만 <br>you are so beautiful <br>이 말보다 더 뭐가 어울릴까요 <br>저녁보다 더 아침이 예뻐 <br>너의 그 걸음걸이 뒷모습에 <br>매번 발그레 하고 있어 <br>주말보다 더 평일이 예뻐 <br>예쁘게 차려 입은 모습보다 <br>잠옷차림 니 모습이 더 <br>주말 되면 데이트 할 생각에 <br>몇 시간씩 찾아보고 <br>조심스레 서울에서 <br>조금 벗어난대도 it's okay <br>오늘은 어디를 가자 말해도 <br>오늘은 조금 늦을 것 같대도 <br>어딜 가든 언제 오든 <br>뭐든 상관 없다 말해주는 너 <br>you are so beautiful <br>매번 들어서 너는 질리겠지만 <br>you are so beautiful <br>이 말보다 더 뭐가 어울릴까요 <br>저녁보다 더 아침이 예뻐 <br>너의 그 걸음걸이 뒷모습에 <br>매번 발그레 하고 있어 <br>주말보다 더 평일이 예뻐 <br>예쁘게 차려 입은 모습보다 <br>잠옷차림 니 모습이 더 <br>저녁보다 더 아침이 예뻐 <br>너의 그 걸음걸이 뒷모습에 <br>매번 발그레 하고 있어 <br>주말보다 더 평일이 예뻐 <br>예쁘게 차려 입은 모습보다 <br>잠옷차림 니 모습이 더 <br>you are so beautiful <br>]]></content><category term="NEON" label="NEON"/><category term="저녁보다 아침이 더 예뻐" label="저녁보다 아침이 더 예뻐"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/나는_지금/</id><title>강승원 - 나는 지금... - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%A7%80%EA%B8%88/" title="강승원 - 나는 지금... - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떠나 보내는데 익숙해졌어 <br>떠나가는 것도 마찬가지야 <br>다시 처음으로 돌아가고 싶지만 <br>나는 지금 <br>유리창에 비친 내 모습 너머로 <br>당신은 내게 멀어지고 있고 <br>사랑이라는 허전함 속에 <br>기쁨보다 슬픔이 많아 <br>끝도 없는 사랑을 믿었는데 <br>가슴이 아파 <br>떠나가는 너를 볼 수가 없어 <br>멀어지는 너를 잡을 수 없어 <br>떠나가지 마라 <br>나의 청춘이 널 따라 멀어진다 <br>나의 사랑이 널 따라 사라진다 <br>떠나간다 멀어진다 사라진다 <br>떠나 보내는데 익숙해졌어 <br>떠나가는 것도 마찬가지야 <br>다시 처음으로 돌아가고 싶지만 <br>나는 지금 <br>나는 지금 <br>떠나가지 마라 <br>나의 청춘이 널 따라 멀어진다 <br>나의 사랑이 널 따라 사라진다 <br>떠나간다 멀어진다 사라진다 <br>떠나 보내는데 익숙해졌어 <br>떠나가는 것도 마찬가지야 <br>다시 처음으로 돌아가고 싶지만 <br>나는 지금 <br>나는 지금 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="나는 지금..." label="나는 지금..."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/서른_즈음에_With_전인권/</id><title>강승원 - 서른 즈음에 (With 전인권) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:05+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:05+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/%EC%84%9C%EB%A5%B8_%EC%A6%88%EC%9D%8C%EC%97%90_With_%EC%A0%84%EC%9D%B8%EA%B6%8C/" title="강승원 - 서른 즈음에 (With 전인권) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[또 하루 멀어져 간다 <br>내뿜은 담배 연기처럼 <br>작기만 한 내 가슴 속에 <br>또 무얼 채워 살고 있는지 <br>점점 더 멀어져 간다 <br>머물러 있는 청춘인 줄 알았는데 <br>비어가는 내 가슴 속엔 <br>더 아무 것도 채울 수 없네 <br>계절은 다시 돌아오지만 <br>떠나간 내 사랑은 어디에 <br>내가 떠나 보낸 것도 아닌데 <br>내가 떠나 온 것도 아닌데 <br>조금씩 잊혀져 간다 <br>머물러 있는 사랑인 줄 알았는데 <br>또 하루 멀어져 간다 <br>매일 이별하며 살고 있구나 <br>계절은 다시 돌아 오지만 <br>떠나간 내 사랑은 어디에 <br>내가 떠나 보낸 것도 아닌데 <br>내가 떠나 온 것도 아닌데 <br>조금씩 잊혀져 간다 <br>머물러 있는 사랑인 줄 알았는데 <br>또 하루 멀어져 간다 <br>매일 이별하며 살고 있구나 <br>매일 이별하며 살고 있구나 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="서른 즈음에 (With 전인권)" label="서른 즈음에 (With 전인권)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/오늘도_어제_같은_나는_With_윤도현/</id><title>강승원 - 오늘도 어제 같은 나는... (With 윤도현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EB%8F%84_%EC%96%B4%EC%A0%9C_%EA%B0%99%EC%9D%80_%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_With_%EC%9C%A4%EB%8F%84%ED%98%84/" title="강승원 - 오늘도 어제 같은 나는... (With 윤도현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아직도 그리움이 남아 있어요 <br>내 가슴속 깊숙한 <br>곳에서 더 커졌나봐요 <br>저만치 멀어지는 내 뒷모습은 <br>오늘도 어제 같은 나를 울려요 <br>바람은 불어오고 또 불어와요 <br>어젯밤 꾸었던 꿈은 어디 있나요 <br>시원했던 바람은 차가와져서 <br>오늘도 어제 같은 나는 추워요 <br>내 맘과 같지 않은 세상 속에서 <br>당신이 서 있었나요 <br>사랑했단 말은 아직 못했던가요 <br>어떻게 말로 하나요 <br>사랑해 <br>사랑해 <br>사랑해 <br>오늘도 어제 같은 나는 <br>바람은 불어오고 또 불어와요 <br>어젯밤 꾸었던 꿈은 어디 있나요 <br>시원했던 바람은 차가와져서 <br>오늘도 어제 같은 나는 추워요 <br>내 맘과 같지 않은 세상 속에서 <br>당신이 서 있었나요 <br>사랑했단 말은 아직 못했던가요 <br>어떻게 말로 하나요 <br>사랑해 <br>사랑해 <br>사랑해 <br>오늘도 어제 같은 나는 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="오늘도 어제 같은 나는... (With 윤도현)" label="오늘도 어제 같은 나는... (With 윤도현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/그_겨울_With_박정현/</id><title>강승원 - 그 겨울 (With 박정현) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/%EA%B7%B8_%EA%B2%A8%EC%9A%B8_With_%EB%B0%95%EC%A0%95%ED%98%84/" title="강승원 - 그 겨울 (With 박정현) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떠난다 사랑도 변해간다 <br>보낸다 내 맘도 함께 실어 <br>잊는다 참 어려운 일이지만 <br>그냥 그렇게 다시 <br>시간은 흘러간다 <br>눈온다 참 많이도 쏟아진다 <br>눈 내리면 어디로 가야 하나 <br>외롭다 세상에 나 혼자다 <br>그냥 그렇게 다시 <br>그 겨울을 넘어간다 <br>그립다 너와 함께했던 추억들 <br>내리는 송이송이 눈꽃송이 <br>다 덮어버린다 <br>웃는다 참 어려운 일이지만 <br>그냥 그렇게 다시 <br>사랑은 흘러간다 <br>마신다 너와 함께 했던 추억들 <br>흐르는 방울방울 눈물방울 <br>다 흘려 보낸다 <br>웃는다 참 어려운 일이지만 <br>그냥 그렇게 다시 <br>사랑은 흘러갔다 <br>또다시 사랑이 올까 <br>꿈꾸던 날들이 기다릴까 <br>그냥 그렇게 다시 <br>그냥 그렇게 다시 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="그 겨울 (With 박정현)" label="그 겨울 (With 박정현)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/술_With_존박/</id><title>강승원 - 술 (With 존박) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/%EC%88%A0_With_%EC%A1%B4%EB%B0%95/" title="강승원 - 술 (With 존박) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[너의 뜨거운 몸이 <br>내게 들어와 <br>그 뜨거운 열기가 <br>내 머리칼까지 전해지면 <br>난 눈을 뜨지 <br>너의 더운 입술이 <br>내 몸에 닿으면 <br>날 둘러싼 상념의 <br>옷들을 모두 벗어던지지 <br>나의 마음이 <br>활짝 열리고 있어 <br>나의 몸에 날개가 <br>자라고 있어 <br>슬픈 내모습 지친 내모습 <br>이젠 모두 안녕 <br>나의 몸은 <br>하늘을 날고 있어 <br>내 마음은 네게로 <br>향하고 있어 <br>움추렸던 어깨 <br>서러웠던 날들 <br>모두 다 떨쳐버리고 <br>난 다시 너의 <br>뜨거운 몸을 마신다 <br>나의 마음이 <br>활짝 열리고 있어 <br>나의 몸에 날개가 <br>자라고 있어 <br>슬픈 내모습 지친 내모습 <br>이젠 모두 안녕 <br>나의 몸은 <br>하늘을 날고 있어 <br>내 마음은 네게로 <br>향하고 있어 <br>움추렸던 어깨 <br>서러웠던 날들 <br>모두 다 떨쳐버리고 <br>난 다시 너의 <br>뜨거운 몸을 마신다 <br>마신다 <br>마신다 <br>마신다 <br>마신다 <br>마신다 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="술 (With 존박)" label="술 (With 존박)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/Him_담배_With_윤하/</id><title>강승원 - Him (담배) (With 윤하) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/Him_%EB%8B%B4%EB%B0%B0_With_%EC%9C%A4%ED%95%98/" title="강승원 - Him (담배) (With 윤하) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[담배를 입에 물었어 <br>끊으려 끊으려 했는데 <br>도깨비풀처럼 내 등에 <br>붙어서 떨어지질 않아 <br>사랑인 줄 알았어 <br>널 끊으려 했는데 <br>강아지풀처럼 내 볼을 <br>간지러 하얀 연기로 <br>가슴이 타서 연기가 나 <br>연기가 나서 눈물이 나 <br>깊은 한숨으로 <br>마음은 흩어져 <br>바람의 모습 들키게 해 <br>내 방에 연기가 가득 찼어 <br>방안에 온통 가득 <br>니 모습 뿐이야 <br>깊은 한숨으로 <br>바람은 흩어져 <br>내 마음 들키게 해 <br>사랑인 줄 알았어 <br>널 끊으려 했는데 <br>도깨비풀처럼 내 등에 <br>붙어서 떨어지질 않아 <br>가슴이 타서 연기가 나 <br>연기가 나서 눈물이 나 <br>깊은 한숨으로 <br>마음은 흩어져 <br>바람의 모습 들키게 해 <br>내 방에 연기가 가득 찼어 <br>방안에 온통 가득 <br>니 모습 뿐이야 <br>내 방에 연기가 가득 찼어 <br>방안에 온통 가득 <br>니 모습 뿐이야 <br>깊은 한숨으로 <br>바람은 흩어져 <br>내 마음 들키게 해 <br>담배를 입에 물었어 <br>끊으려 끊으려 했는데 <br>도깨비풀처럼 <br>내 등에 붙어서 음 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="Him (담배) (With 윤하)" label="Him (담배) (With 윤하)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/Digital_World_With_장기하/</id><title>강승원 - Digital World (With 장기하) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/Digital_World_With_%EC%9E%A5%EA%B8%B0%ED%95%98/" title="강승원 - Digital World (With 장기하) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우리들은 살고 죽고 살고 <br>사랑하고 미워하고 <br>울고 웃는 세상에 있어 <br>잠이 들면 깨고 자고 깨고 <br>달이 뜨면 해가 지고 <br>오고가는 세상에 있어 <br>너는 내게 사랑한다 하고 <br>변했다고 하고 <br>나를 떠나고 있어 <br>나는 네게 변한다고 하고 <br>사랑한다 하며 <br>가지마라 널 잡고 있어 <br>Digital World <br>Save me Save me Save me <br>Click me <br>Digital World <br>Save me Save me Save me <br>Click me <br>Digital World <br>Save me Save me Save me <br>Click me <br>Digital World <br>Save me Save me <br>우리들은 살고 죽고 살고 <br>사랑하고 미워하고 <br>울고 웃는 세상에 있어 <br>잠이 들면 깨고 자고 깨고 <br>달이 뜨면 해가 지고 <br>오고가는 세상에 있어 <br>너는 내게 사랑한다 하고 <br>변했다고 하고 <br>나를 떠나고 있어 <br>나는 네게 변한다고 하고 <br>사랑한다 하며 <br>가지마라 널 잡고 있어 <br>Digital World <br>Save me Save me Save me <br>Click me <br>Digital World <br>Save me Save me Save me <br>Click me <br>Digital World <br>Save me Save me Save me <br>Click me <br>Digital World <br>Save me Save me <br>사랑할 수 있는 건 오늘뿐이야 <br>변하는 것은 그저 기억뿐이고 <br>너와 나의 연결 <br>연결 연결 연결 속에서 <br>오늘의 나는 그저 사랑할 수 밖에 <br>Save me Save me Save me <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="Digital World (With 장기하)" label="Digital World (With 장기하)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/무중력_With_ZionT/</id><title>강승원 - 무중력 (With Zion.T) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/%EB%AC%B4%EC%A4%91%EB%A0%A5_With_ZionT/" title="강승원 - 무중력 (With Zion.T) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[당신의 겉모습과 <br>속마음은 똑같아 <br>나를 보며 웃어주는 모습 <br>그림같아 슬퍼보여요 <br>기억나지 않는 <br>엄마의 품 속같아 <br>어떻게 할까 <br>어떻게 하나 <br>당신의 겉모습과 <br>속마음은 달라요 <br>나를 보며 다시 웃는 모습 <br>달라보여 그래도 그림같아 <br>잊혀진 내 어린 날 <br>슬픈 기억이 나 <br>어떻게 할까 어떻게 하나 <br>너를 만지면 <br>나는 날아올라 <br>봄바람에 흩어진 꽃잎처럼 <br>시간은 멈추고 <br>무중력 상태 <br>이 순간만이 있는 <br>세상에서 음음 <br>너의 몸짓 그 눈빛 <br>그 속삭임 그 눈물 <br>나는 너 너는 나 <br>그렇게 사랑은 지나간다 <br>I Believe in U and Me <br>I Believe in U and Me and U <br>I Believe in U and Me <br>너를 만지면 <br>나는 날아올라 <br>봄바람에 흩어진 꽃잎처럼 <br>시간은 멈추고 <br>무중력 상태 <br>이 순간만이 있는 <br>세상에서 음음 <br>너의 몸짓 그 눈빛 <br>그 속삭임 그 눈물 <br>나는 너 너는 나 <br>그렇게 사랑은 지나간다 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="무중력 (With Zion.T)" label="무중력 (With Zion.T)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/안드로메다_With_성시경_정유미/</id><title>강승원 - 안드로메다 (With 성시경, 정유미) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/%EC%95%88%EB%93%9C%EB%A1%9C%EB%A9%94%EB%8B%A4_With_%EC%84%B1%EC%8B%9C%EA%B2%BD_%EC%A0%95%EC%9C%A0%EB%AF%B8/" title="강승원 - 안드로메다 (With 성시경, 정유미) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[간다 <br>가니 <br>안드로메다로 <br>안 돌아 올 꺼니 <br>간다 <br>그 곳에 <br>태양계 너머로 <br>태양계 너머로 <br>은하수 건너서 <br>은하수 건너서 <br>안드로메다에 <br>안드로메다에 <br>가면 <br>이젠 <br>이젠 <br>니 달빛 미소도 <br>니 사랑 노래도 <br>순수의 시간도 <br>내 별빛 눈물도 <br>없다 <br>혼돈 <br>시간 <br>내 맘에 춤추고 <br>우리를 가두고 <br>행복 <br>사랑 <br>니 그림자 속에 <br>어디서 왔는지 <br>두고 왔는지 <br>어디로 가는지 <br>사랑 심각했는데 <br>은하수 건너서 <br>넌 웃고 있구나 <br>넌 떠나갔구나 <br>간다 <br>가면 <br>안드로메다로 <br>안 돌아 올 꺼니 <br>너를 찾아서 <br>나를 찾아서 <br>또 나를 찾아서 <br>시간에 갇혀서 살지 <br>더 이상 숨쉬기도 힘들어 <br>거기엔 시작도 끝도 없고 <br>숨쉬지 않아도 숨 쉬어지고 <br>혼자 있어도 외롭지 않고 <br>영원한 자유와 사랑만이 <br>가자 안드로메다로 <br>가자 태양계 너머로 <br>은하수 건너서 <br>안드로메다에 가면 <br>거긴 <br>이젠 <br>내 사랑 노래도 <br>니 사랑 노래도 <br>니 달빛 미소도 <br>니 별빛 눈물도 <br>없다 <br>없다 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="안드로메다 (With 성시경, 정유미)" label="안드로메다 (With 성시경, 정유미)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/달려가야_해/</id><title>강승원 - 달려가야 해 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/%EB%8B%AC%EB%A0%A4%EA%B0%80%EC%95%BC_%ED%95%B4/" title="강승원 - 달려가야 해 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[자동차에 시동을 걸면 <br>내 가슴은 뛰기 시작해 <br>또 하루가 열리고 있고 <br>또 하나를 얻어야 하고 <br>빨간 불이 차를 세우면 <br>내 마음은 더욱 초조해 <br>공평하지 못한 출발선 위에 <br>나를 앞서 떠나가는 차들 <br>더욱 세게 페달을 밟고 <br>이제 겨우 한 대 지나쳤고 <br>숨이 차도 멈추면 안돼 <br>오늘 또 하루를 잃을지도 몰라 <br>달려가야 해 <br>달려가야 해 <br>멈추면 누군가 앞지를지 몰라 <br>달려가야 해 <br>달려가야 해 <br>달려도 눈 앞에 앞서가는 차들 <br>종일 달려도 앞서가는 차들 <br>사라지지 않고 <br>다시 생각해 보면 <br>우리는 모두 <br>함께 달리고만 있는지도 몰라 <br>더욱 세게 페달을 밟고 <br>이제 겨우 한 대 지나쳤고 <br>숨이 차도 멈추면 안돼 <br>오늘 또 하루를 잃을지도 몰라 <br>달려가야 해 <br>달려가야 해 <br>멈추면 누군가 앞지를지 몰라 <br>달려가야 해 <br>달려가야 해 <br>달려도 눈 앞에 앞서가는 차들 <br>달려가야 해 <br>달려가야 해 <br>멈추면 누군가 앞지를지 몰라 <br>달려가야 해 <br>달려가야 해 <br>달려도 눈 앞에 앞서가는 차들 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="달려가야 해" label="달려가야 해"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/나는_지금_With_이적/</id><title>강승원 - 나는 지금... (With 이적) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/%EB%82%98%EB%8A%94_%EC%A7%80%EA%B8%88_With_%EC%9D%B4%EC%A0%81/" title="강승원 - 나는 지금... (With 이적) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[떠나 보내는데 익숙해졌어 <br>떠나가는 것도 마찬가지야 <br>다시 처음으로 <br>돌아가고 싶지만 나는 지금 <br>유리창에 비친 <br>내 모습 너머로 <br>당신은 내게 멀어지고 있고 <br>사랑이라는 허전함 속에 <br>기쁨보다 슬픔이 많아 <br>끝도 없는 사랑을 믿었는데 <br>가슴이 아파 <br>떠나가는 너를 볼 수가 없어 <br>멀어지는 너를 잡을 수 없어 <br>떠나가지 마라 <br>나의 청춘이 널 따라 멀어진다 <br>나의 사랑이 널 따라 사라진다 <br>떠나간다 멀어진다 사라진다 <br>떠나 보내는데 익숙해졌어 <br>떠나가는 것도 마찬가지야 <br>다시 처음으로 <br>돌아가고 싶지만 나는 지금 <br>떠나가지 마라 <br>나의 청춘이 널 따라 멀어진다 <br>나의 사랑이 널 따라 사라진다 <br>떠나간다 멀어진다 사라진다 <br>떠나 보내는데 익숙해졌어 <br>떠나가는 것도 마찬가지야 <br>다시 처음으로 <br>돌아가고 싶지만 나는 지금 <br>나는 지금 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="나는 지금... (With 이적)" label="나는 지금... (With 이적)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강승원/20세기_캐럴_19792016_With_린/</id><title>강승원 - 20세기 캐럴 (19792016) (With 린) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%8A%B9%EC%9B%90/20%EC%84%B8%EA%B8%B0_%EC%BA%90%EB%9F%B4_19792016_With_%EB%A6%B0/" title="강승원 - 20세기 캐럴 (19792016) (With 린) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[첫사랑 막막하던 그날 밤 <br>우린 어디로 가나 <br>거리엔 가득한 사람들 물결 <br>함께 떠내려가볼까 <br>주머니 속 차가웠던 너의 손 <br>맘은 얼어오지만 <br>내일은 없다 고요한밤 <br>눈 쏟아진다 <br>우리는 젊었다 사랑하고 있다 <br>오늘밤은 거룩하다 <br>복잡한 명동 종로 벗어난다 <br>광화문 앞을 걸어본다 <br>여기저기 보초서는 군인들 <br>없던 내일이 다가온다 <br>기억나지 않는 어제와 함께 <br>시간은 돌고 돌아 다시 그 자리에 <br>또 다시 그 자리에 서있다 <br>우린 어디로 가나 <br>거리엔 가득한 사람들 물결 <br>함께 떠내려 갈까 우린 아직 젊다 <br>오늘밤은 자유다 <br>복잡한 강남 역 2호선 전철 타고 <br>시청 앞 광화문을 걸어본다 <br>여기저기 고함치는 사람들 <br>잊었던 어제가 다가온다 없던 <br>내일도 함께 <br>시간은 돌고 돌아 다시 그 자리에 <br>줄을 선다 앞은 보이지 않아도 <br>어찌 되겠지 내일은 <br>세상이 어디 그리 만만하더냐 <br>그래도 우린 젊다 사랑하고 있다 <br>거룩한 밤 눈 쏟아져라 <br>우린 아직 젊다 사랑하고 있다 <br>오늘 밤은 자유다 <br>]]></content><category term="강승원" label="강승원"/><category term="20세기 캐럴 (19792016) (With 린)" label="20세기 캐럴 (19792016) (With 린)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VAS_LEON/Active_Clean_Ver/</id><title>VAS LEON - Active (Clean Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:10:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:10:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/VAS_LEON/Active_Clean_Ver/" title="VAS LEON - Active (Clean Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[All my n***** <br>Active <br>Tryna get to the money thats why <br>All my n***** <br>Active <br>Thats why your girl be acting funny thats 'cause <br>All my n***** <br>Active <br>She be creeping round your back that's 'cause <br>All my n***** <br>Active <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeahwe <br>Active <br>We getting racks All my All my <br><br>Dressed in <br>BBC Louis <br>Bathing ape with the Gucci <br>When we walk in the club <br>We leaving with your Julie <br>We put it all on the line <br>Working nine until nine <br>Yeah thats twenty four seven <br>Three hundred and sixty five <br>Thats right we get it <br>Yeah we get it huh <br>My n***** we don't regret it <br>Don't regret it huh <br>Failure only happens to you if you let it <br>If you let it <br>I look in your girls eyes and she already wet <br>That 'cause girl you know I'm <br><br>Active <br>Tryna get to the money thats why <br>All my n***** <br>Active <br>Thats why your girl be acting funny thats 'cause <br>All my n***** <br>Active <br>She be creeping round your back that's 'cause <br>All my n***** <br>Active <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah we <br>Active <br>We getting racks All my All my <br><br>Yeah we came from the ground and up <br>If you think you can play us then you're <br>Out of luck <br>Weighty bars with the balance man this beats a triple beam <br>My style is so addictive that it'll make your girl <br>Scream <br>Oo no oo you know we <br>Get it <br>Yeah we get it huh <br>My n***** we don't regret it <br>Don't regret it huh <br>Failure only happens to you if you let it <br><br>I look in your girls eyes and she already wet <br>That 'cause girl you know I'm <br><br>Active <br>Tryna get to the money thats why <br>All my n***** <br>Active <br>Thats why your girl be acting funny thats 'cause <br>All my n***** <br>Active <br>She be creeping round your back that's 'cause <br>All my n***** <br>Active <br>Yeah yeah yeah yeah we <br>Active <br>We getting racks All my All my]]></content><category term="VAS LEON" label="VAS LEON"/><category term="Active (Clean Ver.)" label="Active (Clean Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/장윤정/벚꽃길_2017/</id><title>장윤정 - 벚꽃길 2017 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:11:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:11:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%A5%EC%9C%A4%EC%A0%95/%EB%B2%9A%EA%BD%83%EA%B8%B8_2017/" title="장윤정 - 벚꽃길 2017 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[남인가 내가 남인 가요 <br>나 없인 안되면서 <br>없을 때 찾지 말고 <br>있을 때나 잘해주지 <br>남자들은 모른다 <br>여자의 속마음을 <br>허전해 옷을 사 입고 <br>사랑이 고파 배고픈 거야 <br>철이 없는 당신 <br>무정한 당신 <br>당신이 얄미워요 <br>때로는 나도 <br>때로는 나도 <br>여자이니까 <br>벚꽃이 날리는 <br>하얗게 날리는 <br>그 좋은 계절엔 <br>살림의 여왕 보다는 <br>애인이고 싶어요 <br>벚꽃 길 걸으면 <br>그 길을 걸으면 <br>향기에 취해서 <br>왠지 울컥해 지는 걸 <br>남자들은 모른다 <br>조금만 날 웃겨주면 <br>아주 많이 웃을 텐데 <br>못한다 화내지 말고 <br>괜찮다고 말해주지 <br>남자들은 모른다 <br>여자의 속마음을 <br>허전해 옷을 사 입고 <br>사랑이 고파 배고픈 거야 <br>철이 없는 당신 <br>무정한 당신 <br>당신이 얄미워요 <br>때로는 나도 <br>때로는 나도 <br>여자이니까 <br>벚꽃이 날리는 <br>하얗게 날리는 <br>그 좋은 계절엔 <br>살림의 여왕 보다는 <br>애인이고 싶어요 <br>벚꽃 길 걸으면 <br>그 길을 걸으면 <br>향기에 취해서 <br>왠지 울컥해 지는 걸 <br>남자들은 모른다 <br>왠지 울컥해 지는 걸 <br>남자들은 모른다 <br>]]></content><category term="장윤정" label="장윤정"/><category term="벚꽃길 2017" label="벚꽃길 2017"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/길을_걷다_Remake/</id><title>Ryan - 길을 걷다 (Remake) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:11:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:11:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/%EA%B8%B8%EC%9D%84_%EA%B1%B7%EB%8B%A4_Remake/" title="Ryan - 길을 걷다 (Remake) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우린 서로 툭하면 또 핀잔을 줘 <br>이 시간들도 넌 내게 말해 <br>듣기만 해줘 <br>보기만 해도 웃기만 했던 <br>좋은 시간들은 간지 오래 <br>서로를 위한 말이 참견이 됐던 <br>우리 얘기에 우리 얘긴 없던 <br>그 순간부터 <br>별로 관심 없어 <br>보이는 얘기에 시간을 부어 <br>점점 더 멀어져 버렸던 <br>우리 사이 이미 돌릴 수 없으니 <br>그냥 walk the road <br>매일 반복된 <br>안부를 묻는 너의 <br>눈빛이 오늘 따라 <br>상당히 거슬리지 <br>그 어떤 대화도 <br>따분함으로만 <br>마감 되는 것은 <br>이번뿐이 아니잖아 <br>우리 사이 <br>친절함을 부탁해 <br>우린 서로에게만 <br>또 차갑게 <br>서로 아무 말 없이 <br>또 준비 했던 <br>그런 날이 그냥 <br>지금 다가왔어 <br>내겐 더 이상 <br>이젠 너란 건 없어 <br>차갑게 돌아설 줄만 <br>알았는데 <br>매 순간에 니가 아른거려 <br>길을 걷다 나 같은 사람이 <br>니 옆을 지나면 <br>아무 말 없이 다가와 줘 <br>아니 토닥여 줘 <br>가만히 길을 걷다 서서 <br>하늘 바라보는 <br>그런 사람 보면 토닥여 줘 <br>아니 보듬어 줘 이 길 위에서 <br>너까지 아프게 할 생각 없어 <br>baby 내가 짊어질게 <br>you never mind never mind <br>서로의 갈 길을 <br>막지 않기를 바래 <br>난 그러길 바래 <br>]]></content><category term="Ryan" label="Ryan"/><category term="길을 걷다 (Remake)" label="길을 걷다 (Remake)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/Pick_You_Up_Remake/</id><title>Ryan - Pick You Up (Remake) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:11:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:11:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/Pick_You_Up_Remake/" title="Ryan - Pick You Up (Remake) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[baby 기다려 <br>금방 데리러갈게 <br>잠깐 있어 기다려 girl <br>걸음은 도도하게 <br>이쁜 척은 내게만 해 <br>저기 늑대들이 또 불러도 <br>넌 쳐다보지마 <br>난 더 더 더 밟어 액셀 <br>좀 더 빨리 널 <br>널 널 볼래 my elf <br>I'm not 안전운전 해 <br>널 만나기 일분전엔 <br>규칙은 필요없어 <br>오늘은 선을 넘어갈래 baby <br>내 차엔 기름 많아서 <br>타긴 정말 쉽지 <br>but 창문은 수동이야 <br>내리기는 조금 쉽지 않아 <br>뒤엔 아무것도 없어 <br>볼 필요는 없지만 <br>앞에는 너랑 있으니 <br>좋은 밤 꽃 향기나네 <br>네 옆모습은 예술 작품 <br>화가가 그린 line <br>빨간불일 땐 <br>또 다시 켜지는 green light <br>아무도 없는 골목길에 <br>몰래 주차해 <br>시동은 이미 껐는데 <br>차는 계속 움직이네 <br>everyday I am <br>just runnin' to you <br>runnin' to you <br>I'm runnin' to you <br>everytime you are <br>just drivin' me crazy <br>drivin' me crazy <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>지나가는 남자들 <br>쳐다보며 수군수군대 <br>이해 하잖아 내 맘 <br>널 또 19금 구금해 <br>의자는 길게 뻗어 <br>그 위 넌 그냥 뻗어 <br>you say ah ah <br>I say uh uh yeah <br>시트는 계속 <br>데워져 뜨거워 <br>땀으로 범벅 <br>우리 둘은 도착했지 <br>여기는 홍콩 밤거리 <br>네 허리가 내 머리에 <br>불타는 오늘밤 burning <br>어둠속에서 둘이 <br>만드는 collaboration <br>yeah 숲을 지나고 <br>그리고 고갤 들었지 <br>저 높은 두개의 <br>산을 지나면 <br>그래 그래 모기도 있겠지 <br>잠시만 우물에서 <br>목 좀 축이고 <br>이젠 자 들어가 <br>우린 또 아까 하던 것 <br>마저 더 하자 <br>니 몸에 body painting <br>너란 캔버스 위에 물감처럼 <br>마지막 남은 걸 짜내고 <br>완성의 끝자락에 <br>널 끌어 안을게 <br>그래 오직 색감은 하나 <br>흑지 위 그려보는 하얀색 나라 <br>난 비슷한 작품 위해 <br>매일 같은 곳에 가네 baby <br>everyday I am <br>just runnin' to you <br>runnin' to you <br>I'm runnin' to you <br>everytime you are <br>just drivin' me crazy <br>drivin' me crazy <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>매일 너와 함께 하고싶어 <br>I can take you to heaven <br>baby to heaven girl <br>구름 위를 <br>걸어다니게 해줄게 <br>wanna take your body <br>I want your body <br>매일 너와 함께 하고싶어 <br>I can take you to heaven <br>baby to heaven girl <br>구름 위를 <br>걸어다니게 해줄게 <br>wanna take your body <br>take your body <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>I'll pick you up tonight <br>]]></content><category term="Ryan" label="Ryan"/><category term="Pick You Up (Remake)" label="Pick You Up (Remake)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/Awesome_Remake/</id><title>Ryan - Awesome (Remake) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:11:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:11:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/Awesome_Remake/" title="Ryan - Awesome (Remake) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[뭐든 궁금해질때가 있어 girl <br>내가 널 바라볼때 처럼 <br>빨간 구두를 신고 <br>옅은 화장은 더 <br>내 호기심을 자극했어 <br>아침 햇살보다도 더 <br>빛나는 저녁 <br>보름달 보다 더 <br>so you make me blind <br>you gotta make me smile <br>널 향한 내 미소를 <br>유지할수 있게 <br>더 기회를 줘 <br>많은 여자들은 <br>날 지나치고 <br>난 자만할 수 밖에 <br>다른 여자들은 <br>널 지나치고 <br>그저 시기 할수 밖에 없게 돼 <br>너무 이기적이야 넌 <br>모두 시기하잖아 널 <br>가끔 신기하게도 넌 <br>다 갖고 있어 <br>awesome <br>맨날 쉬지않고서 널 <br>매일 생각하잖아 더욱 <br>그저 멈추려고 하면 <br>너무 이기적이야 넌 <br>혹시 어디야 고향이 <br>다른 여자와는 <br>다르게 깊어 소양이 <br>손 모양이 이쁘지만 거칠어 <br>즉 궁금한게 많았어 <br>like 고양이 hey <br>모든 여자에게 해당은 nope <br>말을 걸게 하지 너는 계속 <br>주제를 이어가는 법을 알어 <br>답 이후 질문 <br>긴장이 계속되니 <br>하게되지 실수 <br>그것마저도 넌 <br>이쁘게 봐줘 <br>hey baby you're so awesome <br>also i love your custom <br>나를 어장에서 건져봐 <br>괜히 다른 <br>여자들은 늘 망쳐놔 <br>도망처 난 또 널 보러 <br>네게 갈 수 밖에 없게 <br>만들어야 해 <br>많은 여자들은 <br>날 지나치고 <br>난 자만할 수 밖에 <br>다른 여자들은 <br>널 지나치고 <br>그저 시기 할 수 밖에 없게 해 <br>너무 이기적이야 넌 <br>모두 시기하잖아 널 <br>가끔 신기하게도 넌 <br>다 갖고 있어 <br>awesome <br>맨날 쉬지않고서 널 <br>매일 생각하잖아 더욱 <br>그저 멈추려고 하면 <br>너무 이기적이야 넌 <br>]]></content><category term="Ryan" label="Ryan"/><category term="Awesome (Remake)" label="Awesome (Remake)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/One_Step_Remake/</id><title>Ryan - One Step (Remake) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:11:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:11:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/One_Step_Remake/" title="Ryan - One Step (Remake) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[니가 내 앞에 서 있는 걸 <br>눈부셔 지금 입은 옷은 <br>언제나 그래 항상 내겐 <br>wedding dress <br>wedding dress <br>wedding dress <br>끝 없는 아름다움의 셔플과 <br>우리 둘 앞 펼쳐지는 <br>one card <br>항상 joker 가진 다음 <br>나를 또 매달리게 하잖아 <br>one step one step <br>한 걸음 더 다가갈 때면 <br>눈이 부셔 <br>아무것도 보이지 않아 <br>넌 돼 줘 <br>my superstar <br>아니 벌써 내겐 <br>superstar <br>그러니 <br>one step one step <br>one step baby <br>ah one step one step <br>one step baby <br>너는 나의 빛 그러니 <br>보이는 곳으로 향했지 <br>항해 뒤 맞이할 아침에 <br>중독된 것처럼 찾아 <br>저 뒤 장대비 사이엔 <br>왠지 니가 보일것 같아 <br>난 한걸음 두걸음 <br>천천히 보이는 실루엣 <br>어차피 안돼는 표정관리는 <br>이젠 멈추고 입술은 씰룩대 <br>내 기분에 이상 기후는 너 <br>나의 기우 는 또 한바탕 <br>폭풍이 몰아 쳐 <br>그리고 네게로 <br>완전히 기울여져 <br>기울어 져 눈과 몸 <br>무릎의 방향 까지 <br>눈감은 순간의 시간까지 <br>기다려 졌어 GIRL <br>널 보는 시간만이 <br>yo yo yo yo <br>낙원이 가까이 있으니 <br>아무 것도 또 두렵지 않지 <br>이건 나를 위한 <br>paradigm <br>무한가지 색의 <br>spectrum <br>맘을 비운 만큼 또 <br>내게 다가오잖아 <br>혹 거울같은 <br>흑색 별 두 개가 <br>내게 위치한 순간 <br>oh girl <br>oh no no no <br>앞서 보이는 <br>저 gay bar 같이 <br>내겐 딴 여잔 상관 없지 <br>니가 다가온 순간 <br>온통 이 우주와 <br>무중력과 이 무력감 <br>이루 말 할 수도 없이 <br>커져버린 다음 <br>나를 덮쳐가 <br>one step <br>so one step <br>one step <br>one step to you tonight <br>한 걸음 더 다가갈 때면 <br>눈이 부셔 <br>아무것도 보이지 않아 <br>넌 돼 줘 <br>my superstar <br>아니 벌써 내겐 <br>superstar <br>그러니 <br>one step one step <br>one step baby <br>ah one step one step <br>one step baby <br>]]></content><category term="Ryan" label="Ryan"/><category term="One Step (Remake)" label="One Step (Remake)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/Preview_Remake/</id><title>Ryan - Preview (Remake) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:11:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:11:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Ryan/Preview_Remake/" title="Ryan - Preview (Remake) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[When i was young <br>나 17살 때쯤 <br>STIVIE 1TYM JACKSON <br>I HAD A GOOD TIME <br>밤새 가사를 써 <br>무대를 누벼 <br>이젠 몇몇 친구들은 <br>니 입에 오르내리고 <br>회사 문 박차고 나온 <br>백수새낀 <br>또 지 주제 파악 못하고 <br>전설을 한대도 <br>I BELIEVE IN MYSELF <br>AND I'LL NEVER SEE BACK <br>이 앨범 매 순간이 내 이력의 <br>PREVIEW <br>이 도시 위 물들인 밤 <br>불빛은 꺼지지않아 <br>LOGIC 위 그려진 NOTE가 <br>이젠 내 삶을 채워가 <br>LETS GET IT STARTED BABY <br>늘 하고 싶은대로 CHILLIN <br>미리보길 원하지 난 성공한 삶 <br>행복과 명예의 DEEP KISS <br>어릴 적 봤었던 WANNA BE <br>STAR 들의 발걸음 따라 <br>또 LEARN IT <br>언젠가 내가 쓸 전설을 <br>아직 못 보여준게 슬퍼져 <br>I SHOWED A PREVIEW <br>오늘 이 밤 갈때까지 <br>JUST I SHOWED YOU <br>계속 반복해도 좋아 <br>PREVIEW <br>SHOWED YOU PREVIEW <br>WITH MA <br>I SHOWED A PREVIEW <br>JUST I SHOWED YOU <br>I SHOWED A PREVIEW <br>JUST I SHOWED YOU <br>]]></content><category term="Ryan" label="Ryan"/><category term="Preview (Remake)" label="Preview (Remake)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simon_Taylor_and_The_Sundowners/New_York_City_Girl/</id><title>Simon Taylor and The Sundowners - New York City Girl - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:12:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:12:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Simon_Taylor_and_The_Sundowners/New_York_City_Girl/" title="Simon Taylor and The Sundowners - New York City Girl - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Let me tell you 'bout a girl who floats 'round this old town and my mind <br>She's got gypsy eyes and raven's hair, she's dressed in leather that fits her just right <br>She keeps the sad sacks at a distance and they wonder what they're missing and why <br>But she doesn't see them in her eyes as the liquor flows throughout the night in style <br><br>I was in her eyeline once, we spent some nights just talking, it was nice <br>Then I blew my little cool, before I knew it she was out of sight <br>She travelled 'cross the Big Pond, to teach some kids some sing song and dance <br>But she kept us in the picture with her Instagram and scripture of jive <br><br>She's a New York City Girl, she goes at ninety miles per hour 'round my world <br>She's a New York City Girl, she's got the rhythm of the city in her soul <br>She's a New York City Girl, hits the sidewalks in her pretty winter coat <br>She's a New York City Girl, so refined and always busy on the go <br><br>Now she's back in town and with her retinue around she's still the same <br>Hitting town again on a night that never ends to dull the pain <br>The shadows of the city hang too heavy on her pretty brow, my friend <br>So she's off to some utopia where there's booze and pills and dope and you're not there <br><br>She's a New York City Girl, she goes at ninety miles per hour 'round my world <br>She's a New York City Girl, she's got the rhythm of the city in her soul <br>She's a New York City Girl, I'm de Niro, you're Minelli, that's the show <br>She's a New York City Girl, dressed like Hepburn A at Tiffany and Co <br><br>And I'm counting on the day when you come 'round my way <br>And we'll find ourselves a little hideaway <br>In Brooklyn Heights we'll play and there we'll hear the strains <br>Of a little song I wrote today <br><br>New York City Girl, New York City Girl, New York City Girl <br>New York City Girl, New York City Girl, New York City Girl <br>New York City Girl, New York City Girl, New York City Girl <br>New York City Girl, New York City Girl, New York City Girl]]></content><category term="Simon Taylor and The Sundowners" label="Simon Taylor and The Sundowners"/><category term="New York City Girl" label="New York City Girl"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/앨리/Utopia/</id><title>앨리 - Utopia - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:12:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:12:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%A8%EB%A6%AC/Utopia/" title="앨리 - Utopia - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오랫동안 기다렸어 오랫동안 널 <br>오랫동안 기다렸어 이제 우릴 <br>우릴 좀 데려가 줘 <br>Faster Higher <br>We ready to go <br>Faster Higher <br>We ready to go <br>오랫동안 기다렸어 오랫동안 널 <br>오랫동안 기다렸어 이제 우릴 <br>우릴 좀 데려가 줘 <br>Faster Higher <br>We ready to go <br>Faster Higher <br>We ready to go <br>Faster Higher <br>We ready to go <br>Faster Higher <br>We ready to go <br>ready to go <br>ready to go <br>ready to go <br>We ready to go <br>ready to go <br>ready to go <br>]]></content><category term="앨리" label="앨리"/><category term="Utopia" label="Utopia"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Two_Friends/Mona_Lisa_Eyes_Extended_Mix/</id><title>Two Friends - Mona Lisa Eyes (Extended Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:12:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:12:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Two_Friends/Mona_Lisa_Eyes_Extended_Mix/" title="Two Friends - Mona Lisa Eyes (Extended Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You've blurred my vision <br>Can you take the keys and drive <br>Both drunk and daydreams <br>Let's just speed through all these signs <br><br>Can we be alone <br>Turn the music low <br>Let the bullshit go <br>You can be so cold <br>Heaven only knows why I try <br><br>You give me Mona Lisa eyes <br>Cuz I can't take my love for you <br>Every time you start a fire <br>I can't help but lose my cool <br>If you tell me that you're mine <br>There's nothing I won't do <br>So won't you come with me tonight <br>I wanna show you how you make me feel <br><br>Burn all your bridges girl <br>You're still <br> you're full but I've been <br><br>Can we be alone <br>Turn the music low <br>Let the bullshit go <br>You can be so cold <br>Heaven only knows why I try <br><br>You give me Mona Lisa eyes <br>Cuz I can't take my love for you <br>Every time you start a fire <br>I can't help but lose my cool <br>If you tell me that you're mine <br>There's nothing I won't do <br>So won't you come with me tonight <br>I wanna show you how you make me feel <br><br>You give me Mona Lisa eyes <br>Cuz I can't take my love for you <br>So won't you come with me tonight <br>I wanna show you how you make me feel]]></content><category term="Two Friends" label="Two Friends"/><category term="Mona Lisa Eyes (Extended Mix)" label="Mona Lisa Eyes (Extended Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Two_Friends/Pacific_Coast_Highway_Feat_Max_Extended_Mix/</id><title>Two Friends - Pacific Coast Highway (Feat. Max) (Extended Mix) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:12:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:12:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Two_Friends/Pacific_Coast_Highway_Feat_Max_Extended_Mix/" title="Two Friends - Pacific Coast Highway (Feat. Max) (Extended Mix) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're the first thing I think of when I wake up <br>But you disappear suddenly as my eyes open up <br>You're just a memory <br>You're still real <br>You're just that one night, one time <br><br>You still make me feel like it's real <br>You're standing right in front of me for real <br>You're dancing in the sun with me <br>I can't believe I didn't think of some way to stay <br>And I can't believe I didn't think of some way to say <br><br>You make me feel like holding on to this feeling and <br>You make me believe I've got you to believe in <br>I'm on Pacific Coast Highway, Coasting up to this evening <br>And then I see you there <br>And the stereo goes <br><br>And the stereo goes <br><br>Oh, you know the last thing I thought was I'd be drawn in your lies <br>Now I'm following your trail, those dashed white lines <br>Your name is yesterday <br>You're still real <br>You're just that one word, one blur <br><br>You still make me feel like it's real <br>You're standing right in front of me for real <br>You're dancing in the sun with me <br>I can't believe I didn't think of some way to stay <br>And I can't believe I didn't think of some way to say <br><br>You make me feel like holding on to this feeling and <br>You make me believe I've got you to believe in <br>I'm on Pacific Coast Highway, Coasting up to this evening <br>And then I see you there <br>And the stereo goes <br><br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes <br><br>You gave me your number, my bad I hit your bumper <br>But you ain't mad <br>Now I'm glad 'cause <br>That one night, that one time <br>It's still real <br>One word, one blur <br>You still make me feel like it's real <br>You're standing right in front of me for real <br>You're dancing in the sun <br><br>I'm on Pacific Coast Highway, Coasting up to this evening <br>And then I see you there <br>And the stereo goes <br><br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes]]></content><category term="Two Friends" label="Two Friends"/><category term="Pacific Coast Highway (Feat. Max) (Extended Mix)" label="Pacific Coast Highway (Feat. Max) (Extended Mix)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Two_Friends/Mona_Lisa_Eyes/</id><title>Two Friends - Mona Lisa Eyes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:12:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:12:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Two_Friends/Mona_Lisa_Eyes/" title="Two Friends - Mona Lisa Eyes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You've blurred my vision <br>Can you take the keys and drive <br>Both drunk and daydreams <br>Let's just speed through all these signs <br><br>Can we be alone <br>Turn the music low <br>Let the bullshit go <br>You can be so cold <br>Heaven only knows why I try <br><br>You give me Mona Lisa eyes <br>Cuz I can't take my love for you <br>Every time you start a fire <br>I can't help but lose my cool <br>If you tell me that you're mine <br>There's nothing I won't do <br>So won't you come with me tonight <br>I wanna show you how you make me feel <br><br>Burn all your bridges girl <br>You're still <br> you're full but I've been <br><br>Can we be alone <br>Turn the music low <br>Let the bullshit go <br>You can be so cold <br>Heaven only knows why I try <br><br>You give me Mona Lisa eyes <br>Cuz I can't take my love for you <br>Every time you start a fire <br>I can't help but lose my cool <br>If you tell me that you're mine <br>There's nothing I won't do <br>So won't you come with me tonight <br>I wanna show you how you make me feel <br><br>You give me Mona Lisa eyes <br>Cuz I can't take my love for you <br>So won't you come with me tonight <br>I wanna show you how you make me feel]]></content><category term="Two Friends" label="Two Friends"/><category term="Mona Lisa Eyes" label="Mona Lisa Eyes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Two_Friends/Pacific_Coast_Highway_Feat_Max/</id><title>Two Friends - Pacific Coast Highway (Feat. Max) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:12:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:12:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Two_Friends/Pacific_Coast_Highway_Feat_Max/" title="Two Friends - Pacific Coast Highway (Feat. Max) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're the first thing I think of <br>when I wake up <br>But you disappear suddenly <br>as my eyes open up <br>You're just a memory <br>You're still real <br>You're just that one night one time <br>You still make me feel like it's real <br>You're standing right <br>in front of me for real <br>You're dancing in the sun with me <br>I can't believe <br>I didn't think of some way to stay <br>And I can't believe <br>I didn't think of some way to say <br>You make me feel <br>like holding on to this feeling and <br>You make me believe <br>I've got you to believe in <br>I'm on Pacific Coast Highway <br>Coasting up to this evening <br>And then I see you there <br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes <br>Oh you know the last thing <br>I thought was I'd be <br>drawn in your lies <br>Now I'm following your trail <br>those dashed white lines <br>Your name is yesterday <br>You're still real <br>You're just that one word one blur <br>You still make me feel like it's real <br>You're standing right <br>in front of me for real <br>You're dancing in the sun with me <br>I can't believe <br>I didn't think of some way to stay <br>And I can't believe <br>I didn't think of some way to say <br>You make me feel <br>like holding on to this feeling and <br>You make me believe <br>I've got you to believe in <br>I'm on Pacific Coast Highway <br>Coasting up to this evening <br>And then I see you there <br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes <br>You gave me your number <br>my bad I hit your bumper <br>But you ain't mad <br>Now I'm glad 'cause <br>That one night that one time <br>It's still real <br>One word one blur <br>You make me feel like it's real <br>You're standing right <br>in front of me for real <br>You're dancing in the sun with me <br>I'm on Pacific Coast Highway <br>Coasting up to this evening <br>And then I see you there <br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes <br>And the stereo goes <br>]]></content><category term="Two Friends" label="Two Friends"/><category term="Pacific Coast Highway (Feat. Max)" label="Pacific Coast Highway (Feat. Max)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Two_Friends/Out_Of_Love_Feat_Cosmos__Creature/</id><title>Two Friends - Out Of Love (Feat. Cosmos &amp; Creature) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:12:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:12:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Two_Friends/Out_Of_Love_Feat_Cosmos__Creature/" title="Two Friends - Out Of Love (Feat. Cosmos &amp; Creature) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How long can you walk around without knowing <br>How long will it take till your faith is broken <br>Tell me how long will you wait for the door to open <br><br>Well I know, I know, I know <br>We never really know <br>So hear me out <br><br>If you're running out of love <br>Then I can fill you up <br>And when it gets too much <br>Just hear me out <br>If you're lost in all the haze <br>Well I can clear the way <br>I know you'd do the same <br><br>So long, till the pain this heart is holding <br>What's wrong when the days we have are golden <br>Will you hold on <br>While the world outside is frozen <br><br>Well I know, I know, I know <br>We never really know <br>So hear me out <br><br>If you're running out of love <br>Then I can fill you up <br>And when it gets too much <br>Just hear me out <br>If you're lost in all the haze <br>Well I can clear the way <br>I know you'd do the same <br><br>If time's all we have <br>Why are you caught in a rush <br>We were made to last <br>All that you are is enough <br><br>If time's all we have <br>Why are you caught in a rush <br>We were made to last <br>All that you are is enough]]></content><category term="Two Friends" label="Two Friends"/><category term="Out Of Love (Feat. Cosmos &amp; Creature)" label="Out Of Love (Feat. Cosmos &amp; Creature)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이수_엠씨_더_맥스/단_한_번의_사랑_Inst/</id><title>이수 (엠씨 더 맥스) - 단 한 번의 사랑 (Inst.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:13:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:13:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%88%98_%EC%97%A0%EC%94%A8_%EB%8D%94_%EB%A7%A5%EC%8A%A4/%EB%8B%A8_%ED%95%9C_%EB%B2%88%EC%9D%98_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_Inst/" title="이수 (엠씨 더 맥스) - 단 한 번의 사랑 (Inst.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[둘 곳 없던 내 맘이 웃었다 <br>미친 듯이 가슴은 뛰었다 <br>숨 막히게 찬란했고 <br>눈물나게 행복했다 <br>내겐 그댄 그댄 <br>단 한 번의 사랑 <br>내 단 하나의 사랑 <br>Always Love You <br>내 전부인 사랑 <br>내 가슴은 이렇게 너만 너만 <br>살아도 사는게 아니야 <br>그대가 또 목 놓아 울었다 <br>내 가슴이 찢긴 듯 아팠다 <br>시린 겨울 눈발 같고 <br>한 순간에 꿈만 같던 <br>그때 그날 우리 <br>단 한 번의 사랑 <br>내 단 하나의 사랑 <br>Always Love You <br>내 전부인 사랑 <br>내 가슴은 이렇게 너만 너만 <br>살아도 사는게 아니야 <br>Always I Love You <br>시간을 넘어서라도 <br>영원히 <br>내 마지막 사랑 <br>내 단 하나의 사랑 <br>Always You <br>내 전부인 사랑 <br>내 가슴은 이렇게 너만 너만 <br>부르고 또 부른다 <br>Love You <br>]]></content><category term="이수 (엠씨 더 맥스)" label="이수 (엠씨 더 맥스)"/><category term="단 한 번의 사랑 (Inst.)" label="단 한 번의 사랑 (Inst.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이수_엠씨_더_맥스/단_한_번의_사랑/</id><title>이수 (엠씨 더 맥스) - 단 한 번의 사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:13:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:13:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%88%98_%EC%97%A0%EC%94%A8_%EB%8D%94_%EB%A7%A5%EC%8A%A4/%EB%8B%A8_%ED%95%9C_%EB%B2%88%EC%9D%98_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="이수 (엠씨 더 맥스) - 단 한 번의 사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[둘 곳 없던 내 맘이 웃었다 <br>미친 듯이 가슴은 뛰었다 <br>숨 막히게 찬란했고 <br>눈물나게 행복했다 <br>내겐 그댄 그댄 <br>단 한 번의 사랑 <br>내 단 하나의 사랑 <br>Always Love You <br>내 전부인 사랑 <br>내 가슴은 이렇게 너만 너만 <br>살아도 사는게 아니야 <br>그대가 또 목 놓아 울었다 <br>내 가슴이 찢긴 듯 아팠다 <br>시린 겨울 눈발 같고 <br>한 순간에 꿈만 같던 <br>그때 그날 우리 <br>단 한 번의 사랑 <br>내 단 하나의 사랑 <br>Always Love You <br>내 전부인 사랑 <br>내 가슴은 이렇게 너만 너만 <br>살아도 사는게 아니야 <br>Always I Love You <br>시간을 넘어서라도 <br>영원히 <br>내 마지막 사랑 <br>내 단 하나의 사랑 <br>Always You <br>내 전부인 사랑 <br>내 가슴은 이렇게 너만 너만 <br>부르고 또 부른다 <br>Love You <br>]]></content><category term="이수 (엠씨 더 맥스)" label="이수 (엠씨 더 맥스)"/><category term="단 한 번의 사랑" label="단 한 번의 사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Saint_Sinner/</id><title>Seez Mics - Saint Sinner - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:30:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:30:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Saint_Sinner/" title="Seez Mics - Saint Sinner - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Getting off here on my way to being on one <br>Finding my short fuse foolish in the long run <br>Just a brunette hoping to have a little blond fun <br>So when the swamp things treat me like pond scum <br>C'mon son don't get slapped by father <br>I been a bloody stone since I tapped my water <br>You're a full time past life martyr <br>Treating the beat like a half life partner <br>Trapped by karma forced to meet the demands <br>A compromised mission that don't agree with your plans <br>No more beach to the sand by sleeping with fans <br>I'm busy decalcifying my pineal gland <br>Breathe and expand, allow me to solve problems <br>Though I'm surrounded by pagans and hobgoblins <br>Focus your fear on Stoli and stock options <br>I'd rather reanimate by reading Tom Robbins <br>Never clock watching, I stay squeezing 65 <br>Multiplied by the counter culture's big divide <br>Pick a side, plenty of room to risk your lives <br>Dignified by your response to which dick you ride <br>It gets you high as it would a lowly plate spinner <br>I'm licking em clean, don't even have to make dinner <br>For the straight spitters, for the crate diggers <br>Seez Mics, my life as Saint Sinner <br><br>These choices <br>I'm making <br>Are making <br>Me <br>Seez Mics, my life as Saint Sinner <br><br>The paradox we call reality duality <br>It knows no man made boundary <br>No religion, no gender, no race <br>Political affiliation or nationality <br>A personality divided in two <br>Does it narrow your perspective the sky's always blue <br>Or broaden your horizon admire the view <br>You see, the virus inside us is bias, and when you try to remove <br>The outer shell of your inner troubles <br>All you find are smaller pieces of a bigger puzzle <br>To put it all together's always been a struggle <br>The Saint Sinner hustle balanced by the opposites <br>The rich and poor are the poor and rich <br>The good evil are the evil and good <br>In this life of contradiction, the most <br>You can ask for's to be understood <br>Understand the oldest trick in the book <br>Will become the newest vice in the streets <br>Double cross when you give em the hook, vic and the crook <br>Man child with spikes in my feet, cypher complete <br>Fighting for peace armed with lead paint thinner <br>Even when hope is only a faint glimmer <br>For the shape shifters, for the brain twisters <br>Seez Mics, my life as Saint Sinner <br><br>These choices <br>I'm making <br>Are making <br>Me <br>Seez Mics, my life as Saint Sinner]]></content><category term="Seez Mics" label="Seez Mics"/><category term="Saint Sinner" label="Saint Sinner"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Wont_You_Feat_Dood_Computer__Dezmatic/</id><title>Seez Mics - Won`t You (Feat. Dood Computer &amp; Dezmatic) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:30:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:30:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Wont_You_Feat_Dood_Computer__Dezmatic/" title="Seez Mics - Won`t You (Feat. Dood Computer &amp; Dezmatic) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Ready on the right, I'm a semi sane southpaw <br>Traveling light with baby wipes and mouthwash <br>On the up and up since the Cruel Fuel downfall <br>When the voices in my head were organizing a town hall <br>Profound flaws, maybe I'm born cynical <br>But seeing suckers get signed's making me more cynical <br>Bunch of bench warmers fronting like floor generals <br>A war criminal, my battle scars absorb minerals <br>I've morphed into two people I've gotta reconcile <br>One is happy go lucky and one'll never smile <br>Cognitive dissonance, position is I've read the file <br>We're all kinda crazy, the difference I got a better style <br>Bless the child who can write their own fresh start <br>No need for loose leaf, we'll use your mom's stretch marks <br>When in Rome, be certain who your friends are <br>Ain't enough Kevlar to protect you from my Death Star <br><br>The difference between us is you say you're on your grizzly <br>But I'll tame a wild kodiak and ride it like a 10 speed <br>Rocking a bed sheet, that toga party couture <br>The origin of every story that you thought was folklore <br>And folks, you're enjoying the illest to ever do it <br>Gorillas that's under the influence of gin fluid <br>And been using a pen to put a muzzle on cats <br>It's got a big bark, but bite off of my dogs when they rap <br>So scrap the session you saying that you were blessing <br>And get stuck for every cent that you were planning on investing <br>Cause I'm putting epinephrine in an epi pen, injecting it <br>In every vein available from pupils to the rectum <br>And then cracking skulls like there the eggs I had for breakfast <br>You're more than welcome to test if you thinking you got a death wish <br>You want that next shit It's the same as your last meal <br>Just rearranged a little bit and stinky as hell, pew <br><br>Fuck Eric Hosmer <br>AND chase utley get stomped at a Terror concert <br>My joints get more run than a pair of converse <br>More beef than the people under the stairs at Bomber's <br>You'll get sonned like Sarah Connor It's unfair it's bonkers how I'm compared to sub saharan thermometers Shit is hot <br>Your squad took the stage we didn't watch <br>I'm sending shots to you little lemon drops <br>Still gotta couple unsettled debts to squash <br>Whether the shit was ever said in jest or not <br>I guess whatever's deaded's better left to rot <br>I'm feelin sentimental maybe we should battle tho <br>Nah, you're better off buckin yourself Plaxico <br>Hoe ass rappers half steppin like a fractured toe, how apropos, yo]]></content><category term="Seez Mics" label="Seez Mics"/><category term="Won`t You (Feat. Dood Computer &amp; Dezmatic)" label="Won`t You (Feat. Dood Computer &amp; Dezmatic)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Until_Then_Feat_Navi__Ardamus/</id><title>Seez Mics - Until Then (Feat. Navi &amp; Ardamus) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:30:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:30:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Until_Then_Feat_Navi__Ardamus/" title="Seez Mics - Until Then (Feat. Navi &amp; Ardamus) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[She's the type to giggle when you let her <br>Get away with murder when delivering the pressure <br>Measure his and hers forever <br>Or temporarily a prisoners' dilemma <br>The minute I remember that I'm owed an apology <br>I forget I wrote an anthology <br>A digital trail of broken philosophy <br>All on account of I hope she don't follow me <br>Open throat policy swallow your pride <br>You're thick where it counts, but hollow inside <br>Maybe it's pheromones, call it a vibe <br>But I'm seeing through the peek a boo walls where she hides <br>Fall from the sky, a beautiful mess <br>But all I see is ugliness due to the stress <br>Maybe one day I'll be immune to her hex <br>Until then, I guess I'm just someone new to impress <br><br>Uhh To clarify my pair of eyes <br>Caught mid stare amidst air and time <br>There in line, through miles worth of crowd <br>You were certainly endowed Saw you <br>flipping Foucault with a furrow in your brow <br>I said 'wow' in an inside voice, a choice unfold <br>Impossible talk points implausible goals <br>Although, I've been told fortune favor the bold <br>Bold's a neighbor to a dangerous and lecherous road <br>And me, I hate that we paved it so you keep a tally of <br>which alleys you avoid and which escapes you've scoped <br>Sudden situation hinging on a trepidation <br>A cat call's a construct of a perilously feral nation <br>So now, I'm frozen I was going in on insecurities <br>And by association, my maturity, when whoops <br>Forgot to stop staring your way <br>I'll pick it up but thanks for now for how you're bearing the weight <br><br>Who brings the truth and provides the lies <br>Our back and forths go side to side <br>Talk show hosts that you idolize <br>Say its none of my biz, when you privatize <br>Online, you say that I'm more than mean <br>When we fight, I post up a Jordan meme it was just a joke <br>And some days the hearts action <br>will sign a peace treaty that's on a bar napkin BUT <br>I recall details to head <br>I asked for your number, email instead BUT <br>It was love, it must be then <br>Plus, you fought about me with your ugly friend BUT <br>We broke up, and now, yeah, we're off of that <br>No hugs, just hi, and awkward dap ah, c'mon, don't leave me hangin' <br>So we do a cool shuffle <br>We're not the right piece so we get a new puzzle LIKE]]></content><category term="Seez Mics" label="Seez Mics"/><category term="Until Then (Feat. Navi &amp; Ardamus)" label="Until Then (Feat. Navi &amp; Ardamus)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Float_Away_Feat_Adeem__Big_SLOP/</id><title>Seez Mics - Float Away (Feat. Adeem &amp; Big SLOP) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:31:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:31:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Float_Away_Feat_Adeem__Big_SLOP/" title="Seez Mics - Float Away (Feat. Adeem &amp; Big SLOP) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[My brain had a big bang, expanding while it melts <br>Throughout a universe that understands how it felt <br>I flew through the galaxy and landed on the shelf <br>Where I floated to the surface before standing by myself <br>Planets like myself don't pretend that we're stars <br>We revolve and evolve in our heads and our hearts <br>I'm glad we got common ground in Kendrick Lamar <br>But my atmospheric pressure'll leave you mentally scarred <br>Now your friends at the bar might not tell you that you're derivative <br>Indicative of hypocrites, gravity's illegitimate <br>Wing and a prayer, an atheist Icarus <br>Waxing poetic on our geometric differences <br>Picture this with a man made telescope <br>Idiots are buying fear, geniuses are selling hope <br>Since my heavenly bodies are hella dope <br>When they ask how I cope, I tell em float <br><br>I've been standing in a one man circle <br>counting all the ways that tomorrow's gonna hurt you <br>the past passed by in the blink of an eye <br>so I readjusted my sight and wore the shoes of the blind <br>funny how different a gimmick looks from afar <br>when you're super hot but not cold enough to be a star <br>cars pass by you hear the subs rumble through <br>forget about the future it's just a fictional truth <br>But if I'm honest about my love for the nonsense <br>I can build something better better amaze and astonish <br>floating through a river moving through the city's conscience <br>rooted in the knowledge that peace brings progress <br>Until then I'll be sky bound with a crack in my crown <br>A disciple of breaks Bambaataa found <br>Wading in a lexicon of long gone style <br>Nobody hold me down I wanna rise for awhile <br><br>Spinning through reality, mind at home still <br>Trying to pay my life debts with these Chrome Bills <br>The cost of life's commerce is more than just a payment <br>Got me standing in the sunshine, but feeling like its rainin' <br>No clouds in the sky but I feel 'em in my heart <br>The egocentric worries of a wannabe star <br>I got dreams and best believe I wanna go far <br>Wondering should I just join my friends at the bar <br>And Drink Away The Pain and maybe cause some Havoc <br>Or boots to the ground and start to get some traction <br>Thinking what are life's pursuits without some passion <br>Is it possible controlling outcomes solely through your actions <br>Thrashing through the waves, but I'm chilling in the current <br>The levity of gravity my only known deterrent <br>The lines of my reality steady stay blurring <br>At the end of my rope, I let go I float]]></content><category term="Seez Mics" label="Seez Mics"/><category term="Float Away (Feat. Adeem &amp; Big SLOP)" label="Float Away (Feat. Adeem &amp; Big SLOP)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Torch_Feat_Ceschi__Esh/</id><title>Seez Mics - Torch (Feat. Ceschi &amp; Esh) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:31:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:31:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Torch_Feat_Ceschi__Esh/" title="Seez Mics - Torch (Feat. Ceschi &amp; Esh) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I never judge a book by its cover up <br>Or swallow so much pride, I need my stomach pumped <br>So from the front that you back with the subtle scuttlebutt <br>Buttercup, I can only assume that you would run amok <br>Sum it up, corner to globe at a quarter to Cole <br>I quartered my soul at the fork in the road <br>Better half, dot dot dash remorse in the code <br>Let em laugh like it's not that bad, absorbing the blow <br>The more that you know, ignorance is blistering, real advice <br>Bring it to you live til they kill the lights <br>Bipolar lower to the thrill of heights <br>Got me feeling like I brought a calculator to a pillow fight <br>Your bill of rights're snide comments and fake smiles <br>I got side projects and WAV files <br>It ain't like me and god share the same tile <br>But by the time I saw 8 mile, I was on my eighth style <br><br>This could really take a while <br>I'll put em in a lake of fireor if I'm feeling friendly maybe Salem style trial <br>They can't hang though <br>They're tangled in tame flows <br>I'll mangle these lame bros with their painfully plain prose <br>No feasting on the pieces of weaklings deceitfully claiming to be peaking but are beneath me <br>Sorry to burst bubbles or hurt feelings <br>believe me this world's a beast it'll eat you while critiquing <br>Out there it's a blitzkrieg of concrete feet dropping quicker and deeper than where fish sleep <br>It's gotta be a preposterous parting treat when your body's tossed in the sea, only caught by a bed of coral reef <br>Now your flesh will only be a tender delicacy for schools of blind swimmers nibbling at your meat <br>All apologies <br>Cobain couldn't even comprehend the awful pain that this is causing me <br><br>I'll never be the king, don't pretend I'm Elvis <br>Even though I'm smoother than a Ken Doll's pelvis <br>Now you and all your men's all jealous <br>Cuz ya feeling my shit like, what is this Velvet <br>I always tell it how I see it <br>Only learned to swim when I fell into the deep end <br>Working to relieve the workers working for the weekend <br>Working on myself because I never want to be them <br>You know, cubicle suit monkey <br>Won't walk a mile in that shoe if it's too funky <br>The truth is, I'd rather be busting with two junkies <br>Then pan handling for that Canada Goose money <br>Is it funny or just a cruel joke <br>If you've got spirit then bust a move, loc <br>Spend everyday trying to do what you don't <br>You take the yacht I'll take the harbor cool boat]]></content><category term="Seez Mics" label="Seez Mics"/><category term="Torch (Feat. Ceschi &amp; Esh)" label="Torch (Feat. Ceschi &amp; Esh)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Please_Subscribe_Feat_Napoleon_Da_Legend__Wax/</id><title>Seez Mics - Please Subscribe (Feat. Napoleon Da Legend &amp; Wax) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:31:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:31:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Please_Subscribe_Feat_Napoleon_Da_Legend__Wax/" title="Seez Mics - Please Subscribe (Feat. Napoleon Da Legend &amp; Wax) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't break habits by wearing straight jackets <br>And let's be honest I'm not exactly a babe magnet <br>I just stay rappin, I display passion <br>I'm amazed so many of you will age backwards <br>And pay taxes on your stick in the mud <br>Before hitting rock bottom with a sickening thud <br>I keep banging away til the stone's dripping in blood <br>And any seed of doubt gets nipped in the bud <br>What Spit for the love, that's one answer <br>When questioning the purpose of seeing no funds transfer <br>I mean that other stuff, peace to Doug Stamper <br>Don't swallow their hot air, it'll give you lung cancer <br>Run Prancer, Santa's gotta kiss god's ass <br>To keep the Kardashians on task <br>Heaven and hell only exist for the contrast <br>Please subscribe to the Chrome Bills podcast <br><br>Plugged in the matrix every plug shameless <br>When the Bucks came in everything I touch famous <br>Dub tapes to club bangers using rough language <br>Nuff anguish to create a buzz like drug sandwich <br>It's iTunes and bandcamp YouTube and tidal <br>New tunes'll make u wanna kill yourself suicidal when <br>Art and money mix you hear a lot of funny shit <br>Raise the rug up and sweep all of the bull up under it <br>Understandable smooth we eating cannibal food <br>You too robotic can't adapt too mechanical when you move <br>I'm promoters dream demote yo team when I perform a scene <br>Getting that Gorgonzola cheese when I record a scheme <br>Let the Killa orca breath make a scene make it seem normal make it Seem like I'm making cream off it <br>I saw it I envisioned it often now im living it <br>So hit the link ASAP get ya subscription in <br><br>How could you not be a subscriber, speaking such fire <br>Keeping ya in line til I freaking retire <br>Me and MacGyver are similar people <br>Turning nothing into something that's considerably lethal <br>Now that's an old reference, but the analogy stands <br>And you'll never snatch this microphone up out of these hands <br>Whether rapping or podcasting <br>Or at karaoke night fucking up Janet Jackson <br>My podcast improv, no note pads <br>As for now, the shit ain't got no ads <br>But I might change up on you bitches <br>Sell out to dollar shave club on you bitches <br>I gets downloads, but not a crazy amount <br>I hope this shit goes up like it's my savings account <br>But mostly I just want ya'll to vibe <br>Be safe out there, and please subscribe]]></content><category term="Seez Mics" label="Seez Mics"/><category term="Please Subscribe (Feat. Napoleon Da Legend &amp; Wax)" label="Please Subscribe (Feat. Napoleon Da Legend &amp; Wax)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Keep_Your_Cool_Feat_Priest_Da_Nomad__K-Cromozone/</id><title>Seez Mics - Keep Your Cool (Feat. Priest Da Nomad &amp; K-Cromozone) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:31:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:31:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Keep_Your_Cool_Feat_Priest_Da_Nomad__K-Cromozone/" title="Seez Mics - Keep Your Cool (Feat. Priest Da Nomad &amp; K-Cromozone) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Another morning of what is and what's not said <br>Complicated by the chemical cobwebs <br>She's pushing buttons cause she knows I'm a hot head <br>I'm refusing to respond, our stubbornness in lock step <br>The nonsense of a communication breakdown <br>Between children on the human race's playground <br>Darken the skies with accumulating rain clouds <br>And the torch of pride can illuminate the ways out <br>I choose to wait now, don't dare pursue it farther <br>I'd rather bare my soul than have to wear a suit of armor <br>Or be the fairy tale therapeutic charmer <br>Just hold myself accountable for where we move as partners <br>There the truth is hardest, gotta learn how to fight <br>Without the foolish torch of pride burning too bright <br>Day became night in the circle of life <br>We got home from work, kissed and made up, the turned out the light <br><br>Priest Da Nomad, I was fresh out the crib <br>Lookin smooth on a calm day <br>Pushin my jont down the BW parkway <br>By 410, with my hype ass, pumpin beats out the truck <br>Rhymin, lights flash now they rollin up on me <br>I'm thinkin Damn slim what the hell they want with me man <br>We already late to the gig, my dude puffin on a cig <br>We nervous as hell dawg, and we ain't done nothing <br>But when you look like me, wrong words, and they blow your stuffin <br>All over your baby's car seat, cerebellum like cherry slurpee <br>They ask for my license and I can see they wanna hurt me <br>Two men robbed a Suntrust They're black in a black truck <br>Dawg How many black dudes you see driving a black truck <br>Gotta be 50% around here, Escalades to Mountaineers <br>My boy said, Keep it Cool Priest out of fear <br>Never mind sir It seems we got the wrong guys <br>Clearly Dude thank God they didn't try to Tamir me <br>I had to keep <br><br>Start the day, like I'm tracking the start date <br>Of my heart rate as we embark on the Stargate <br>Accelerates as we elevate <br>You can't telestrate development as it comes <br>So let's take a sec to step back true <br>A good playlist can put you in the right mood <br>My mood is karma mood swing is unspoken <br>Unheard one word one motion <br>The ebb and flow is the ocean <br>So I don't ride the wave of emotion <br>I took a crash course in coping <br>From that bum living on the platform at Fulton <br>And took the time to breathe out <br>live a little slower like an off season beach town <br>We found, if you swallow your pride and follow in stride <br>Every missed shot has a rebound]]></content><category term="Seez Mics" label="Seez Mics"/><category term="Keep Your Cool (Feat. Priest Da Nomad &amp; K-Cromozone)" label="Keep Your Cool (Feat. Priest Da Nomad &amp; K-Cromozone)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Howl_At_The_Sky_Feat_Uptown_XO_Kokayi/</id><title>Seez Mics - Howl At The Sky (Feat. Uptown XO, Kokayi) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:31:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:31:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Seez_Mics/Howl_At_The_Sky_Feat_Uptown_XO_Kokayi/" title="Seez Mics - Howl At The Sky (Feat. Uptown XO, Kokayi) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't wanna sit and stare at a spreadsheet <br>That is telling me humanity is dead meat <br>My kind of fun is solitary and stress free <br>Refilling the tank when my empathy is empty <br>Friends see it all the good and the bad <br>So when I'm bad at being good, it's for the good of the math <br>Add the energy you have, put a foot on the path <br>Before judging another's smile as too crooked to laugh <br>Mistook it for wrath, the lesson was one of benevolence <br>discovering elements <br>Of surprise, surprise we're all under development <br>Hate to say I told you so for the love of intelligence <br>None of it's relevant, so listen up <br>We all drink the same water, just from different cups <br>A cigarette's the only time I'm kissing butts <br>Cause I know my way around every nip and tuck, zip it shut <br><br>I don't wanna sit and stare at the city streets <br>I need a outlet a plug it's 10 degrees <br>My heart will freeze if I go below zero <br>So whenever I see doe I docie doe <br>Stability is required for manhood <br>Didn't understand the mechanics until I lifted up my damn hood <br>Fuck materialism that isn't him you or me <br>And killing your brother for nothing doesn't make you a G <br>I talk to God everyday he created you and me <br>The planets and stars are organized <br>Today I thought of lines to make <br>The sourt of lime <br>light to over ride <br>Any team I'm the coach of mine <br>Approach the mic with a cultured mind <br>Here to take the game into overtime <br>Like Jordan 23 or 45 <br>With the truth I'm flashy <br>like Nas I'm nasty <br>I tell em perseverance what got me here when they ask me <br><br>I don't wanna sit and stare at a sketched piece <br>Mugshot slug shots now he resting <br>Blood shot eye water no jet stream <br>The purge of further murder his mother utters the next thing <br>Jah bless em cuz he nah wan tessem test em <br>Now he peeking from the urn top a beech wood dresser but she preached good lessons <br>Yet he heed no warnings but got inspired by the choir every Sunday morning <br>Lawd lord please save em she beseeching <br>Betwixt her grieving amidst relieving <br>the third shift at the shipping and receiving <br>Juxtaposed to his growing greed and packages he stuck both his feet in <br>good til the product ain't a factor but his math was misleading <br>so his path lack the crumbs of bread to lead em back now she howling at the sky with a tear stuck to her lashes <br>a quarter moon amidst the stars as the waves keep crashing, so]]></content><category term="Seez Mics" label="Seez Mics"/><category term="Howl At The Sky (Feat. Uptown XO, Kokayi)" label="Howl At The Sky (Feat. Uptown XO, Kokayi)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Legend/City_Of_Stars__Audition_-_Medley/</id><title>John Legend - City Of Stars &amp; Audition - Medley - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:31:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:31:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/John_Legend/City_Of_Stars__Audition_-_Medley/" title="John Legend - City Of Stars &amp; Audition - Medley - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[City of stars <br>Are you shining just for me <br>City of stars <br>There's so much that I can't see <br>Who knows <br>Is this the start of something <br>wonderful and new <br>Or one more dream <br>that I cannot make true <br>Barefoot she smiled <br>And leapt without looking <br>And tumbled into the Seine <br>The water was freezing <br>She spent a month sneezing <br>But said she would do it again <br>Here's to the ones who dream <br>Foolish as they may seem <br>Here's to the hearts that ache <br>Here's to the mess we make <br>She told me <br>A bit of madness is key <br>To give us new colors to see <br>Who knows where it will lead us <br>And that's why they need us <br>So bring on the rebels <br>The ripples from pebbles <br>The painters and poets and plays <br>And here's to the fools who dream <br>Crazy as they may seem <br>Here's to the hearts that break <br>Here's to the mess we make <br>City of stars <br>Are you shining just for me <br>City of stars <br>You never shined so brightly <br>]]></content><category term="John Legend" label="John Legend"/><category term="City Of Stars &amp; Audition - Medley" label="City Of Stars &amp; Audition - Medley"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/주희_Joohee/Bad_Dream/</id><title>주희 (Joohee) - Bad Dream - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A3%BC%ED%9D%AC_Joohee/Bad_Dream/" title="주희 (Joohee) - Bad Dream - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[oh 난 그냥 길을 걷고 있었어 <br>갑자기 눈앞이 보이질 않아 <br>숨이 막혀 몸이 말을 안 들어 <br>처음 보는 사람들이 <br>내 이름을 외치고 막 <br>손가락질을 하네 <br>tv에 나오는 여자 <br>bad dream bad dream <br>somebody wake me please <br>숨이 끊어져 죽겠지 <br>근데 왜 나를 비웃지 <br>날 깨워줘 <br>help me help me <br>누가 좀 도와줘 <br>제발 현실이 아니길 <br>차라리 죽을 것 같은 <br>악몽 그 뿐이길 <br>두려움이 검은 파도 되어 <br>날 집어삼켜 <br>터져라 숨을 쉬어 봐도 <br>더 모자라 <br>tv에 나오는 여자 <br>bad dream bad dream <br>somebody wake me please <br>숨이 끊어져 죽겠지 <br>근데 왜 나를 비웃지 <br>날 깨워줘 <br>help me help me <br>누가 좀 도와줘 <br>제발 현실이 아니길 <br>차라리 죽을 것 같은 <br>악몽 그 뿐이길 <br>]]></content><category term="주희 (Joohee)" label="주희 (Joohee)"/><category term="Bad Dream" label="Bad Dream"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/주희_Joohee/Shes_Mine/</id><title>주희 (Joohee) - She`s Mine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A3%BC%ED%9D%AC_Joohee/Shes_Mine/" title="주희 (Joohee) - She`s Mine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[게으른 넌 해가 진 후에나 일어나 <br>밤새 두 눈 두 귀를 막아놓고선 <br>무책임하게 넌 도망가 버려 <br>니가 떠나버린 빈자리의 잔해들 <br>치우는 건 온전히 내 몫이네 <br>이기적인 너는 멋대로 <br>시간을 멈추고 <br>어지러운 감정들로 <br>날 마비시켜 <br>아무 생각하지도 못하게 <br>get out get out of my zone <br>her body body oh she's mine <br>No no no no no <br>she's my ma ma ma <br>ma ma ma ma my baby <br>get out get out of my world <br>nobody body can stay here <br>No no no no no <br>she's my ma ma ma <br>ma ma ma ma my baby <br>넌 내가 계획했던 모든 걸 망쳐 <br>꿈 추억 낭만 영혼 환상 <br>전부 철 지난 얘기들 <br>그 속에 빠져있네 <br>또 주저앉아 울기만 하네 <br>아이처럼 <br>어제와 똑같이 술이네 <br>마치 내일이 오지 않을 것 같이 <br>get out get out of my zone <br>her body body oh she's mine <br>No no no no no <br>she's my ma ma ma <br>ma ma ma ma my baby <br>get out get out of my world <br>nobody body can stay here <br>No no no no no <br>she's my ma ma ma <br>ma ma ma ma my baby <br>There is one thing <br>you will never know <br>Fact that you are the one <br>who is killing her <br>get out get out of my zone <br>her body body oh she's mine <br>No no no no no <br>she's my ma ma ma <br>ma ma ma ma my baby <br>get out get out of my world <br>nobody body can stay here <br>No no no no no <br>she's my ma ma ma <br>ma ma ma ma my baby <br>]]></content><category term="주희 (Joohee)" label="주희 (Joohee)"/><category term="She`s Mine" label="She`s Mine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/주희_Joohee/Imma/</id><title>주희 (Joohee) - Imma - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A3%BC%ED%9D%AC_Joohee/Imma/" title="주희 (Joohee) - Imma - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[댄싱 to the left <br>to the left 똑같이 <br>다시 to the right <br>to the right 뭣같이 <br>내가 나일 수 없는 이 파티 <br>가면 놀이는 난 싫어 <br>더는 못하겠어 <br>이젠 날 위해서 <br>He said adventure is out there <br>I’mma sing a song <br>어디서든 노래할래 <br>I can sing a song <br>어디든지 거기 갈래 <br>이 목소리만 있다면 <br>그게 어디든 <br>I’mma sing a song <br>그게 돈이든 인기든 <br>I can sing a song <br>나는 상관 안 해 지금 <br>중요한 건 이곳에 <br>내가 서있어 <br>음악은 직업이 아닌 내 존재 <br>내가 유명인이 아니게 돼도 <br>It’s my life 아무 미련 없이 <br>좋아서 하는 거니까 <br>다시 돌아갈래 <br>이젠 날 위해서 <br>I say adventure is out there <br>I’mma sing a song <br>어디서든 노래할래 <br>I can sing a song <br>어디든지 거기 갈래 <br>이 목소리만 있다면 <br>그게 어디든 <br>I’mma sing a song <br>그게 돈이든 인기든 <br>I can sing a song <br>나는 상관 안 해 지금 <br>중요한 건 이곳에 <br>내가 서있어 <br>tv에 흘러나오는 <br>나의 목소리 <br>근데 무대 위에 <br>저 여자는 누구지 <br>나는 거기 없었어 <br>내가 아니었어 <br>울고 있었어 <br>I’mma sing a song <br>어디서든 노래할래 <br>I can sing a song <br>어디든지 거기 갈래 <br>이 목소리만 있다면 <br>그게 어디든 <br>I’mma sing a song <br>그게 돈이든 인기든 <br>I can sing a song <br>나는 상관 안 해 지금 <br>중요한 건 이곳에 <br>내가 서있어 <br>]]></content><category term="주희 (Joohee)" label="주희 (Joohee)"/><category term="Imma" label="Imma"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/주희_Joohee/여배우/</id><title>주희 (Joohee) - 여배우 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%A3%BC%ED%9D%AC_Joohee/%EC%97%AC%EB%B0%B0%EC%9A%B0/" title="주희 (Joohee) - 여배우 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[오늘도 완벽히 속였어 <br>사람들이 속았어 <br>여배우 난 명배우가 된 듯이 <br>하지만 난 알아 알아 <br>슬픈 이 드라마의 끝을 <br>예쁘기도 하지 <br>사람들은 그녀를 사랑해 <br>착하기도 하지 <br>사람들은 그런 <br>그녀를 좋아해 <br>내 기분은 오늘도 <br>엉망인데 연습해 <br>나는 또 웃는 표정 <br>거울 속에 서 있는 <br>저 여자는 아까부터 웃네 <br>나는 우는데 울지 마 <br>사람들은 싫어할걸 <br>사람들은 <br>keep calm and smiling <br>들켜선 안돼 드러내선 안돼 <br>오늘도 완벽히 속였어 <br>사람들이 속았어 <br>여배우 난 명배우가 된 듯이 <br>하지만 난 알아 알아 <br>슬픈 이 드라마의 끝을 <br>예뻐야만 하지 <br>사람들은 그걸 좋아해 <br>착해야만 하지 <br>사람들은 그래 그걸 좋아해 <br>모두가 내게 <br>환호해 사랑해 <br>처음 보는 사람들의 <br>기대를 저버릴 순 없으니 <br>붉은 내 입술 같은 <br>레드 카펫 위를 <br>미끄러지듯 걸어가며 <br>손을 흔들어 우아하게 <br>마치 그렇게 태어난 듯 <br>마치 그렇게 살아온 듯 <br>오늘도 완벽히 속였어 <br>사람들이 속았어 <br>여배우 난 명배우가 된 듯이 <br>하지만 난 알아 알아 <br>슬픈 이 드라마의 끝을 <br>누구나 될 순 있지만 <br>내가 될 순 없지 <br>하지만 이 가면을 <br>벗고 싶진 않아 <br>혼자이고 싶지 않아 <br>잊혀지고 싶지 않아 두려워 <br>이 드라마가 <br>영원하길 기도해 <br>오늘도 완벽히 속였어 <br>나 자신도 속았어 <br>이대로 난 어디로 가는지 <br>어디쯤일까 일까 <br>슬픈 이 드라마의 끝은 <br>]]></content><category term="주희 (Joohee)" label="주희 (Joohee)"/><category term="여배우" label="여배우"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/혜화동소년/너의_바다를_나서네_After_Your_Sea/</id><title>혜화동소년 - 너의 바다를 나서네 (After Your Sea) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%98%9C%ED%99%94%EB%8F%99%EC%86%8C%EB%85%84/%EB%84%88%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%94%EB%8B%A4%EB%A5%BC_%EB%82%98%EC%84%9C%EB%84%A4_After_Your_Sea/" title="혜화동소년 - 너의 바다를 나서네 (After Your Sea) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[비가 올 때 그대 우산에 슬며시 <br>옮겨가 함께 걷는다면 <br>내 마음을 들킬까요 <br>버스에서 그대 어깨에 슬며시 <br>잠든 척 머릴 기댄다면 <br>내 마음을 들킬까요 <br>데려다 주던 이 길은 <br>항상 짧게만 느껴졌어 <br>돌아오는 길보다 <br>바보처럼 오늘도 말 못하고 <br>집에 가는 뒷모습만 보네 <br>겨울처럼 얼어붙은 입 <br>봄이 되면 사랑한다 <br>말 할 수 있을까 <br>움츠려 있던 발 끝에 용기도 <br>새싹 되어 자라나고 있어 <br>고요하게 찾아왔던 너 <br>하지만 난 너만 보면 휩쓸려버려 <br>파도가 넘치듯 설레는 마음은 <br>배가되어 너의 바다를 나서네 <br>겨울처럼 얼어붙은 입 <br>봄이 되면 사랑한다 <br>말 할 수 있을까 <br>움츠려 있던 발 끝에 용기도 <br>새싹 되어 자라나고 있어 <br>고요하게 찾아왔던 너 <br>하지만 난 너만 보면 휩쓸려버려 <br>파도가 넘치듯 설레는 마음은 <br>배가되어 너의 바다를 나서네 <br>너의 바다를 나서네 <br>]]></content><category term="혜화동소년" label="혜화동소년"/><category term="너의 바다를 나서네 (After Your Sea)" label="너의 바다를 나서네 (After Your Sea)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/이주아/많이/</id><title>이주아 - 많이 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9D%B4%EC%A3%BC%EC%95%84/%EB%A7%8E%EC%9D%B4/" title="이주아 - 많이 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[다 괜찮겠지 <br>조금 허전할 뿐야 <br>네가 없이 살아왔던 <br>날들로 돌아가는 거야 <br>많이 힘들겠지 <br>울기도 할 거야 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>널 간직할게 <br>많이 슬프겠지 <br>주저앉을 거야 <br>흔적도 없어진 <br>널 잊어볼게 <br>다 정리했어 <br>조금 생각날 뿐야 <br>네가 없이 살아가는 <br>날들이 많아지는 거야 <br>네 생각하면서 <br>가끔 웃기도 해 <br>하지만 좋았던 <br>기억도 지울 거야 <br>많이 힘들겠지 <br>울기도 할 거야 <br>아무도 모르게 <br>널 간직할게 <br>많이 슬프겠지 <br>주저앉을 거야 <br>흔적도 없어진 <br>널 잊어볼게 <br>]]></content><category term="이주아" label="이주아"/><category term="많이" label="많이"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김창훈과_블랙스톤즈/독백_Full_Ver/</id><title>김창훈과 블랙스톤즈 - 독백 (Full Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%B0%BD%ED%9B%88%EA%B3%BC_%EB%B8%94%EB%9E%99%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A4%EC%A6%88/%EB%8F%85%EB%B0%B1_Full_Ver/" title="김창훈과 블랙스톤즈 - 독백 (Full Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어두운 거리를 <br>나 홀로 걷다가 <br>밤하늘 바라보았소 <br>어제처럼 별이 <br>하얗게 빛나고 <br>달도 밝은데 <br>오늘은 <br>그 어느 누가 태어나고 <br>어느 누가 잠들었소 <br>거리의 나무를 <br>바라보아도 <br>아무 말도 하질 않네 <br>어둠이 개이고 <br>아침이 오면은 <br>눈부신 햇살이 <br>머리를 비추고 <br>해밝은 웃음과 <br>활기찬 걸음이 <br>거리를 가득 메우리 <br>하지만 밤이 <br>다시 찾아오면 <br>노을 속에 <br>뿔뿔이 흩어지고 <br>하릴없이 이리저리 헤매다 <br>나 홀로 되어 남으리 <br>야윈 어깨 너머로 <br>무슨 소리 들려 <br>돌아다보니 아무것 없고 <br>차가운 바람만 <br>얼굴을 부딪고 <br>밤이슬 두 눈 적시네 <br>나 혼자 눈감는 건 <br>두렵지 않으나 <br>헤어짐이 헤어짐이 서러워 <br>쓸쓸한 비라도 <br>내리게 되면은 <br>금방 울어 버리겠네 <br>]]></content><category term="김창훈과 블랙스톤즈" label="김창훈과 블랙스톤즈"/><category term="독백 (Full Ver.)" label="독백 (Full Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/김창훈과_블랙스톤즈/독백_Radio_Edit/</id><title>김창훈과 블랙스톤즈 - 독백 (Radio Edit) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B9%80%EC%B0%BD%ED%9B%88%EA%B3%BC_%EB%B8%94%EB%9E%99%EC%8A%A4%ED%86%A4%EC%A6%88/%EB%8F%85%EB%B0%B1_Radio_Edit/" title="김창훈과 블랙스톤즈 - 독백 (Radio Edit) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어두운 거리를 <br>나 홀로 걷다가 <br>밤하늘 바라보았소 <br>어제처럼 별이 <br>하얗게 빛나고 <br>달도 밝은데 <br>오늘은 <br>그 어느 누가 태어나고 <br>어느 누가 잠들었소 <br>거리의 나무를 <br>바라보아도 <br>아무 말도 하질 않네 <br>어둠이 개이고 <br>아침이 오면은 <br>눈부신 햇살이 <br>머리를 비추고 <br>해밝은 웃음과 <br>활기찬 걸음이 <br>거리를 가득 메우리 <br>하지만 밤이 <br>다시 찾아오면 <br>노을 속에 <br>뿔뿔이 흩어지고 <br>하릴없이 이리저리 헤매다 <br>나 홀로 되어 남으리 <br>야윈 어깨 너머로 <br>무슨 소리 들려 <br>돌아다보니 아무것 없고 <br>차가운 바람만 <br>얼굴을 부딪고 <br>밤이슬 두 눈 적시네 <br>나 혼자 눈감는 건 <br>두렵지 않으나 <br>헤어짐이 헤어짐이 서러워 <br>쓸쓸한 비라도 <br>내리게 되면은 <br>금방 울어 버리겠네 <br>]]></content><category term="김창훈과 블랙스톤즈" label="김창훈과 블랙스톤즈"/><category term="독백 (Radio Edit)" label="독백 (Radio Edit)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/레베카/이_밤을_보내면/</id><title>레베카 - 이 밤을 보내면 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EB%A0%88%EB%B2%A0%EC%B9%B4/%EC%9D%B4_%EB%B0%A4%EC%9D%84_%EB%B3%B4%EB%82%B4%EB%A9%B4/" title="레베카 - 이 밤을 보내면 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[눈 감으면 어둠은 <br>나에게 다가와 <br>널 잊으라 해 <br>눈을 감으면 선명한 <br>기억만 아직도 <br>내 마음속에 남아 <br>새벽은 날 재우지만 <br>너의 얼굴은 <br>또 나를 깨우네 <br>언제쯤 이 밤은 <br>너를 데려가 줄까 <br>잊혀질까 내 남은 사랑이 <br>나 혼자선 이제 <br>어떤 것도 할 수 없어 <br>나를 데려가 줄래 <br>아무도 없이 <br>혼자 지우는 이름 <br>나를 도와줄래 <br>너를 잊을 수 있게 <br>새벽은 날 재우지만 <br>너의 얼굴은 <br>또 나를 깨우네 <br>언제쯤 이 밤은 <br>너를 데려가 줄까 <br>잊혀질까 내 남은 사랑이 <br>나 혼자선 이제 <br>어떤 것도 할 수 없어 <br>나를 데려가 줄래 <br>아무도 없이 <br>혼자 지우는 이름 <br>나를 도와줄래 <br>너를 잊을 수 있게 <br>]]></content><category term="레베카" label="레베카"/><category term="이 밤을 보내면" label="이 밤을 보내면"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/와니/나를_두고_가지_말아요/</id><title>와니 - 나를 두고 가지 말아요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%99%80%EB%8B%88/%EB%82%98%EB%A5%BC_%EB%91%90%EA%B3%A0_%EA%B0%80%EC%A7%80_%EB%A7%90%EC%95%84%EC%9A%94/" title="와니 - 나를 두고 가지 말아요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나를 두고 가지 말아요 <br>내 사랑은 여기 있는데 <br>너가 없이 또 하루가 <br>흘러가게 두긴 싫어요 <br>나를 두고 가지 말아요 <br>네가 떠나 가던 날 <br>왜 이러죠 웃지 않죠 <br>뻔한 이야기 지루한가요 <br>공기 조차 어색 하죠 <br>그댄 지금 어딜 봐요 <br>나는 옆에 있는데 <br>말도 없이 답답하죠 <br>살며시 들려오는 <br>너의 예쁜 목소리 <br>귓가에 맴도는데 헤어지자니 <br>제발 나를 두고 가지 말아요 <br>내 사랑은 여기 있는데 <br>너가 없이 또 하루가 <br>흘러가게 두긴 싫어요 <br>나를 두고 가지 말아요 <br>네가 떠나 가던 날 <br>알 수 없죠 마음이란 <br>변치 않을 것만 같았죠 <br>나 혼자의 착각이죠 <br>살며시 내게 다가와 <br>설레이게 해주고 <br>마음속에 남겨준 말 <br>사랑 하지 않아 <br>나를 두고 가지 말아요 <br>내 사랑은 여기 있는데 <br>너가 없이 또 하루가 <br>흘러가게 두긴 싫어요 <br>나를 두고 가지 말아요 <br>네가 떠나 가던 날 <br>나를 두고 가지 말아요 <br>내 사랑은 여기 있는데 <br>너가 없이 또 하루가 <br>흘러가게 두긴 싫어요 <br>나를 두고 가지 말아요 <br>네가 떠나 가던 날 <br>]]></content><category term="와니" label="와니"/><category term="나를 두고 가지 말아요" label="나를 두고 가지 말아요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/원준혁/You/</id><title>원준혁 - You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9B%90%EC%A4%80%ED%98%81/You/" title="원준혁 - You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[넌 이별을 몰랐고 <br>난 사랑을 몰랐고 <br>넌 내게 주기만 했고 <br>난 그저 당연시 했고 <br>you 마지막으로 <br>할 말이 없냐며 <br>you 말없이 고개만 <br>숙이고 있네 <br>넌 상처를 받았고 <br>난 사랑을 받았고 <br>넌 항상 힘들어했고 <br>난 매번 몰랐던 거고 <br>you 마지막으로 <br>할 말이 없냐며 <br>you 말없이 고개만 <br>숙이고 있네 <br>미리 알았더라면 <br>조금만 일찍 <br>여기까지 오진 <br>않았을텐데 <br>니 얼굴을 보는데 <br>나도 모르게 울컥 <br>울컥 그저 멍하니 있네 <br>you 미안해 그 동안 <br>많이 힘들었지 <br>you 잘지내 <br>행복하길 바랄게 <br>]]></content><category term="원준혁" label="원준혁"/><category term="You" label="You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/아몬드_블라썸/예수의_바람/</id><title>아몬드 블라썸 - 예수의 바람 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:32:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:32:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%95%84%EB%AA%AC%EB%93%9C_%EB%B8%94%EB%9D%BC%EC%8D%B8/%EC%98%88%EC%88%98%EC%9D%98_%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C/" title="아몬드 블라썸 - 예수의 바람 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예수 날 자유케 하는 <br>용서의 이름 <br>예수 우릴 화해케 하는 <br>사랑의 이름 <br>예수 날 자유케 하는 <br>용서의 이름 <br>예수 우릴 화해케 하는 <br>사랑의 이름 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>예수님 말씀 <br>우리 안에 계신 성령님 <br>우리 안에 계신 성령님 <br>우리 안에 계신 성령님 <br>새일 행하시네 <br>예수의 바람 우리에게 불어와 <br>억눌린 우릴 자유케 하시네 <br>진리의 말씀 우리에게 다가와 <br>원수 된 우릴 용서케 하시네 <br>예수 날 자유케 하는 <br>용서의 이름 <br>예수 우릴 화해케 하는 <br>사랑의 이름 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>예수님 말씀 <br>우리 안에 계신 성령님 <br>우리 안에 계신 성령님 <br>우리 안에 계신 성령님 <br>새일 행하시네 <br>예수의 바람 우리에게 불어와 <br>억눌린 우릴 자유케 하시네 <br>진리의 말씀 우리에게 다가와 <br>원수 된 우릴 용서케 하시네 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>예수님 말씀 <br>우리 안에 계신 성령님 <br>우리 안에 계신 성령님 <br>우리 안에 계신 성령님 <br>새일 행하시네 <br>예수의 바람 우리에게 불어와 <br>억눌린 우릴 자유케 하시네 <br>진리의 말씀 우리에게 다가와 <br>원수 된 우릴 용서케 하시네 <br>성령의 바람 우리에게 불어와 <br>갈라진 우릴 화목케 하시네 <br>예수는 자유케 하시는 <br>용서의 바람 <br>예수는 하나 되게 하시는 <br>사랑의 바람 <br>예수는 자유케 하시는 <br>용서의 바람 <br>예수는 하나 되게 하시는 <br>사랑의 바람 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>너희에게 평화가 있기를 <br>]]></content><category term="아몬드 블라썸" label="아몬드 블라썸"/><category term="예수의 바람" label="예수의 바람"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신새롬/Fine/</id><title>신새롬 - Fine - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:33:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:33:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%83%88%EB%A1%AC/Fine/" title="신새롬 - Fine - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알아요 내 탓인걸 <br>다시는 날 찾으려 하지 않겠죠 <br>내게 냉정했던 그 모습조차도 <br>나 너무 그리워하는데 <br>내가 참 바보 같아 <br>생각보다 훨씬 한심한 것 같아 <br>좀 더 태연하게 보내고 싶은데 <br>왜 맘이 흔들리는 건지 <br>꼭 나를 떠나야만 한다면 <br>더 잔인하게 날 대해야 해요 <br>훗날 그대와의 추억에 기대어 <br>또 눈물 보이지 않도록 <br>과분한 꿈이었나요 <br>그대를 원해온 내 모습 <br>제발 나 아닌 누굴 더 <br>사랑한다고 말하지 마요 <br>나 죽어가겠죠 <br>살아도 사는 게 아닌 난 <br>이미 슬픔에 모든 걸 다 <br>뺏겨버린 채 <br>oh 그대 꿈을 꾸겠죠 <br>꼭 헤어지는 그 순간만은 <br>왜 죄가 됐나요 <br>그대를 원해온 날들이 <br>제발 나 아닌 누굴 더 <br>사랑한다고 말하지 마요 <br>나 죽어가겠죠 <br>살아도 사는 게 아닌 난 <br>이미 슬픔에 모든 걸 다 <br>뺏겨버린 채 <br>oh 이렇게 난 <br>왜 나만이 너를 그리워하는 거야 <br>더 이상 혼자란 생각에 <br>참을 수 없어 널 잊지 못해 <br>널 사랑해 내게로 제발 돌아와 줘 <br>너만을 그리며 또 울고 있잖아 <br>oh 돌아와 줘 내게로 <br>]]></content><category term="신새롬" label="신새롬"/><category term="Fine" label="Fine"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/신새롬/바람_愛/</id><title>신새롬 - 바람 愛 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:33:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:33:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%A0%EC%83%88%EB%A1%AC/%EB%B0%94%EB%9E%8C_%E6%84%9B/" title="신새롬 - 바람 愛 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대는 알리 없죠 이런 내 사랑을 <br>차마 전하지 못할 애달픈 마음을 <br>그녀를 향한 미소 내 것 이길 <br>난 못된 바램 기도 드리죠 <br>바람이 불어오기를 <br>이 마음 그대에게 닿기를 바라죠 <br>바람에 흔들려 나를 봐주길 <br>세상 하루라 해도 좋을 텐데 <br>나의 숨이 다하고 끝내 잠이 들면 <br>그댈 향한 내 마음 멈추게 될까요 <br>따뜻한 그대 손길 그 눈빛 <br>날 안아주길 간절히 원하죠 <br>난 바람 불어와주길 <br>이 마음 그대에게 닿기를 바래요 <br>바람에 흔들려 내게 온다면 <br>세상 단 하루라 해도 <br>나는 행복 할게요 <br>나의 바램이 이뤄지길 <br>끝내 벌 나 받아도 <br>나 그댈 가질 수 있으면 된 거죠 <br>바람이 불어오네요 <br>바람이 불어오네요 <br>이 마음 그대에게 닿기를 바래요 <br>바람에 날 돌아본 그대 미소가 <br>너무 행복해 눈물이 나요 <br>그대가 나를 보네요 <br>이 마음 그대에게 닿아진 건가요 <br>바람에 나의 마음이 닿았다면 <br>그대 날 안아주세요 <br>단 하루라 해도 <br>]]></content><category term="신새롬" label="신새롬"/><category term="바람 愛" label="바람 愛"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤일/Better_Man/</id><title>헤일 - Better Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:33:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:33:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%BC/Better_Man/" title="헤일 - Better Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[축 처진 어깨에 <br>항상 땅만 보는 눈동자 <br>한숨에 또 한숨 <br>뭐가 그리 자신 없는지 <br>이제는 사랑한단 말도 <br>그저 위로하는 줄 알고 <br>힘 없이 웃죠 <br>넌 너무 예뻐 근데 난 <br>그댄 더 환상적이죠 <br>가진 게 하나도 없어 <br>ohh hold on I'll tell you <br>그래 난 끝내주는 여자 <br>but 처음부턴 아냐 <br>당신이 만든 거야 <br>세상이 다 아는 걸 <br>그대는 그 정도로 작지 않죠 <br>사람을 변화시키는 힘이 있죠 <br>이보다 근사할 수 없어 <br>내가 증거죠 <br>You make me better man <br>맨 처음 사랑을 시작한 <br>이유가 뭐게요 <br>그대의 허세 없는 진심 <br>가진 건 없어도 나 하난 <br>책임질 수 있을 것 같았죠 <br>기억하나요 <br>그대는 그 정도로 작지 않죠 <br>사람을 변화시키는 힘이 있죠 <br>이보다 근사할 수 없어 <br>내가 증거죠 <br>You make me better man <br>잠시 넘어지면 어때요 <br>비교하지 말아요 <br>지금 이 모습 그대로 <br>충분한걸요 <br>You are my fortune <br>사랑해요 <br>그대는 그 정도로 작지 않죠 <br>사람을 변화시키는 힘이 있죠 <br>이보다 근사할 수 없어 <br>내가 증거죠 <br>난 노력했죠 널 만난 후로 <br>You make me better man <br>]]></content><category term="헤일" label="헤일"/><category term="Better Man" label="Better Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤일/어지러워/</id><title>헤일 - 어지러워 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:33:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:33:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%BC/%EC%96%B4%EC%A7%80%EB%9F%AC%EC%9B%8C/" title="헤일 - 어지러워 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[나 어지러워 <br>나한테만 웃어주는 <br>너잖아 <br>잘생긴 강아지 <br>날 보며 찡긋해 <br>돌아가시겠어 <br>들켜버렸어 <br>여자마음 쉽게 <br>내 주면 안 되는데 <br>점점 날 닮아가는 <br>네 말투 네 표정 <br>떨어져있어도 <br>맴도는 그대의 향기 <br>그런 너를 매일 못 보다니 <br>말도 안돼 <br>보고 싶어서 현기증이나 <br>보고 싶다고 말도 못하고 <br>이러다가 나 쓰러진다면 <br>달려와서 꼭 안아주겠지 <br>보고 싶어서 현기증이나 <br>보고 싶다고 말도 못하고 <br>이러다가 나 쓰러질 거야 <br>달려와서 꼭 안아줘야 해 <br>조절이 안돼 <br>며칠 만에 보는 거야 <br>도대체 <br>얼굴은 똑같고 <br>마음만 깊어져 <br>어떻게 된 거야 <br>손 잡아줘요 주인 잃은 내 손 <br>지금 외로워 <br>차갑게 두지 말고 <br>네 품에 넣어줘 <br>떨어져있어도 맴도는 <br>그대 목소리 <br>그런 너를 매일 못 보다니 <br>말도 안돼 <br>보고 싶어서 현기증이나 <br>보고 싶다고 말도 못하고 <br>이러다가 나 쓰러진다면 <br>달려와서 꼭 안아주겠지 <br>보고 싶어서 현기증이나 <br>보고 싶다고 말도 못하고 <br>이러다가 나 쓰러질 거야 <br>달려와서 꼭 안아줘야 해 <br>]]></content><category term="헤일" label="헤일"/><category term="어지러워" label="어지러워"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤일/Drink_Alone/</id><title>헤일 - Drink Alone - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:33:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:33:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%BC/Drink_Alone/" title="헤일 - Drink Alone - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[어둠이 깊게 내려앉아 <br>또 다시 찾아오는 혼자만의 시간 <br>방 안에 불을 켜고 <br>내뱉는 한숨 소리 <br>어느새 돌아오는 공허한 외로움 <br>익숙해지지 않는 그 조용함에 <br>답답한 공기라도 벗어나볼까 <br>흘러가는 tv 잡음소리 <br>오늘도 마시네 <br>오늘도 마시네 <br>오늘만 마실게 <br>외로움을 잊으려 해 <br>또 한 잔 기울이지 <br>지워지지 않고 맴도는 <br>너와 내가 나눈 사소한 얘기들 <br>얼어붙은 시간에 <br>머물러 있는 듯해 <br>전화도 못하는 밤 눈물만 쏟아내 <br>오늘도 마시네 <br>오늘도 마시네 <br>오늘만 마실게 <br>외로움을 잊으려 해 <br>또 한 잔 또 한 잔 <br>언제쯤이면 익숙해질까 <br>시간이 흘러도 <br>반갑지 않은 이 조용함이 <br>]]></content><category term="헤일" label="헤일"/><category term="Drink Alone" label="Drink Alone"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/헤일/버스를_기다리는_사람들_Remastered_Ver/</id><title>헤일 - 버스를 기다리는 사람들 (Remastered Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:33:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:33:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%97%A4%EC%9D%BC/%EB%B2%84%EC%8A%A4%EB%A5%BC_%EA%B8%B0%EB%8B%A4%EB%A6%AC%EB%8A%94_%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%8C%EB%93%A4_Remastered_Ver/" title="헤일 - 버스를 기다리는 사람들 (Remastered Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[이제 곧 널 만나는 시간 <br>이마엔 땀 송글 맺히고 <br>해는 아직 놀고 싶은지 날 불렀어 <br>때마침 너에게 문자가 <br>아이고 어쩌지 <br>나 반대로 탄 것 같아 <br>멍청이 그래도 괜찮아 <br>여긴 꽤나 즐거워 <br>할머니 품에 안긴 아기 <br>날 보며 방긋거리고 <br>무거운 장바구닐 든 어머니 <br>청소시간에 벌어진 일들을 <br>재잘대는 저 소녀들 <br>버스 정류장이라는 <br>마을엔 사람들이 살죠 <br>사랑을 기다리는 <br>멀리 그 사랑을 발견하면 <br>언제 기다렸단 듯 함박웃음을 <br>한번 더 너에게 문자를 <br>어디쯤이니 내일쯤 도착하니 <br>아니야 거의 다 왔는걸 <br>백을 세고 있어줘 <br>할머니 품에 안긴 아기 <br>날 보며 방긋거리고 <br>무거운 장바구닐 든 어머니 <br>만난 지 얼마 안 된 저 연인은 <br>우리같네 참 예뻐 <br>차분한 하늘 아래서 <br>천천히 널 생각하면서 <br>사랑을 기다리는 이들과 함께 <br>널 기다려 <br>]]></content><category term="헤일" label="헤일"/><category term="버스를 기다리는 사람들 (Remastered Ver.)" label="버스를 기다리는 사람들 (Remastered Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한해/상을_받아야_돼_Feat_버벌진트/</id><title>한해 - 상을 받아야 돼 (Feat. 버벌진트) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:34:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:34:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%ED%95%B4/%EC%83%81%EC%9D%84_%EB%B0%9B%EC%95%84%EC%95%BC_%EB%8F%BC_Feat_%EB%B2%84%EB%B2%8C%EC%A7%84%ED%8A%B8/" title="한해 - 상을 받아야 돼 (Feat. 버벌진트) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>YEAH <br>TROPHIES I GOT SOME <br>YEAH <br>몇 갠 옷장 속 <br>YEAH <br>몇 갠 어디 있는지 <br>기억이 안 나 <br>타고났나 봐 상복 <br>YEAH <br>RECORDS I GOT SOME <br>YEAH <br>SIX OF'EM REGULAR <br>FOUR OF'EM EP'S <br>ONE OF'EM CRIMINAL <br>반성하네 오늘 밤도 <br>YEAH <br>누군간 내게 묻네 <br>그 얘긴 대체 계속 <br>왜 음악에 <br>넣냐고 다른 뜻은 없네 <br>IT'S JUST A REMINDER FOR MYSELF <br>YEAH <br>TALKIN' TO MYSELF <br>I'VE BEEN DOIN' <br>THAT A LOT THESE DAYS <br>그러다 보면 내가 나를 씹네 <br>아직 철판은 잘 못 까는 삼십 대 <br>YEAH <br>수많은 문제들이 <br>나를 둘러싸지만 <br>RAP AIN'T ONE OF'EM <br>한해와 같이 했던 게 <br>몇 번쯤 되더라 대충 서너 번 <br>HE EVOLVED <br>I EVOLVED <br>THROUGH THE YEARS <br>SO DON'T WE ALL <br>DESERVE A TROPHY <br>아니 난 빼도 되는데 <br>한해는 충분한 자격 <br>가졌잖아 DON'T HE <br>I GOT ENOUGH TROPHIES <br>성배 속의 독이 <br>이젠 두렵네 <br>I DON'T HAVE MY EYES <br>ON THE PRIZE <br>알 거야 <br>IF YOU KNOW ME <br>I GOT ENOUGH TROPHIES <br>이젠 이걸 다 보관할 곳이 <br>모자랄 정도니 <br>하나 둘 버릴 때 <br>SLOWLY BUT SURELY <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>내가 먼저 제안했지 <br>HENNEY한테 <br>잘하는데 기회가 <br>오지 않잖아 <br>IT'S TIME TO GET MOFUCKIN TROPHY <br>Aye 내가 데려가겠냐고 <br>내리막길 <br>그건 여기저기 붙었다 <br>떨어지는 새끼들에게 <br>난 거기 없지 <br>난 착하지만 착한 척은 <br>안 해서 <br>I FEEL LONELY <br>래퍼들이 많은 자리 <br>FUCKIN 진저리 <br>때문에 나를 아는 <br>사람들은 피곤이 <br>쌓이지만 <br>DON'T TRY TO <br>PULL THAT SHIT ON ME <br>존경했던 래퍼들은 <br>전부 뒤졌지 <br>상을 뺏어야 돼 <br>걔네 들은 진작에 <br>아니 걔네 들 건 <br>너무 많이 빛 바랬어 <br>진짜로 진태형 빼고는 <br>나는 의아해 <br>나보고 못한단 쟨 관둬야 돼 <br>감 없는데 마음마저 <br>급한 너네 정신 차려야 돼 <br>다 낡아 빠졌어 나한테 <br>맡겨줘 쟤네 씨 말려야 돼 <br>씨를 말려야 돼 앞길 <br>막어야 돼 정신 차려야 돼 <br>정신 차려야 돼 너넨 <br>알어야 돼 우릴 빨어야 돼 <br>우린 빨려야 해 <br>HENNEY 상 줘야 돼 <br>CASHVILLE 상 줘야 돼 <br>이건 팔려야 돼 <br>아니 받아야 돼 <br>상을 상을 <br>브랜뉴에서 이거 누가 해 <br>누가 해 <br>다시 한번 물을게 <br>브랜뉴에서 이걸 누가 해 <br>누가 해 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>난 정말 상을 받아야 돼 <br>]]></content><category term="한해" label="한해"/><category term="상을 받아야 돼 (Feat. 버벌진트)" label="상을 받아야 돼 (Feat. 버벌진트)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/한해/LIPSTICK_ON_MY_여기저기/</id><title>한해 - LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-13T20:34:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-13T20:34:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%95%9C%ED%95%B4/LIPSTICK_ON_MY_%EC%97%AC%EA%B8%B0%EC%A0%80%EA%B8%B0/" title="한해 - LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[알잖아 LIPSTICK이 내 몸에 <br>잔뜩 묻었네 얘넨 나를 원해 <br>난 서둘러서 얘네들을 보내 <br>GOD DAMN <br>내 여자친구 친구 친구들 때문에 <br>OH FUCKIN’ <br>LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>왜 내 번호 물어봐 <br>미안 못 알려주겠어 <br>조금 있으면 <br>다른 애들이 또 와 <br>술 맛있게 먹었으면 안녕 <br>마중은 지금 못 나가겠어 <br>조심히 들어가 이제 <br>그만 떼써 <br>애초에 너랑 잘 생각은 <br>안 했어 <br>니가 나라면 너랑 <br>하루를 보내겠어 <br>지금 다른 여자애들이 <br>넘어 온 댔어 <br>시간은 너무나 빨리 가네 <br>몇 배속 <br>립스틱이 묻어 <br>새로 산 옷에도 <br>술과 범벅이 되어 <br>내일 걱정이 되어 <br>망설일 거라면 닥치고 <br>빨리 GO TO HELL YO <br>내 삶은 내 마음대로 <br>어지러운 가운데도 <br>또 한 명이 눈에 보이네 <br>진짜 안될 놈인가 봐 내도 <br>내 ADRENALIN <br>폭발 우주를 부수자고 <br>폭파 맞아 오늘이 종말 <br>오늘도 내일이 되면 소중한 <br>알잖아 LIPSTICK이 나의 몸에 <br>잔뜩 묻었네 얘넨 나를 원해 <br>난 서둘러서 얘네들을 보내 <br>GOD DAMN <br>내 여자친구 친구 친구들 때문에 <br>OH FUCKIN’ <br>LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>I DON’T WANNA DIE TOO YOUNG <br>얘넬 봐봐 외치게 돼 오 주여 <br>예쁜 누나들 CALL ME 오빠 <br>또는 불러 <br>HENNEY HONEY HONEY HENNEY <br>나는 립스틱 위에서 수영 <br>YSL부터 CHANEL 알잖아 <br>그게 뭐던 간에 <br>난 상관없지 잘 지워지기만 <br>하면 되지 다 같애 <br>GOD DAMN 못 말려 <br>얘네들은 전부 다 HIGH해 <br>제대로 취했거든 <br>DAMN 여자애들이 <br>한해를 업고 가려 해 <br>한해도 취했거든 <br>CASHVILLE RING RING SHIT <br>PICK UP THE PHONE <br>전화받어 BRO BRO SHIT <br>PICK UP THE PHONE <br>경찰 불러 얘넨 너무 위험해 <br>아니 911이 불을 꺼야 돼 <br>알잖아 LIPSTICK이 나의 몸에 <br>잔뜩 묻었네 얘넨 나를 원해 <br>난 서둘러서 얘네들을 보내 <br>GOD DAMN <br>내 여자친구 친구 친구들 때문에 <br>OH FUCKIN’ <br>LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>OH LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기 <br>]]></content><category term="한해" label="한해"/><category term="LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기" label="LIPSTICK ON MY 여기저기"/></entry></feed>