<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://webmastertool.naver.com"><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/</id><title>lyric</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:56:00+09:00</updated><link href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/"/><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강전한/오늘따라/</id><title>강전한 - 오늘따라 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:45:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:45:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%A0%84%ED%95%9C/%EC%98%A4%EB%8A%98%EB%94%B0%EB%9D%BC/" title="강전한 - 오늘따라 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[가끔 네가 그리울 때마다 <br>보고 싶은 사진을 꺼낼까도 <br>애써 누른 마음이 아려서 <br>못내 꺼내어 본적도 많았어 <br>너의 너의 그 작은 어깨에 <br>기대어 쉬던 그날이 <br>오늘따라 그리워 <br>나의 나의 모자람 채워준 <br>날 위해줬던 네 마음 <br>덕에 내가 여기서 있어 <br>고마워 고마워 <br>나는 아직 갈 길을 모르고 <br>머무르지 못하는 내 마음은 <br>너를 떠오르게 했던 많은 <br>순간순간이 파고들 뿐이야 <br>너의 너의 그 작은 손끝에 <br>맺혀있던 그 온기가 <br>오늘따라 그리워 <br>나의 나의 마음에 녹여준 <br>날 보고 웃던 네 얼굴 생각하면 <br>가끔 웃다가 눈물 나 <br>언젠가 바래진 마음에 <br>다시 꽃이 피겠지 <br>유난히 오늘따라 지지 않는 너 <br>너의 너의 그 작은 어깨에 <br>기대어 쉬던 그날이 <br>오늘따라 그리워 <br>우리 우리 잊혀진 날들과 <br>다 바래져 남은 맘에 <br>지지 않는 너를 새길게 영원히 <br>]]></content><category term="강전한" label="강전한"/><category term="오늘따라" label="오늘따라"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강전한/우연이라도_Feat_윤딴딴/</id><title>강전한 - 우연이라도 (Feat. 윤딴딴) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:45:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:45:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%A0%84%ED%95%9C/%EC%9A%B0%EC%97%B0%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC%EB%8F%84_Feat_%EC%9C%A4%EB%94%B4%EB%94%B4/" title="강전한 - 우연이라도 (Feat. 윤딴딴) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우연이라도 마주치게 된다면 <br>그댄 그냥 날 무시하고 가세요 <br>우연이라도 혹시라도 날 보면 <br>못 본 사람인 척 <br>지나치기를 바래요 <br>단 한 순간에도 난 그댈 <br>잊어보려 한 적이 없었지만 <br>이제 그댈 잊어야 잊어야 한다면 <br>마치 우연이라도 난 <br>우연이라도 보고 싶을 거예요 <br>잊지 말기로 했던 나의 그대 <br>단 한 순간에도 난 그댈 <br>잊어보려 한 적이 없었지만 <br>이제 그댈 잊어야 잊어야 한다면 <br>마치 우연이라도 난 <br>혹시 내 안에 아직 그대가 있다면 <br>아직도 잊지 못한 내 미련이라면 <br>다시 그댈 만나고 만나고 싶다고 <br>마치 우연이라도 난 <br>우연이라도 보고 싶을 거예요 <br>한때 사랑했었던 나의 그대 <br>]]></content><category term="강전한" label="강전한"/><category term="우연이라도 (Feat. 윤딴딴)" label="우연이라도 (Feat. 윤딴딴)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강전한/그대여/</id><title>강전한 - 그대여 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:45:52+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:45:52+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%A0%84%ED%95%9C/%EA%B7%B8%EB%8C%80%EC%97%AC/" title="강전한 - 그대여 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대여 나를 잊지는 말아요 <br>우리는 이렇게 헤어지지만 <br>나는 몰랐죠 흘러가는 말에 <br>그대 마음 한구석에 <br>있는 외로움을 <br>잘해주겠다던 그 약속들 <br>지키지 못해 미안해요 <br>사랑이란 게 다 그런 거라고 <br>익숙해졌다고 말했던 지난날 <br>사실 나 많이 후회해요 <br>그대여 나를 잊지는 말아요 <br>우리는 이렇게 헤어지지만 <br>우리가 사랑했었던 만큼만 <br>행복했던 그 순간만큼 <br>내가 보고 싶을 그 순간만큼만 <br>잊지 말아요 그대 <br>처음만 생각하자 <br>알고도 변해가는 <br>우리 모습을 바라만 봤죠 <br>지킬 수 있었던 그 시간들 <br>지키지 못해 미안해요 <br>사랑했었던 마음이야 남아 <br>그리워하지만 돌아선 그대는 <br>손에 닿지 않는 별 같아 <br>그대여 나를 잊지는 말아요 <br>우리는 이렇게 헤어지지만 <br>우리가 사랑했었던 만큼만 <br>행복했던 그 순간만큼 <br>내가 보고 싶을 그 순간만큼만 <br>그대여 나를 잊으면 안 돼요 <br>한 번만 나를 더 바라봐 줘요 <br>잊혀질 사랑이란 거 알지만 <br>행복했던 그 순간만큼 <br>이 노랠 듣고 있을 그 순간만큼만 <br>잊지 말아요 그대 <br>잊지 말아요 그대 <br>]]></content><category term="강전한" label="강전한"/><category term="그대여" label="그대여"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강전한/그날_새벽/</id><title>강전한 - 그날 새벽 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:45:55+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:45:55+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%A0%84%ED%95%9C/%EA%B7%B8%EB%82%A0_%EC%83%88%EB%B2%BD/" title="강전한 - 그날 새벽 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[우연히 네게 닿았던 <br>나의 연락이 불편하니 <br>힘들잖아 많이 아팠잖아 <br>사실 우연은 아니야 <br>있잖아 너 없이 지낸 <br>짧고도 길었던 그 시간이 <br>내 마음을 어떻게 바꿨는지 <br>또 네 맘을 어떻게 헤아릴지 <br>정말 많이 생각했어 <br>네 생각에 <br>잠 못 이루고 지샌 밤 <br>자꾸 뒤척이며 너를 찾고 있는 <br>이런 작은 모습도 보이지만 <br>미소 대신 자리한 걱정 어린 <br>네 얼굴이 보이잖아 <br>언젠가 우리 나눴던 <br>평생을 함께 하자는 말들 <br>참 예뻤던 너무 아름다웠던 <br>또 그리워 많이 울어버렸던 <br>너도 나처럼 지내니 <br>그때 우리 아무 말도 못했었고 <br>고요함 속에 눈물만 흐르던 난 <br>너의 우는 모습도 <br>보고 싶어 내 품에 안겨있었던 <br>이제 다른 사람 곁에 웃고 있는 <br>네 모습 보면서 잊어볼게 <br>다시 만날 수 있다는 희망을 <br>그 마음을 <br>예전처럼 돌아갈 수 있다는 <br>그 믿음을 <br>잊어볼게 <br>]]></content><category term="강전한" label="강전한"/><category term="그날 새벽" label="그날 새벽"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강전한/널_만나러_가는_길_Feat_PDAY/</id><title>강전한 - 널 만나러 가는 길 (Feat. PDAY) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:45:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:45:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%A0%84%ED%95%9C/%EB%84%90_%EB%A7%8C%EB%82%98%EB%9F%AC_%EA%B0%80%EB%8A%94_%EA%B8%B8_Feat_PDAY/" title="강전한 - 널 만나러 가는 길 (Feat. PDAY) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[아무런 말도 필요 없지 <br>처음 널 봤던 순간부터 <br>따스한 마음으로 내게 <br>웃어준 너에게 <br>언제였는지 설레었던 게 <br>가끔은 정말 무섭기도 했지 <br>어느새 나는 너라는 <br>설렘을 안고 <br>널 만나러 가는 길 <br>사랑한단 말이 아니어도 <br>난 괜찮아 <br>억지로 기분 맞춰 주지 <br>않아도 좋아 <br>좋아하니까 난 좋아하니까 <br>네가 내게 웃어준다면 <br>언제든 내가 필요할 땐 <br>네 옆을 지킬게 <br>그게 사랑이 아니라도 <br>나는 괜찮아 <br>사랑하니까 난 널 사랑하니까 <br>조금만 더 알아준다면 <br>난 괜찮아 <br>조금 어색할 것 같아 <br>아니 내가 조심스러운 걸까 <br>만나러 가는 길 다짐해 <br>너와의 오늘을 <br>욕심인 걸까 이런 내 맘이 <br>어쩌면 바라고 있을지 몰라 <br>저 멀리 네가 날 보며 <br>환하게 웃네 <br>난 그냥 네가 좋아 <br>사랑한단 말이 아니어도 <br>난 괜찮아 <br>억지로 기분 맞춰 주지 <br>않아도 좋아 <br>좋아하니까 난 좋아하니까 <br>네가 내게 웃어준다면 <br>언제든 내가 필요할 땐 <br>네 옆에 지킬게 <br>그게 사랑이 아니라도 <br>나는 괜찮아 <br>사랑하니까 난 널 사랑하니까 <br>조금만 더 알아준다면 <br>난 괜찮아 <br>마음 가는 대로 했을 뿐 <br>난 원하지 않아 <br>우리 시간을 어설픈 <br>밀고 당김 따위로 <br>낭비하기는 싫어 <br>다만 아직 준비가 <br>안 됐다면 나 역시도 <br>천천히 갈게 <br>네게 가는 길은 <br>이미 잘 알고 있어 <br>그래 넌 지켜주기만 하면 돼 <br>내가 채울 <br>너의 옆자리 말야 bae <br>사랑한단 말이 아니어도 <br>난 괜찮아 <br>억지로 기분 맞춰 주지 <br>않아도 좋아 <br>좋아하니까 난 좋아하니까 <br>네가 내게 웃어준다면 <br>언제든 내가 필요할 땐 <br>네 옆을 지킬게 <br>그게 사랑이 아니라도 <br>나는 괜찮아 <br>사랑하니까 난 널 사랑하니까 <br>조금만 더 알아준다면 <br>난 괜찮아 <br>]]></content><category term="강전한" label="강전한"/><category term="널 만나러 가는 길 (Feat. PDAY)" label="널 만나러 가는 길 (Feat. PDAY)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강전한/너는_없다_New_Ver/</id><title>강전한 - 너는 없다 (New Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:45:59+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:45:59+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%A0%84%ED%95%9C/%EB%84%88%EB%8A%94_%EC%97%86%EB%8B%A4_New_Ver/" title="강전한 - 너는 없다 (New Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지하철을 기다리다 있던 <br>그 자리를 뒤돌아 본다 <br>밥을 먹고 일어나서 두고 <br>온건 없나 뒤돌아 본다 <br>매일 매일 니가 있던 자리도 <br>지하철을 타도 밥을 먹어도 <br>너는 없다 <br>난 잃어 버린 게 없는데 <br>너는 없다 <br>아무리 돌아봐도 그 자리에 <br>너는 없다 <br>난 잃어 버린 게 없는데 <br>너는 없다 <br>아무리 돌아봐도 그 자리에 <br>너는 없다 <br>난 돌이킬 수가 없는데 <br>너는 없다 너는 없다 너는 없다 <br>사람들이 많이 앉아 있던 <br>그 벤치를 뒤돌아본다 <br>길을 걷다 같이 듣곤 했던 <br>그 노래가 흘러 나온다 <br>매일매일 니가 있던 자리도 <br>길을 걷다 벤치에 걸터앉아도 <br>너는 없다 <br>난 잃어버린 게 없는데 <br>너는 없다 <br>아무리 돌아봐도 그 자리에 <br>너는 없다 <br>난 돌이킬 수가 없는데 <br>너는 없다 너는 없다 너는 없다 <br>너는 없다 <br>난 잃어버린 게 없는데 <br>너는 없다 <br>아무리 돌아봐도 그 자리에 <br>너는 없다 <br>난 돌이킬 수가 없는데 <br>너는 없다 너는 없다 너는 없다 <br>]]></content><category term="강전한" label="강전한"/><category term="너는 없다 (New Ver.)" label="너는 없다 (New Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/강전한/midnight/</id><title>강전한 - midnight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:46:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:46:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B0%95%EC%A0%84%ED%95%9C/midnight/" title="강전한 - midnight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[하루가 지나가는 시간 <br>왠지 모르게 우울해져 <br>괜한 생각에 잠겨있던 나 <br>카페에 앉아 <br>폰만 바라보고 있다가 <br>무심코 고갤 들면 <br>나도 모르게 생각이 나 <br>우리 얘기를 쓰고 있더라 <br>이 밤이 지나갈 때쯤이면 <br>너도 듣고 있겠지 <br>조금은 날 보겠지 <br>모든 게 우리 사랑 얘긴 걸 <br>너와 나눈 추억들 <br>사랑이 가득했던 네 모습 <br>made at midnight <br>made at midnight <br>어느새 추워지던 날씨 <br>집에만 있는 내가 싫어 <br>어디론가 향하는 발걸음 <br>아무도 없는 곳에서 <br>흥얼거리다가 <br>자연스레 나오던 <br>너의 얘기들 우리 멜로디 <br>어느새 내가 부르고 있어 <br>이 밤이 지나갈 때쯤이면 <br>너도 듣고 있겠지 <br>조금은 날 보겠지 <br>모든 게 우리 사랑 얘긴 걸 <br>너와 나눈 추억들 <br>사랑이 가득했던 네 모습 <br>어디서 듣고 있니 <br>가끔 보고 싶지만 <br>이렇게라도 내 마음 전할게 <br>우리 사랑 얘긴 걸 <br>너와 나눈 추억들 <br>사랑이 가득했던 네 모습 <br>made at midnight <br>made at midnight <br>]]></content><category term="강전한" label="강전한"/><category term="midnight" label="midnight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임수정/달빛사랑_MR/</id><title>임수정 - 달빛사랑 (MR) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:46:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:46:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%88%98%EC%A0%95/%EB%8B%AC%EB%B9%9B%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91_MR/" title="임수정 - 달빛사랑 (MR) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 처음 본 순간 <br>내 가슴은 몹시 뛰었지 <br>어쩐지 내사랑 일것같은 <br>행복한 예감이 들었소 <br>해맑은 그대 모습은 <br>어느덧 사랑이 되어 <br>이제는 하루만 못보아도 <br>견딜수 없게 되었네 <br>아 사랑은 이렇게 <br>말없이 찾아와서 <br>이토록 그대 생각에 <br>잠 못들게 하는가 <br>그대여 내게 와주오 <br>달빛 고요한 이밤에 <br>살며시 나에게 찾아와서 <br>내 마음 달래어 주오 <br>아 사랑은 이렇게 <br>말없이 찾아와서 <br>이토록 그대 생각에 <br>잠 못들게 하는가 <br>그대여 내게 와주오 <br>달빛 고요한 이밤에 <br>살며시 나에게 찾아와서 <br>내 마음 달래어 주오 <br>살며시 나에게 찾아와서 <br>내 마음 달래어 주오 <br>내 마음 달래어 주오]]></content><category term="임수정" label="임수정"/><category term="달빛사랑 (MR)" label="달빛사랑 (MR)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/임수정/달빛사랑/</id><title>임수정 - 달빛사랑 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:46:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:46:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%9E%84%EC%88%98%EC%A0%95/%EB%8B%AC%EB%B9%9B%EC%82%AC%EB%9E%91/" title="임수정 - 달빛사랑 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[그대를 처음 본 순간 <br>내 가슴은 몹시 뛰었지 <br>어쩐지 내사랑 일것같은 <br>행복한 예감이 들었소 <br>해맑은 그대 모습은 <br>어느덧 사랑이 되어 <br>이제는 하루만 못보아도 <br>견딜수 없게 되었네 <br>아 사랑은 이렇게 <br>말없이 찾아와서 <br>이토록 그대 생각에 <br>잠 못들게 하는가 <br>그대여 내게 와주오 <br>달빛 고요한 이밤에 <br>살며시 나에게 찾아와서 <br>내 마음 달래어 주오 <br>아 사랑은 이렇게 <br>말없이 찾아와서 <br>이토록 그대 생각에 <br>잠 못들게 하는가 <br>그대여 내게 와주오 <br>달빛 고요한 이밤에 <br>살며시 나에게 찾아와서 <br>내 마음 달래어 주오 <br>살며시 나에게 찾아와서 <br>내 마음 달래어 주오 <br>내 마음 달래어 주오 <br>]]></content><category term="임수정" label="임수정"/><category term="달빛사랑" label="달빛사랑"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soundfish/Foreigner_Again_Feat_Stacey_Sang/</id><title>Soundfish - Foreigner Again (Feat. Stacey Sang) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:46:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:46:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Soundfish/Foreigner_Again_Feat_Stacey_Sang/" title="Soundfish - Foreigner Again (Feat. Stacey Sang) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The girl from outer space <br>pulled me quietly <br>She came to me in a star <br>from the dark skies <br>It was the first time <br>I ever saw her <br>In my last <br>and only memory of her <br>she was to leave the earth <br>I could't imagine a life <br>without her <br>I truely didn't want her to leave <br>So I just stood there <br>Staring at her <br>with my teary black eyes <br>with my teary black eyes <br>She left me her score <br>of a classical piece <br>and short words <br>that she'd be back by 9:30 <br>But she didn't come back to me <br>One year later <br>I arranged her classical piece <br>for a astare <br>at the dark sky <br>in a black suit <br>with a glass of wine <br>in my hand <br>with a glass of wine <br>in my hand <br>]]></content><category term="Soundfish" label="Soundfish"/><category term="Foreigner Again (Feat. Stacey Sang)" label="Foreigner Again (Feat. Stacey Sang)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오로라스팅/Woo_City_AMer9_Ver/</id><title>오로라스팅 - Woo City (AMer9 Ver.) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:46:57+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:46:57+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EB%A1%9C%EB%9D%BC%EC%8A%A4%ED%8C%85/Woo_City_AMer9_Ver/" title="오로라스팅 - Woo City (AMer9 Ver.) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[언젠간 모든 게 <br>사라진다 나 들었죠 <br>아프지 말라던 <br>내 사람들은 어디로 갔죠 <br>Don’t laugh me <br>그때도 지금도 난 같은 맘 <br>and I can say <br>어떤 말도 하지 마요 <br>어제도 오늘도 내일도 <br>난 여전히 그대로 <br>대단하게 말고 <br>천천히 걸어가고 있는데 <br>Don’t laugh me <br>그때와 지금의 나 달라졌나요 <br>and I can say <br>어떤 말도 필요 없어 <br>we will run for the better side <br>or we could go to the brightest side <br>but we will break on through <br>to the other-side <br>Yeah Break on through <br>to the other-side <br>I could make u smile dear <br>I will run for our right direction <br>I will keep on ma smiling <br>Woo <br>언젠간 모든 게 <br>사라진다 나 들었죠 <br>아프지 말라던 <br>내 사람들은 어디로 갔죠 <br>Don’t laugh me <br>]]></content><category term="오로라스팅" label="오로라스팅"/><category term="Woo City (AMer9 Ver.)" label="Woo City (AMer9 Ver.)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2ski/마지막이라면_너를_불러본다/</id><title>2ski - 마지막이라면 너를 불러본다 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:47:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:47:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/2ski/%EB%A7%88%EC%A7%80%EB%A7%89%EC%9D%B4%EB%9D%BC%EB%A9%B4_%EB%84%88%EB%A5%BC_%EB%B6%88%EB%9F%AC%EB%B3%B8%EB%8B%A4/" title="2ski - 마지막이라면 너를 불러본다 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[예전의 추억을 <br>떠올리며 <br>좋았던 그때를 <br>생각하며 <br>저 멀리 따뜻한 <br>네 마음이 <br>지나쳐 버려진 <br>시간들이 <br>붓으로 그렸던 <br>너의 마음 <br>마음으로 떠올렸던 <br>너의 모습 <br>펼쳐진 하얀 종이 위에 <br>이렇게 널 그려본다 <br>어느샌가 찾아왔던 <br>너의 자리 <br>흩날릴까 부여잡은 <br>너의 손목이 <br>연기처럼 하얗게 <br>사라질지 <br>구름처럼 닿을 수 <br>없게 멀어질지 <br>모든 게 아름답게 <br>느껴짐에 <br>우리가 사랑이라 <br>속삭일까 <br>지금 이 순간이 <br>마지막이라면 <br>미소 지어 네 이름을 <br>불러본다 <br>눈앞의 얼굴이 보여 <br>그때의 모습이 흐려지며 <br>내 마음의 상처가 <br>더 하얗게 피어온다 <br>눈부시게 사랑했던 <br>그 때 우리 <br>따스하게 감싸주던 <br>너의 손길이 <br>연기처럼 하얗게 <br>사라질지 <br>구름처럼 닿을 수 <br>없게 멀어질지 <br>모든 게 아름답게 <br>펼쳐질 때 <br>우리가 사랑이라 <br>느껴질까 <br>지금 이 순간이 <br>마지막이라면 <br>다시 한번 네 이름을 <br>불러본다 <br>]]></content><category term="2ski" label="2ski"/><category term="마지막이라면 너를 불러본다" label="마지막이라면 너를 불러본다"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/수뜨_Sudd/Like_A_Dream/</id><title>수뜨 (Sudd) - Like A Dream - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:47:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:47:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%88%98%EB%9C%A8_Sudd/Like_A_Dream/" title="수뜨 (Sudd) - Like A Dream - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[fly ye <br>fly like <br>fly like a dream like oh <br>fly like <br>fly like a dream like ye <br>]]></content><category term="수뜨 (Sudd)" label="수뜨 (Sudd)"/><category term="Like A Dream" label="Like A Dream"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/수뜨_Sudd/Kingsford_Feat_Clasick/</id><title>수뜨 (Sudd) - Kingsford (Feat. Clasick) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:47:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:47:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%88%98%EB%9C%A8_Sudd/Kingsford_Feat_Clasick/" title="수뜨 (Sudd) - Kingsford (Feat. Clasick) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Kingsford <br>the town i used to be <br>there for a while <br>Kingsford <br>날 거기로 데리고 가 <br>Kingsford <br>the town i used to be <br>there for a while <br>Kingsford <br>날 거기로 데리고 가 <br>세 평 남짓 방 <br>여긴 내 작은 섬 <br>느껴져 아주 어렴풋 <br>It's calm before the storm <br>비행기는 <br>요즘 내겐 가능성 <br>희박한 기행일뿐 <br>진해지는 <br>그리움에 비례해 <br>커지는 현실의 문 <br>No sky is the limit <br>아니 everyday was my limit <br>아무 준비없이 <br>고비 맞닥뜨려 <br>완전히 풀어진 고삐 <br>My soul gettin' ugly <br>공부나 할 줄 알았지 <br>여기 오니 혼자서 a to z <br>쉬운 건 절대 없네 열까지 <br>My home flies iPhone died <br>총체적 난국 한 두어달 <br>Rest in peace my laptop <br>Sein and jaine my colleagues <br>O-week passed so 빨리 <br>심심해 다 모여 끼리끼리 <br>밥 나눠먹어 <br>chitty chatty <br>Roomy alex flea market <br>Mongoose 잘 굴러가네 <br>당시 나의 best rollies <br>영어 못해 exchange student <br>빅맥 하나 못시키는 <br>감당 안돼 뒷사람 눈 <br>벙어리 says just no 2 <br>Kingsford <br>the town i used to be <br>there for a while <br>Kingsford <br>날 거기로 데리고 가 <br>Kingsford <br>the town i used to be <br>there for a while <br>Kingsford <br>날 거기로 데리고 가 <br>한국음식 내 soul food <br>끓여먹기 어려워 된장국 <br>집 앞 식당에 flipflop <br>20 bucks 내 집밥 <br>Bus 안에선 차별 shit <br>싫어 Aussie White Policy <br>일어나 자릴 옮기지 <br>다시 한번 느껴 난 이방인 <br>날 감싸보려 아는 척 <br>자존심 세워 don't give a f <br>잘 나가는 척 가당치 않어 <br>내가 입은 후딘 싸구려 <br>변함없는 routine <br>더러워 늘 kitchen <br>Roommate 대부분 Chinese <br>just gave up on hygeine <br>뻑적지근한 파티에 비해 <br>내 텐션은 미지근해 <br>놀아보지 못한 Asian shit <br>감출 수 없는 풋내 <br>잘 지내는 척 Facebook <br>삶이 구려도 act cool <br>다들 외로워도 티내기 싫어 <br>오히려 허세를 떨구 <br>수업은 태반이 졸려 <br>날 본체 만체해 tutor <br>but Kosta 애들은 정이 많아서 <br>늦깍이도 잘 챙겨 <br>일식집 알바 주방 형 <br>Chinese cigarette 말아펴 <br>깨먹은 그릇 다 내 꺼 <br>내 하루처럼 늘 뒷전 <br>Kingsford <br>the town i used to be <br>there for a while <br>Kingsford <br>날 거기로 데리고 가 <br>Kingsford <br>the town i used to be <br>there for a while <br>Kingsford <br>날 거기로 데리고 가 <br>우리 교회 전도사님 <br>밤엔 병원 청소하지 <br>그래도 항상 날 재워줘 <br>every Sunday 행복했지 <br>예배보다 식사가 설레 <br>저녁엔 AMF bowling <br>첨이자 마지막 bday party <br>좁은 집에 한 40 명 <br>축하해줘서 고마웠지 <br>좋은 기분이 날 감쌌지 <br>Whitehouse 냄새 그리워 <br>Jordan은 날 잘 챙겨줘 <br>방금 튀긴 fries dippin' <br>Coke sippin' <br>camper trip on recess <br>그 때 친구들 잘 지내 <br>가고 싶어 Bondi beach <br>걷고 싶어져 매일 <br>죽이는 파도 앞에서도 <br>맥주병은 못해 surfin' <br>가까워 좋았던 Coogee <br>산책로 가득해 풀잎 <br>돌아가고파 빨리 <br>just wanna tape back <br>my vibe <br>just wanna get <br>my life <br>웃고 싶어 난 당장 <br>서울에 적응 중 all day <br>아직도 영어를 잘 못해 <br>그래도 수고 참 많이 했어 <br>좋은 앞날을 약속해 <br>곧 여행을 떠나게 될테니까 <br>여권을 준비해 <br>Kingsford <br>the town i used to be <br>there for a while <br>Kingsford <br>날 거기로 데리고 가 <br>Kingsford <br>the town i used to be <br>there for a while <br>Kingsford <br>날 거기로 데리고 가 <br>]]></content><category term="수뜨 (Sudd)" label="수뜨 (Sudd)"/><category term="Kingsford (Feat. Clasick)" label="Kingsford (Feat. Clasick)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/수뜨_Sudd/Everything_Goes_Feat_Clasick/</id><title>수뜨 (Sudd) - Everything Goes (Feat. Clasick) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:47:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:47:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%88%98%EB%9C%A8_Sudd/Everything_Goes_Feat_Clasick/" title="수뜨 (Sudd) - Everything Goes (Feat. Clasick) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>like this <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>like <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>like this <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>like <br>내가 바래왔던 <br>good life yea <br>괴리감은 커져 불만에 <br>사로잡힌 나의 지난날 <br>그래 뒤를 보기 싫어 난 <br>수많은 선택의 길이 <br>나를 괴롭혀 <br>내 어머닌 꿈의 <br>잠꼬대를 들었어 <br>다음날 말해 아들 <br>많이 힘들어 아뇨 <br>하지만 연기가 안돼 <br>내 표정 <br>그래 난 멈춰있어 <br>어디도 향하지 않고 <br>백 한 갈래 앞에 stop <br>청춘 내 봄의 색깔 <br>너무 흐릿해 <br>안경 없인 전혀 <br>선명하지 않어 <br>이랬던 친구는 <br>저렇게 한 뼘 <br>저랬던 친구는 <br>또 이렇게 완전 <br>변했지만 내 말투는 여전 <br>다들 변해가는걸 <br>지켜보며 난 벙쪄 <br>언제든 날 돕겠다던 동생놈은 <br>이제 자기 한몸 추스르기 바쁘고 <br>앞에서 날 멋지다고 칭찬하던 <br>선배 하난 몰래 뒷얘기를 흘리고 <br>그래 한국 아래 영원한건 없어 <br>약속과 우정의 무게 참 가벼워 <br>이렇게 말하고 있는 나도 없어 <br>어디선가 비난과 <br>비참을 주워잡숴 <br>그래도 뭐 어쩌겠어 <br>하루는 가는데 <br>걷는거야 사람 삶 지나가는데 <br>같은 방향 아니라도 나의 인생 <br>결국 열린 결말을 향해 다르게 <br>비슷하단 말이 제일 듣기 싫어 <br>지금 이대로의 나인게 제일 멋져 <br>구름 심장 안에 집어넣고 <br>날고 싶어 <br>영원히 시선은 두발보다 <br>하늘 품 안 <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>like this <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>like <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>like this <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>it's life <br>난 강남역의 냄새가 싫어 <br>분주한 삶 또 만들어진 미녀 <br>풍기는 인위적인 냄새가 비려 <br>스치는 걸음걸인 이상하게 빨라 <br>그 템포에 발걸음 꼬여서 <br>홀린듯이 어디론가 <br>가다보면 새벽 네 시 <br>갑자기 느끼는 허무한 감정 <br>그건 마치 절벽 동굴속 <br>처럼 길이 없어 <br>우리 삶 마치 2호선 <br>밀리고 찍히고 찢겨 <br>웃음마저 도려가 <br>매일 순환선 <br>어디론가 갈아타고 싶어도 <br>늘 다시 오는 출발점 <br>내 걸음처럼 삶도 많이 절어 <br>지키지도 못할 헛마음만 <br>많이 먹어 <br>그래도 많이 먹다보니 소화됐어 <br>꿈을 담을 위대한 팔이 생겼어 <br>당연한게 당연한게 <br>아니었음 좋겠어 <br>세상 일이란게 다 그런게 <br>아니었음 좋겠어 <br>동의받으면서 사는 삶 허망해 <br>결정의 모든 순간 <br>자신에게 허락해 <br>빠르지 않아도 <br>스스로 선택해 <br>겁쟁이로 사는 삶 너나 해 <br>억지로 우겨넣은 suit 안멋있네 <br>내가 선택한 이 옷이 <br>더욱 빛날 때 <br>알아주는 사람에게 속을 보여 <br>내 주머니를 노리고 <br>뎀비면 속보여 <br>내가 내 믿음을 강요하지 않듯 <br>너도 니 믿음 내게 강요않길 바래 <br>목표 진짜로 살고 말하는 것 <br>애써 지어낸 박제웃음 멈추는 것 <br>제발 비아냥대지마 <br>세상 다 산 것 처럼 <br>소중히 널 아껴 평생 쓸 것처럼 <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>like this <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>like <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>like this <br>everything goes <br>everything goes everything goes <br>it's LIFE <br>]]></content><category term="수뜨 (Sudd)" label="수뜨 (Sudd)"/><category term="Everything Goes (Feat. Clasick)" label="Everything Goes (Feat. Clasick)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/탐라/모두_거짓말/</id><title>탐라 - 모두 거짓말 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:47:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:47:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%90%EB%9D%BC/%EB%AA%A8%EB%91%90_%EA%B1%B0%EC%A7%93%EB%A7%90/" title="탐라 - 모두 거짓말 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[모두 거짓말 <br>내가 울잖아 <br>또렷한 내 맘이 <br>전해지도록 <br>조금만 더 버텨줘요 <br>누가 좀 말려줘요 <br>날 떠나지 않게 <br>함께했잖아 <br>견뎌왔잖아 <br>기다렸잖아 <br>그대 정말 날 떠나나요 <br>그대가 없는 난 <br>눈물이 나네요 <br>이젠 끝인가봐 <br>날 안아주던 그대가 <br>자꾸 멀어지네요 <br>Don’t Know Why <br>Why Why Why Why <br>언제부턴지 모르게 <br>Because You <br>You You You You <br>한없이 그댈 바라봤죠 <br>End now Bye <br>Bye Bye Bye Bye <br>이젠 날 떠나가지만 <br>I Say Why <br>Why Why Why Why <br>그대가 돌아서고 <br>다시 난 울고불고 <br>그댈 찾아요 <br>Because of You <br>가슴 한 편이 <br>조금씩 아려와 <br>서투른 이별에 <br>울지 않도록 <br>조금만 더 안아줘요 <br>그대 와 줄까요 <br>가슴이 뛴다면 <br>이젠 아닌가봐 <br>날 감싸주던 그대를 <br>애써 밀어내봐요 <br>Don’t Know Why <br>Why Why Why Why <br>언제부턴지 모르게 <br>Because You <br>You You You You <br>한없이 그댈 바라봤죠 <br>End now Bye <br>Bye Bye Bye Bye <br>이젠 날 떠나가지만 <br>I Say Why <br>Why Why Why Why <br>그대가 돌아서고 <br>다시 난 울고불고 <br>그댈 찾아요 <br>Because of You <br>잊어도 될까요 <br>이렇게 그대를 <br>놓아도 될까요 미안해요 <br>Don’t Know Why <br>Why Why Why Why <br>언제부턴지 모르게 <br>Because You <br>You You You You <br>한없이 그댈 바라봤죠 <br>End now Bye <br>Bye Bye Bye Bey <br>이젠 날 떠나가지만 <br>I Say Why <br>Why Why Why Why <br>그대가 돌아서고 <br>다시 난 바보처럼 <br>그댈 찾아요 <br>Because of you <br>]]></content><category term="탐라" label="탐라"/><category term="모두 거짓말" label="모두 거짓말"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/오유준/부탁이_있어요/</id><title>오유준 - 부탁이 있어요 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:47:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:47:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%98%A4%EC%9C%A0%EC%A4%80/%EB%B6%80%ED%83%81%EC%9D%B4_%EC%9E%88%EC%96%B4%EC%9A%94/" title="오유준 - 부탁이 있어요 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지금쯤 말해보면 <br>혹시나 전해질까 <br>다시 돌아와달라는 말은 <br>하지 않을게요 <br>난 마지막으로 부탁이 있어요 <br>조금 이상하게 들릴지도 몰라요 <br>밥도 잘 챙겨먹고 <br>아프지 말아줘요 <br>흘려 듣지말구요 <br>부탁이 있어요 <br>나를 지우려고 노력하지 말아요 <br>그럴 리 없겠지만 내 생각난다면 <br>편하게 연락해요 <br>어쩌면 꿈이라고 <br>가끔씩 우겨봐요 <br>말도 안 되는 상상만 하고 <br>이러고 있네요 참 바보 같은 나 <br>부탁이 있어요 <br>조금 이상하게 들릴지도 몰라요 <br>밥도 잘 챙겨먹고 <br>아프지 말아줘요 <br>흘려 듣지말구요 <br>부탁이 있어요 <br>나를 지우려고 노력하지 말아요 <br>그럴 리 없겠지만 내 생각난다면 <br>편하게 연락해요 <br>혹시 술에 취해 전화한다 해도 <br>다그치지 말아요 <br>내가 울고불고 매달린다 해도 <br>참아주세요 <br>널 지우는 방법 중 하나니까 <br>나도 노력해 볼 테니까 <br>나 혼자 아프면 되니까 <br>난 여기 있어요 <br>서로 아파하며 사랑했던 시간들 <br>함께했던 추억만 <br>아름다운 기억만 <br>간직하고 있어요 <br>난 여기 있어요 <br>나를 지우려고 노력하지 말아요 <br>그럴 리 없겠지만 우연히 만나면 <br>웃으며 인사해요 <br>부탁이 있어요 꼭 들어주세요 <br>]]></content><category term="오유준" label="오유준"/><category term="부탁이 있어요" label="부탁이 있어요"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/시나_Sina/Sur_La_Pointe_Du_Coeur_조금씩_다가가/</id><title>시나 (Sina) - Sur La Pointe Du Coeur (조금씩 다가가) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:47:30+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:47:30+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EC%8B%9C%EB%82%98_Sina/Sur_La_Pointe_Du_Coeur_%EC%A1%B0%EA%B8%88%EC%94%A9_%EB%8B%A4%EA%B0%80%EA%B0%80/" title="시나 (Sina) - Sur La Pointe Du Coeur (조금씩 다가가) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Je m'en irai <br>Tout en douceur <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>En secret <br>En mineur <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>Tant qu'a devenir <br>Un souvenir <br>J'aimerais qu'il soit le meilleur <br>Rayon d'mon soleil interieur <br>Dans un tiroir <br>De ta memoire <br>Un peu de clarte de fraicheur <br>Hasard <br>Leger <br>D'un soir <br>Dore <br>Regard <br>Change <br>Je m'en irai <br>Tout en douceur <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>Je te laisserai une fleur <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>Jouer le role <br>Charmant et drole <br>De celle qui eloignait la peur <br>De celle qui donnait des couleurs <br>La resonance <br>D'une innocence <br>Un peu d'eau Claire et de splendeur <br>Presence <br>Nacree <br>Une chance donnee <br>Nuances <br>Cachees <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Oooh Oooh Oooh <br>Sur la pointe du coeur <br>]]></content><category term="시나 (Sina)" label="시나 (Sina)"/><category term="Sur La Pointe Du Coeur (조금씩 다가가)" label="Sur La Pointe Du Coeur (조금씩 다가가)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Found_Glory/Tennessee/</id><title>New Found Glory - Tennessee - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/New_Found_Glory/Tennessee/" title="New Found Glory - Tennessee - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lord I've really been real stressed <br>Down and out, losing ground <br>Although I am black and proud <br>Problems got me pessimistic <br>Brothers and sisters keep messing up <br>Why does it have to be so damn tuff <br>I don't know where I can go <br>To let these ghosts out of my skull <br>My grandmas past, my brothers gone <br>I never at once felt so alone <br>I know you're supposed to be my steering wheel <br>Not just my spare tire home <br>But lord I ask you home <br>To be my guiding force and truth home <br>For some strange reason it had to be home <br>He guided me to Tennessee home <br><br>Take me to another place <br>Take me to another land <br>Make me forget all that hurts me <br>Let me understand your plan <br><br>Lord it's obvious we got a relationship <br>Talking to each other every night and day <br>Although you're superior over me <br>We talk to each other in a friendship way <br>Then outta nowhere you tell me to break <br>Outta the country and into more country <br>Past Dyesburg into Ripley <br>Where the ghost of childhood haunts me <br>Walk the roads my forefathers walked <br>Climbed the trees my forefathers hung from <br>Ask those trees for all their wisdom <br>They tell me my ears are so young home <br>Go back to from whence you came home <br>My family tree my family name home <br>For some strange reason it had to be home <br>He guided me to Tennessee home <br><br>Now I see the importance of history <br>Why people be in the mess that they be <br>Many journeys to freedom made in vain <br>By brothers on the corner playing ghetto games <br>I ask you lord why you enlightened me <br>Without the enlightenment of all my folks <br>He said cuz I set myself on a quest for truth <br>And he was there to quench my thirst <br>But I am still thirsty <br>The lord allowed me to drink some more <br>He said what I am searching for are <br>The answers to all which are in front of me <br>The ultimate truth started to get blurry <br>For some strange reason it had to be <br>It was all a dream about Tennessee]]></content><category term="New Found Glory" label="New Found Glory"/><category term="Tennessee" label="Tennessee"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lorene_Drive/Hey_Ya/</id><title>Lorene Drive - Hey Ya! - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Lorene_Drive/Hey_Ya/" title="Lorene Drive - Hey Ya! - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[1, 2, 3, uh <br><br>My baby don't mess around me <br>'Cause she loves me so <br>And this I know fo sho Uh <br>But does she really wanna <br>'Cause she can't stand to see me walk out the do' <br>Don't try to fight the feeling <br>'Cause the thought alone <br>Is killing me right now Uh <br>Thank God for Mom and Dad <br>For sticking two together <br>'Cause we don't know how <br><br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br><br>You think you've got it <br>Oh, you think you've got it <br>But got it just don't get it <br>Til there's nothing at all Ah <br>We get together <br>Oh, we get together <br>But separate's always better <br>When there's feelings involved Oh <br>If what they say is nothing is forever <br>Then what makes <br>Then what makes <br>Then what makes <br>Then what makes <br>Then what makes What makes What makes <br>Love the exception <br>So why oh, why oh <br>Why oh, why oh, why oh <br>Are we so in denial <br>When we know we're not happy here <br><br>Ya'll don't want to hear me <br>You just want to dance <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br><br>Oh oh <br>Oh oh <br>Don't want to meet your daddy Oh oh <br>Just want you in my Caddy Oh oh Oh oh <br>Don't want to meet your momma Oh oh <br>Just want to make you come a Oh oh <br>I'm Oh oh <br>I'm Oh oh <br>I'm just being honest Oh oh <br>I'm just being honest <br><br>Hey Alright now <br>Alright now, fellas Yeah <br>Now what's cooler than being cool Ice cold <br>I can't hear ya <br>I say what's, what's cooler than being cool Ice cold <br>Alright 15x <br><br>Okay now, ladies Yeah <br>Now we gon' break this thing down in just a few seconds <br>Now don't have me break this thing down for nothin <br>Now I wanna see ya'll on ya'll baddest behavior <br>Lend me some suga <br>I am your neighbor <br>Ah Here we go Uh <br><br>Shake it, sh shake it Oh oh <br>Shake it, sh shake it <br>Shake it, sh shake it <br>Shake it, shake it <br>Sh shake it Oh oh <br>Shake it like a Polaroid picture <br>Shake it, sh shake it Hey ya <br>Shake it, sh shake it <br>Shake it, shake it <br>Shake it, sh shake it Shake it sugar <br>Shake it like a Polaroid picture <br><br>Shake it, sh shake it <br>Shake it, sh shake it <br>Shake it, sh shake it <br>Shake it, shake it <br>Sh shake it <br>Shake it like a Polaroid picture <br>Shake it, sh shake it <br>Shake it, sh shake it <br>Shake it, shake it <br>Shake it, sh shake it <br>Shake it like a Polaroid picture <br><br>Now all Beyonce's and Lucy Liu's and baby dolls <br>Get on the floor <br>Get on the floor <br>You know what to do <br>You know what to do <br>You know what to do <br><br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya <br>Hey Ya Hey Ya]]></content><category term="Lorene Drive" label="Lorene Drive"/><category term="Hey Ya!" label="Hey Ya!"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Rod_Circu/Gin_And_Juice/</id><title>Hot Rod Circu - Gin And Juice - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:27+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:27+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hot_Rod_Circu/Gin_And_Juice/" title="Hot Rod Circu - Gin And Juice - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[With so much drama in the L B C <br>It's kinda hard bein Snoop D O double G <br>But I, somehow, some way <br>Keep comin up with funky ass shit like every single day <br>May I, kick a little something for the G's yeah <br>And, make a few ends as yeah I breeze, through <br>Two in the mornin and the party's still jumpin <br>Cause my momma ain't home <br>I got bitches in the living room gettin it on <br>And, they ain't leavin til six in the mornin six in the mornin <br>So what you wanna do, sheeeit <br>I got a pocket full of rubbers and my homeboys do too <br>So turn off the lights and close the doors <br>But but what we don't love them hoes, yeah <br>So we gonna smoke a ounce to this <br>G's up, hoes down, while you motherfuckers bounce to this <br><br>Rollin down the street, smokin endo, sippin on gin and juice <br>Laid back with my mind on my money and my money on my mind <br><br>Rollin down the street, smokin endo, sippin on gin and juice <br>Laid back with my mind on my money and my money on my mind <br><br>Now, that, I got me some Seagram's gin <br>Everybody got they cups, but they ain't chipped in <br>Now this types of shit, happens all the time <br>You got to get yours but fool I gotta get mine <br>Everything is fine when you listenin to the D O G <br>I got the cultivating music that be captivating he <br>Who listens, to the words that I speak <br>As I take me a drink to the middle of the street <br>And get to mackin to this bitch named Sadie Sadie <br>She used to be the homeboy's lady Oh, that bitch <br>Eighty degrees, when I tell that bitch please <br>Raise up off these N U T's, bitch you gets none of these <br>At ease, as I mob with the Dogg Pound, feel the breeze <br>Beeeitch, I'm just <br><br>Rollin down the street, smokin endo, sippin on gin and juice <br>Laid back with my mind on my money and my money on my mind <br><br>Later on that day <br>My homey Dr Dre came through with a gang of Tanqueray <br>And a fat ass J, of some bubonic chronic that made me choke <br>Shit, this ain't no joke <br>I had to back up off of it and sit my cup down <br>Tanqueray and chronic, yeah I'm fucked up now <br>But it ain't no stoppin, I'm still poppin <br>Dre got some bitches from the city of Compton <br>To serve me, not with a cherry on top <br>Cause when I bust my nut, I'm raisin up off the cot <br>Don't get upset girl, that's just how it goes <br>I don't love you hoes, I'm out the do' <br>And I'll be <br><br>Rollin down the street, smokin endo, sippin on gin and juice <br>Laid back with my mind on my money and my money on my mind <br><br>Rollin down the street, smokin endo, sippin on gin and juice beeotch <br>Laid back with my mind on my money and my money on my mind <br>Rollin down the street, smokin endo, sippin on gin and juice beeotch <br>Laid back with my mind on my money and my money on my mind]]></content><category term="Hot Rod Circu" label="Hot Rod Circu"/><category term="Gin And Juice" label="Gin And Juice"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Escape_Frame/Nothin_But_A_G_Thang/</id><title>The Escape Frame - Nothin` But A `G` Thang - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Escape_Frame/Nothin_But_A_G_Thang/" title="The Escape Frame - Nothin` But A `G` Thang - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[One, two, three and to the fo' <br>Snoop Doggy Dogg and Dr Dre is at the do' <br>Ready to make an entrance, so back on up <br>cause you know we're bout to rip shit up <br>Gimme the microphone first, so I can bust like a bubble <br>Compton and Long Beach together, now you know you in trouble <br>Ain't nuttin but a G thang, baaaaabay <br>Two loc'ed out niggaz so we're craaaaazay <br>Death Row is the label that paaaaays me <br>Unfadeable, so please don't try to fade this Hell yeah <br>But uhh, back to the lecture at hand <br>Perfection is perfected, so I'ma let em understand <br>from a young G's perspective <br>And before me dig out a bitch I have to find a contraceptive <br>You never know she could be earnin her man <br>and learnin her man and at the same time burnin her man <br>Now you know I ain't with that shit, Lieutenant <br>Ain't no pussy good enough to get burnt while I'm up in it <br>YEAH And that's realer than Real Deal Holyfield <br>And now you hookers and hoes know how I feel <br>Well if it's good enough to get broke off a proper chunk <br>I'll take a small piece of some of that funky stuff <br><br>It's like this and like that and like this and uh <br>It's like that and like this and like that and uh <br>It's like this and like that and like this and uh <br>Dre, creep to the mic like a phantom <br><br>Well I'm peepin, and I'm creepin, and I'm creep in <br>But I damn near got caught, cause my beeper kept beepin <br>Now it's time for me to make my impression felt <br>So sit back, relax, and strap on your seatbelt <br>You never been on a ride like this befo' <br>with a producer who can rap and control the maestro <br>At the same time with the dope rhyme that I kick <br>You know, and I know, I flow some ol funky shit <br>to add to my collection, the selection <br>symbolizes dope, take a toke, but don't choke <br>If you do, you'll have no clue <br>on what me and my homey Snoop Dogg came to do <br><br>It's like this and like that and like this and uh <br>It's like that and like this and like that and uh <br>It's like this <br>And who gives a fuck about those <br>So just chill, til the next episode <br><br>Fallin back on that ass, with a hellafied gangsta lean <br>Gettin funky on the mic like a old batch of collard greens <br>It's the capital S, oh yes I'm fresh, N double O P <br>D O double G Y, D O double G, ya see <br>Showin much flex when it's time to wreck a mic <br>Pimpin hoes and clockin a grip like my name was Dolomite <br>Yeah, and it don't quit <br>I think they in the mood for some motherfuckin G shit <br>Hell yeah So Dre Whattup Dogg <br>Gotta give em what they want What's that, G <br>We gotta break em off somethin Hell yeah <br>And it's gotta be bumpin City of Compton <br><br>It's where it takes place so when asked, yo' attention <br>Mobbin like a muh'fucker, but I ain't lynchin <br>Droppin the funky shit that's makin the sucka niggaz mumble <br>When I'm on the mic, it's like a cookie, they all crumble <br>Try to get close, and your ass'll get smacked <br>My motherfuckin homie Doggy Dogg has got my back <br>Never let me slip, cause if I slip, then I'm slippin <br>But if I got my Nina, then you know I'm straight trippin <br>And I'ma continue to put the rap down, put the mack down <br>And if you bitches talk shit, I'll have to put the smack down <br>Yeah, and you don't stop <br>I told you I'm just like a clock when I tick and I tock <br>But I'm never off, always on, to the break of dawn <br>C O M P T O N, and the city they call Long Beach <br>Puttin the shit together <br>Like my nigga DOC, No One Can Do it Better <br><br>Like this, that and this and uh <br>It's like that and like this and like that and uh <br>It's like this <br>And who gives a fuck about those <br>So just chill, til the next episode]]></content><category term="The Escape Frame" label="The Escape Frame"/><category term="Nothin` But A `G` Thang" label="Nothin` But A `G` Thang"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scary_Kids_Scaring_Kids/Notorious_Thugs/</id><title>Scary Kids Scaring Kids - Notorious Thugs - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Scary_Kids_Scaring_Kids/Notorious_Thugs/" title="Scary Kids Scaring Kids - Notorious Thugs - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's Bone and Biggie Biggie x3 Rock the party, party <br>Yes Bone and Biggie Biggie Betta run and tell everybody <br>it's Bone and Biggie Biggie x3 Everybody, everybody <br><br>Let's Ride let's ride let's ride let's ride <br>Get high, get high, get high, c'mon <br>Let's ride let's ride let's ride let's ride <br>Get high, get high, get high <br>x2 <br><br>Armed and dangerous, ain't too many can bang with us <br>Straight up weed no angel dust, label us Notorious <br>Thug ass niggaz that love to bust, it's strange to us <br>Y'all niggaz be scramblin, gamblin <br>Up in restaraunts with mandolins, and violins <br>We just sittin here tryin to win, tryin not to sin <br>High off weed and lots of gin <br>So much smoke need oxygen, steadily countin them Benjamins <br>Nigga you should too, if you knew <br>What this game'll do to you <br>Been in this shit since ninety two <br>Look at all the bullshit I been through <br>So called beef with you know who <br>Fucked a few female stars or two <br>Nigga, blue light, nigga, move like Mike, shit <br>not to be fucked with <br>Motherfucker better duck quick, cause <br>Me and my dogs love to buck shit <br>Fuck the luck shit, strictly aim <br>No aspirations to quit the game <br>Spit yo' game, talk yo' shit <br>Grab yo' gat, call yo' click <br>Squeeze yo' clip, hit the right one <br>Pass that weed, I got to light one <br>All them niggaz I got ta fight one <br>All them hoes I got ta like one <br>Our situation is a tight one <br>Whatcha gonna do, fight or run <br>Seems to me that you'll take B <br>Bone and Big, nigga die slowly <br>I'ma tell you like a nigga told me <br>Cash Rule Everything Around Me <br>Shit, lyrically, niggaz can't see me <br>Fuck it, buy the coke <br>Cook the coke, cut it <br>Know the bitch 'fore you caught yourself lovin' it <br>Nigga with a Benz fuckin it <br>Doesn't it seem odd to you <br>Big come through with mobs and crews <br>Goodfellas down to the Mo Thugs dudes <br>Who's the killa, me or you <br><br>We forgive you, for you know not what you do <br><br>Seven AM woke in the mornin <br>With Hen and caffine and green and nicotine <br>No dough so pop a couple of doze <br>Lil Ripsta, nigga Mista Clean <br>Nigga Dean, deep in my temple and not to get <br>sentimentally sting, wit my <br>Instrumelody, and heated <br>especially for your team <br>And a forty five indeed will beam <br>in between the scenes destroy your dreams <br>You willin to die, we'll see <br>how many flees when I cause the scene <br>We mean mug, Mo Thugs <br>Trained to be perfect, disciples <br>When it's survival tongue, never double edged sword <br>Triple, six rivals spittin fire <br>This the real truth, bitch <br>Breakin out for lies <br>My Messiahs better be ready for Armageddeon shoot's expired <br>It's wild, bless the child <br>The one that became a man <br>Put in positions off in the Claire <br>All that I had to do was stare <br>Test me now, contender never no surrender no pretend <br>Pick up my gun, in my hand <br>One of my trusted friend friend, hey <br>Open it let's see if we're real, we all suited <br>Beg my pardon to Martin <br>Baby we ain't marchin we shootin <br>In daily recruitin there's a tough law <br>Everyday in the ghetto <br>We start em off little we give em a bottle <br>and a pen and a pad to hit the label kick it <br><br>Yo fuck you bitch <br><br>Nigga roll wit Bone up into the Thug spot <br>To the dome wit a shot of bird <br>Never get tossed to the curb <br>Be feelin that urge to splurge <br>But I'm broke as fuck son gimme that Mossberg swerve <br>Up into my bag, cause I gotta get my mask and shells <br>to put in this twelve gauge sawed off <br>Get em all off, nigga yo' loss, take it all off <br>Got a nigga car door <br>But the Bone not Leatherface, too many are thinkin they Thugs <br>They need the most help to pull it in doves <br>And bitch if you stickin we buckin them guzzlers, fucked up <br>Now let me get done with the grime <br>Gotta go purchase a dime <br>Put in a state to get done with the crime <br>Smokin the reefer to ease my mind <br>Swig some wine, step on the block with the rocks <br>But Willie be servin em clemency <br>Gotta buck him on down if he come back talkin <br>like gimme back me money <br>Thuggin with me killers, need us a leader <br>or liquor but niggaz ain't got shit <br>Wit a sawed off pump chrome thirty eight pistol <br>Now who ready to get bent <br>Nigga like me feenin for them green leaves <br>But I ain't had no dough <br>Gotta make some money so <br>I'm makin my dummy rocks if I go broke <br><br>It's Bone and Biggie Biggie x4 We gonna rock the party <br>Rock the party, party <br>It's Bone and Biggie Biggie x4 Betta run and tell everybody <br>Everybody, everybody <br><br>Let's Ride let's ride let's ride let's ride <br>Get high, get high, get high, c'mon <br>Let's ride let's ride let's ride let's ride <br>Get high, get high, get high <br><br>Yeah, Little Lay hey comin in the form of scripture <br>Finna get ya and hit ya wit magic <br>Droppin down licks betta call on my gadgets <br>With an automatics status we spray time to load the glocks <br>But I'm thinkin not <br>There's another he forced tellin me do what I gotta do <br>So my otha potnah nigga die tonight <br>And I'm always runnin from the boys in blue <br>Biggie booms on my ass now provide the cellular phone <br>The carphone, what's happenin <br>Grab artillery niggaz start packin <br>Cause a motherfucker try to get me in a jacket, and I did him <br>Hit him right between the eyes, despise the wise <br>Wanna test a nigga size, that'll cost him <br>Nigga fuck around wit the wrong shit <br>Y'all get mo murdered all day all day <br>We done paved the way and I'm on the run <br>I'ma call my boys and bring all the guns <br>Y'all niggaz wanna have a little fun wit number one <br>One, one, then it red red rum rum rum rum rum rum <br>But it red red rum rum rum rum rum rum <br>But it red red rum <br><br>It's Bone and Biggie Biggie x4 We gonna rock the party <br>Rock the party, party <br>It's Bone and Biggie Biggie x4 Betta run and tell everybody <br>Everybody, everybody <br><br>Let's Ride let's ride let's ride let's ride <br>Get high, get high, get high, c'mon <br>Let's ride let's ride let's ride let's ride <br>Get high, get high, get high]]></content><category term="Scary Kids Scaring Kids" label="Scary Kids Scaring Kids"/><category term="Notorious Thugs" label="Notorious Thugs"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/All_Time_Low/Umbrella/</id><title>All Time Low - Umbrella - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/All_Time_Low/Umbrella/" title="All Time Low - Umbrella - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You had my heart <br>and we'll never be world apart <br>Maybe in magazines <br>but you'll still be my star <br>Baby cause in the dark <br>You can see shiny cars <br>And that's when you need me there <br>With you I'll always share <br>Because <br><br>When the sun shines <br>We'll shine together <br>Told you I'll be here forever <br>Said I'll always be your friend <br>Took an oath <br>I'mma stick it out 'till the end <br>Now that it's raining more than ever <br>Told you we'll still have each other <br>You can stand under my umbrella <br>You can stand under my umbrella <br>Ella ella eh eh eh <br>Under my umbrella <br>ella ella eh eh eh <br>Under my umbrella <br>ella ella eh eh eh <br>Under my umbrella <br>ella ella eh eh eh eh eh eh <br><br>These fancy things <br>will never come in between <br>You are my entity <br>Here for infinity <br>When the war has took its part <br>When the world has dealt it's cards <br>If the hand is hard <br><br>Together we'll mend your heart <br>Because <br><br>When the sun shines <br>We'll shine together <br>Told you I'll be here forever <br>Said I'll always be your friend <br>Took an oath <br>I'mma stick it out 'till the end <br><br>Now that it's raining more than ever <br>Told you we'll still have each other <br>You can stand under my umbrella <br>You can stand under my umbrella <br>Ella ella eh eh eh <br>Under my umbrella <br>ella ella eh eh eh <br>Under my umbrella <br>ella ella eh eh eh <br>Under my umbrella <br>ella ella eh eh eh eh eh eh <br><br>You can run into my arms <br>It's okay don't be alarmed <br>Come into me <br>There's no distance in between our love <br>Gonna let the rain pour <br>I'll be all you need and more <br>Because <br><br>When the sun shines <br>We'll shine together <br>Told you I'll be here forever <br>Said I'll always be your friend <br>Took an oath <br>I'mma stick it out 'till the end <br>Now that it's raining more than ever <br>Told you we'll still have each other <br>You can stand under my umbrella <br>You can stand under my umbrella <br>Ella ella eh eh eh <br>Under my umbrella <br>ella ella eh eh eh <br>Under my umbrella <br>ella ella eh eh eh <br>Under my umbrella <br>ella ella eh eh eh eh eh eh <br><br>It's raining raining <br>O baby it's raining <br>baby come into me <br>Come into me <br>It's raining raining <br>O baby it's raining <br>O baby come into me <br>Come into me]]></content><category term="All Time Low" label="All Time Low"/><category term="Umbrella" label="Umbrella"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Devil_Wears_Prada_Soundtrack/Still_Fly/</id><title>The Devil Wears Prada Soundtrack - Still Fly - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Devil_Wears_Prada_Soundtrack/Still_Fly/" title="The Devil Wears Prada Soundtrack - Still Fly - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[What's up Fresh, it's our turn baby <br><br>Gator Boots, with the pimped out Gucci suit <br>Ain't got no job, but I stay sharp <br>Can't pay my rent, cause all my money's spent <br>But that's OK, cause I'm still fly <br><br>Gotcha car play gems on shine, said it's mine, get a mink, baby girl lets ride <br>You da Numba 1 stunna, and we gonna glide <br>And go straight to the mall, and turn out the inside <br>Prowler Gucci full length leather, Burbons cooler, Coogi sweater <br>Twenty inches pop my feather, The Bird man daddy I fly in any weather <br>Alligator seats with the head in the <br>Inside <br>Swine on the dash, G Wagon so Fly <br>Numba 1 don't tangle and twisle <br>When it come to these cars my hands are faithful <br>The Gucci with the matching interior <br>3 wheel ride with the tire in the middle <br>It's Fresh and stunna and we like brothers <br>We shine like paint daddy this our summer <br><br>Gator Boots, with the pimped out Gucci suit <br>Ain't got no job, but I stay sharp <br>Can't pay my rent, cause all my money's spent <br>But that's OK, cause I'm still fly <br>Got a quarter tank gas in my new E class <br>But that's alright cause I'm gon' ride <br>Got everything in my moma's name <br>But I'm hood rich da dada dada da <br><br>Have you ever seen the crocodile seats in the truck <br>Turn around and sit it down and let em' bite ya butt <br>See, the steering wheel is Fendi, dashboard Armani <br>With Your baby momma playa is where u can find me <br>Pushing through the parking lot on 24's Cadillac Escalade with the chromed out nose <br>With the navigation arrow headed straight to iHop <br>Aunt Jaimama likes me cause my syrup is so hot <br>Put the Caddy up, Start the 3 wheel Benz <br>Hyper white lights, ultra violet lens <br>Sumitomo tires and they gotta be run flat <br>TV where the horn go, boy can you top that <br>I'ma show you somethin rookie press that button <br>The trunk went Eh eh and all of a sudden <br>4 15's didn't see no wire's, and then I heard boom from the amplifiers <br><br>Let me slide in the Benz with the fished out fins <br>Impala Loud pipes, Drinking that Hen <br>It's the birdy birdy man I'll do it again <br>In the Cadillac truck 24's with 10's <br>Looking at my Gucci it's about that time <br>6 banders flying in at 9 <br>New Suburban truck with page up showin' <br>Black and White and Red and Gold and <br>Bodies on the Roadster Lexus You know with that hard top beamer <br>Momma that's your truck <br>I'm coming up the hood been lovely <br>Open up the top and I wake up the bubbley <br>430 lex with convertible top <br>The rims keep spinning every time I stop <br>I got a superman Benz that I scored from shaq <br>With a old school Caddy with a diamond in the back <br><br>Gator Boots, with the pimped out Gucci suit <br>Ain't got no job, but I stay sharp <br>Can't pay my rent, cause all my money's spent <br>But that's OK, cause I'm still fly <br>Got a quarter tank gas in my new E class <br>But that's alright cause I'm gon' ride <br>Got everything in my moma's name <br>But I'm hood rich da dada dada da]]></content><category term="The Devil Wears Prada Soundtrack" label="The Devil Wears Prada Soundtrack"/><category term="Still Fly" label="Still Fly"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Person_L/The_Seed_20/</id><title>Person L - The Seed (2.0) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Person_L/The_Seed_20/" title="Person L - The Seed (2.0) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Knocked up nine months ago <br>And where we goin she don't know <br>She wants neo soul cause hip hop is old <br>She don't want no rock'n roll <br>She want platinum, ice and gold <br>She want a whole lot of somethin' to fold <br>If you're an obstacle she'll just drop you cold <br>Cause one monkey don't stop the show <br>Little Mary's bad <br>In these streets she done ran <br>E'ry since when the heat began <br>I told the girl look here <br>Calm down I'm gonna hold your hand <br>To enable you to keep the plan <br>Because you'se quick to learn <br>And we can make money to burn <br>If you allow me the lay this game <br>I don't ask for much but enough to room to spread my wings <br>And a world fittin to know my name, just listen to me <br><br>I don't ask for much these days <br>And I don't bitch and whine if I don't get my way <br>I only wanna fertilize another behind my lover's back <br>I sit and watch it grow standin where I'm at <br>Fertilize another behind my lover's back <br>And I'm keepin my secrets mine <br>I push my seed in her bush for life <br>It's gonna work because I'm pushin it right <br>If Mary dropped my baby girl tonight <br>I would name her rock n roll <br><br>A Cadillac need space to roam <br>Where we headed for She don't know <br>We in the city where the pros shake, rattle, and roll <br>And I'm a God dang rollin stone <br>I don't beg, I can hold my own <br>I don't break, I can hold the chrome <br><br>And it's weighin a ton, and I'm a son of a gun <br>My code name is The Only One <br>And Black Thought is bad <br>The mean streets he done ran <br>E'r since when the game began <br>I never played the fool <br>Matter fact, I've been keepin it cool <br>Since money been changin hands <br>And I'm left to shine <br>The legacy I leave behind <br>Be the seed that'll keep the flame <br>I don't ask for much but enough room to spread these wings <br>And the world finna know my name <br><br>I don't beg from no rich man <br>And I don't scream and kick when his shit don't fall in my hands, man <br>Cause I know how to steal <br>Fertilize another against my lover's will <br>I lick the opposition cause she don't take no pill <br>Oooh oooh oooh dear <br>You'll be keepin my secrets mine <br>I push my seed in her bush for life <br>It's gonna work because I'm pushin it right <br>If Mary dropped my baby girl tonight <br>I would name her rock n roll <br><br>Oooh break it down, break down the beat <br><br>I push my seed somewhere deep in her chest <br>I work it naked cause I've taken my test <br>Deliver it, Mary, it don't matter the sex <br>I'm gon name it rock n roll <br><br>I push my seed in her bush for life <br>Oh It's gonna work because I'm pushin it right <br>If Mary dropped my baby girl tonight <br>I would name her rock n roll <br>I would name her rock n roll <br>I would name her rock n roll]]></content><category term="Person L" label="Person L"/><category term="The Seed (2.0)" label="The Seed (2.0)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Emanuel/Kryptonite/</id><title>Emanuel - Kryptonite - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Emanuel/Kryptonite/" title="Emanuel - Kryptonite - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I be on it all night, man, I be on it day day day <br>All day, straight up, pimp <br>If you want me, you can find me in the <br><br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br><br>Time and time again, I gotta turn back 'round and tell these hoes <br>That I'm the H N I C, bitch, that's just the way it goes <br>I be on that shit that have you on it, I don't want no more <br>At this time, I'll need all my freak hoes to get down on the floor <br>If you came to rep your set, break that bitch, I let them know <br>If it's jail I get for stomping haters to sleep, fuck it, I go <br>Freak, I'll be off in your sheets, straight geeked, swervin' down your street <br>In a stolen Bonneville with 23's on the feet <br>Collection while he do brown, back in town to do re bag <br>Give me face, I love the sound <br>Slap the taste, they hit the ground <br>Back in the A <br>Hooked up, clicked up with some people that don't play <br>On that Kryptonite, stay <br>So high we might fly away <br><br>I be on that Kryptonite <br>Straight up on that Kryptonite <br>I be on that, straight up on that <br>I be on that Kryptonite <br><br>I be on that Kryptonite <br>Straight up on that Kryptonite <br>I be on that, straight up on that <br>I be on that Kryptonite <br><br>I, I, I, I, I, be on it all night, man, I be on it day day day <br>All day, straight up, pimp <br>If you want me, you can find me in the <br><br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br><br>Kryptonite, on that Kryptonite <br>I'm on that Kryptonite <br>On that Kryptonite <br><br>Time and time again I gotta tell these bitches and these hoes <br>I'm from College Park, where we move that weed and we sling that blow <br>Get dope on a daily basis <br>Get high, make them ugly faces <br>Pull the dro' and I'm on probation <br>My blunts, I don't be lacing <br><br>I'm on that Kryptonite <br>Come to my crib tonight <br>Let me beat that puss all night <br>Run, tell your buddies I fucked you right <br>Tell them 'bout the plaques on the walls <br>Tell them how you licked my balls <br>Tell them how Konkrete run the streets <br>Big Boi, he put us on <br><br>Chevy riders, slingin' powders Simpson Road, Dixie Hills <br>Diamonds pressed against that wood, candy paint, spinnin' wheels <br>Grind time, rap game, remember bitches, Killer Kill <br>Purple Ribbon rollin' o's, and we all be on that Kryp <br><br>I be on that Kryptonite <br>Straight up on that Kryptonite <br>I be on that, straight up on that <br>I be on that Kryptonite <br><br>I be on that Kryptonite <br>Straight up on that Kryptonite <br>I be on that, straight up on that <br>I be on that Kryptonite <br><br>I, I, I, I, I, be on it all night, man, I be on it day day day <br>All day, straight up, pimp <br>If you want me, you can find me in the <br><br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br><br>Kryptonite, on that Kryptonite <br>I'm on that Kryptonite <br>On that Kryptonite <br><br>Time and time again, I gotta turn back 'round and tell C Bone <br>Grab that kurl on out my book bag, I smell 'dro all on you, homes <br>Suppose the po po get whiff of the spliff that you smoke, them folk gonna trip <br>Probably will cause the canines, move it the side of the road, let's take a sniff <br>Shit, the only thing we ridin' dirty is GBK CD, Tackleberry <br>So we may be on our merry way <br>'Cause you just ain't gonna find no yah <br>Play, I got a tough team of attorneys <br>Make a judge lean like he sippin' syrupy <br>They dirty, he can't touch me <br>Verdict be not guilty, search me <br><br>Chevy riders, slingin' powders Simpson Road, Dixie Hills <br>Diamonds pressed against that wood, candy paint, spinnin' wheels <br>Grind time, rap game, remember bitches, Killer Kill <br>Purple Ribbon rollin' o's, and we all be on that Kryp <br><br>I be on that Kryptonite <br>Straight up on that Kryptonite <br>I be on that, straight up on that <br>I be on that Kryptonite <br><br>I be on that Kryptonite <br>Straight up on that Kryptonite <br>I be on that, straight up on that <br>I be on that Kryptonite <br><br>I, I, I, I, I, be on it all night, man, I be on it day day day <br>All day, straight up, pimp <br>If you want me, you can find me in the <br><br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br><br>Kryptonite, I'm on it on that Kryptonite I'm on it <br>I'm on that Kryptonite I'm on it <br>On that Kryptonite <br><br>I, I, I, I, I be on that Kryptonite <br>Straight up on that Kryptonite <br>I be on that, straight up on that <br>I be on that Kryptonite <br><br>I be on that Kryptonite <br>Straight up on that Kryptonite <br>I be on that, straight up on that <br>I be on that Kryptonite <br><br>I, I, I, I, I, be on it all night, man, I be on it day day day <br>All day, straight up, pimp <br>If you want me, you can find me in the <br><br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br>Ay I'm on it <br><br>Kryptonite, on that Kryptonite <br>I'm on that Kryptonite <br>On that Kryptonite <br><br>Girls <br>Boy stop <br>Yeah <br>Haha]]></content><category term="Emanuel" label="Emanuel"/><category term="Kryptonite" label="Kryptonite"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Maine/I_Wanna_Love_You/</id><title>The Maine - I Wanna Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Maine/I_Wanna_Love_You/" title="The Maine - I Wanna Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Convict Music and You know we up front <br><br>I see you winding, grinding, up on that pole <br>I know you see me looking at you and you already know <br>I wanna love you <br>you already know, I wanna love you <br>You already know <br><br>Money in the air as more fell <br>Grab you by your coat tail, take you to the motel, ho sale <br>Don't tell, won't tell <br>baby say, I don't talk, girl, unless you told on me <br>Baby stick on me, I'm gonna stick on you <br>and if You pick me, then baby I'll pick you <br>D O Double G I'm gonna put it on you <br><br>I see you winding, grinding, up on that pole <br>I know you see me looking at you and you, already know <br>I wanna love you love you <br>you already know, I wanna love you love you <br>You already know <br><br>Mobbin' in the club and I'm pressin' <br>I'm sitting back in the smoker's section <br>Bird's eye, I've got a clear view <br>You can't see me, but I can see you <br>It's cool, we jet, the mood is set <br>Your lips are wet <br>You're rubbing your back, and touching your neck <br>Your body's moving <br><br>I see you winding, grinding, up on that pole <br>I know you see me looking at you and you, already know <br>I wanna love you love you <br>you already know, I wanna love you love you <br>You already know <br><br>And you know my pedigree <br>Used to move 'phetamines <br>And I'm loving the way you shake your ass <br>In those jeans <br><br>I see you winding, grinding, up on that pole <br>I know you see me looking at you and you, already know <br><br>I wanna love you love you <br>you already know, I wanna love you love you <br><br>I see you winding, grinding, up on that pole <br>I know you see me looking at you and you, already know <br>I wanna love you love you <br>you already know, I wanna love you love you <br>You already know <br><br>4 8 0 6 0 2 <br>Big O Tropicanic <br>Young P Yo it's my town <br>J Dubb I'm Pete Naturally Diesel, I'm out <br>I ain't goin' back to jail]]></content><category term="The Maine" label="The Maine"/><category term="I Wanna Love You" label="I Wanna Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/My_American_Heart/California_Love/</id><title>My American Heart - California Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/My_American_Heart/California_Love/" title="My American Heart - California Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[California love <br><br>Now let me welcome everybody to the wild, wild west <br>A state that's untouchable like Elliot Ness <br>The track hits ya eardrum like a slug to ya chest <br>Pack a vest for your Jimmy in the city of sex <br>We in that sunshine state with a bomb ass hemp beat <br>The state where ya never find a dance floor empty <br>And pimps be on a mission for them greens <br>Lean mean money makin machines servin fiends <br>I been in the game for ten years makin rap tunes <br>Ever since honeys was wearin sassoon <br>Now it's '95 and they clock me and watch me <br>Diamonds shinin lookin like I robbed Liberace <br>It's all good, from Diego to tha Bay <br>Your city is tha bomb if your city makin pay <br>Throw up a finger if ya feel the same way <br>Mah puttin it down for <br>Californ i a <br><br>California knows how to party knows how to party <br>California knows how to party yes we do it, do it <br>In the citaaay of LA <br>In the citaaay of good ol' Watts <br>In the citaaay, the city of Compton <br>We keep it rockin We keep it rockin <br><br>C'mon <br>Shake, shake it baby <br>Yeah <br>Shake, shake it <br>Cali <br>Shake, shake it mama <br>That's right <br>Shake it Cali <br>C'mon, c'mon <br>Shake, shake it baby <br>Yeah <br>Shake, shake it <br>Cali <br>Shake, shake it mama <br>Yeah <br>Shake it Cali <br><br>Out on bail fresh outta jail, California dreamin <br>Soon as I stepped on the scene, I'm hearin hoochies screamin <br>Fiendin for money and alcohol <br>The life of a west side playa where cowards die and its all ball <br>Only in Cali where we riot not rally to live and die <br>In LA we wearin Chucks not Ballies <br>Dressed in Locs and khaki suits and ride is what we do <br>Flossin but have caution we collide with other crews <br>Famous cause we program worldwide <br>Let'em recognize from Long Beach to Rosecrans <br>Bumpin and grindin like a slow jam, it's west side <br>So you know the row won't bow down to no man <br>Say what you say <br>But give me that bomb beat from Dre <br>Let me serenade the streets of LA <br>From Oakland to Sac town <br>The Bay Area and back down <br>Cali is where they put they mack down <br>Give me love <br><br>x2 <br>Shake, shake it baby <br>Shake, shake it <br>Shake, shake it mama <br><br>Shake, shake it baby <br>Now let me welcome everybody to the wild, wild west <br>Shake, shake it <br>Shake, shake it mama <br><br>Say what you say, but give me that bomb beat from Dre <br>Shake, shake it baby <br>Shake, shake it <br>Now let me welcome everybody to the wild, wild west, wild, wild west, wild wild west <br>Shake, shake it mama <br><br>Shake, shake it baby <br>California love Shake, shake it <br>Shake, shake it mama <br><br>Shake, shake it baby <br>Shake, shake it <br>Shake, shake it mama <br>California love <br>Californ i a]]></content><category term="My American Heart" label="My American Heart"/><category term="California Love" label="California Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Forever_The_Sickest_Kids/Men_In_Black/</id><title>Forever The Sickest Kids - Men In Black - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Forever_The_Sickest_Kids/Men_In_Black/" title="Forever The Sickest Kids - Men In Black - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[here come the men in black <br>it's the MIBs, uh, here come the MIBs <br>here come the men in black <br>they won't let you remember, no <br><br>nah nah nah <br>the good guys dress in black, remember that <br>just in case we're ever face to face and make contact <br>the title held by me, MIB <br>means what you think you saw you didn't see <br>so don't blink, b, what was there is now gone <br>black suits with the black ray bans on <br>walk in shadow, move in silence <br>guard against extra terrestrial violence <br>yo, we ain't on no government list <br>we straight don't exist, no names and no fingerprints <br>saw something strange, watch your back <br>'cause you never quite know where the MIBs at, uh <br><br>here come the men in black <br>galaxy defenders <br>here come the men in black <br>they won't let you remember, no <br><br>uh huh, now, from the deepest of the darkest night <br>on the horizon, bright light enters the sight, tight <br>cameras zoom on the impending doom <br>but then like boom, black suits fill the room up <br>with the quickness, talk with the witnesses <br>hypnotizer, neuralizer <br>vivid memories turn to fantasies <br>ain't no MIBs, can i please <br>do what we say, that's the way we kick it <br>y'know what i mean <br>see my noisy cricket get wicked on ya <br>we're your first, last, and only line of defense <br>against the worst scum of the universe <br>don't fear us, cheer us <br>if you ever get near us <br>don't jeer us, we're fearless <br>MIBs freezin' up all the flack <br>what's that stand for <br>men in black <br><br>let me see ya bounce with me <br>just bounce with me, just bounce it with me <br>c'mon, let me see ya just slide with me <br>just slide with me, just slide with me <br>c'mon, let me see ya take a walk with me <br>just walk with me, take a walk with me <br>c'mon, make your neck work <br>now freeze <br><br>here come the men in black <br>galaxy defenders <br>here come the men in black <br>they won't let you remember, no <br><br>alright check it, slow down, son <br>you're worryin' about the wrong thing, pimp <br>whoa, that's awesome, bro <br>817, FTSK]]></content><category term="Forever The Sickest Kids" label="Forever The Sickest Kids"/><category term="Men In Black" label="Men In Black"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Secret_Handshake/I_Wish/</id><title>The Secret Handshake - I Wish - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Secret_Handshake/I_Wish/" title="The Secret Handshake - I Wish - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I wish I was little bit taller <br>I wish I was a baller <br>I wish I had a girl who looked good <br>I would call her <br>I wish I had a rabbit in a hat with a bat <br>and a '64 Impala <br><br>I wish I was like six foot nine <br>So I could get with Leoshi <br>Cause she don't know me but yo she's really fine <br>You know I see her all the time <br>Everywhere I go, and even in my dreams <br>I can scheme of ways to make her mine <br>Cause I know she's livin phat <br>Her boyfriend's tall and he plays ball <br>So how am I gonna compete with that <br>'Cause when it comes to playing basketball <br>I'm always last to be picked <br>And in some cases never picked at all <br>So I just lean upon the wall <br>Or sit up in the bleachers with the rest of the girls <br>Who came to watch their men ball <br>Dag y'all I never understood <br>Why the jocks get the fly girls <br>And me I get the hood rats <br>I tell 'em scat, skittle, skibobble <br>Got hit with a bottle <br>And put in the hospital, for talkin' that mess <br>I confess it's a shame when you livin' in a city <br>That's the size of a box and nobody knows yo' name <br><br>I wish I was little bit taller <br>I wish I was a baller <br>I wish I had a girl who looked good <br>I would call her <br>I wish I had a rabbit in a hat with a bat <br>and a '64 Impala <br><br>Glad I came to my senses <br>Like quick quick got sick sick to my stomach <br>Overcome with my thoughts of me and her together <br>Right <br>So when I asked her out she said I wasn't her type <br><br>I wish I had a brand new car <br>So far, I got this hatchback <br>And everywhere I go, yo I gets laughed at <br>And when I'm in my car I'm laid back <br>I got an 8 track and a spare tire in the backseat <br>But that's flat <br>And do you really wanna know what's really wack, What <br>See I can't even get a date <br>So, what do you think of that <br>I heard that prom night is the bomb night <br>With a hood rat you can hold tight <br>But really tho' on figuero <br>When I'm in my car I can't even get a hello <br>Well so many people wanna cruise Crenshaw on Sunday <br>Well then I'm gonna have to get in my car and go <br>You know I take the 110 to the 105 <br>Get off on Crenshaw tell my homies look alive <br>Cause it's hard to survive <br>Livin' in a concrete jungle and <br>These girls just keep passin' me by <br>She looks fly, she looks fly <br>Makes me say my, my, my <br><br>I wish I was a little bit taller <br>I wish I was a baller <br>I wish I was a little bit taller y'all <br>I wish I was a baller <br><br>Hey, I wish I had my way <br>'Cause everyday would be a Friday <br>You could even speed on the highway <br>I would play ghetto games <br>Name my kids ghetto names <br>Little Mookie, big Al, Lorraine <br>Yo you know that's on the real <br>So if you're down on your luck <br>Then you should know just how I feel <br>Cause if you don't want me around <br>See I go simple, I go easy, I go greyhound <br>Hey, you, what's that sound <br>Everybody look what's going down <br>Ahhhh, yes, ain't that fresh <br>Everybody wants to get down like that <br><br>I wish, I wish, I wish]]></content><category term="The Secret Handshake" label="The Secret Handshake"/><category term="I Wish" label="I Wish"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Say_Anything/I_Got_Your_Money/</id><title>Say Anything - I Got Your Money - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Say_Anything/I_Got_Your_Money/" title="Say Anything - I Got Your Money - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Oh Baby <br>I dedicate this to all the pretty girls <br>To all the pretty girls to ohhh <br>All the pretty girls in the world <br>And the ugly girls too <br>'Cuz to me you're pretty anyways, baby <br><br>You give me your number <br>I call you up <br>You act like your pussy don't interrupt <br>I don't have no trouble with you fucking me <br>But I have a little problem with you not fucking me <br>Baby you know I'll take care of you <br>'Cuz you say you got my baby and I know it ain't true <br>Is it a good thing No, it's bad bitch <br>For good or worse, makes you switch <br>So I walk on over with my Cristal <br>Bitch ass niggas put away your pistols <br>Bemis won't be havin it in this house <br>'Cuz bitch I'll cripple your style <br>Now that you heard my calm voice <br>Couldn't get another nigga, hootchie won't get moist <br>If you wanna look good and not be bummy <br>Girl you better gimmie that money <br>Hoo <br><br>Hey, dirty, baby I got your money <br>Don't you worry <br>I said hey, baby I got your money <br>Hey, dirty, baby I got your money <br>Don't you worry <br>I said hey, baby I got your money <br><br>Yo, so I glanced at the girls, girls glanced at me <br>I whispered in their ear you wanna be with me <br>You wanna look pretty though, in my video <br>Ol Bemis on the hat and I let you all know <br>Just dance like you're caught up in the Holy Ghost trance <br>If you stop, I'll put the killer ants in your pants <br>I'm the M A B as you can see <br>FBI, don't you be watchin' me <br>I don't want no problems, 'cuz I'll put you down <br>In the ground where you cannot be found <br>I'm just Beem Dog tryin to make some money <br>So gimme my streaks and gimme my honey <br>Radios play this all day every day <br>Recognize I'm a fool and you love me <br>None of you, nuh, better look at me funny <br>Nuh, you know my name now gimmie my money <br><br>Hey, dirty, baby I got your money <br>Don't you worry <br>I said hey, baby I got your money <br>Hey, dirty, baby I got your money <br>Don't you worry <br>I said hey, baby I got your money <br>Hey, dirty, baby I got your money <br>Don't you worry <br>I said hey, baby I got your money <br>Hey, dirty, baby I got your money <br>Don't you worry <br>I said hey, baby I got your money <br><br>Sing it <br>Sing it girls <br>Sing it right now <br>If Bemis want his money, just give him his money <br>That's how I like giiiiirrrrrrlllll <br>Sexy, sexy, sexy <br>Sexy, sexy, sexy <br>Sexy, sexy, sexy <br>Sexy, sexy, sexy <br><br>Play'n the club like this all night <br>Bitches put your ass out and let me hold it tight <br>Your looking at my wrist saying it's so nice <br>The price, bitch, is diamonds, shining disco lights <br>You better help me solve my problem <br>Or I'll get this money and rob them <br>Lucky dog when I won the lotto <br>Ran up my cards for carrying raw loads <br>Well hold on now you can call me Bemis <br>And then lift up your skirt <br>And if you want this Bemis <br>God made Beem and Beem will bust your ass <br>Stop annoying me, yeah I play my music loud <br>Take the bastard Old Bemis to move the crowd <br>They say he had his balls in his mouth <br>Cisco Adler taught me that back at the house <br>But give me my money <br><br>Hey, dirty, baby I got your money <br>Don't you worry <br>I said hey, baby I got your money <br>Hey, dirty, baby I got your money <br>Don't you worry <br>I said hey, baby I got your money <br>Hey, dirty, baby I got your money <br>Don't you worry <br>I said hey, baby I got your money <br>Hey, dirty, baby I got your money <br>Don't you worry <br>I said hey, baby I got your money]]></content><category term="Say Anything" label="Say Anything"/><category term="I Got Your Money" label="I Got Your Money"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Set_Your_Goals/Put_Yo_Hood_Up/</id><title>Set Your Goals - Put Yo Hood Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:48:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:48:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Set_Your_Goals/Put_Yo_Hood_Up/" title="Set Your Goals - Put Yo Hood Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Out in the wild we have the dinosaurs but listen very carefully <br>Yeah <br>Yo, whats up SYG 2008 <br>Orinda, Moraga, Pleasant Hill, Crescent Drive, New Found Glory, Yoda <br>Calavera's House, Creekside, Century Movie Theatre BITCH <br>Obi Wan, Light Saber, Tice Valley Gym Dodgeball, Santa <br>Halo 3, Say Northcoast motha fuckas <br><br>Put yo hood up 4X <br>Put yo click up 4X <br>Represent yo' shit muthafuuuucka 2X <br>Represent yo click muthafuuuucka 2X <br><br>Well shake yo' drink up and spray the muthafuckin' crowd 2X <br>Throw yo' click up and say it muthafuckin' loud 2X <br>Now drop yo' bows on em' and get buck ass wild 2X <br>You supposed to act up with a black and fuckin' mild 2X <br>Cuz' them eastbay jedi don't give a fuck <br>Them westbay jedi is quick to buck <br>Them northbay jedi will cut you up <br>And them southbay jedi will put you in a trunk <br><br>Now jump jump jump jedi <br>Stomp stomp stomp jedi <br>Jump jump jump jedi <br>Stomp stomp jedi <br><br>Put yo hood up 4X <br>Put yo click up 4X <br>Represent yo' shit muthafuuuucka 2X <br>Represent yo click muthafuuuucka 2X <br><br>If you scared to throw it up get the fuck out the club 2X <br>If you don't give a fuck then throw that muthafucka up 2X <br>I'm wit my hommies in this bitch, and you know we fucked up 2X <br>We clicked up 30 deep and we always strapped up 2X <br>Who you wit Who you wit <br>Who you wit get crunk, who you wit 2X <br>Well who run this bitch We run this bitch 4X <br><br>Put yo hood up 4X <br>Put yo click up 4X <br>Represent yo' shit muthafuuuucka 2X <br>Represent yo click muthafuuuucka 2X <br><br>Aye, check dis out I need all my real african american people <br>To look around the muthafuckin' club <br>If you see a jedi and he throwin' up a set and it ain't yo' set <br>Or it ain't yo' click <br>I want chall jedi to tell dem' out like dis <br>I want you to get up in that muthafucka' face <br>This ain't no real mother fuckin' chickasaaw <br>This is a real mother fuckin' chickasaw nation <br>Keepin' it real <br>WHAT <br><br>Put yo hood up 4X <br>Put yo click up 4X <br>Represent yo' shit muthafuuuucka 2X <br>Represent yo click muthafuuuucka 2X <br><br>Put yo hood up 4X We some eastbay jedi 2X <br>Put yo click up 4X We some westbay jedi 2X <br>Represent yo' shit muthafuuuucka 2X We some northbay jedi 2X <br>Represent yo click muthafuuuucka 2X We some southbay jedi 2X]]></content><category term="Set Your Goals" label="Set Your Goals"/><category term="Put Yo Hood Up" label="Put Yo Hood Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hideous_Sun_Demon/Monogamy/</id><title>Hideous Sun Demon - Monogamy - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:49:41+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:49:41+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hideous_Sun_Demon/Monogamy/" title="Hideous Sun Demon - Monogamy - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You been calling me a bad guy <br>I see you crawling in the back on your back with my third eye <br>What you do that for anyway <br>Feel you grab me round my neck had you vexed by my disarray <br>Because it’s worse than you thought <br>You’re forced to resort <br>To resigning to my timing <br>As your life surmounts to nought <br>Because its not what you feel <br>Beyond what is real <br>Mental prism is a prison <br>Play you like a glockenspiel <br>And the chance that you had <br>Was a chance you didn’t grab <br>Now your life is wrapped in plastic <br>Sealed up in a ziplock bag <br>And it’s not what is hers <br>It’s not what is his <br>I’m gonna have a kid with you <br>And I don’t even care what your name is <br><br>i’m not interested in clarity <br>Project an image watch it warp and contort your reality <br>My vibe will leave you here petrified <br>Inclined to rewind and resign the design you thought was bonafide <br>And if you start to protest <br>Your pride I’ll ingest <br>Let you struggle in the puddle <br>Of the discharge from your chest <br>Coz its more than you are <br>It feeds off bizzare <br>It torments you in your sleep <br>So don’t be calling me a liar <br>Cause it's past boiling point <br>It fiends off disjoint <br>And dead-arm stimulation <br>Leaves you bloated and annoyed <br>And if time’s in the past <br>Then time’s what you missed <br>I’m gonna have a kid with you <br>And I don’t even care what your name is <br><br>M.O.N.O.G <br>Personality <br>M.O.N.O.G <br>Mono-Harmony <br><br>Monogamy <br>For you and me]]></content><category term="Hideous Sun Demon" label="Hideous Sun Demon"/><category term="Monogamy" label="Monogamy"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/검정가죽/가져_Own_Me/</id><title>검정가죽 - 가져 (Own Me) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:49:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:49:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%EA%B2%80%EC%A0%95%EA%B0%80%EC%A3%BD/%EA%B0%80%EC%A0%B8_Own_Me/" title="검정가죽 - 가져 (Own Me) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[걱정 안해도 되 <br>U gotta own my day yeah <br>오늘 하루는 <br>너만을 위해 쓸게 <br>for you just tell me <br>everything u want <br>가지고 싶은거 가져 <br>가지고 싶은거 가져 <br>you're so beautiful <br>eh eh oh eh eh oh <br>you're so beautiful <br>eh eh oh eh eh oh <br>좀 독보적인 너 <br>Yeah i'm hesitated so <br>Tell me everything bout u <br>아직 베일에 갇혀서 <br>널 갖고싶어도 <br>내진심의 반의 반도 <br>못보여줬네 <br>만약 너도 날 원한다면 <br>I hope we gotta own eachother <br>시간이없어 <br>make it up <br>더 머리 아프게 <br>고민하지말고 <br>own me <br>oh love <br>당신이 원하는게 뭔가요 <br>oh no <br>그만큼 가졌으면 됬잖아 <br>내게 말해준다면 <br>나를 믿어준다면 <br>어때 오늘 밤 <br>무르익은 너와나 <br>함께 하자 모든걸 <br>다줄테니까 <br>원해 몰래 내 몸을 <br>안아줄때에 <br>스트로베리같은 <br>니 입술을 가질래 <br>넌 날 가져 <br>난 널 가져 <br>넌 날 가져 <br>난 널 가져 <br>바라보는거 말고 <br>너에 관한 건 <br>하나 둘씩 갖고 싶어져 <br>이제 입장 바꿔서 <br>날 어떻게 생각할지 <br>그게 알고 싶어져 <br>If 너도 나와 생각같다면 babe <br>더 이상 시간낭비 안해도 되 <br>Always be there <br>니 옆에 있을게 <br>Take it slow gonna <br>love for each other <br>oh love <br>당신이 원하는게 뭔가요 <br>oh no <br>그만큼 가졌으면 됬잖아 <br>내게 말해준다면 <br>꼭 얻어줄게 <br>나를 믿어준다면 <br>생각해볼게 <br>어때 오늘 밤 <br>무르익은 너와 나 <br>함께 하자 모든 걸 <br>다줄테니까 <br>원해 몰래 내 몸을 <br>안아줄때에 <br>스트로베리같은 <br>니 입술을 가질래 <br>넌 날 가져 <br>난 널 가져 <br>넌 날 가져 <br>난 널 가져 <br>]]></content><category term="검정가죽" label="검정가죽"/><category term="가져 (Own Me)" label="가져 (Own Me)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LOPE_로페/omitted/</id><title>LOPE (로페) - omitted - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:34+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:34+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/LOPE_%EB%A1%9C%ED%8E%98/omitted/" title="LOPE (로페) - omitted - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[까맣게 타버린 내 머리 <br>어젠 뭐 말하나 마날걸 <br>두 번 다신 안 보낸다 <br>다짐을 또 해도 이미 넌 없는데 <br>똑같은 매일이 지나가고 <br>허무한 내일은 기다리고 <br>벌써 찾아온 아침이 <br>떠나간 네가 왜 이리 미운지 <br>아까워 넌 you know how I feel <br>아무도 모르게 널 찾아 떠나 <br>어딘지 모르지만 가볼래 나 <br>어두워질 때 끝내 다를 게 없단 걸 <br>누구보다 제일 잘 알아 <br>봤던 네 사진을 다시 꺼내봐 <br>아득하기만 한 너의 품 <br>너의 숨소리가 <br>창살에 삐져나온 햇살처럼 <br>자꾸 나를 찔러 눈이 부셔 <br>네가 없는 난 어둡기만 한데 <br>어딨냐 매일 묻네 <br>답 없는 널 기다린 난 뻔해 <br>어쩔 수 없는 나 부탁해 <br>어차피 너밖에 안 보여 girl <br>까맣게 타버린 내 머리 <br>어젠 뭐 말하나 마날걸 <br>두 번 다신 안 보낸다 <br>다짐을 또 해도 이미 넌 없는데 <br>똑같은 매일이 지나가고 <br>허무한 내일은 기다리고 <br>벌써 찾아온 아침이 <br>떠나간 네가 왜 이리 미운지 <br>아까부터 한참을 울었어 <br>보낼 수밖에 없던 나의 모습 <br>되돌려 보기엔 멀어진 우리 <br>도무지 알 수 없어 <br>나도 왜 너만을 찾아 <br>또 헤매이는지 <br>봤던 네 사진을 다시 꺼내봐 <br>아득하기만 한 너의 품 <br>너의 숨소리가 <br>창살에 삐져나온 햇살처럼 <br>자꾸 나를 찔러 눈이 부셔 <br>네가 없는 난 어둡기만 한데 <br>어딨냐 매일 묻네 <br>답 없는 널 기다린 난 뻔해 <br>어쩔 수 없는 나 부탁해 <br>어차피 너밖엔 안 보여 girl <br>까맣게 타버린 내 머리 <br>어젠 뭐 말하나 마날걸 <br>두 번 다신 안 보낸다 <br>다짐을 또 해도 이미 넌 없는데 <br>똑같은 매일이 지나가고 <br>허무한 내일은 기다리고 <br>벌써 찾아온 아침이 <br>떠나간 네가 왜 이리 미운지 <br>]]></content><category term="LOPE (로페)" label="LOPE (로페)"/><category term="omitted" label="omitted"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/A_Near_Death_Experience/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - A Near Death Experience - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:36+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:36+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/A_Near_Death_Experience/" title="Hellogoodbye - A Near Death Experience - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I must have been unconscious for a while <br>I didn't realize that I nearly died <br>That I nearly died <br>So I came to terms that everything was changed <br>But I tried to touch your hand <br>I could have tried to touch your hand with the passing glass <br><br>You didn't know I felt that way <br>And I just shrugged it off <br>Anyways <br><br>So I hadn't tried I thought if I had died <br>I never would have had a chance to hold you for <br>the first time since I almost died <br><br>You didn't know I felt that way <br>And I just shrugged it off <br>You didn't know I felt that way <br>And I just shrugged it off <br>Anyways <br><br>Ooohh <br><br>You didn't know I felt that way <br>And I just shrugged it off <br>You didn't know I felt that way <br>And I just shrugged it off <br>Anyways x4]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="A Near Death Experience" label="A Near Death Experience"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/Die_Young_Die_Dumb_Not_Soon/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - Die Young, Die Dumb; Not Soon - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:38+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:38+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/Die_Young_Die_Dumb_Not_Soon/" title="Hellogoodbye - Die Young, Die Dumb; Not Soon - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Head down the street <br>by the grace of your feet <br>And you can't comprehend <br>Where in space we will meet <br><br>So you can't explain <br>Every atom in your brain <br><br>Just get into it <br><br>Just waiting for the car to pull around <br>Waiting for your feet to leave the ground <br>Wait until there's nothing left to know <br>Waiting for your heart to start to slow <br>I may not ever really grasp <br>What it is and if it's gonna pass <br>Still I'm sure it's better not to know <br><br>Die young, die dumb, just not soon <br><br>Start turning in <br>At nine thirty or ten <br>It's so hard not to be <br>In the place that you're in <br><br>So you won't escape <br>Get into your early grave <br><br>Just get into it <br><br>Just waiting for the car to pull around <br>Waiting for your feet to leave the ground <br>Wait until there's nothing left to know <br>Waiting for your heart to start to slow <br>I may not ever really grasp <br>What it is and if it's gonna pass <br>Still I'm sure it's better not to know <br><br>Die young, die dumb <br>Die young, die dumb, not soon <br><br>Head down the street <br>By the grace of your feet <br>And you head down the street <br>By the grace of your feet <br>Of your feet <br>Of your feet <br><br>Just waiting for the car to pull around <br>Waiting for your feet to leave the ground <br>Wait until there's nothing left to know <br>Waiting for your heart to start to slow <br>I may not ever really grasp <br>What it is and if it's gonna pass <br>Still I'm sure it's better not to know <br><br>Die young, die dumb <br>Die young, die dumb, not soon <br><br>Die young, not soon <br>Die young, not soon <br>Die young, not soon <br>Die young, not soon]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="Die Young, Die Dumb; Not Soon" label="Die Young, Die Dumb; Not Soon"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/An_External_Force/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - An External Force - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:40+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:40+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/An_External_Force/" title="Hellogoodbye - An External Force - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're waiting for the streetlights to come on <br>I haven't seen your face like this since dawn <br>And all the time I ever thought I knew <br>I realized I never had a clue <br><br>It didn't seem too much at first <br>Certainly it's getting worse <br>you fell this pull oh it's getting tight <br>Suddenly you're feeling light cause <br><br>We're waiting for our pupils to adjust <br>We couldn't tell the stars for all the dust <br>For all the time it takes to get to you <br>Something pulls me in, I've wanted to <br><br>It didn't seem too much at first <br>Certainly it's getting worse <br>You feel this pull oh it's getting tight <br>Suddenly you're feeling light cause <br><br>Something grabs a hold of you and I <br><br>When you became the sea <br>Your tide washed up on me <br>It's just the beginning <br><br>It didn't seem too much at first <br>Certainly it's getting worse <br>You feel this pull oh it's getting tight <br>Suddenly you're feeling light cause <br><br>Something grabs a hold of you and I]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="An External Force" label="An External Force"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/How_Wrong_I_Can_Be/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - How Wrong I Can Be - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:43+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:43+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/How_Wrong_I_Can_Be/" title="Hellogoodbye - How Wrong I Can Be - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And I was afraid <br>I ran so fast I cried I didn't know <br>I would awake in just the nick of time <br>And I could see <br>And I could see your sun in me <br><br>And it was a shove <br>So I shoved right back, you have to understand <br>I was in love and I will try to fight for it <br>And I could see <br>And I could see your sun in me <br><br>I could see just how long I could be your <br>How long it could take to figure out <br><br>Holding you close <br>I danced around for a little while <br>I didn't know I was your heart beat <br><br>And I could see just how long I could be your <br>and how long it could take to figure out <br>And I could see just how long I could be your <br>And how long it could take to figure out]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="How Wrong I Can Be" label="How Wrong I Can Be"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/I_Dont_Worry_As_Much_As_I_Should/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - I Don`t Worry (As Much As I Should) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:45+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:45+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/I_Dont_Worry_As_Much_As_I_Should/" title="Hellogoodbye - I Don`t Worry (As Much As I Should) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How do I never worry half as much as I know that I should <br>And how did I get so far on such dumb luck when I thought I was good <br>How do I want so bad to bring about the future that I'm tearing off the sutures halfway through <br>And every time I build it up some more <br>You <br><br>And all I do is hold on to it <br>And all I do is hold on to you <br>To you <br>To you <br>To you <br><br>How did I forget how much it meant when you were there when I woke up <br>And how did I forget for just a moment how much meaning I bestole upon that fleeting little hope <br><br>And every time I build it up some more <br>You <br><br>And all I do is hold on to it <br>And all I do is hold on to you <br>To you <br>To you <br>To you <br><br>To you <br>To you <br><br>To you <br>To you <br><br>And all I do is hold on to it <br>And all I do is hold on to it <br>And all I do is hold on to it <br>And all I do is hold on to you]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="I Don`t Worry (As Much As I Should)" label="I Don`t Worry (As Much As I Should)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/Just_Dont_Let_Go_Just_Dont/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - Just Don`t Let Go Just Don`t - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:47+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:47+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/Just_Dont_Let_Go_Just_Dont/" title="Hellogoodbye - Just Don`t Let Go Just Don`t - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you wanna know <br>I've always tried to take it slow <br>Never let you go <br>I'm always chasing after your rope <br><br>Afraid you didn't know I would be <br>At the end of it <br>And I won't let you go <br>At the end of it <br>So just don't let go <br><br>At the end of it <br>You didn't know I would be <br>At the end of it <br>So just don't let go, just don't <br><br>If you wanna go <br>I would take you there, I hope you know <br>Is it getting cold <br>If you're staying in I wouldn't dare go <br>Out anymore <br><br>If you trace the thread <br>You will find a knot inside my head <br>Barely moves an inch <br>Guess it's not a very present issue <br>Please, just don't let go <br><br>At the end of it <br>You didn't know I would be <br>At the end of it <br>So just don't let go, just don't <br>So just don't let go, just don't <br><br>If you wanna go <br>I would take you there, I hope you know <br>Never let you go <br>So just don't let go <br><br>At the end of it <br>You didn't know I would be <br>At the end of it <br>So just don't let go, just don't <br>So just don't let go <br>So just don't let go <br><br>And I won't let you go]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="Just Don`t Let Go Just Don`t" label="Just Don`t Let Go Just Don`t"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/Summer_Of_The_Lily_Pond/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - Summer Of The Lily Pond - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:49+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:49+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/Summer_Of_The_Lily_Pond/" title="Hellogoodbye - Summer Of The Lily Pond - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Summer of the lily pond how long I didn't know <br>Halfway there your golden hair <br>It just started to show <br>The way things tend to grow <br>It started out so slow <br><br>I guess I just don't understand <br>How a good thing becomes bad <br>Oh and I just wanted it to be <br>What I wanted it to be <br>Well I was wrong about it then <br><br>The summer of the shrug it off <br>A song you didn't know <br>The lilies spread around your head <br>It's so hard to see it so <br>The way things tend to grow <br>It got all out of control <br><br>I guess you just don't understand <br>How a good thing becomes bad <br>Oh and you just wanted it to be <br>What you wanted it to be <br><br>I guess you just don't understand <br>How you held it in your hands <br>Oh and you wouldn't set it free <br>Yeah you couldn't let it be <br><br>You were wrong about it then <br>And I hope you're not again <br>Soon <br><br>And I was wrong about Downton <br>I was wrong about how one should view the world <br>How should I find the confidence <br>In a thought, I've been wrong before <br><br>And I was wrong about that again <br>And I was wrong about how long one should wait <br>How should I find the confidence <br>Then I thought <br>I'd been right before <br><br>I was wrong that I've been right before <br>I was wrong about it then <br><br>I was wrong about it then <br>Now I won't be wrong again <br>Soon]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="Summer Of The Lily Pond" label="Summer Of The Lily Pond"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/Swear_Youre_In_Love/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - Swear You`re In Love - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:51+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:51+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/Swear_Youre_In_Love/" title="Hellogoodbye - Swear You`re In Love - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[No, I never meant to be vague <br>There's just this thing <br>No, I don't know how to explain, what I mean by thing <br>Oh we could be down on Willow street <br>For a midnight drink, water down prestige <br>Somehow you've got to lean into <br>Oh, I need you to <br>I need you to <br><br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br><br>Oh, if your heart was starting to pound <br>Then I couldn't tell <br>No, my love is less like a sound <br>and more like a well <br><br>We could be down your Father's street <br>Down in memory for eternity <br>Somehow you've got to read into <br>Oh, I need you to <br>I need you to <br><br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br><br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br><br>If you're in love, swear you're in love <br>If you're in love, swear you're in love]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="Swear You`re In Love" label="Swear You`re In Love"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/The_Magic_Hour_Is_Now/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - The Magic Hour Is Now - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/The_Magic_Hour_Is_Now/" title="Hellogoodbye - The Magic Hour Is Now - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I need to see the sunset <br>So I can give my eyes the sense that <br>Something in the world will end <br>Nothing ever ends <br><br>I want to feel infinite <br>But I don't think my heart's that in it <br>I just want to remain in love <br>Like everybody does <br><br>The thing about the sun is that <br>It's going to set and rise again <br>Over you <br><br>Every time you run away it gets closer <br>You can't escape it's raw power <br>It's coming up <br>The magic hour is now <br><br>I want to feel infinite <br>But I don't think my heart's that in it <br>I just wanna remain in love <br>Like everybody does <br><br>I wanna be your lover <br>I'll never ever touch another <br>I just wanted to see the dawn <br>We'll watch it from the lawn <br><br>The thing about your love is that <br>It's gonna let some sun light in <br>Just for you <br><br>Every time you run away it gets closer <br>You can't escape it's raw power <br>It's coming up <br>The magic hour is now <br>The magic hour is now <br><br>The magic hour is now <br>You cannot slow it down <br>The magic hour is now <br>The magic hour is now <br>You cannot slow it down <br>The magic hour is now <br><br>Every time you run away it gets closer <br>You can't escape it's raw power <br>It's coming up <br>The magic hour is now <br>The magic hour is now <br>The magic hour is now <br>The magic hour is now <br>The magic hour is now <br>The magic hour is now <br>The magic hour is now]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="The Magic Hour Is Now" label="The Magic Hour Is Now"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/Everything_Is_Debatable/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - (Everything Is) Debatable - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:56+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:56+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/Everything_Is_Debatable/" title="Hellogoodbye - (Everything Is) Debatable - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I was frozen there <br>Paralyzed and floating in the air <br>Or I thought <br>Cause no one really knows <br>I couldn't stop <br><br>So I wanted her <br>To feel the breeze <br>Just blowing through the trees <br>A ghost <br>Of something in our love we don't yet know <br><br>It's such an arbitrary line that we dance <br>We waited centuries to throw up our hands <br>It's such an arbitrary line that we dance <br>We dance we dance <br>Oh everything is debatable <br>everything is debatable <br><br>So I waited there <br>Burdened by some things I shouldn't have <br>Cared about <br>I brushed them off <br>And dug my heart back out <br><br>It's such an arbitrary line that we dance <br>We waited centuries to throw up our hands <br>It's such an arbitrary line that we dance <br>We dance we dance <br>Oh everything is debatable <br>everything is debatable <br><br>I seem kinda strange <br>I saw the other side <br>Floating around in the room <br>I realized <br>You thought I'd look the same <br>Despite some flashing lights <br>Floating around over you <br><br>It's such an arbitrary line that we dance <br>We waited centuries to throw up our hands <br>It's such an arbitrary line that we dance <br>We dance we dance <br>Oh everything is debatable <br>I saw the other side <br>The other side and beyond, oh <br>Everything is debatable <br>Everything is debatable <br><br>Everything is debatable <br>Debatable <br>Everything is]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="(Everything Is) Debatable" label="(Everything Is) Debatable"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/And_Everything_Becomes_A_Blur/</id><title>Hellogoodbye - And Everything Becomes A Blur - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:50:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:50:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Hellogoodbye/And_Everything_Becomes_A_Blur/" title="Hellogoodbye - And Everything Becomes A Blur - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Of all the friends you made along the way <br>Every single one will pass away <br>And everything they are, never were <br>And somehow all of it become a blur <br><br>All the friends you made along the way <br>Every single one is here to stay <br>Everything we've done gets to you <br>And somehow some of it returns to you <br><br>You floated by like waves of light <br>I saw you there in flats and tights <br>I didn't know you move that fast <br>No one ever did <br>Nobody every did <br>Nobody every did <br><br>All we feel disintegrates <br>Just keep your feet into the lake <br><br>Oh what a pretty tragedy <br>To be alive is anything I really want to be all the time <br>Cause everything you are is so much more <br>Than anything you were an hour before <br><br>You floated by like waves of light <br>I saw you there in flats and tights <br>I didn't know you move that fast <br>No one ever did <br>But nobody every did <br>But nobody every did <br>No <br><br>All we feel disintegrates <br>Just keep your feet into the lake <br>If all we feel disintegrates <br>Don't dig your heels into the pavement <br><br>All the friends you made along the way <br>Every single one is here to stay]]></content><category term="Hellogoodbye" label="Hellogoodbye"/><category term="And Everything Becomes A Blur" label="And Everything Becomes A Blur"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/If_I_Knew/</id><title>Every Avenue - If I Knew - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/If_I_Knew/" title="Every Avenue - If I Knew - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Couldn't believe it when I heard it <br>It was enough to make a heartbeat stop <br>Reminded me of the uncertain and love that we've lost <br>I know I took our hearts for granted <br>I never thought the sun would fail to rise <br>How am I to understand this all on my own <br><br>If I knew it'd be the last time <br>Id try a little harder <br>Make that goodbye last a little longer <br>Woulda held you just a little stronger <br>If I, I knew it'd be the last time <br><br>You know you never see it coming <br>Time always finds a way to pass us by <br>But I still feel you all around me when I close my eyes <br><br>All the flowers on the side walk and every single tear that we cried <br>How I wish that I could change it and bring you back tonight <br><br>If I knew it'd be the last time <br>Id try a little harder <br>Make that goodbye last a little longer <br>Woulda held you just a little stronger <br>If I, I knew it'd be the last time <br><br>So Lauren lay your head down <br>I'll be right beside you <br>So Lauren close your eyes now <br>I'll be right behind you <br>Couldn't believe it when I heard it <br>It was enough to make a heartbeat stop <br><br>If I knew it'd be the last time <br>Id try a little harder <br>Make that goodbye last a little longer <br>Woulda held you just a little stronger <br>If I, I knew it'd be the last time <br>Id try a little harder <br>Make that goodbye last a little longer <br>Woulda held you just a little stronger <br>If I knew, I knew it'd be the last time]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="If I Knew" label="If I Knew"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Watch_The_World/</id><title>Every Avenue - Watch The World - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:02+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:02+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Watch_The_World/" title="Every Avenue - Watch The World - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're too young to figure out how <br>Forget to breathe once in a while <br>Fade out, no sound <br>The white lines are slower now <br>Face up, run back <br><br>Chase it down, spin around <br>Watch the world from the ground <br>The crush and burn leaves us dry <br>Picks us up, back to life <br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh <br>Watch the world <br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh <br>Watch the world <br><br>In the darkness it all comes out <br>In the moment it all makes sense <br>Fade out, no sound <br>The white lines are faster now <br>Face up, run back <br><br>Chase it down, spin around <br>Watch the world from the ground <br>The crush and burn leaves us dry <br>Picks us up, back to life <br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh <br>Watch the world <br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh <br>Watch the world <br><br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh, ooh, oh, ooh <br><br>Chase it down, spin around <br>Watch the world from the ground <br>The crush and burn leaves us dry <br>Picks us up back to life <br><br>Chase it down, spin around <br>Watch the world from the ground <br>The crush and burn leaves us dry <br>Picks us up, back to life <br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh <br>Watch the world <br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh <br>Watch the world <br>Yeah, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah <br><br>Chase it down oh oh <br>Spin around oh oh <br>Watch the world oh oh <br>Watch the world <br>The crush and burn oh oh <br>Leaves us dry oh oh <br>Picks us up oh oh <br>Watch the world <br><br>Oh oh, oh oh, oh oh <br>Watch the world oh, oh, oh <br>Yeah, yeah <br>Yeah, yeah]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="Watch The World" label="Watch The World"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/I_Cant_Not_Love_You/</id><title>Every Avenue - I Can`t Not Love You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:04+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:04+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/I_Cant_Not_Love_You/" title="Every Avenue - I Can`t Not Love You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It feels like I'm up on a wire <br>And you just keep lifting it higher <br>I'm right on the edge <br>And I'm doing my best not to fall <br><br>It feels like the world's spinning faster <br>Towards a beautiful perfect disaster <br>The moment you kissed me <br>I knew I was risking it all <br><br>The further I run from you baby <br>The closer I get to the truth <br>And I feel like nothing can save me <br>It's something I just can't undo <br>Cause I can't not love you <br><br>I'm bracing myself for collision <br>In the back seat of my heart's decision <br>I'm rounding the curb <br>And I don't have the nerve to say no <br><br>The further I run from you baby <br>The closer I get to the truth <br>And I feel like nothing can save me <br>It's something I just can't undo <br>Cause I can't not love you <br>Yeah, ooh, ooh <br>Yeah <br><br>The further I run from you baby <br>The closer I get to the truth <br>And I feel like nothing can save me <br>It's something I just can't undo <br>Cause I can't not love you <br>Yeah <br>But baby, baby I can't <br>I can't not love you baby <br>I can't not]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="I Can`t Not Love You" label="I Can`t Not Love You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Hit_Me_Where_It_Hurts_The_Most/</id><title>Every Avenue - Hit Me Where It Hurts The Most - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:07+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:07+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Hit_Me_Where_It_Hurts_The_Most/" title="Every Avenue - Hit Me Where It Hurts The Most - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You got me going crazy <br>Running around in circles lately <br>I can't deny it, I kinda like it <br>I'm wound up tighter than your jeans fit <br>You got me lit up like a cigarette <br><br>Hit me where it hurts the most <br>Break me down to the bone <br>You wouldn't be the first <br>It can't get any worse <br>Just hit me where it hurts the most <br><br>I taste it all over your lips <br>You know all my little secrets <br>I'm a fool to play your little mind games <br>I'm tying knots over a chair with three legs <br>You keep me hanging by a little thread <br><br>Hit me where it hurts the most <br>Break me down to the bone <br>You wouldn't be the first <br>It can't get any worse <br>Just hit me where it hurts the most <br><br>You got me on my knees Most <br>Why don't you set me free <br>You got me lit up like a cigarette <br><br>Hit me where it hurts the most <br>Break me down to the bone <br>You wouldn't be the first <br>It can't get any worse <br>Just hit me where it hurts the most <br><br>Hit me where it hurts the most <br>Break me down to the bone <br>You wouldn't be the first <br>It can't get any worse <br>Just hit me where it hurts]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="Hit Me Where It Hurts The Most" label="Hit Me Where It Hurts The Most"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Someday_Somehow/</id><title>Every Avenue - Someday, Somehow - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:09+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:09+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Someday_Somehow/" title="Every Avenue - Someday, Somehow - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Headlights burning on the interstate pavement <br>I take a slow drag and my mind slips away <br>Away, away <br><br>It's a long night down the 95 <br>Trying to beat the sunrise <br>Staying up all night <br>I'm not sleeping till I cross the state line <br><br>Someday, somehow <br>I'll make it home and I, I'll stick around <br>One day I'll say <br>No more packing up <br>I'm settling down <br>Someday, someday I'll figure it out <br>Someday, somehow <br><br>High school sweetheart serving <br>Broken spirits at the local bar <br>First love with a new last name, yeah <br>Next stop, my old home <br>It's got a new front porch <br>Where flowers used to grow <br>Everybody has something to show <br>I've got a thousand different stories <br>And nothing to hold <br><br>Someday, somehow <br>I'll make it home and I, I'll stick around <br>One day I'll say <br>No more packing up <br>I'm settling down <br>Someday, someday I'll figure it out <br>Someday, somehow <br><br>No more birthdays from the telephone <br>No more holidays spent alone <br>No more asking when I'm coming home <br>I, I, I'm sticking around <br>Yeah <br><br>Someday, somehow <br>I'll make it home and I, I'll stick around <br>One day I'll say <br>No more packing up <br>I'm settling down <br>Someday, someday I'll figure it out <br>Someday, somehow <br>Someday, somehow <br>Someday, somehow]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="Someday, Somehow" label="Someday, Somehow"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Only_Place_I_Call_Home/</id><title>Every Avenue - Only Place I Call Home - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Only_Place_I_Call_Home/" title="Every Avenue - Only Place I Call Home - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Leaving your tears on my shoulder <br>Your eyes beg me to stay <br>We were finally changing <br>It's our luck, we're a little too late <br>I'd take you with me if there was a way <br>Sorry, don't cut it so I say <br><br>Take all of your doubts <br>You can throw 'em out <br>You may be unsure, but I know <br>I'm always coming back <br>You can bet on that <br>You're the only place I call home <br>Near or far, where you are is where I want to be <br>Every lonely night <br>Every drunken fight <br>Couldn't make it right, I know <br>If it hurts you bad <br>Put it on my tab <br>I can pay it back tenfold <br>You're the only place I've ever called my home <br><br>Years pass, we're growing older <br>And you're not sure you can wait <br>So I promise, it won't always be like this <br>You say, It's always the same <br>We're falling apart if you think so <br>I'm holding on even if you let go <br><br>Take all of your doubts <br>You can throw 'em out <br>You may be unsure, but I know <br>I'm always coming back <br>You can bet on that <br>You're the only place I call home <br>Near or far, where you are is where I want to be <br>Every lonely night <br>Every drunken fight <br>Couldn't make it right, I know <br>If it hurts you bad <br>Put it on my tab <br>I can pay it back tenfold <br>You're the only place I've ever called my home <br><br>If I had my way <br>You'd fill these empty beds <br>Someday I'll come back for you <br>And never leave again <br><br>Take all of your doubts <br>You can throw 'em out <br>You may be unsure, but I know <br>I'm always coming back <br>You can bet on that <br>You're the only place I call home <br>Near or far, where you are is where I want to be <br>Every lonely night <br>Every drunken fight <br>Couldn't make it right, I know <br>If it hurts you bad <br>Put it on my tab <br>I can pay it back tenfold <br>You're the only place I've ever called my home]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="Only Place I Call Home" label="Only Place I Call Home"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/No_One_But_You/</id><title>Every Avenue - No One But You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/No_One_But_You/" title="Every Avenue - No One But You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Tonight, you're mine <br>I wanna shake it <br>Your eyes can't lie <br>No you can't fake it <br><br>Tonight, you're mine <br>I wanna shake it <br>Your eyes can't lie <br>No you can't fake it <br><br>This is everything that I wanted tonight <br><br>So come on, whoa <br>I've got no one, whoa <br>No one but you <br>Yeah whoa <br>Yeah, I've got no one I've got no one <br>No one but you <br><br>I want your heart <br>So I can break it <br>I want to be inside your web <br>With no escaping <br><br>This is everything that I wanted tonight <br><br>Yeah <br><br>So come on, whoa <br>I've got no one, whoa <br>No one but you <br>Yeah whoa <br>Yeah, I've got no one I've got no one <br><br>Don't stop, we're just gettin' started <br>Don't talk, I know you want it <br>I'm gonna get what I want <br>You get what you want <br>We're just gettin' started <br><br>Don't stop, we're just gettin' started <br>Don't talk, I know you want it <br>I'm gonna get what I want <br>You get what you want <br>We're just gettin' started <br><br>So come on, whoa <br>I've got no one, whoa <br>No one but you no one but you <br>Whoa, yeah I've got no one I've got no one <br>I've got no one <br>I've got no one yeah <br>No one but you]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="No One But You" label="No One But You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Fall_Apart/</id><title>Every Avenue - Fall Apart - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Fall_Apart/" title="Every Avenue - Fall Apart - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Electrified, we burn all night <br>Paralyzed by black and white <br>But who are you, and who am I <br>Electrified, we burn all night <br><br>I want you to fall apart like I did <br>You to hurt for all of this <br>All the pain you put me through <br>I wanna hear you say <br>I don't deserve you <br>Fall apart like I did <br>You to hurt for all of this <br>All the pain you put me through <br>I wanna hear you say <br>I don't deserve you <br>Fall apart <br><br>Terrified by waking eyes <br>The empty space you left behind <br>But who are you, and who I am <br>Terrified by waking eyes <br><br>I want you to fall apart like I did <br>You to hurt for all of this <br>All the pain you put me through <br>I wanna hear you say <br>I don't deserve you <br>Fall apart like I did <br>You to hurt for all of this <br>All the pain you put me through <br>I wanna hear you say <br>I don't deserve you <br>Fall apart <br><br>Oh oh oh, ohhh oh <br>Oh oh oh, ohhh oh <br><br>Electrified, we burn all night <br><br>I want you to fall apart like I did <br>You to hurt for all of this <br>All the pain you put me through <br>I wanna hear you say <br>I don't deserve you <br>Fall apart like I did <br>You to hurt for all of this <br>All the pain you put me through <br>I wanna hear you say <br>I don't deserve you <br><br>Electrified, we burn all night]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="Fall Apart" label="Fall Apart"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/There_Tonight/</id><title>Every Avenue - There Tonight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:18+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:18+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/There_Tonight/" title="Every Avenue - There Tonight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The city lights are burning bright on that big Hollywood sign <br>You're probably sleeping in your east coast time <br>Man, what I'd give just to be there tonight <br><br>And I hear people getting high in the next room <br>Talking about life and how we don't have a clue <br><br>I used to dream of making it in this town <br>Now I'm dreaming of making it out <br><br>I'm sick of waking up alone <br>Cause I can't be home <br>All this pain from missing you <br>It's just too strong <br>All I want is just to be there with you <br>Baby, it's true <br>I'd give it all up for you <br>It's the least I could do <br><br>Another night I spend drinking with myself <br>And counting the channels in this rundown hotel <br>I just hide it, all the pain so no one knows <br>I'm talking to myself everywhere I go Everywhere I go <br><br>I used to say that I would never go back <br>And now I swear I'll never get the chance <br><br>I'm sick of waking up alone <br>Cause I can't be home <br>All this pain from missing you <br>It's just too strong <br>All I want is just to be there with you <br>Baby, it's true <br>I'd give it all up for you <br>It's the least I could do <br><br>The hardest part is <br>I could never give you what you needed <br>But just so you know <br>A part of you will always be right here with me <br><br>Waking up alone <br>Cause I can't be home <br>And all this pain from missing you <br>It's just too strong <br>All I want is just to be there with you <br>Baby, it's true, Baby, it's true <br>I'd give it all up for you <br>It's the least I could do]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="There Tonight" label="There Tonight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Whatever_Happened_To_You/</id><title>Every Avenue - Whatever Happened To You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Whatever_Happened_To_You/" title="Every Avenue - Whatever Happened To You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You got your new pills, some kind of cheap thrills <br>we use to bet who'd be the first one to make it out <br><br>You got your rat race, i got my goose chase <br>were running circles round the same thing, aren't we now <br><br>But time will never wait <br>I learned the hard way <br>cause I don't recognize <br>the face in front of me <br><br>I am the same as I was when I was younger <br>whatever happened to you <br>I'll never change with the lines on my face <br>I'm still the person you knew <br>whatever happened to you <br><br>You know you had a chance <br>the world in your hands <br>you could have had it all <br>if you'd have got your shit straight <br><br>You're off the deep end, and all your old friends <br>Are sick of drowning in your sorrows Listen now <br>We fought the same fight, and i stood by your side <br>but I can't stick around and watch you crumble <br><br>Time will never wait ill learn the hard way <br>cuz I won't recognize the face in front of me <br><br>I am the same as I was when I was younger <br>whatever happened to you <br>I'll never change with the lines on my face <br>I'm still the person you knew <br>whatever happened to you <br><br>I am the same as I was when I was younger <br><br>I am the same as I was when I was younger <br>whatever happened to you <br>I'll never change with the lines on my face <br>I'm still the same person you knew <br>whatever happened to you]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="Whatever Happened To You" label="Whatever Happened To You"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Tie_Me_Down/</id><title>Every Avenue - Tie Me Down - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Every_Avenue/Tie_Me_Down/" title="Every Avenue - Tie Me Down - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Looking around for more excuses <br>Spinning my head around again <br>I'm getting use to feeling useless <br>Pacing the cage you keep me in <br><br>I'll be here in pieces <br>When you finally pull the pin <br>And blow me away again <br><br>Tie me down and fuck me up tonight <br>Rip my heart out <br>Hurt me good before you say goodbye <br>Lets do this right now <br>Lead me on to get you off <br>And watch me come undone <br>Tie me down and fuck me up baby <br>Rip my heart out <br><br>You told me boy don't get addicted <br>I'm like a drug that's hard to find <br>You hit a vein and I can't kick it <br>I wanna be on you all the time <br><br>I'll be here in pieces <br>When you finally pull the pin <br>And blow me away again <br><br>Tie me down and fuck me up tonight <br>Rip my heart out <br>Hurt me good before you say goodbye <br>Lets do this right now <br>Lead me on to get you off <br>And watch me come undone <br>Tie me down and fuck me up baby <br>Rip My heart out, out <br><br>Keep on going down <br>You hold me there and then <br>You just spit me out <br>Why do I do this to myself <br><br>Tie me down and fuck me up baby <br>Rip my heart out <br>Hurt me good before you say goodbye <br>Lets do this right now <br>Lead me on to get you off <br>And watch me come undone <br>Tie me down and fuck me up baby <br>Rip my heart out]]></content><category term="Every Avenue" label="Every Avenue"/><category term="Tie Me Down" label="Tie Me Down"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Smoke_Monster/</id><title>The Word Alive - Smoke Monster - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Smoke_Monster/" title="The Word Alive - Smoke Monster - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[The storm is coming, run <br>It will swallow you whole <br>And crush your soul <br><br>Tell me what you feel right now <br>You can't escape <br>It's the end of this town <br>Tell me what you feel right now <br>You can't escape <br>It's the end of this town <br><br>It will swallow you whole <br>Run for your life <br>It will swallow you whole <br><br>You could never be replaced <br><br>It was hard to see you go away <br>I can't save you, I couldn't save you <br>I couldn't save <br>I couldn't save anyone <br>Fear for your life, fear for the ending <br><br>It was hard to see you go away <br>I can't save you, I couldn't save you <br>I couldn't save <br>I couldn't save anyone <br>Fear for your life, fear for the ending <br><br>I'm ready to die <br>The wave is crashing around me <br>Your soul leaves your body <br><br>I know you couldn't make it home tonight <br>For fear we come spilling this <br>All there is will never be again <br><br>You could never be replaced <br><br>It was hard to see you go away <br>I can't save you, I couldn't save you <br>I couldn't save <br>I couldn't save anyone <br>Fear for your life, fear for the ending <br><br>It was hard to see you go away <br>I can't save you, I couldn't save you <br>I couldn't save <br>I couldn't save anyone <br>Fear for your life, fear for the ending <br><br>I'm not the one <br>Who will lie in this casket <br>This prison was built for you <br>This prison was built for you <br>You'll be consumed when they crush you <br><br>You could never be replaced <br><br>It was hard to see you go away <br>I can't save you, I couldn't save you <br>I couldn't save <br>I couldn't save anyone <br>Fear for your life, fear for the ending <br><br>It was hard to see you go away <br>I can't save you, I couldn't save you <br>I couldn't save <br>I couldn't save anyone <br>Fear for your life, fear for the ending <br><br>You'll be washed away Away]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Smoke Monster" label="Smoke Monster"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Astral_Plane/</id><title>The Word Alive - Astral Plane - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Astral_Plane/" title="The Word Alive - Astral Plane - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[And I have been here before <br>I don't understand how I've returned <br>I have seen where this takes me <br>I didn't choose this path <br><br>Take me home <br>I've found the road <br><br>Take me home <br>Take me home <br>I've found my home <br><br>Take me to a better place <br>Where I'm who I was born to be <br>This wasn't what I envisioned <br>I'm not who I know I'm Supposed to be <br><br>I've searched and searched, I've laid awake at night <br>I've walked through the darkness <br>I've ran to the light <br>I've ran to the light <br><br>And there was nothing there but questions I had <br>With answers I couldn't find <br>Have I lost my mind <br>Is this all there is left to life <br>Is this all there is <br>Is this it <br>Is this all there is left to life <br><br>Take me home]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Astral Plane" label="Astral Plane"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Room_126/</id><title>The Word Alive - Room 126 - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:29+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:29+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Room_126/" title="The Word Alive - Room 126 - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[There's no sign we'll survive <br>There's no sign we'll survive <br>Let me out <br>They've trapped me here and I'll waste away <br>While you figure this out <br>This room won't hold for long <br><br>The world that we knew has come and gone <br>If we can't win, this will be the end <br>The world that we knew has come and gone <br>If we can't win, this will be the end <br><br>I never knew, I never knew that this could happen to me <br>I never wanted this <br>That something I read about was more than a story <br>I can feel this taking a hold of me <br>Will we survive <br>If we stop this now, there's a chance to break away <br><br>This is our chance to break away <br>Break away <br>This is our chance to break away <br><br>Break away <br><br>They keep circling around and round these walls <br>Their faces are cold and lifeless <br>As they stare back at me <br>Their only thought is to devour me <br><br>This is our chance, can we escape <br>I never knew <br><br>I never knew, I never knew that this could happen to me <br>I never wanted this <br>That something I read about was more than a story <br>I can feel this taking a hold of me <br>Will we survive <br>If we stop this now, there's a chance to break away <br><br>I've never felt the fear of death, until it reached out for me <br>I've never felt the fear of death <br>I've never felt the fear, the fear of death <br><br>I never thought that this could happen <br>That something I read was more than a story <br><br>I can feel this taking a hold of me <br>Will we survive <br>If we stop this now, there's a chance to break away <br>There's a chance to break away <br>There's a chance to break away <br>There's a chance to break, to break away <br><br>I never felt the fear of death]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Room 126" label="Room 126"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Belong/</id><title>The Word Alive - Belong - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Belong/" title="The Word Alive - Belong - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I just want to belong <br>I just want to belong <br>I just want to belong <br><br>I've been searching for far too long <br>When I feel I've reached my destination <br>I can't control these feelings <br>I just wanna stop reaching <br><br>Illuminate the path before me <br>So I can finally find my way <br>I've been dying to stop wandering <br>I just want to know my place <br><br>Don't we all just want to belong <br>I don't know if I'm strong enough <br>We'll find a better way <br>I just want to belong <br>Don't we all just want to belong <br>I don't know if I'm strong enough <br><br>Everyday I begin to hate this more <br>Clinging on to a world so worn <br>I know this feeling is feeling to familiar <br>Cary on <br><br>Do you know when you've seen it all <br>The world around you doesn't make sense at all <br>You got lost in your progress <br><br>Illuminate the path before me <br>So I can finally find my way <br>I've been dying to stop wandering <br>I just want to know my place <br><br>Don't we all just want to belong <br>I don't know if I'm strong enough <br>We'll find a better way <br>I just want to belong <br>Don't we all just want to belong <br>I don't know if I'm strong enough <br><br>Here we go here we go, let's take this life <br>And lets start living <br>Here we go here we go, let's take this life <br>And lets start living <br>Here we go <br>Let's take this life, let's start living <br>start living <br>Let's take this life, let's start living <br>start living <br><br>Don't we all just want to belong <br>I don't know if I'm strong enough <br>We'll find a better way <br>I just want to belong <br>Don't we all just want to belong <br>I don't know if I'm strong enough <br>We'll find a better way <br>I just want to belong <br>I've searched for far too long <br>I can't control these feelings <br>I found my destination <br>I need to stop reaching <br>Don't we all just want to belong <br>I don't know if I'm strong enough]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Belong" label="Belong"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Live_A_Lie/</id><title>The Word Alive - Live A Lie - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Live_A_Lie/" title="The Word Alive - Live A Lie - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I won't live a lie, I don't hide <br>I don't hide <br>I won't let you pull me down <br>I'll be who I am and I will, I will live <br>I'm alive <br><br>If you think I'll break because you think I'm the same <br>I won't live a lie, I won't live a lie <br>You can't keep me this way, I will escape <br>I won't live a lie, I won't live a lie <br>Fear will never conquer me <br>It will guide my way <br>I welcome this day <br>Welcome me this way <br>Fear will never overcome me <br><br>Finally, you begin to see, I was built to be more <br>Never will I settle for your worth <br>You can't trust what you know, this is just the beginning <br>I'm right here You can't deter me <br>I'm right here You can't escape me <br>I'm right here <br>You'll never find your way out <br><br>This is me <br>This is me <br><br>If you think I'll break because you think I'm the same <br>I won't live a lie, I won't live a lie <br>You can't keep me this way, I will escape <br>I won't live a lie, I won't live a lie <br>Fear will never conquer me <br>It will guide my way <br>I welcome this day <br>Welcome me this way <br>Fear will never overcome me <br><br>So many times <br>I've laid by the wayside <br>While I let them tear at me <br>It's my time to believe <br>If you ever believed in something <br>It's time you believed in me <br><br>If you think I'll break because you think I'm the same <br><br>If you think I'll break because you think I'm the same <br>I wont live a lie, I won't live a lie <br>You can't keep me this way, I will escape <br>I won't live a lie, I won't live a lie <br>Fear will never conquer me, it will guide my way <br>I welcome this day Welcome me this way <br>It will never overcome me <br><br>I won't let anything come before me <br>This is who I am, I am alive]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Live A Lie" label="Live A Lie"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Ambitionary/</id><title>The Word Alive - Ambitionary - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Ambitionary/" title="The Word Alive - Ambitionary - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[How much further must I go before <br>I can't escape my past <br>Oh <br>I wish I could have lived, without regrets <br>But I made, my mistakes so many times <br><br>Where do you go when the darkness finds you <br>All I want is to see better days <br>And have my past washed away <br>All I want is better days <br><br>But where do I go But where do I go <br>I need a place to call my own <br>Where we can we find hope Where can we find hope <br>I need you to show me the road <br><br>Life shouldn't be this hard, not a reminder of <br>Of how much you've failed <br>Remind yourself you've come this far, you've come so far <br>Remind yourself you've come this far, you've come so far <br><br>But where do I go But where do I go <br>I need a place to call my own <br>Where can we find hope Where can we find hope <br>I need you to show me the road <br><br>But where do I go But where do I go <br>I need a place to call my own <br>Where can we find hope Where can we find hope <br>I need you to show me the road <br><br>Why wasted this for me <br>Show me where to go <br>Show me anything, give me everything <br>Show me where to go <br>Show me anything, give me everything <br><br>I keep waiting more and more <br>But I can't see, Can't start alone <br><br>But where do I go But where do I go <br><br>But where do I go But where do I go <br>I need a place to call my own <br>Where can we find hope Where can we find hope <br>I need you to show me the road <br><br>But where do I go But where do I go <br>I need a place to call my own <br>Where can we find hope Where can we find hope <br>I need you to show me the road <br><br>Wanted you to show me the road]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Ambitionary" label="Ambitionary"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Hidden_Lakes/</id><title>The Word Alive - Hidden Lakes - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Hidden_Lakes/" title="The Word Alive - Hidden Lakes - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You may not make it home tonight <br>You may not last another fight <br>You may not make it home tonight <br>When you meet your end, walk towards the light <br>Walk towards the light <br><br>Together, together we'll always be <br>In life and death I will always have peace <br>I believe you're here with me <br>You're here with me <br>Knowing you found the way before the end <br>Has allowed me to live <br><br>Sometimes, you'll think of me and say I miss you <br>The stories you'd tell me <br>You'll wish we had more time, you got to say goodbye <br>Don't forget don't forget what I told you <br>You gotta live gotta live like I showed you <br>I'm proud of who you are <br>And it's not too late <br>It's not too late <br><br>Sometimes I wonder if you're looking down <br>Have I strayed too far because I'm longing <br>To find the truth I've always known, show the way <br>The way to you <br>I have so much I need to say <br>What would you say <br>Knowing you found the way before the end <br>Has enabled me to live <br><br>Sometimes, you'll think of me and say I miss you, the stories you'd tell me <br>You'll wish we had more time, you got to say goodbye <br>Don't forget don't forget what I told you <br>You gotta live gotta live like I showed you <br>I'm proud of who you are <br>And it's not too late <br>It's not too late <br><br>If you're still there, pick me up, empower me <br>To stand alone, I'm coming home <br>I wonder if you'll be there <br><br>I miss you <br>I wonder if you're listening, watching <br>Your memory will will never fade <br>You'll live in me <br>You'll live through me <br>You'll live through me <br><br>Sometimes, you'll think of me and say I miss you, the stories you'd tell me <br>You'll wish we had more time, you got to say goodbye <br>Don't forget Don't forget what I told you <br>You gotta live gotta live like I showed you <br>I'm proud of who you are <br>And it's not too late <br>It's not too late <br>It's not too late <br>It's not too late]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Hidden Lakes" label="Hidden Lakes"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Evolution/</id><title>The Word Alive - Evolution - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:39+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:39+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Evolution/" title="The Word Alive - Evolution - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm back for more <br>This stories heading for its final twist <br>ready for its final twist <br>I finally see what it means to cut you out <br>From the peace I lived without <br><br>I tried to see this through, so many times before <br>But you've always had a way of reeling me back, back for more <br><br>Back for more, of your fucking deceiving eyes <br>I can't describe how much I despised my life <br>I can't explain how much I wish you'd fucking die <br>Wished you'd fucking die <br><br>I want to know what you're thinking <br>When you find yourself alone <br>Do you even know what it means to be loved <br><br>I'm back for more <br>I wanna tear you apart <br>I wanna see you fall to the floor <br>I wanna watch as you reach out your hand for mercy <br>And then you'll finally breathe no more <br>Breathe no more <br><br>Tell me what the hell were you thinking <br>Realize at best you're disgusting <br><br>I want to know what you're thinking <br>When you find yourself alone <br>Do you even know what it means to be loved <br>I never thought that I'd find a way to say to you <br>I couldn't take anymore <br>I'd become something I hated to face everyday <br>I couldn't take anymore <br><br>Can't take anymore <br>I'm not me anymore <br>Can't take anymore <br>If you want me, Drag me to hell <br>Drag me to hell <br>If you had the chance, slash your wrists <br><br>I do believe <br>You love the misery <br><br>I wanna know what you're thinking <br>When you find yourself alone <br>Do you even know what it means to be loved <br>I never thought that I'd find a way to say to you <br>I couldn't take anymore <br>I'd become something I hated to face everyday <br>I couldn't take anymore <br><br>I'm back for more x5]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Evolution" label="Evolution"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Life_Cycles/</id><title>The Word Alive - Life Cycles - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:42+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:42+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Life_Cycles/" title="The Word Alive - Life Cycles - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'd rather die for what I believe <br>Than live a life without meaning <br><br>I'd rather die for what I believe <br>Than live a life without meaning <br>I'd rather die for what I believe <br>Than live a life without meaning <br>I'd rather die for what I believe <br>Than live a life without meaning <br><br>And now that I'm older <br>And now that I'm older <br>I'm finding out How <br>What it means <br>To start over <br><br>Well, it's never gonna be that easy <br>I've searched and searched <br>But the searchlights have left me <br>I've tried to find a way, I swear I tried <br>All I have left is you by my side <br><br>So please take the time <br>To get inside my mind <br><br>I've longed for the lights <br>I've stayed awake, stayed awake <br>Through the nights <br>What if this is all I have <br>What if this is all that's left <br>What if this is all that's left <br>All that's left <br><br>And now that I'm older <br>And now that I'm older <br>I'm finding out how <br>What it means <br>To start over <br>I never thought I would <br>I'm finding out how <br>What it means <br>To start over <br>Now that I'm older <br>I'm finding out how <br>What it means <br>To start over <br><br>So can you feel it now <br>Beneath the surface where the shadows dwell <br>You can't hide from the path you chose <br>So take it in, take it in <br>All the burdens of the world <br><br>I never thought I'd end up this way <br>I never thought I could fall so far away <br><br>So far away <br><br>And now that I'm older <br>And now that I'm older <br>I'm finding out how <br>What it means <br>To start over <br>I never thought I would <br>I'm finding out how <br>What it means <br>To start over <br>And now that I'm older <br>I'm finding out how <br>What it means <br>To start over <br><br>I'm starting over <br>I'm starting over <br>I'd rather die for what I believe <br>Than live a life without meaning <br><br>Meaning <br><br>Oh <br><br>I'm starting over]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Life Cycles" label="Life Cycles"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Bar_Fight/</id><title>The Word Alive - Bar Fight - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:44+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:44+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Bar_Fight/" title="The Word Alive - Bar Fight - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Am I still a burden to you now <br>Am I still a burden <br><br>Am I still a burden to you now <br>Fading away from sight and sound <br>What will you say when they take me away <br>What will you say <br><br>You should have listened <br>You should have been more careful <br>your words forced love to crumble <br>You should have been more careful <br><br>Now you'll live with regret for the rest of your life <br>Gave up when you should have stayed <br>Now you'll live with regret for the rest of your life <br>Gave up when you should have stayed, this is goodbye <br>Good bye <br><br>It's so simple, When I tried to explain, you didn't believe <br>It's so simple, It's so simple <br>Oh, why do people run Let's not live life this way <br>Let's not live life this way <br><br>What was the purpose of your destruction <br><br>Will you sleep sound at night <br>I kept begging for the answers <br>You could not seem to reply <br>You could have saved a life <br><br>Now you'll live with regret for the rest of your life <br>Gave up when you should have stayed <br>Now you'll live with regret for the rest of your life <br>Gave up when you should have stayed <br><br>It's so simple, When I tried to explain, you didn't believe <br>It's so simple, It's so simple <br>Oh, why do people run Let's not live life this way <br>Let's not live life this way <br><br>How could you be so naive <br>Not even death could save you from me <br>Not even death could save you from me <br>I tried and tried to show you the light <br>You could have saved a life <br><br>It's so simple, When I tried to explain <br>you didn't believe <br>It's so simple <br><br>Oh, why do people run Let's not live life this way <br>Let's not live life this way <br>Oh, why do people run Let's not live life this way <br>I just wanted you to stay <br>It's so simple, When I tried to explain <br>you didn't believe <br>It's so simple, It's so simple <br>Oh, why do people run <br>Let's not live life this way]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Bar Fight" label="Bar Fight"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/For_Your_Health/</id><title>The Word Alive - For Your Health - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:46+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:46+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/For_Your_Health/" title="The Word Alive - For Your Health - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't understand why <br>but the view from here, is much different when <br>you're alone <br>But the view from here, is all I've ever known <br><br>I didn't know if this was meant to be <br>Perfect strangers taking ahold of me <br>I was searching for the answers right in front of me <br>I don't know if this is meant to be <br>Was it fate that chose me to lead <br><br>Is the answer right in front of me <br>I think this is what completes me <br><br>We are still here <br>We are right here <br>So many have come and gone <br>We are still here <br>Finding out what makes a man <br><br>What makes a man <br>These patterns and these thoughts, they seem to control me <br><br>I can't define what keeps me going <br>Alone in a crowd with the lights glowing <br>I keep hiding behind what's in front of me <br>What is wrong, wrong with me <br>Am I driven to feel this way <br><br>Is the answer right in front of me <br>I think this is what completes me <br><br>We are still here <br>We are right here <br>So many have come and gone <br>We are still here <br>Finding out what makes a man <br><br>We are still here <br>We are still here <br><br>Pretend to like those around me <br>People smiling, secretly seething <br>I pretend I don't hear their voices <br>As they betray without boundaries <br><br>We are still here <br><br>We are still here <br>We are right here <br>So many have come and gone <br>We are still here <br>Finding out what makes a man <br>We all know what it means to come home <br>We are right here <br>We all know what it means to come home <br>We are right here <br><br>We are still here <br>We are still here]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="For Your Health" label="For Your Health"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Entirety/</id><title>The Word Alive - Entirety - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:48+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:48+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Entirety/" title="The Word Alive - Entirety - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're all I have You're all I have <br><br>I can't decide <br>If I love it or hate it <br>Now it's a part of me <br>Warmer now <br>I feel you within me <br>It keeps creeping deeper <br><br>It's not something you can prepare for <br>I tried to fight it off <br>You kept pulling me in <br>I think I found that 'one in a million,' <br>And I can't breathe <br><br>You're all I have <br>And I haven't trusted anyone <br>Finding out feeling isn't easy <br>You're all I have <br>This is more than I deserve, I know <br>I've just go to believe <br><br>You didn't seem to care <br>When I distanced myself <br>So here's the real me <br><br>You didn't seem to notice <br>When I looked away <br>You wanted to show me how to believe <br>How to believe <br><br>You're all I have <br>And I haven't trusted anyone <br>Finding out feeling isn't easy <br>You're all I have <br>This is more than I deserve, I know <br>I've just go to believe <br><br>Feelings are a deadly thing <br>When you fail <br>You give yourself to something <br>You may never know what it's like <br>To lose everything <br><br>If I lost you, I'd lose everything <br><br>Give yourself and you'll start to believe <br>That there was meaning <br>That you can trust what you see <br>Give yourself and you'll start to believe <br>That there was meaning <br>That you can trust what you see <br>You're all i have <br><br>You're all I have <br>And I haven't trusted anyone <br>Finding out feeling isn't easy <br>You're all I have <br>This is more than I deserve, I know <br>I've just go to believe <br><br>You're all I have <br>This is more than I deserve <br>You're all I have <br>Feeling isn't easy <br>This is more than I deserve <br>You're all I have <br><br>You're all I have <br>And I haven't trusted anyone <br>Finding out feeling isn't easy <br>You're all I have <br>This is more than I deserve, I know <br>I've just go to believe <br><br>You're all I have]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Entirety" label="Entirety"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Wishmaster/</id><title>The Word Alive - Wishmaster - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:50+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:50+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Wishmaster/" title="The Word Alive - Wishmaster - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We're here to fight <br>We're here to die <br>We're here to save your life <br>We're here to fight <br>We're here to die <br>We're here to save your life <br><br>What do we say <br>When our backs <br>Are up against the wall <br>The empire remains <br>And it will always <br><br>We've come <br>From all over the world <br>We are the ones <br>Who stand as one <br>Side by side <br>If any man here fear their demise <br>Then we've already lost <br><br>We're here to save the world <br><br>And above all else <br>We'll hunt the ones who <br>Seek to destroy it <br>We're here <br>You're not alone <br>Can't be defeated <br>We'll protect you <br>When all others fail <br><br>Tell me now <br>What would you give up <br>My family, friends for a brotherhood <br>Who stands to gain if we survive <br>You probably weren't born <br>Just to give your life <br><br>Welcome to my life <br>If you make it through today <br>You might survive <br><br>And above all else <br>We'll hunt the ones who <br>Seek to destroy it <br>We're here <br>You're not alone <br>Can't be defeated <br>We'll protect you <br>When all others fail <br><br>I can't believe <br>The cost of what is right <br>Reach for the light <br>Know that we are here <br>We'll always survive <br><br>If you come ill prepared to die <br>You've already lost <br>If you come here and you give up <br>You've already lost <br>Lost the fight <br><br>Welcome to my life <br>You might survive <br>You might survive <br><br>And above all else <br>We'll hunt the ones who <br>Seek to destroy it <br>We're here <br>You're not alone <br>Can't be defeated <br>We'll protect you <br>When all others fail <br><br>I can't believe <br>The cost of what is right <br>Reach for the light <br>Know that we are here <br>We'll always survive <br><br>You might survive <br>You might survive <br>Welcome to my life <br>You might survive <br>You might survive]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Wishmaster" label="Wishmaster"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Dragon_Spell/</id><title>The Word Alive - Dragon Spell - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:51:53+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:51:53+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/The_Word_Alive/Dragon_Spell/" title="The Word Alive - Dragon Spell - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm still the king of the world <br>I'll never falter or squander my dreams <br>I've still got control over my enemies <br>They still beg me for mercy <br>Show no mercy <br>Show no mercy <br><br>I've fought for this kingdom <br>I'll take hold of what is mine <br>I'll be the lord of the universe <br>If you want me, I'm right here <br><br>I'd give everything <br>Everything that I had <br>There's always a war within me <br>I'd never let it show <br>I'll never let my family down <br>Fight for what you stand for <br><br>I feel further than a thousand oceans <br>My thoughts are eating at me now <br>I have so much riding on me <br>To be the man I was born to be <br><br>This is a family <br>We won't crumble in the face of our enemies <br>This is a family <br>We won't crumble in the face of our enemies <br>This is a family <br>Don't fuck with family <br><br>We won't fall <br>I will not ever let this kingdom fall <br>I'd give everything <br>Everything that I had <br>There's always a war within me <br>I'd never let it show <br>I'll never let my family down <br>Fight for what you stand for <br><br>If you were me, would you stand strong <br>would you fold <br>My sacrifice <br>My sacrifice <br>I've never giving up <br>For those I love back home <br>My sacrifice <br>My sacrifice <br><br>Your dreams have come to an end <br>Because this was mine and I won't give in <br>Your dreams have come to an end <br>Because this was mine and I won't give in <br>Your dreams have come to an end <br><br>I'll never lose sight of what I believe <br>I'll fight for my friends, my family <br><br>We won't fall <br>I'd give everything <br>Everything that I had <br>There's always a war within me <br>I'd never let it show <br>I'll never let my family down <br>Fight for what you stand for <br><br>If you were me, would you stand strong <br>would you fold <br>My sacrifice <br>My sacrifice <br>I've never giving up <br>For those I love back home <br>My sacrifice <br>My sacrifice <br><br>I'm still the king of the world <br>I'm still the king of the world]]></content><category term="The Word Alive" label="The Word Alive"/><category term="Dragon Spell" label="Dragon Spell"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/태서니/Im_Your_Fan/</id><title>태서니 - I`m Your Fan - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:53:16+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:53:16+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/%ED%83%9C%EC%84%9C%EB%8B%88/Im_Your_Fan/" title="태서니 - I`m Your Fan - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[지켜볼 수 있다는 것이 <br>무엇보다 중요하다는 걸 <br>네가 숨쉬고 있다는 것이 <br>무엇보다 중요하다는 걸 <br>단지 너 이기 때문에 <br>바로 너 이기 때문에 <br>오직 너 이기 때문에 <br>I'm your fan in my life <br>I'm your fan forever <br>Wherever you are <br>Wherever you go <br>I'm your fan <br>I'm your fan on my mind <br>I'm your fan on your mind <br>Whenever you go <br>Whatever you do <br>I'm your fan <br>기 다 릴 게 <br>두 팔 벌 리 고 <br>워 어 <br>기 다 릴 게 <br>이 자 리 에 서 <br>워 어 <br>I'm your fan in my life <br>I'm your fan forever <br>Wherever you are <br>Wherever you go <br>I'm your fan <br>I'm your fan on my mind <br>I'm your fan on your mind <br>Whenever you go <br>Whatever you do <br>I'm your fan <br>이유는 없는 거야 <br>그냥 니가 좋은 거야 <br>무슨 말이 필요해 <br>더이상 뭐가 필요해 <br>I'm your fan <br>세상이 외면해도 <br>사람들이 뭐라해도 <br>나는 너를 믿어 <br>너만은 믿어 <br>I'm your fan <br>무슨 말이 필요해 <br>더이상 뭐가 필요해 <br>I'm your fan <br>나는 너를 믿어 <br>너만을 믿어 <br>I'm your fan <br>]]></content><category term="태서니" label="태서니"/><category term="I`m Your Fan" label="I`m Your Fan"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/I_Am_Forever/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - I Am Forever - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:11+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:11+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/I_Am_Forever/" title="For All Those Sleeping - I Am Forever - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's the same story <br>That I've heard a thousand times <br>I put my heart out on the line <br>But that's not good enough for you <br>I'm never good enough for you <br>At the end of the day what have you done <br>How can you sleep <br>Well I won't rest until <br>I give a voice to all the weak <br><br>What makes you think that I need to impress you <br>What makes you think <br><br>If you wanted a war well you've got it <br>I'm coming for you <br>If you think I'll be forgotten <br>Then I've got news for you <br>You're always talking <br>I hear all your words <br>But now it's time to make a move <br>You may be today but I am forever <br><br>It's the same story <br>That I have already seen <br>I wear my heart out on my sleeve <br>But that's not good enough for you <br>I'm never good enough for you <br><br>What makes you think that I need to impress you <br>What makes you think <br><br>If you wanted a war well you've got it <br>I'm coming for you <br>If you think I'll be forgotten <br>Then I've got news for you <br>You're always talking <br>I hear all your words <br>But now it's time to make a move <br>You may be today but I am forever <br><br>If you're gonna step up <br>Stay strong and stand for something x4 <br><br>If you wanted a war well you've got it <br>I'm coming for you <br>If you think I'll be forgotten <br>Then I've got news for you <br>You're always talking <br>I hear all your words <br>But now it's time to make a move <br>You may be today but I am forever]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="I Am Forever" label="I Am Forever"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Backstabber/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Backstabber - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:13+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:13+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Backstabber/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Backstabber - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lets get this straight <br>You're reaching out for me <br>After all the times you watched me bleed <br>Now you expect me to put my hand out for you <br>I'll never stop <br>I'll never quit <br>You deserve everything you're about to get <br>You're out of second chances <br>You're out of time <br>There's are no exits left so you can burn in your own fire <br><br>Watch your back <br>After all the ones you stabbed <br>You know you're bound to make some enemies like me <br>It's to late for apologies <br>You may never regret what you've done <br>Buy you're going to regret me <br><br>I'll set you straight <br>Do you think this is a game <br>After all the times you walked on me <br>How can you expect me to have sympathy <br>Is it so hard to understand <br>After all the lives you ruined <br>Some might want revenge <br>So go on keep smiling <br>We'll see who has the laugh last <br><br>Watch your back <br>After all the ones you stabbed <br>You know you're bound to make some enemies like me <br>It's to late for apologies <br>You may never regret what you've done <br>Buy you're going to regret me <br><br>I told you this wasn't a game <br><br>This is your judgement day <br>It's me you have to face <br>I'll never stop <br>I'll never quit <br>You deserve everything you're going to get]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Backstabber" label="Backstabber"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/One_Kiss/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - One Kiss - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:15+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:15+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/One_Kiss/" title="For All Those Sleeping - One Kiss - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I used to know a girl <br>A girl I love to hate <br>She stole me with her words <br>And kept me with her face <br><br>And the nights we spent together <br>Were a dark embrace <br>With her I'd spend forever <br>But she'd never wait <br><br>I used to know a girl <br>A girl who changed my ways <br>I believed every word <br>That fell from her pale face <br><br>And the nights we spent together <br>Turned to darkened days <br>With her I'd spend forever <br>But she'd never wait <br><br>I know I should've walked away <br>But how could I <br>Every time I hear her say <br><br>One kiss and we'll live forever and always <br>One kiss and I'll never leave <br>If one kiss will always keep you here with me <br>Then I'll lean in, close my eyes and just believe <br><br>I used to know a girl <br>A girl I tried to save <br>She wore her broken wings <br>With an angel's grace <br><br>And the nights we spent together <br>Set the sky in flames <br>With her I'd spend forever <br>But she'd never wait <br><br>I know I should've turned away <br>But how could I forget all you promised me <br><br>One kiss and we'll live forever and always <br>One kiss and I'll never leave <br>If one kiss will always keep you here with me <br>Then I'll lean in, close my eyes and just believe <br><br>You promised me forever <br>You promised me the world <br>I'll never live, love or trust again <br>Because you promised? me <br>You promised <br><br>One kiss and we'll live forever <br>One kiss and I'll never leave <br><br>You said you'd never leave <br><br>One kiss and we'll live forever and always <br>One kiss and I'll never leave <br>If one kiss will always keep you here with me <br>Then I'll lean in, close my eyes and just believe <br>Then I'll lean in, close my eyes and just believe <br><br>I used to know a girl <br>A girl I love to]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="One Kiss" label="One Kiss"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Shaken_Not_Stirred/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Shaken Not Stirred - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Shaken_Not_Stirred/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Shaken Not Stirred - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Don't you know <br>This is the life I choose <br>I sacrificed so much <br>But I won't for you <br><br>Slow and cold <br>You turn away <br>You can't bear to look at me <br>But can't you see <br>I'd rather be hated for what I've done <br>Than not known for anything <br><br>I'll never leave any of my dreams <br>Just for you, you <br>Can't you see I'll give everything I have <br>To say I made it right to your face <br><br>Break me down, shake me up <br>Up,up <br>I've had enough <br>Finally I see <br>You <br>Tear it down, turn this up <br>Up,up <br>you've had enough <br>Were in control <br>That's just the way that it goes <br><br>I'm calling the shots <br>I'm calling you out <br>I call the shots <br>Whether you like it or not <br><br>I'll never leave all that I believe <br>Just for you, you <br>Can't you see I'll give everything I have <br>To say I made it and watch you fade <br><br>Break me down, shake me up <br>Up,up <br>I've had enough <br>Finally I see <br>You <br>Tear it down, turn this up <br>Up,up <br>you've had enough <br>Were in control <br>That's just the way that it goes <br><br>I've fell down <br>I've bled out <br>I've made my mistakes <br>I fought all in my way just to get here today <br>So if you think I give a shit what you say <br>Listen to me stay the fuck out of my way <br><br>Break me down, shake me up <br>Up,up <br>I've had enough <br>Finally I see <br><br>Break me down, shake me up <br>Up,up <br>I've had enough <br>Finally I see <br>You <br>Tear it down, turn this up <br>Up,up <br>you've had enough <br>Were in control <br>That's just the way that it goes]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Shaken Not Stirred" label="Shaken Not Stirred"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Never_Trust_A_Dead_Man/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Never Trust A Dead Man - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:20+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:20+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Never_Trust_A_Dead_Man/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Never Trust A Dead Man - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[It's all the same shit everyday <br>Just another place I'll forget anyway <br>If you could see through my bloodshot eyes <br>I bet you wouldn't last a single day <br>It's all the same shit every night <br>You're just another face ill forget tomorrow <br>Just leave your luck at the door <br>Cause I've been here before <br>And I'm one tough act to follow <br><br>Applause all around <br>Face to the ground <br>I'll never stand the test of time <br>And I'd never try <br><br>I sold my soul but <br>I won't slow down <br>till I'm screaming at the top <br>Can you hear me now <br>Can you hear me <br>You said I'd die alone <br>But I'm already dead <br>And you can't trust a dead man <br>I sold my soul but <br>I won't slow down <br>till I'm standing at the top <br>Can you see me now <br>Can you see me <br>You said I'd die alone <br>But I'm already dead <br>And you should never trust a dead man <br><br>There I go again <br>Always circling <br>The drain of life <br>And this time I'm in over my head <br><br>Applause all around <br>Face to the ground <br>I'll never stand the test of time <br>And I'd never try <br><br>It's just the way I play the game <br>There are no rules and there's no balance <br>Now it's your turn <br>Whether win or burn <br>You'll always wish you hadn't <br><br>When death comes for me <br>I'll greet him with my glass up <br><br>I sold my soul but <br>I won't slow down <br>till I'm screaming at the top <br>Can you hear me now <br>Can you hear me <br>You said I'd die alone <br>But I'm already dead <br>And you can't trust a dead man <br>I sold my soul but <br>I won't slow down <br>till I'm standing at the top <br>Can you see me now <br>Can you see me <br>You said I'd die alone <br>But I'm already dead <br>And you should never trust a dead man <br><br>Black out or get the fuck out <br>Don't stop till the bottle drops <br><br>I sold my soul but <br>I won't slow down <br>till I'm screaming at the top <br>Can you hear me now <br>Can you hear me <br>You said I'd die alone <br>But I'm already dead <br>And you can't trust a dead man <br>I sold my soul but <br>I won't slow down <br>till I'm standing at the top <br>Can you see me now <br>Can you see me <br>You said I'd die alone <br>But I'm already dead <br>And you should never trust a dead man]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Never Trust A Dead Man" label="Never Trust A Dead Man"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Love_Isnt_Real/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Love Isn`t Real - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:22+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:22+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Love_Isnt_Real/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Love Isn`t Real - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Love it's a dangerous word <br>The kind I wish I never heard <br>But now I hear it from your lips <br>This word and I must admit <br>I hate when you say it <br>Why couldn't of you have saved it <br>For another boy, another night <br>But now we have to face this <br><br>Walk away <br>That's fine by me you're making this easy <br>Making this easy <br>Romance is a concept that I will never get no <br>I will never get <br>But neither do you so just stop pretending <br>That you ever thought that there'd be a happy ending <br>This is the ending to the story we wrote <br><br>Hey there love <br>You don't exist <br>You don't exist for me <br>You pull me in to tear me down <br>How can I believe there is love <br>You won't exist <br>You won't exist for me <br>To everyone who feels the same come on and sing with me <br><br>You don't know what love is <br>Don't tell me to believe in what can't be seen <br>I gave up on it when it gave up on me <br><br>I know it's hard to hear this <br>But it's harder to take the years I've wasted on it <br><br>Hey there love <br>You don't exist <br>You don't exist for me <br>You pull me in to tear me down <br>How can I believe there is love <br>You won't exist <br>You won't exist for me <br>To everyone who feels the same come on and sing with me]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Love Isn`t Real" label="Love Isn`t Real"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Life_On_Fire/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Life On Fire - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:24+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:24+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Life_On_Fire/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Life On Fire - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Your life on fire <br>Your life on fire <br><br>Oh god it never ends <br>I gave my life for you <br>And you just left me for dead <br>But nothing goes without consequence <br><br>Who do you think you are <br>The day that you left me <br>Was the day I left my heart <br><br>I wanna watch you burn <br>I wanna be the one <br>To strike the match that sets your life on fire <br>I wanna watch you fall <br>I swear I'll be the one <br>I am the one <br>I'll set your life on fire <br><br>Your life on fire <br>Your life on fire <br><br>Do you want to know what it is like to lose everything <br>I'll take what you love one by one until you're left with nothing <br>You should of known you cant get rid of me that easy <br>Now I won't think twice when I get the chance to make you pay <br><br>Who do you think you are <br>Don't you know the day that you left me <br>Was the day I left my heart <br><br>I wanna watch you burn <br>I wanna be the one <br>To strike the match that sets your life on fire <br>I wanna watch you fall <br>I swear I'll be the one <br>I am the one <br>I'll set your life on fire <br><br>I'll take this gasoline <br>Then I'll take this lighter <br>And I'll set your life on <br>I'll set your life on fire <br>Fire, Fire, Fire <br><br>Oh God <br><br>I wanna watch you burn <br>I wanna be the one <br>To strike the match that sets your life on fire <br>I wanna watch you fall <br>I swear I'll be the one <br>I am the one <br>I'll set your life on fire <br><br>Your life on fire <br>Your life on fire]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Life On Fire" label="Life On Fire"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Turn_Of_The_Century/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Turn Of The Century - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:26+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:26+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Turn_Of_The_Century/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Turn Of The Century - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Nothing you say will ever take the place of what you've done to me <br>Now you have to learn the hard way that <br>You picked the wrong guy to fuck with <br><br>I will make you listen <br>I will make you feel pain <br>I will make you listen <br>To every word that I say <br><br>For the first time I made up my mind <br>This is the end <br>This is the end <br>You know you crossed the line <br>You better believe this is the changing of time <br>This is the turn of the century <br>For the last time say goodbye <br>This is the end <br>This is the end <br>Of your wasted life <br>You better believe this is the changing of time <br>This is the turn of the century <br><br>Admit that you were always wrong <br><br>Nothing you do will ever change all the hate that I have for you <br>Now you have to learn the hard way <br>That you picked the wrong guy to fuck with <br><br>This is the end of you <br>And the rise of me <br><br>This is the end of you <br>And the rise of me <br><br>This is the end of you <br>And the rise of me <br><br>This is your end <br>This is my rise <br><br>For the first time I made up my mind <br>This is the end <br>This is the end <br>You know you crossed the line <br>You better believe this is the changing of time <br>This is the turn of the century <br>For the last time say goodbye <br>This is the end <br>This is the end <br>Of your wasted life <br>You better believe this is the changing of time <br>This is the turn of the century]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Turn Of The Century" label="Turn Of The Century"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Follow_My_Voice/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Follow My Voice - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:28+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:28+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Follow_My_Voice/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Follow My Voice - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Hope can seem so hard to find <br>When all around is falling <br>And there's never enough light <br>To see your way out <br>But in the darkest times <br>You find out what you're made of <br>And I swear there's more to you than you know <br><br>I don't want to be the voice of a generation <br>I just want to be a voice for you <br>Alone we may be lost but together we stand tall <br><br>Follow my voice <br>Let me carry you away <br>I can see you're broken <br>But we're all the same <br>We're all the same <br>Follow my voice <br>And let me carry you away <br>I can see you're lost and alone <br>So let this song guide you <br><br>Alone we may be lost but together we stand tall <br><br>Scars can be so hard to hide <br>When all around is flawless <br>But where we've been makes us who we are <br>But in the darkest times <br>You find out what you're made of <br>And I swear there's more to you than you know <br><br>Alone we may be lost but together we stand tall <br><br>Follow my voice <br>Let me carry you away <br>I can see you're broken <br>But we're all the same <br>We're all the same <br>Follow my voice <br>And let me carry you away <br>I can see you're lost and alone <br>So let this song guide you <br><br>Alone we may be lost but together we stand tall <br><br>I'll let you know <br>I was like you too <br>Now every night <br>I take the stage <br>I do it for you <br>So you can let out all the hate <br>And all the rage inside <br>Life may never seem right <br>But well always have tonight <br><br>Alone we may be lost but together we stand tall <br>Alone we may be lost but together we stand tall <br><br>Follow my voice <br>Let me carry you away <br>I can see you're broken <br>But we're all the same <br>We're all the same <br>Follow my voice <br>And let me carry you away <br>I can see you're lost and alone <br>So let this song guide you <br><br>Alone we may be lost but together we stand tall]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Follow My Voice" label="Follow My Voice"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Tell_Me_The_Truth/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Tell Me The Truth - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:31+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:31+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Tell_Me_The_Truth/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Tell Me The Truth - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You need to stop <br>Take a second <br>To figure out how you got here <br>All alone questioning why <br>But to me the answers clear <br><br>You never cared <br>You were never there <br>When someone needed you <br>Now the tables turned <br>Funny how life works <br>This was long overdue <br>Is that clear enough for you <br><br>Tell me truth <br>Get up get up <br>Just walk out <br>Cause you're a liar Yeah <br>And a thief Yeah <br>And that's just the start so <br>Let me remind you <br>That all you are <br>Is a liar Yeah <br>And a thief Yeah <br>You'll always be nothing to me <br><br>You'll never learn <br><br>I'll take you for granted <br>Like you took me <br>I'll take you for granted <br>Like you should be <br><br>Maybe I'm wrong <br>And there's hope for you deep down in you somewhere <br>But who am I kidding you'll always be the shallow person you always were <br><br>Tell me truth <br>Get up get up <br>Just walk out <br>Cause you're a liar Yeah <br>And a thief Yeah <br>And that's just the start so <br>Let me remind you <br>That all you are <br>Is a liar Yeah <br>And a thief Yeah <br>You'll always be nothing <br><br>Wake the fuck up <br><br>You've <br>You've done it now <br>You've done it <br>Let me remind you of how this ends <br>With my hands around your neck <br>As you take your last breath <br>Is that clear enough for you <br><br>Tell me truth <br>Get up get up <br>Just walk out <br>Cause you're a liar Yeah <br>And a thief Yeah <br>And that's just the start so <br>Let me remind you <br>That all you are <br>Is a liar Yeah <br>And a thief Yeah <br>You'll always be nothing to me <br>To me]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Tell Me The Truth" label="Tell Me The Truth"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Mark_My_Words/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Mark My Words - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:33+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:33+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Mark_My_Words/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Mark My Words - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You're fucked now <br>Did you think I wouldn't find out <br>Secrets don't last long in this town <br>And neither will you <br>At the rate you burn bridges you will burn out <br><br>You are a waste of a life <br>You are a waste of my time <br><br>I'm not the one who made you this way <br>But I'll be the one to make you wish you never changed <br><br>Don't tell me you're sorry <br>Because I know, oh I know you're not <br>Don't waste your breath on me <br>I won't hold mine <br>Give it away <br>'Cause you're the reason that you're falling apart <br>There's no way I'd ever forget you <br>But mark my words I'll never miss you <br><br>You're fucked now <br>I can see you but you'll never see it coming <br><br>You're lower than dirt <br>And that's where you belong <br>Face down in the ground <br>Not making a sound <br>Someday you'll find that the countless times <br>You stepped on me were fueling my fire <br><br>Come on what are you waiting for <br>Step up <br>This is what I've been waiting for <br>Step Up <br><br>Make me move <br>If you have the guts to <br>Make your move <br>I'm standing right here]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Mark My Words" label="Mark My Words"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Once_A_Liar_Always_A_Fake/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Once A Liar (Always A Fake) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:35+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:35+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Once_A_Liar_Always_A_Fake/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Once A Liar (Always A Fake) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You'll never change <br>And you'll never change me <br>I've waited so long to take you down <br>Now we're face to face <br><br>I never wanted anything more than all of you <br>But I know you all too well <br>You only wanted to control me <br>How did I think you were Heaven <br>When you put me through Hell <br><br>You are everything I hate <br>How can you tell <br>what's right for someone <br>If you don't know yourself <br>I won't let you bury me Bury me <br>Cause I won't ever let myself become that weak <br><br>The oceans between you <br>And where your heart should be <br>Is sickening sickening <br><br>Just wait for the day that you wake up all alone <br>And know you'll always be <br><br>I never wanted anything more than all of you <br>But I know you all too well <br>You only wanted to control me <br>How did I think you were Heaven <br>When you put me through Hell <br>How did I think you were heaven <br>When you put me through hell <br><br>You are a liar and fake <br>Nothing you do will make me change <br>You are a liar and a fake <br>Nothing about you will ever change <br>Once a liar always a fake <br>Once a liar always a fucking fake <br><br>Just wait for the day that you wake up all alone <br>And know you'll always be <br><br>I never wanted anything more than all of you <br>But I know you all too well <br>You only wanted to control me <br>How did I think you were Heaven <br>When you put me through Hell <br>How did I think you were heaven <br>When you put me through hell <br><br>Once a liar always a fake <br>Once a liar always a fake <br>Once a liar always a fake <br>Once a liar always a fucking fake]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Once A Liar (Always A Fake)" label="Once A Liar (Always A Fake)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Outspoken/</id><title>For All Those Sleeping - Outspoken - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:54:37+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:54:37+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/For_All_Those_Sleeping/Outspoken/" title="For All Those Sleeping - Outspoken - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Step up or shut the fuck up <br>Just try and tear me down if you can <br>You may have before <br>But never again <br>Now is when it ends <br>This is outspoken]]></content><category term="For All Those Sleeping" label="For All Those Sleeping"/><category term="Outspoken" label="Outspoken"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/My_Distorted_Reflection/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - My Distorted Reflection - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:01+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:01+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/My_Distorted_Reflection/" title="Upon A Burning Body - My Distorted Reflection - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[See me staring back in the mirror <br>You don't have to try so hard <br>Suddenly life is much clearer <br>You don't have to change a thing <br><br>I'm not perfect and that's okay with me <br>I'm not perfect and that's okay <br><br>And I don't care what they think of me <br>Cause I'm not ashamed <br>Of the person I am today <br>I want you to see the happiest that I'll ever be <br>Is just being myself <br><br>Because I'm not perfect and that's okay with me <br>I'm not perfect and that's okay And that's okay <br><br>Over and over, I pay the cost of playing this game <br>What can I do to escape <br>I will never be the man I want to be <br>If I can't learn from my mistakes <br><br>I'm not perfect and that's okay with me <br>I'm not perfect and that's okay And that's okay <br>I'm not perfect and that's okay I'm not perfect <br>I'm not perfect and that's okay I'm not perfect]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="My Distorted Reflection" label="My Distorted Reflection"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/The_Outcast/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - The Outcast - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:03+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:03+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/The_Outcast/" title="Upon A Burning Body - The Outcast - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Stop letting critics be your rudder and make your own way <br>No matter what you achieve they try to take it away <br><br>Go <br><br>This one's for the black sheep, the bullied, the ones like me <br>To the divergent, the outcast <br>I want you to scream with me <br>We won't listen to the pointless words you say <br>About how we aren't the same <br>We are the ones who will change the world today <br>Tirelessly, we break society's chains that bind us to hate <br><br>The pain and sorrow wilt away <br>And from it blooms a brand new day <br>Free I can feel the sun looking down on me <br><br>Feeling like no one ever gave you a chance <br>They judge too fast, brand you the outcast <br>I used to be just like you <br>Hated the thought of getting bullied at school <br>Insecure about the color of my skin <br>So sad I just wanted to fit in <br>Terrified of going home most nights <br>A broken home, this can't be right <br><br>The pain and sorrow wilt away <br>And from it blooms a brand new day <br>Free I can feel the sun looking down on me <br><br>Remember it's never too late to believe in yourself <br>Rules are made to be broken <br>Doors can be slammed shut but they can also be opened <br>Inspire someone, walk through the fire for someone <br>Rebuild the good we have lost with the odds against us <br>Push through at any cost <br><br>The pain and sorrow wilt away <br>And from it blooms a brand new day <br>Free I can feel the sun looking down on me <br>Inspire someone, walk through the fire for someone <br>Rebuild the good we have lost with the odds against us <br>Push through at any cost]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="The Outcast" label="The Outcast"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/DTA_Dont_Trust_Anyone/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - D.T.A. (Don`t Trust Anyone) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:06+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:06+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/DTA_Dont_Trust_Anyone/" title="Upon A Burning Body - D.T.A. (Don`t Trust Anyone) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I'm tired of the same ol' bullshit <br>Tired of the liars, the cheats and all you hypocrites <br>I'm just trying to live my life <br>Squeeze a dollar out of a dime just to survive <br>I'm not looking for sympathy <br>But right now you don't want to fuck with me <br><br>You can't take what you haven't earned <br>You keep playing with fire you're bound to get burned <br><br>Ah shit here we go again <br>Work all day ain't got no time to play <br>It's the same shit just a different day <br><br>Ah shit here we go again <br>I'm living my life the best I can <br>You want a fucking role model but I'm just a man <br><br>The pressure is killing me <br>The weight of the world is on my shoulders <br>I'm not the person you think I am <br>You've turned me into a monster <br><br>I'm tired of the same ol' bullshit <br>DTA motherfucker, don't trust anyone <br>It's dog eat dog in the big world <br>So don't start shit, there won't be shit <br>Ain't got the time for piece of mind <br>When everyone's trying to get a piece of mine <br><br>You can't take what you haven't earned <br>You keep playing with fire you're bound to get burned <br><br>Ah shit here we go again <br>Work all day ain't got no time to play <br>It's the same shit just a different day <br><br>Ah shit here we go again <br>I'm living my life the best I can <br>You want a fucking role model but I'm just a man <br><br>The pressure is killing me <br>The weight of the world is on my shoulders <br>I'm not the person you think I am <br>You've turned me into a monster <br>Don't waste my time with your same ol' bullshit <br><br>Fuck <br><br>Ah shit here we go again <br>Work all day ain't got no time to play <br>It's the same shit just a different day <br><br>Ah shit here we go again <br>I'm living my life the best I can <br>You want a fucking role model but I'm just a man <br><br>The pressure is killing me <br>The weight of the world is on my shoulders <br>I'm not the person you think I am <br>You've turned me into a monster <br>Don't waste my time with your same ol' bullshit]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="D.T.A. (Don`t Trust Anyone)" label="D.T.A. (Don`t Trust Anyone)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Fake_Plastic_Smile/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - Fake Plastic Smile - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:08+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:08+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Fake_Plastic_Smile/" title="Upon A Burning Body - Fake Plastic Smile - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[We bow down to no one <br><br>You walk around with your head in the clouds <br>Thinking this life is your life like you should be proud <br>We live every day getting beaten down but stand tall <br>Push it back, push it back, we're about to attack <br>Flaunting this and that better watch your back <br>Because I'm calling you out for everything that you lack <br><br>Rich boy, bitch boy thinking you're the shit boy <br>Motherfucker you don't deserve that new whip <br>You didn't pay for it <br>Them fly clothes <br>You didn't buy that shit <br>Rollie on your wrist <br>You little spoiled ass bitch <br>You think you're rich boy You're just a bitch boy <br><br>You walk around with your head in the clouds <br>Thinking this life is your life like you should be proud <br>You can't keep playing pretend <br>You had a good run on that high horse <br>It's time you comprehend <br>I'm calling you out and I hope it stings <br>Trust me I'm not trying to teach you anything <br><br>I see through your fake plastic smile <br>All the money in the world can't make you happy <br>All the money in the world couldn't make me like you <br>You think you can live like this for the rest of your life <br>Where will you turn when your daddy's money runs out <br>You never worked a fucking day in your life <br>I don't even expect you to know how to fight <br><br>Rich boy, bitch boy, you don't know shit boy <br>Motherfucker you don't deserve that new whip <br>You didn't pay for it <br>Them fly clothes <br>You didn't buy that shit <br>Rollie on your wrist <br>You little spoiled ass bitch <br>You think you're rich boy You're just a bitch boy <br><br>You walk around with your head in the clouds <br>Thinking this life is your life like you should be proud <br>You can't keep playing pretend <br>You had a good run on that high horse <br>It's time you comprehend <br>I'm calling you out and I hope it stings <br>Trust me I'm not trying to teach you anything <br><br>Born with a silver spoon in your mouth <br>'Bout time someone put you in your place bitch]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="Fake Plastic Smile" label="Fake Plastic Smile"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Walk_Alone_Again/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - Walk Alone Again - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:10+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:10+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Walk_Alone_Again/" title="Upon A Burning Body - Walk Alone Again - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I can't escape <br>My past is going to haunt me forever <br>The darkness tries to haunt me <br>Give in <br>Just a taste of what you desire <br>Get out of my head you fucking liar <br>Everywhere I look there's a constant reminder <br>My demon's coming here to take me under <br>I won't go down without putting up a fight <br>I'll be bruised and bleeding before I let you take my life <br><br>I am the one who will claw my way out <br>You can push and pull but you won't drag me down <br>I am the one to walk alone again <br>You can beg and plead but you're dead to me <br><br>Let go of me <br>Your grip is failing to hold me down now <br>I'll walk out, lock the door and throw the key away <br>You can have my past, that's all you are to me <br>You can have my past, trapped with all that misery <br>That's not me anymore <br>I've come too far to fail <br>Knife to the throat of me giving in <br>I can see the eyes bearing from the fire inside <br>All of my demons try to drag me down to Hell <br>I am the master of my own way out <br><br>I am the one who will claw my way out <br>You can push and pull but you won't drag me down <br>I am the one to walk alone again <br>You can beg and plead but you're dead to me <br><br>No you're not welcome in my head <br>Your condescending words about who I am <br>No you're not welcome anymore]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="Walk Alone Again" label="Walk Alone Again"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Leave_The_Pain_Behind/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - Leave The Pain Behind - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:12+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:12+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Leave_The_Pain_Behind/" title="Upon A Burning Body - Leave The Pain Behind - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Lay me down to sleep tonight, pray that I wake up this time <br>Cause I've been living my whole life one bottle at a time <br><br>I don't need you in my skin just to feel alive again <br>I'm awake for the first time <br>You can't change what's in my mind <br>I'm awake maybe this time I will leave the pain behind <br><br>I can feel them trying to wake me <br>I can feel you trying to break me <br>I don't need you in my head <br>I'd rather feel alive instead <br><br>I don't need you in my skin just to feel alive again <br>I'm awake for the first time <br>You can't change what's in my mind <br>I'm awake maybe this time I will leave the pain behind <br><br>I'm no longer dead inside <br>I'm coming alive <br><br>I'm awake for the first time <br>You can't change what's in my mind <br>I'm awake maybe this time I will leave the pain behind <br>I don't need you in my skin just to feel alive again]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="Leave The Pain Behind" label="Leave The Pain Behind"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Straight_From_The_Barrio_210/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - Straight From The Barrio (210) - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:14+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:14+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Straight_From_The_Barrio_210/" title="Upon A Burning Body - Straight From The Barrio (210) - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Now for those of you who don't know, you got two choices <br>Either get up, or get the fuck out <br><br>Here we come <br><br>Motherfuckers back at it again <br>We're back in town, feel the heat <br>The new black is brown <br>Come get that good shit, that hood shit <br>That straight from Texas music and before we're done <br>We're going to own this town <br>San Antonio we're about to explode <br>Straight from the barrio <br>We're out of control <br>The party don't start we kick in <br>All you fake motherfuckers you out we in <br><br>From the bottom of the barrel to the top of the world <br>This is still who I am from the river city to the ocean shores <br>I won't forget you <br><br>Get up <br><br>Born and raised in that dirty, dirty, dirty South <br>I walk the walk, kid You just run your mouth <br>If you respect me I'll respect you that's without a doubt <br>But if you don't like my city you can get the fuck out <br>Light it up, burn it down, feel the heat, we own this town <br><br>From the bottom of the barrel to the top of the world <br>This is still who I am from the river city to the ocean shores <br>I won't forget you <br>From down in the gutter when all we had was each other <br>This is still who I am <br>You believed in me when this was only a dream <br>And I won't forget you <br><br>San Antonio we're about to explode <br>Straight from the barrio <br>We are the 210 San Antonio <br>We rep that 210 and we're outta control <br>Ain't nobody going to represent the city like we do <br>You bleed for me and I'll bleed for you too <br>Ain't nobody putting SA on the map like we do <br>You bleed for me and I'll bleed for you too <br><br>I'm on top of the world <br>And this is still who I am from the river city to the ocean shores <br>I won't forget you <br>From down in the gutter when all we had was each other <br>This is still who I am <br>You believed in me when this was only a dream <br>And I won't forget you <br><br>Get up]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="Straight From The Barrio (210)" label="Straight From The Barrio (210)"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/BMF/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - B.M.F. - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:17+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:17+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/BMF/" title="Upon A Burning Body - B.M.F. - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I don't got a problem with the way I'm living <br>When I look around at what the world's becoming <br>Stay the fuck out the way cause it's my way <br>My way or the highway <br>All of the money, just problems <br>All of the problems, I solve them <br>All of the shit you've been talking <br>You don't want problems you walking <br><br>I'm living life on the wild side <br>Fuck you <br>Tattooed middle finger to the sky <br>Fuck you <br>Bad boy 'til the day I die <br>Fuck you <br>Feel the heat when I come alive <br>Step up <br><br>All that hype you been spitting going to get you knocked down <br>Another level put down <br>Ya'll wanna tear this place up give me a Hell yeah <br>Ya'll wanna burn this place down let me hear Hell yeah <br><br>Everybody else just looking for attention and mentions <br>But your intentions are to go the extra mile to troll my profile <br>You are the punch to my lines <br>Your nights don't come close to mine <br>You wish that you could live this <br>Your vacation, that's my whole life <br><br>I'm living life on the wild side <br>Fuck you <br>Tattooed middle finger to the sky <br>Fuck you <br>Bad boy 'til the day I die <br>Fuck you <br>Feel the heat when I come alive <br>Step up <br><br>All that hype you been spitting going to get you knocked down <br>Another level put down <br>Ya'll wanna tear this place up give me a Hell yeah <br>Ya'll wanna burn this place down let me hear Hell yeah <br><br>Fuck the ones who doubt me, talk shit about me <br>You're just a bitch and I'm a bad motherfucker <br><br>Ya'll wanna tear this place up give me a Hell yeah <br>Ya'll wanna burn this place down let me hear Hell yeah <br>Ya'll wanna tear this fucking place up give me a Hell yeah <br>Ya'll wanna burn this place down let me hear Hell yeah]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="B.M.F." label="B.M.F."/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Media_Blackout/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - Media Blackout - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:19+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:19+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Media_Blackout/" title="Upon A Burning Body - Media Blackout - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[If you got a problem with me <br>Come say that shit to my face <br><br>Hate me, cause I know you love it <br>Love me, but I know you hate it <br>You fake piece of shit <br>You're waiting for me to fall <br>I'm at the top sipping my alcohol <br><br>Why you always gotta be <br>Why you always gotta be, always gotta be fucking with me <br><br>I know you would love to break me <br>Media's always trying to blame me <br>With one hand holding my dick <br>I say Fuck you if you don't like it <br><br>Let me see a show of hands if you're perfect <br>That's what I thought <br>But you're so quick to judge me <br>You want my spotlight but you don't deserve it <br>Just like the rest, you could take it but you will serve it <br><br>I know you would love to break me <br>Media's always trying to blame me <br>With one hand holding my dick <br>I say Fuck you if you don't like it <br><br>Talked by many <br>Hated by some <br>Guess how many fucks I give <br>Talked by many <br>Hated by some <br>Guess how many fucks I give <br>3, 2, none <br>Keep talking shit about me <br>Me, me, me <br>Keep talking shit about me <br>Me, me, me <br><br>I know you would love to break me <br>Media's always trying to blame me <br>With one hand holding my dick <br>I say Fuck you if you don't like it]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="Media Blackout" label="Media Blackout"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/You_Dont_Own_Me/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - You Don`t Own Me - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:21+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:21+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/You_Dont_Own_Me/" title="Upon A Burning Body - You Don`t Own Me - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Motherfucker, you don't own me <br><br>You can't please everyone so listen up and understand <br>I make music for me and for the people who love it <br>I don't need permission from you <br>And I damn sure ain't your fucking puppet <br>All I hear is Walk this way <br>And talk this way, do it just how I say <br>I won't be criticized for the man I am <br>A word of advice start your own band <br><br>I say what I mean, I mean what I say <br>Like the words of a king <br>From the bottom on the grind to the top <br>You think I'm sorry, I'm not <br>I say what I mean, I mean what I say <br>Like the words of a king <br>From the bottom on the grind to the top <br>So if you're with me <br>I'll give you all I've got <br><br>Oh yeah, I see you looking at me <br>And I can see your mouth moving but I'm not listening <br>You ain't got nothing better to do <br>Than talk shit about who's who from what you've seen on YouTube <br>All the shit it took me to get here <br>You couldn't hang with me if you wanted to <br>I won't be criticized for the man I am <br>A word of advice start your own band <br><br>I'ma do what I want <br>And I'll do it the way I want <br>I'ma sing what I want <br>And I'll sing it the way I want <br>I'ma do what I want <br>And I'll do it the way I want <br>I don't need permission from you <br>Who the fuck do you think you are <br><br>I say what I mean, I mean what I say <br>Like the words of a king <br>From the bottom on the grind to the top <br>You think I'm sorry, I'm not <br>I say what I mean, I mean what I say <br>Like the words of a king <br>So true fans put your hands up, stand up <br>And scream it with me <br><br>Motherfucker, you don't own me <br>And I don't owe you a god damn thing <br><br>I say what I mean, I mean what I say <br>Like the words of a king <br>From the bottom on the grind to the top <br>You think I'm sorry, I'm not <br>I say what I mean, I mean what I say <br>Not the words of a king <br>From the bottom on the grind to the top <br>So if you're with me <br>I'll give you all I've got]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="You Don`t Own Me" label="You Don`t Own Me"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Already_Broken/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - Already Broken - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:23+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:23+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Already_Broken/" title="Upon A Burning Body - Already Broken - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[You can't break me cause I'm already broken <br>You can't break me cause I'm already broken <br>I'm already broken inside <br><br>I've seen so many bad things, I will never be the same <br>Taken too many times <br>It's hard to explain the pain <br>But I've grown and developed sense of sight <br>One that leads me to believe <br>Things can be alright <br>No me puedes quebrar porque estoy quebrado <br><br>You can't break me, cause I'm already broken <br>No me puedes quebrar <br>You can't break me, cause I'm already broken <br>Porque estoy quebrado <br><br>This moment marks the day I believe in me <br>Once a hollow shell now radiates infinity <br>I will become a new kind of entity <br>One that would be heard now and for centuries <br><br>You can't break me, cause I'm already broken <br>No me puedes quebrar <br>You can't break me, cause I'm already broken <br>Porque estoy quebrado <br><br>No more being played like this <br>I'm done <br>I'm numb from all the pain <br>No more, I didn't ask for this <br>I'm done <br>I'm moving on <br><br>You can't break me cause I'm already broken <br>You can't break me cause I'm already broken <br>I'm already broken <br>You can't break me, cause I'm already broken <br>No me puedes quebrar <br>You can't break me, cause I'm already broken <br>Porque estoy quebrado]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="Already Broken" label="Already Broken"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Til_The_Break_Of_Dawn/</id><title>Upon A Burning Body - `Til The Break Of Dawn - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:25+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:25+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Upon_A_Burning_Body/Til_The_Break_Of_Dawn/" title="Upon A Burning Body - `Til The Break Of Dawn - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Damas y caballeros, 'estan listos para los mas chingones <br>Si vienen de Texas, cuidado, porque cuando la musica comienza <br>'A la verga <br><br>U A B B be repping that south side <br>That west side, cruising that low ride <br>I'm brown and I'm proud <br>I'm wild, and I'm loud <br>You know we gotta party all the time <br>Tequila on my mind <br>And you know I got five on the Dime <br>Roll it up, smoke it up <br>Pour it up, drink it up <br><br>Pa' arriba, pa' abajo <br>Pal' centro, pa' dentro <br><br>Vamos a pistear, toda la noche <br>We like to party all night long <br>Estamos despiertos hasta que el sol sale <br>We're rolling 'til the break of dawn, baby <br><br>Puro chicano, puro texano <br>Taking over the world with my hermanos <br>LWO I'll be in the camino <br>Represent where you come from north side <br>Represent where you come from east side <br>Represent where you come from west side <br>Represent where you come from south side <br><br>Pa' arriba, pa' abajo <br>Pal' centro, pa' dentro <br><br>Vamos a pistear, toda la noche <br>We like to party all night long <br>Estamos despiertos hasta que el sol sale <br>We're rolling 'til the break of dawn, baby <br>Vamos a pistear, toda la noche <br>We like to party all night long <br>Estamos despiertos hasta que el sol sale <br>We're rolling 'til the break of dawn, baby <br><br>You know my people on the come up <br>Let's show these motherfuckers what's up <br>You tryna hang, we gon' turn up <br>Everybody here get buck, buck, buck <br>Where the fuck the party at <br>You know you runnin' with the best <br>Got the east, got the west <br>Got the north, got the south <br>Man, that's what we're about yeah <br><br>Vamos a pistear, toda la noche <br>We like to party all night long <br>Estamos despiertos hasta que el sol sale <br>We're rolling 'til the break of dawn, baby <br>Vamos a pistear, toda la noche <br>We like to party all night long <br>Estamos despiertos hasta que el sol sale <br>We're rolling 'til the break of dawn, baby]]></content><category term="Upon A Burning Body" label="Upon A Burning Body"/><category term="`Til The Break Of Dawn" label="`Til The Break Of Dawn"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Little_Jeans/Waking_Up/</id><title>Mr. Little Jeans - Waking Up - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:55:58+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:55:58+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Little_Jeans/Waking_Up/" title="Mr. Little Jeans - Waking Up - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[I know I made the same mistakes <br>For you don't want caught up the stakes <br>Gotta lock the good outside my window <br><br>We run out of ground at the big big black <br>It's all looking bold with caffeine, yes it's okay <br><br>Won't you take me there <br>Floating in the air <br>I go solitare and I ain't waking up <br>When the night is young <br>moving like we're one <br>Dance until it's gone <br>and I ain't waking up <br><br>and I ain't waking up <br>and I ain't waking up <br>and I ain't waking up <br>and I ain't waking up <br>And if they should let the lights die <br><br>Tied up through low, we've got the sky <br>Gotta lock the good out at my window <br>We run out of ground at the big big black <br>It's all looking bold with caffeine, yes it's okay <br>Won't you take me there <br>Floating in the air <br>I go solitare and I ain't waking up <br><br>When the night is young <br>moving like we're one <br>Dance until it's gone <br>and I ain't waking up <br>You can wait unlock my way <br>Stay here <br>I'll wait a thousand years <br>For you <br><br>I don't wanna have to wait <br>Stay here <br>I don't wanna have to wait <br>For you <br>Won't you take me there <br>Floating in the air <br>I go solitare and I ain't waking up <br><br>When the night is young <br>moving like we're one <br>Dance until it's gone <br>and I ain't waking up <br>Won't you take me there <br>Floating in the air <br>I go solitare and I ain't waking up <br>When the night is young <br>moving like we're one <br>Dance until it's gone <br>and I ain't waking up <br>and I ain't waking up <br>and I ain't waking up <br>and I ain't waking up]]></content><category term="Mr. Little Jeans" label="Mr. Little Jeans"/><category term="Waking Up" label="Waking Up"/></entry><entry><id>http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Little_Jeans/Fool_4_You/</id><title>Mr. Little Jeans - Fool 4 You - 가사</title><author><name>lyric</name></author><updated>2018-04-22T16:56:00+09:00</updated><published>2018-04-22T16:56:00+09:00</published><link rel="via" href="http://lyric.vicharas.net/artist/Mr_Little_Jeans/Fool_4_You/" title="Mr. Little Jeans - Fool 4 You - 가사"/><content type="html"><![CDATA[Light, light as a feather <br>Oh what I wouldn't <br>Wouldn't give to be <br>Like no matter the weather <br>But I've got blood and bones <br>And a heart that beats <br><br>Go hard or run free <br>They both will undo me <br>Can't see anything <br>With clouds blocking the sun <br><br>It sinks in like honey <br>A fiction just for me <br>Tell me my daydream's <br>Coming back for no one <br><br>All I need is black and white <br>Air to fire or no light <br>But you give me <br>Everything in between <br>So before my body breaks <br>Aim the arrow I'll make <br>Lemme see our bedroom light <br>From the street <br>So I can breathe <br><br>Looking over my shoulder <br>Looking for something other <br>Than what I see <br>Lies, they keep getting older <br>Until the air gets too thin <br>For us to breathe <br><br>It sinks in like honey <br>A fiction just for me <br>Tell me my daydream's <br>Coming back for no one <br><br>These streets <br>These streets <br>Or me <br>Let's leave <br>These streets <br>These streets <br>Or me]]></content><category term="Mr. Little Jeans" label="Mr. Little Jeans"/><category term="Fool 4 You" label="Fool 4 You"/></entry></feed>